(SWORDS CLANGING,
SOLDIERS GRUNTING)
[KARASHIN] WOW! YOU'VE REALLY
GOTTEN
THEIR LEVELS UP, HAVEN'T YOU?
[ISAAC] UH?
[KARASHIN] THEN AGAIN I
SHOULDN'T EXPECT ANYTHING LESS
FROM THE BLACK SWORD KNIGHTS.
YOU'RE A BUNCH OF STUDS!
OF COURSE! THEY KNOW WHO
TO CALL TO GET THINGS DONE!
[ITHERUS] MISTER ISAAC YOU'RE
REALLY AMAZING AT THIS!
YOU JUST KEEP ONE MAKING
ALL OUR SOLDIERS TOUGH.
[ITHERUS] BOTH OF YOU ARE REALLY
HELPING MAIHAMA RIGHT NOW
WITH ALL YOUR HARD
WORK! THANK YOU.
[REZARICK] HAVING YOU SAY THAT
MAKES ALL THE TIME WE'RE
PUTTING IN WORTHWHILE,
MASTER ITHERUS.
WOULDN'T YOU SAY, MISTER ISAAC?
(ISAAC GROWLS)
[KARASHIN] I CAN TELL YOU'VE
BEEN WORKING PRETTY HARD
AT THIS, MISTER ISAAC!
(CHUCKLING)
[ISAAC] (SNARLING) YOU CALL
ME "MISTER" ONE MORE TIME,
AND I'LL CUT YOUR
STUPID HEADS OFF!
[RODERICK] NOW, ABOUT
THIS REQUEST OF YOURS,
TO FACILITATE CONSTRUCTION OF
A LUNAR COMMUNICATION DEVICE.
[SHIROE]
IT'S GONNA COST THIS MUCH?
[RODERICK]
THE PROBLEM'S THE SCALE...
IT'D TAKE MORE THAN THREE
YEARS OF WHAT WE SET ASIDE
FOR THE CITY'S OPERATING BUDGET.
[SHIROE]
YOU HAVE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
[RODERICK]
THERE'S ANOTHER CAVEAT.
THERE'S NO GUARANTEE WE CAN MAKE
SOMETHING LIKE THIS WORK
IN THE FIRST PLACE OR KEEP
IT RUNNING AFTER IT'S UP.
[SHIROE]
WELL, OF COURSE.
[RODERICK]
YOU'RE SERIOUS ABOUT THIS?
TRYING TO FIND A
WAY TO GO BACK HOME?
[SHIROE] (EXHALE) I NEVER
THOUGHT IT WOULD BE EASY.
[AKATSUKI] SO WHAT DID YOU TELL
EVERYONE
AT THE ROUND TABLE ANYWAY?
IF WE MAKE CONTACT
WITH THE MOON,
THE TRAVELLERS UP THERE
MIGHT BE ABLE TO GIVE US SOME
IDEA ABOUT HOW TO GET BACK HOME.
THAT BEING SAID, I
DIDN'T GO OUT OF MY WAY
TO RAISE ANYONE'S
EXPECTATIONS, EITHER.
(SIGH)
THE WAY THINGS ARE RIGHT NOW,
THERE'S NO WAY
THEY'D APPROVE IT.
HUH?
UH... WHAT'RE YOU
DOING, AKATSUKI?
[AKATSUKI] REMEMBER
YOUR FOREHEAD.
YOU'RE GETTING OLD
MAN WRINKLES AGAIN.
I FORBID ANY MORE WRINKLES.
I'LL WORK ON IT.
[SERARA] IS WHAT MASTER SHIROE
SAID BEFORE IS ALL TRUE?
I REALLY WOULDN'T MIND
GOING BACK HOME, YOU KNOW?
[MINORI] A LOT OF WHAT HE
SAID IS STILL UNCONFIRMED,
SO WE SHOULD PROBABLY KEEP
IT TO OURSELVES FOR NOW,
SINCE NOTHING'S SET.
[ISUZU] YEAH,
THAT WON'T BE EASY!
THAT'S NOT THE KINDA THING
YOU CAN KEEP SECRET FOR LONG.
SERIOUSLY, JUST THINK ABOUT
WHAT IT REALLY MEANS.
YEAH... IT'S COMPLICATED...
OH MAN, AS MUCH AS I WANT TO
SEE MY MOM AND DAD AGAIN...
I DON'T WANNA LEAVE
ALL THE PEOPLE
WHO'VE BEEN WITH ME
THROUGH THIS WHOLE THING.
THEY'RE IMPORTANT TO ME.
[MINORI]
OH, SERARA...
I HEAR WHAT YOU'RE SAYING.
NOW THAT WE'RE ALL FRIENDS
AND
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH
SO MUCH TOGETHER.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, MINORI?
HUH? WELL, I DON'T KNOW...
I HAVEN'T GIVEN IT
A LOT OF THOUGHT.
MPH?
(EXHALE)
I WOULD IF I COULD.
HUH?
[TOYA] I'M SURE MOST OF US
WOULD DO THE SAME THING...
IT'S NOT LIKE WE WOKE UP ONE DAY
AND SAID WE WANTED TO BE HERE.
[ISUZU] IT'S TRUE. WE'RE
ALL VICTIMS IN THIS.
NONE OF US HAD A CHOICE IN
THE MATTER; THAT'S FOR SURE.
BUT I ALSO WOULDN'T MIND
STAYING HERE EITHER.
I MEAN I FEEL LIKE I'VE
MADE MYSELF USEFUL, Y'KNOW.
IN FACT, I THINK I'VE MANAGED
TO ACCOMPLISH MORE HERE
THAN I EVER DID BACK HOME.
OKAY, TOYA...
[RUDY] I UNDERSTAND WHERE
YOU'RE COMING FROM TOYA.
UH... RUDY...
IT'S NATURAL FOR EVERYONE
TO WANNA GO HOME...
AND SAYING GOODBYE...?
I'M READY FOR THAT.
[RUDY] WHATEVER TOYA WANTS,
AS LONG AS IT ISN'T
ANOTHER FORCED RELOCATION
AT THE HANDS OF SOME
UNFORESEEN CIRCUMSTANCES.
SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
[ISUZU]
TOYA?
MISS ISUZU, IF YOU END UP
GOING BACK TO YOUR HOMELAND,
WON'T YOU BE ABLE TO PLAY
MUSIC WITH YOUR FATHER?
UH... IT'S NOT THAT SIMPLE...
I DON'T KNOW IF THERE'S A
RIGHT OR WRONG ANSWER RUDY.
[SERARA] OH WHY DOES EVERYTHING
HAVE TO BE SO DIFFICULT?
MPH.
[ISAAC] THE CITY'S GETTIN' MORE
AND MORE LIKE THE OLD AKIHABARA,
ISN'T IT? [MAN] SHORT SLEEVED
T‐SHIRTS HALF OFF TODAY!
[REZARICK] I GUESS OUR
CULTURE'S RUBBING OFF
ON THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND
MORE THAN WE COULD'VE EXPECTED.
[KARASHIN]
IT CERTAINLY HAS.
SO WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF ALL THIS?
[ITHERUS] I LOVE IT!
PEOPLE OF THE LAND NEED
TO EMBRACE ADVENTURER CULTURE
SO WE CAN KEEP GROWING!
MY GRANDFATHER SAYS THAT'S AN
IMPORTANT PART OF OUR FUTURE.
[ISAAC] SPEAKING OF, HOW LONG'RE
YOU GONNA BE FOLLOWING ME?
[ITHERUS] AS LONG AS IT TAKES,
I'VE GOTTA GET TO KNOW
ADVENTURERS LIKE YOU THE SAME
WAY RAYNESHIA DID.
YOU'RE STUCK WITH
ME, MISTER ISAAC!
(ISAAC GROWLING)
[REZARICK] I DON'T SUPPOSE NOW'D
BE A GOOD TIME TO REMIND YOU
THAT PROTECTING THE YOUNG
MASTER'S ONE OF OUR DUTIES.
[ISAAC] HMPH. YEAH,
WHATEVER MAN.
[KARASHIN] THE BOY SEEMS
TO BE AWFULLY FOND OF YOU.
[ISAAC] IT'S NOT MY STYLE.
[KARASHIN] WELL MAYBE
IT SHOULD BE...
A FRIENDSHIP LIKE THIS
CAN MAKE THE TIES BETWEEN
MAIHAMA AND AKIHABARA STRONGER.
IT'S JUST THAT WE'VE GOT
ANOTHER ISSUE WE'RE
GOING TO NEED TO DEAL WITH.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
[KARASHIN] COME ON. YOU'VE GOTTA
REMEMBER
THE LAST CONFERENCE MEETING.
YOU KNOW, TRYING TO
TALK TO THE MOON?
[ISAAC] YOU MEAN THAT THING THAT
MIGHT TELL US
HOW WE'RE GONNA GET BACK HOME?
[KARASHIN] EXACTLY. AND IT'S
PROBABLY GONNA THROW
A MONKEY WRENCH IN
THIS WORLD'S POLITICS.
COULDN'T CARE LESS ABOUT IT...
ESPECIALLY WHEN POLITICIANS
USE OTHER PEOPLE TO FIGHT.
REALLY? BUT THIS COULD HELP OUR
CHANCES OF GETTING BACK HOME.
I'M MORE OF A SIT AND WAIT KINDA
GUY INSTEAD OF A WORRY‐WART.
YEAH, I GUESS...
COME ON...
A HIGH PRICE TAG DOESN'T MEAN
THAT SWORD'S WORTH A DAMN.
[ITHERUS] HUH?
[ISAAC] REZARICK, YOU
SHOULD KNOW BETTER.
MISTER ISAAC IS MUCH BETTER
JUDGE OF SWORDS THAN I AM.
GIMME A BREAK, WILLYA?
(EXHALE)
HERE... THIS'LL WORK.
AH... OH GOODNESS.
BUT IT'S EXPENSIVE, AND
IT'S LEVEL‐RATING IS
A LOT HIGHER THAN WHAT I
SHOULD BE USING RIGHT NOW.
I CAN'T USE IT YET... LET'S GO.
I WAS TRYING TO
HELP THE KID OUT.
KNOWING HIS OWN LIMITATIONS
IS A GOOD THING.
HE ACTS KINDA LIKE A
KID IN A LOT OF WAYS,
BUT THAT WAS PRETTY IMPRESSIVE.
OKAY... WHATEVER. HUH?
HM?
[REZARICK]
IS SOMETHING... WRONG?
NOTHING... LET'S
GET OUTTA HERE.
[SERJIAD] HOW'S THE TRAINING FOR
THE SOLDIERS
COMING ALONG, MASTER ISAAC?
[ISAAC]
THEY'RE OKAY SO FAR.
THEY'RE LEVELING
UP QUICK ENOUGH.
THAT KIND OF NEWS
IS ENCOURAGING.
TIMES ARE SUCH THAT WE COULD BE
EMBROILED IN WAR AT ANY MOMENT.
DID YOU REALLY HAVE ME COME
OUT HERE TO DRINK TEA
AND MAKE SMALL TALK, OLD MAN?
(CLEARING THROAT)
I'M CONCERNED ABOUT ITHERUS.
[ISAAC]
HUH?
WE'VE DECIDED THAT WE'RE GOING
TO HOLD A GRAND CEREMONY
FOR HIS BIRTHDAY IN A FEW DAYS.
IT WILL ALSO SERVE AS MY
OPPORTUNITY TO NAME HIM
AS THE PROPER HEIR
TO HOUSE COWEN.
THE "PROPER HEIR"?
THAT LITTLE BOY?
[SERJIAD]
HMMM.
I THOUGHT YOU
ALREADY HAD A SON
TO TAKE OVER WHEN YOU
DECIDE TO STEP DOWN.
[SERJIAD]
FERNELLE MARRIED INTO MY FAMILY.
HE'S A MAGNIFICENT
STATESMAN AND WARRIOR,
BUT THE PEOPLE WOULD NEVER
ACCEPT HIS ASCENSION.
THEY WANT MY SUCCESSOR TO HAVE
THE COWEN BLOOD FLOWING
IN THEIR VEINS.
MY DAUGHTER, SARARIYA,
AND FERNELLE
HAVE THREE CHILDREN TOGETHER.
THEIR ELDEST
DAUGHTER, RISSELTHEA,
THEIR SECOND
DAUGHTER, RAYNESHIA,
AND THEIR YOUNGEST OF
COURSE IS ITHERUS.
RISSELTHEA ABANDONED
HER RIGHT AS SUCCESSOR
BY MARRYING OUTSIDE NOBILITY..
LEAVING US WITH
RAYNESHIA AND ITHERUS.
[ISAAC] THAT'S RIGHT, I
FORGOT ABOUT HER, DIDN'T I?
I WAS BLINDED BY WHAT
I THOUGHT WAS RESOLVE.
FRANKLY, HER OUTBURST AT THE
LORDS
WAS A HARSH AWAKENING
AT MY FOOLISH OPTIMISM.
SHE WILL STILL HAVE A ROLE IN
OUR GOVERNMENT,
BUT YOU CAN BE SURE IT
WON'T BE HEAD OF STATE.
SO SHE ISN'T GONNA
BE RUNNING THINGS.
[SERJIAD] AND BESIDES,
A LORDSHIP REQUIRES
A MAN'S QUALITIES.
I'M SURE ITHERUS
WILL GROW INTO THIS.
[ISAAC] SO BASICALLY THIS
WHOLE SUCCESSION THING
HAS BEEN WEIGHING HEAVY
ON YOUR MIND, HUH, CHIEF?
[SERJIAD] (GRUNT) HENCEFORTH,
IT WILL BE ESSENTIAL FOR A LORD
TO FOSTER UNDERSTANDING
WITH THE ADVENTURERS.
MASTER ISAAC, YOU KNOW AS WELL
AS I DO, ITHERUS IS JUST A BOY.
I ASK A FAVOR, PLEASE MENTOR HIM
WHILE YOU'RE HERE.
THEY'RE THINGS YOU KNOW,
WE CANNOT TEACH.
(SIGH)
I REALLY DON'T KNOW ABOUT
ALL THIS, MAN... HM?
(MAID SOBBING)
[ITHERUS] NOW LOOK,
IF THERE'S ANYTHING ELSE YOU
NEED HELP WITH JUST LET ME KNOW.
I'LL TALK TO MY GRANDFATHER
AND SEE WHAT I CAN DO!
[MAID A] THANKS SO
MUCH, YOUNG MASTER!
[ITHERUS] I THOUGHT THAT MAYBE
IF WE WIDENED THIS WATERWAY,
MORE SHIPS COULD PASS THROUGH.
THAT OUGHT TO HELP US
EXPAND OUR MARITIME
TRADE PROFITS MOVING FORWARD.
[ITHERUS] GREAT JOB!
THE STRAWBERRIES THIS
YEAR ARE SO YUMMY!
AHHHHHHHHH!
[ITHERUS] UGH!
(GRUNT)
[ITHERUS] ONE MORE TIME!
(PANTING)
HEH!
[ISAAC] I THOUGHT HE WAS
JUST A PAMPERED LITTLE SNOT,
BUT HE'S ACTUALLY GONNA BE
A LORD SOMEDAY... GO FIGURE.
[KARASHIN] MASTER ITHERUS
IS IN A KEY POSITION.
IT'S A CRITICAL TIME
FOR THE CITY RIGHT NOW.
WHAT WITH THINGS THREATENING
TO GET NASTY WITH WESTELANDE.
[ISAAC] AND I SUPPOSE THAT HAS
SOMETHING TO DO WITH WHAT
THOSE JERKS IN MINAMI
ARE TRYING TO PULL.
[KARASHIN] WELL NOW! THAT WAS
PRETTY OBSERVANT OF YOU!
MISTER ISAAC'S A
POLITICIAN, NOW?
(GRUNTS)
I KNOW, TAKE IT EASY.
WELL, WESTELANDE AND MINAMI SEEM
TO BE RUBBING ELBOWS, RIGHT...
AND IT ALL COMES FROM WESTELANDE
LOOKING LIKE THEY WERE MAKING
A BIG PLAY FOR EASTAL. AND BY
A "BIG PLAY," I MEAN A BIG WAR.
ENLIGHTEN ME, PLEASE.
IN THEIR HISTORY, IT LOOKS
LIKE THE WHOLE ISLAND
OF YAMATO WAS GOVERNED BY WHAT
USED TO BE CALLED
THE IMPERIAL DYNASTY
OF WESTELANDE.
[KARASHIN] HOWEVER, AT SOME
POINT,
THE ENTIRE ISLAND WAS ENGULFED
IN A MASSIVE CIVIL WAR...
AND ONCE ALL THE
BATTLES HAD DIED DOWN,
THE DYNASTY FELL APART
UNDER ITS OWN WEIGHT.
WHAT'S LEFT, DIVIDED THINGS INTO
THE HOLY EMPIRE OF WESTELANDE,
AND EASTAL'S LEAGUE
OF FREEDOM CITIES.
AND EVEN AFTER ALL THIS TIME,
WESTELANDE IS STILL CLAIMING
THEY HAVE SOME SOVEREIGNTY
OVER THE LAND.
SO THEY'RE TRYING TO PROFIT OFF
THE NAME OF AN OLD DYNASTY?
WHAT A BUNCH OF IDIOTS... (GULP)
IF YOU GET ENOUGH PEOPLE
TOGETHER,
THERE'S BOUND TO BE
TROUBLE OF SOME KIND.
AND OF COURSE THAT "BUNCH
OF IDIOTS" ARE FOAMING
AT THE MOUTH TO GET
ALL OF US ADVENTURERS
INVOLVED IN THEIR MESS IF
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
AND YOU KNOW WAY TOO MUCH!
INFORMATION IS A MERCHANT'S
GREATEST ASSET, YOU KNOW?
SPEAKING OF "INFO,"
HERE'S A LITTLE GIFT.
SO WHAT'S THIS THEN?
(CHUCKLES)
[ISAAC, THINKING]
HRUMPH... WHAT A MESS,
PEOPLE OF THE LAND AND THE
ADVENTURERS
ARE BOTH A PAIN IN THE ASS.
I ALWAYS TURNED A BLIND
EYE TO IT AND SAID,
"NOPE, THAT'S ABOVE
MY PAY GRADE."
I MEAN, I REALLY
CAN'T STAND IT...
(CHOMP)
[ISAAC, THINKING] BUT
SOMETIMES IT'S GOT IT'S PERKS.
[ITHERUS]
HWAH, HUAH, HA!
UWAH!
(EXHALE)
[ISAAC] HEY...
[ITHERUS] UH?
[ISAAC] WHY DON'T YOU TRY THIS?
YOU'RE NOT EXACTLY MY SIZE,
JUNIOR. THAT'LL FIT YA BETTER.
GET YOUR BALANCE AND
FOOTWORK DOWN
AND THEN YOU OUGHTA
DO ALL RIGHT.
BUT THIS SWORD... IT WAS
EXPENSIVE, WASN'T IT?
IT'S YOUR BIRTHDAY...
IT'S MY GIFT TO YOU.
I DON'T THINK...
I DON'T THINK YOU REALLY
UNDERSTAND ECONOMICS,
DO YOU, MISTER ISAAC?
WELL YOU CAN ALWAYS
GIVE IT BACK!
IT WAS A JOKE.
I APPRECIATE IT! THANK
YOU VERY KINDLY, SIR!
[TETORA]
MARIELLE...
AREN'T WE SUPPOSED TO
BE GOING OVER TO SUIFUU
TO SEE THE PRINCESS TODAY?
[MARIELLE] SHE SAID SHE'S GOING
BACK TO MAIHAMA
TO ATTEND HER LITTLE
BROTHER'S BIRTHDAY PARTY.
[HENRIETTA] RIEZE'S GONE WITH
HER TO PROVIDE SECURITY.
[TETORA] FRICKITY FRACK! BUT I
WANTED TO TALKED TO HER ABOUT
THE TWO OF US FORMING
A NEW UNIT TOGETHER!
[BOTH] WHAT KIND OF "NEW UNIT"?
[TETORA]
CHECK IT!
A GALAXY‐STYLE STARLET
PRINCESS SPECIAL UNIT.
IT'LL BE CALLED...
TETONESHIA!
CAN'T YOU JUST
SEE IT, YOU GUYS?!
TWO YOUNG SUPER‐HOTTIES MAKING
THEIR DEBUT TOGETHER ON STAGE!
AFTER ALL, I GOTTA
MAKE A NAME FOR MYSELF
BEFORE WE ALL GO BACK HOME!
WE'LL MAKE OUR FIRST GIG, OUR
LAST GIG, THAT WOULD BE SO EPIC!
ALL WE'D HAVE TO DO
IS SHOW A LITTLE LEG...
YOU KNOW, HENRIETTA, WE'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO TELL THE PRINCESS
THAT WE MAY END UP
GOING BACK PRETTY SOON.
YEAH, IT'S NOT GOING TO BE
AN EASY GOODBYE FOR ANY OF US.
[RAYNESHIA] RIEZE?
[RIEZE] HUH?
[RAYNESHIA] I'M SORRY TO
FORCE THIS REQUEST ON YOU.
I KNOW YOU'RE EXTREMELY
BUSY WITH YOUR DUTIES,
RUNNING YOUR GUILD.
YOU MUST BE EXHAUSTED.
[RIEZE] OH, PLEASE.
I'M DOING FINE, REALLY.
YOU KNOW, TO BE HONEST,
A SECURITY DETAIL
LIKE THIS WOULD NORMALLY
BE GIVEN TO A MAN
OR AT LEAST SOMEONE IN THE
GUARD, WOULDN'T YOU THINK?
I MEAN, WHERE IS KRUSTY?
WHAT'S TAKING HIM SO LONG?
[RIEZE] UH... HM.
(STREET CHATTER)
[SERJIAD] I SUPPOSE FROM
AN ADVENTURER'S PERSPECTIVE
A GRAND DIPLOMATIC FUNCTION LIKE
THIS MUST SEEM A BIT TRIVIAL.
[ISAAC] NOT REALLY... WE'VE HAD
OUR SHARE OF PARTIES
BACK HOME AND HERE, TOO.
AND HONESTLY, SOME OF
US CAN GET PRETTY
GEEKED UP ABOUT BIRTHDAYS.
[SERJIAD]
SPLENDID.
MY GRANDSON IS AN
INTELLIGENT YOUNG MAN...
HE UNDERSTANDS A GREAT DEAL.
BUT STILL, THE BOY'S JUST
TURNED NINE YEARS OLD.
[SERJIAD] I SOMETIMES WONDER IF
I GAVE HIM TOO MUCH
RESPONSIBILITY TOO QUICKLY.
[ISAAC] WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT, OLD MAN?
YOU'VE BEEN SHOULDERING A LOT OF
THIS RESPONSIBILITY
YOURSELF, YOU KNOW?
DON'T YOU THINK YOU
HAVE ENOUGH GREY HAIR?
[SERJIAD]
HMMM...
[ISAAC]
OK, HE'S NINE.
BUT FROM WHAT I'VE SEEN YOU'VE
ALREADY MADE A MAN OUT OF HIM.
HE TAKES RESPONSIBILITY WELL.
IF HE WASN'T CAPABLE OF TAKING
IT HE WOULD'VE BROKEN ALREADY.
AND IF THINGS DO
GET HEAVY FOR HIM,
HE'S GOT PEOPLE
AROUND HIM TO HELP.
[SERJIAD] FOR ITHERUS'
SAKE I HOPE YOU'RE RIGHT.
[ISAAC]
HE'S DEFINITELY OKAY BY ME,
THE LITTLE FELLA STILL HAS
THE NERVE TO
CALL ME "MISTER," AFTER ALL.
HUH?
(EXCITEMENT WELLING UP)
[NOBLEMAN A]
PRINCESS RAYNESHIA!
[NOBLEMAN B]
SO BEAUTIFUL, AS ALWAYS.
[RAYNESHIA] I'M SORRY EVERYONE,
I KNOW I'M LATE...
MY APOLOGIES TO EVERYONE HERE.
PLEASE EXCUSE MY
TARDINESS, GRANDFATHER.
[ITHERUS] BIG SISTER
RAYNESHIA, WELCOME BACK!
I'M SORRY I GOT HERE
SO LATE, ITHERUS.
I HOPE YOU'VE
BEEN DOING WELL.
[ITHERUS]
YEAH!
I SPENT THE WHOLE TIME
YOU WERE AWAY TRYING
TO MAKE MORE ADVENTURER
FRIENDS JUST LIKE YOU DID.
[RAYNESHIA]
UH‐HUA. YOU HAVE TO BE VIGILANT!
MAKING A FRIEND WITH AN
ADVENTURER ISN'T EASY.
AND YOU HAVE TO BE CAREFUL,
YOU NEVER KNOW WHAT KIND
OF PERSON THEY ARE.
THERE ARE MONSTERS AMONG
THEM,
NOT TO MENTION A FEW
VILLAINS AS WELL.
IN FACT, TO BE SAFE, JUST STAY
AWAY FROM THE ONES WITH GLASSES.
WELL IN THAT CASE, EVERYTHING
SHOULD BE JUST FINE.
LOOK. MASTER ISAAC
DOESN'T WEAR GLASSES.
[RAYNESHIA]
OH, THAT'S GOOD THEN.
[ITHERUS] I'M ABOUT
TO MAKE MY DEBUT...
WOULD YOU DO ME A FAVOR AND
KEEP AN EYE ON ME, DEAR SISTER?
[RAYNESHIA] OF COURSE, I WILL.
[ITHERUS] MM!
(CHEERS AND CLAPPING)
[NOBLEMAN] MY LORD ITHERUS,
THIS JUICE IS MADE FROM THE
FRUIT GROWN IN OUR REGION.
IT IS OUR HUMBLE GIFT
TO YOU, YOUR GRACE.
[ITHERUS] AHH...
[NOBLEMAN] HMPH.
HEH HE HEH...
[ITHERUS]
UH?
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
MISTER ISAAC?
THAT WAS A PRETTY SLOPPY
ASSASSINATION ATTEMPT,
IF YOU ASK ME.
(DRINK POURING)
[MAID] WHAT? WHATEVER
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
[NOBLEMAN] NOW WAIT A MINUTE,
SIR. WE WOULD NEVER...
IT'S MERELY A GIFT
FOR THE NEW KING!
(CONCERNED CROWD)
YOU DIDN'T COUNT ON THE
ASSAULT ALERT EARRING
GIVEN TO ME BY THE
RODERICK'S CRAFTSMEN!
[ISAAC] OF COURSE, I WASN'T
EXPECTING IT
TO GO OFF THIS SOON,
BUT WHAT THE HELL.
[NOBLEMAN] UNGH.
UWA‐HAA!
[ISAAC] POISON! UWA!
(SCREAMS, DISORIENTED CROWD)
[ISAAC] DON'T BREATH, GOT IT?!
[MAID] GET OUTTA THE
WAY, ADVENTURER!
THIS DOESN'T CONCERN YOU!
[NOBLEMAN] WE'RE DOING THIS
FOR THE PEACE OF YAMATO!
[ISAAC] HA.
[ITHERUS] WHOA!
[ISAAC] HEY REZARICK,
DISTRACTION!
HYAHHH!
(GLASS BREAKING)
(PANTING)
[ITHERUS] ARE YOU OKAY?
[ISAAC] I'M FINE.
JUST BURNS A LITTLE.
[ISAAC, THINKING] THEY'RE
PRETTY TOUGH FOR NPCS...
I WONDER IF THEY'RE
THE ONES WHO...
[ISAAC]
HUH...?
[MAID]
YAAAH!
(GRUNT)
UGH!
(SURPRISED)
WHY DON'T YOU PICK
ON SOMEONE
TWICE YOUR SIZE!
UWAH!
SWORD OF PAIN BLACK!
[ASSASSIN A]
A BINDING SPELL!
[ASSASSIN B]
NO! DAMMIT!
NOW YOU BASTARDS CAN'T
ATTACK ANYBODY BUT ME!
YOU'RE NOT PUTTIN' ANOTHER HAND
ON THE KID ANYMORE, YOU GOT ME?!
WELCOME TO MY LITTLE
ASS‐KICKIN' PARTY!
WAH!
NNNGH!
HWAHHH!
HA!
UWAHA!
HUWAH!
HA!
YAHH!
UWAH!
UUWAAHHH! UNGH!
HA!
UH...
(COLLAPSE)
THAT'S WHAT YOU GET FOR
SAYIN' YOU'RE GONNA KILL
A KID FOR THE SAKE OF PEACE!
[ISAAC] YOU COWARDS!
[KARASHIN] WOW, ISAAC,
YOU'RE DEFINITELY MY HERO NOW.
[REZARICK] HANG ON A SECOND
YOU COULD USE SOME HEALING.
[ISAAC] I'LL BE OKAY, MAN...
I MADE SURE I DIDN'T GET
A WHOLE LUNG FULL OF IT.
SERIOUSLY, WHY'RE
THESE GUYS SO JACKED?
[KARASHIN] MINAMI WAS SUPPOSEDLY
LEVELING UP PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
I GUESS I OWE YOU BIG TIME
FOR ALL THAT INFORMATION
YOU GAVE ME THE OTHER DAY.
LOOKS LIKE YOUR PRESENT
FROM RODERICK'S MERCHANT
GUILD HELPED.
I STILL HAVEN'T FIGURED
OUT HOW YOU KNEW
WESTELANDE ASSASSINS
WOULD BE COMING?
I THINK I REMEMBER
SAYING INFORMATION
IS A MERCHANT'S BEST FRIEND.
WELL KARASHIN,
YOU'RE NOT AS MUCH OF
A WUSS AS I THOUGHT.
[KARASHIN] YEAH. AND I THOUGHT
YOU WERE ALL BRAWN
AND NO BRAINS.
[ISAAC] ITHERUS, YOU
SHOULD BE SAFE NOW.
[ITHERUS]
UH‐HUH.
DON'T YOU WORRY.
I'M NOT GOIN' ANYWHERE
LITTLE BUDDY 'O MINE!
YOU GOT THAT, SQUIRT....
[ITHERUS] OW...
[ITHERUS]
MM‐HM.
[ISAAC]
HEH...
[ITHERUS] THANK
YOU, MR. ISAAC.
[SHIROE] I SEE. PLEASE LET ME
KNOW IF ANYTHING ELSE HAPPENS.
GOOD WORK, GO AHEAD AND STAY
ON TOP OF THINGS...
THANKS, KARASHIN.
(VOICE CHAT ENDING)
[SHIROE, THINKING]
I KNEW IT.
OUR PRESENCE HERE IS THROWING
ALL THE OTHER SOCIETIES
OUT OF BALANCE.
[SHIROE] WE'VE GOTTA FIND A
WAY TO GET BACK HOME?
(SIGH) (DOOR OPENING)
[REGAN] IT'S BEEN A WHILE,
HASN'T IT, MASTER SHIROE?
[SHIROE] WHY ARE YOU ALWAYS
LURKING AROUND LIKE A CREEP?
[REGAN] I FINALLY
MADE SOME HEADWAY
IN MY INVESTIGATION OF SUSUKINO.
I DO APOLOGIZE FOR
IT TAKING SO LONG.
[REGAN] WOULD YOU LIKE
TO HEAR ABOUT IT?
[SHIROE] HOW'S
EVERYONE DOING THERE?
[REGAN] THEY'RE DOING
WELL, AND THEY MADE SURE
TO TELL ME TO SEND
YOU THEIR REGARDS.
[SHIROE] AND I SUPPOSE
THE SITUATION
WITH THE TRANSPORT
GATES IS THE SAME?
[REGAN] YES. AS I CONTINUED MY
RESEARCH,
I DISCOVERED THAT FAIRY RINGS
ARE INDEED AFFECTED
BY THE LUNAR CYCLES.
WHICH MAKES THE LEGEND OF
ANCIENT ALV RUINS
UP ON THE MOON ALL THE MORE
INTERESTING. (CHUCKLING)
[SHIROE, THINKING] THERE
MIGHT ACTUALLY BE A CONTROL
BEACON ON THE MOON AFFECTING
THE TRANSPORT COORDINATES.
THE MOON'S DEFINITELY IT...
[SHIROE] WE'VE GOTTA FIND
A WAY TO TALK TO THEM.
[REGAN]
"TALK TO THEM"?
[SHIROE]
YEAH.
RIGHT NOW, WE'RE INVESTIGATING
ANYTHING THAT MIGHT SEND
THE ADVENTURERS HOME.
AND AT THE MOMENT, COMMUNICATION
WITH THE MOON SEEMS
TO BE OUR BEST OPTION.
[REGAN]
AH. (MUNCHES)
[SHIROE] HOWEVER, THE
COST OF THE EQUIPMENT
TO DO IT HAS PROVEN
PROHIBITIVE.
[SHIROE] SO THINGS
AREN'T VERY PROMISING.
[REGAN] MASTER SHIROE,
SHIBUYA HAS AN ANTENNA.
[SHIROE]
I KNOW.
[SHIROE] SHIBUYA'S OLD
RADIO AND TV COMPLEX.
YAMATO'S ONLY
COMMUNICATIONS FACILITY.
WE LOOKED INTO IT A WHILE BACK,
AND I DON'T REMEMBER IT WORKING.
I DUNNO WHEN I INVESTIGATED IT,
I GOT A SIGNAL,
FAINT, BUT THERE NONETHELESS.
PERHAPS THERE MIGHT
STILL BE A CHANCE?
YOU GOT A SIGNAL?
(VOICE CHAT PING)
UH...?
[ISAAC, VOICE CHAT]
HEY, VILLAIN IN GLASSES!
YOU KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON?!
NPCS'RE DROPPING LIKE FLIES!
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?!
WHAT WAS THAT?! WHAT
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?!
JUST SLOW DOWN...!
[MINORI] MASTER SHIROE!
[BOTH] UH...!
WE NEED HELP!
WE'VE GOT A PROBLEM!
[ALL]
HUH?!
[AKATSUKI, VOICEOVER] THE PEOPLE
BEGIN MYSTERIOUSLY FALLING
INTO A DEEP SLEEP...
AS A BLACK SHADOW
ECLIPSES THE MOONLIT SKY.
SHIBUYA BECOMES A RAID ZONE,
AND IS OVERRUN BY MONSTERS.
WHO COULD BE TRYING TO STOP THE
ADVENTURERS
FROM RETURNING TO THE
WORLD THEY CAME FROM?
SHIROE DIVES INTO COMBAT,
CONCEALING THE UNCERTAINTY
WITHIN HIS HEART.
[SHIROE] MY COMRADES
ARE ALWAYS BESIDE ME.