[SHIROE, VOICEOVER] IT HAPPENED
ON CHRISTMAS EVE NIGHT.
[NAOTSUGU] WHOA! I KNEW
HE WAS SUPPOSED TO BE BIG,
BUT THAT IS RIDICULOUS!
[FEDERICO]
RUSEATO OF THE SEVENTH GARDEN...
[VOINEN]
IT'S JUST LIKE THE SCOUTS SAID,
HE'S THE SPITTING IMAGE OF
THE BOSS FROM THE HEILOS RAID!
[NAOTSUGU]
LET'S BREEZE THROUGH THIS
SO WE CAN CHOW DOWN
ON SOME CHICKEN.
[SHIROE]
I DON'T THINK WE'RE GONNA
"BREEZE THROUGH" ANYTHING...
[WILLIAM] BUT WE MIGHT
KEEP OURSELVES ALIVE
IF WE STICK TO THE PLAN.
[TETORA]
UMM...
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK
OUR CHANCES ARE, STRATEGIST?
[SHIROE]
FIFTY... FIFTY!
[SHIROE] WE'RE LESS THAN
TWENTY METERS AWAY!
WATCH IT, YOU GUYS!
COME ON!
(GRUNT)
(YELL)
HEAL!
SHIELD'S UP!
GO FOR IT!
[DINKURON]
I GOT HIM WHERE I WANT HIM!
ANCHOR HOWL!
(ROAR)
[WILLIAM] ALL RIGHT RAIDERS!
LET'S DO THIS...
DROP HIM WHERE HE STANDS!
(GRUNT)
HWAH!
[WILLIAM]
PARTY 3 AND 4, KEEP HITTING HIM!
PARTY 2 LEAD ELEMENT,
BACK 'EM UP!
ANYONE NOT ATTACKING,
CAST HEALING BUFFS
ON PARTY ONE'S TANKS!
UH...? WATCH IT!
KEEP AN EYE ON RUSEATO!
THAT GLOW MEANS SOMETHING!
UWAHHHH!
[DEMICAS, STRUGGLING]
UWAHEHEH...
TWO ARE DEAD...! AND SEVERAL
MORE ARE CRITICALLY WOUNDED!
REINFORCE THE FRONTLINE'S BUFFS!
SASAMEYUKI,
GIMME A COUNT!
MM. 1! 2!
[WILLIAM] KEEP HITTING HIM
FROM A DISTANCE,
WHILE WE CAST THE HEALING
AND RESURRECTION SPELLS!
YOU SEE WHAT HE DID...?
THAT WAS CRAZY OUT THERE!
THE ORIGINAL WASN'T
ANYWHERE NEAR AS POWERFUL!
THAT ONE JUST CAME AND
HIT US WITHOUT ANY WARNING!
23! 24!
[ELTON DISKA] HE'S COMING!
[RAGOMARU] MOVE IT! MOVE IT!
[SHIROE] WAIT! HE'S DOING
SOMETHING DIFFERENT THIS TIME!
(YELL)
EACH ATTACK UNLEASHES
A TON OF DAMAGE!
THERE'S NO WAY WE CAN
SURVIVE ONE OF THOSE.
[SASAMEYUKI]
88! 89! 90!
[SHIROE] NOW!
[WILLIAM] SHIELDS, PEOPLE!
SACRED BARRIER!
SANCTUARY!
[HIGHLAND]
IF YOU LIVE THROUGH IT,
START DOING A COUNT!
[NAOTSUGU]
YEAH! I HEAR YA ON THAT ONE!
(YELLING)
(STRUGGLED GRUNTS)
[SHIROE] EVERYONE SURVIVED!
90 SECONDS TO RECAST!
[DEMICAS] I NEED A HEALING SPELL
OVER HERE!
[TETORA] I'M ON IT, DEMI‐POO!
LOOKS LIKE HE'S WIDE OPEN
AFTER USING HIS ATTACK.
IT'S TIME FOR US TO
GO ON THE OFFENSIVE!
[NAOTSUGU] SO EVERYONE MADE IT
THROUGH HIS SECOND ATTACK?
NOT TOO SHABBY GUYS!
[SHIROE] YEAH. LOOKS LIKE WE'RE
ADAPTING PRETTY WELL OUT HERE.
(ROAR)
COME ON YOU GUYS!
DON'T LET UP ON ME!
I NEED EVERYTHING YOU'VE GOT!
NOW TAKE HIM DOWN.
[NAOTSUGU]
CROSS SLASH!
[FEDERICO]
ROUND WINDMILL!
[DEMICAS]
TURNING SWALLOW!
RESOUNDING BEAT!
LOOKS LIKE WE'RE
MAKING A COMEBACK!
(ROAR)
YOU'RE DOING TOO MUCH!
HE'S GOING TO REDIRECT HIS
ATTENTION!
YOU'RE GONNA END UP GETTING HIT!
UH? OH GOD! WHAT'S
GOING ON, I CAN'T MOVE?!
[BOLOGNESE MASTER] WHAT'S IS
THIS GUNK COMING OUT OF HIM!
[HIGHLAND] WHATEVER IT IS,
I'M STUCK IN IT!
[DINKURON] I'M LOSING HIT
POINTS! THIS CRAP IS POISONED!
[DINKURON] I CAN'T GET MY
ATTACK SPEED AND POWER UP!
I NEED A BUFF OUT HERE!
[SHIROE] I DON'T REMEMBER
THIS PATTERN IN HEILOS.
BUT IT DOESN'T SEEM TO
INFLICT MUCH DAMAGE.
[DINKURON]
ANCHOR HOWL!
WHAT THA?! HE'S
JUST IGNORING IT?!
[NAOTSUGU] ANCHOR HOWL
DIDN'T WORK?
[WILLIAM] HE'S GOT US TRAPPED.
HE'S USING AN
IMMOBILIZING ATTACK!
[WILLIAM] EH?
[SHIROE] THEY'RE IN TROUBLE!
[WILLIAM]
AOE BARRIERS!
DO WHAT YOU CAN
TO KEEP THEM HEALTHY.
HOLD YOUR GROUND!
(STRUGGLE)
[NAOTSUGU]
HOLY CRAP...!
(YELL)
AHHHHH!!!
(GRUNT)
UGH!
(GRUNT)(COLLAPSE)
AHHHHH!
[SHIROE]
W‐WE LOST TEN‐‐ NO, ELEVEN!
[WILLIAM] (STRUGGLE) PARTY 1'S
HEALERS, SUPPORT THE FRONTLINE.
PARTY 2, CAST HEALING
ON YOURSELVES
3 AND 4 LOWER YOUR DAMAGE...
BY 70 PERCENT!
GET HEALTHY, PEOPLE
EH...(LAUGHING)
I LOVE IT!
(CHUCKLE)
IS THIS A RAID, OR WHAT?!
[DEMICAS]
LIGHTNING STRAIGHT!
WYVERN KICK!
(GASP)
SHIROE...
TANK EXCHANGE!
NAOTSUGU! GET IN THERE!
ALL RIGHT! LET'S DO IT!
I GOT SOMETHING FOR
YA. AND YOUR MOM!
LOOKS LIKE HE'S ABOUT TO SWITCH
INTO A DIFFERENT CONFIGURATION!
THIS WAS JUST A GIMMICK WHEN
WE FOUGHT IT IN HEILOS.
I GUESS THIS BOSS CAN
DO IT ANY TIME HE WANTS!
[VOINEN] GREAT!
SO NOW WE'RE DEALING WITH
"TRUE WHITE KNIGHT" MODE?
[SHIROE] THE FIGHT'S
JUST GETTING STARTED!
DON'T LET YOUR GUARD DOWN.
[BOLOGNESE MASTER] IT'S JUST
AS THE SCOUTS REPORTED!
ALL HIS BROKEN ARMOR
IS TURNING INTO MORE BEASTS!
[FEDERICO] I DON'T THINK I'VE
EVER SEEN SO MANY.
CAN WE EVEN DO THIS?
IS IT POSSIBLE?
[DEMICAS] QUIT YER WHINING
SISSY PANTS! LET'S DO IT!
[WILLIAM] FRONT LINE DRAW THE
ATTENTION OF THE MOB!
EVERYONE ELSE ATTACK
RUSEATO AND MAKE IT COUNT!
HYAHHHHHHHH!
AAAH!
[DEMICAS]
YAHHH!
HUH? WHAT THE F...?
YOU KNOW? I DON'T THINK
THAT WAS A GOOD IDEA.
[NAOTSUGU] HUH? OH, COME ON!
THEY'RE RESTORING HIS HEALTH?!
[SHIROE]
I GET IT NOW...
EVERY ONE WE BEAT GIVES RUSEATO
SOME OF HIS HEALTH BACK..
PRETTY CLEVER ACTUALLY.
LOOK, HE'S BACK IN
BLACK KNIGHT MODE!
DOESN'T THIS
GUY EVER QUIT?!
88! 89! 90!
WAIT, LOOK! HE'S
REGAINING HIS STRENGTH!
(SCREAM)
[WILLIAM]
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHETHER HE'S GETTING HIS
STRENGTH BACK OR NOT!
IF WE HIT HIM FASTER
THAN HE CAN REGROUP,
THEN HE'LL NEVER CATCH UP.
YAHHHH!!!
[DEMICAS]
WHAT?! HE'S DOING IT AGAIN?!
[BOLOGNESE MASTER] THIS IS...
THIS IS PURE INSANITY!
AGGHHHHH!!!
HAHHHH!!!
I DON'T THINK
THIS IS WORKING...
WE NEED TO BE GOING AFTER
THAT GIANT FREAKING KNIGHT!
WE CAN'T JUST IGNORE THE SHADOW
VANGUARD!
IF WE LET 'EM GET PAST US!
THEY'LL KILL OUR HEALERS!
WE CAN'T BREAK UP.
WE WON'T HAVE A PARTY LEFT
TO HIT THIS GUY!
[SHIROE]
IT'S A NUMBERS GAME...
[NAOTSUGU] MM?
[DEMICAS] HMM....
[SHIROE] THE NUMBER OF
SHADOW VANGUARD THAT APPEAR
IS DIRECTLY RELATED TO
THE NUMBER OF PEOPLE
THAT CAUSE DAMAGE TO RUSEATO
IN BLACK KNIGHT MODE.
[NAOTSUGU]
OKAY, SO WHAT DO WE DO?
[SHIROE]
WE DO THIS...
WE ONLY LET OUR HEAVY
HITTERS TAKE HIM ON.
WE'LL TRAIN HIS FOCUS...
EVERYONE ELSE WILL
TAKE ON SUPPORT ROLES.
HYAH!
HWAH!
[SHIROE] THAT SHOULD CONTROL THE
NUMBER OF SHADOW VANGUARD,
ONLY RE‐SPAWNING TEN NEXT TIME.
[JUNZO] LET 'EM GET MAD,
BUT DON'T KILL 'EM THIS TIME!
[DEMICAS]
YEAH I KNOW! (GRUNT)
(GROWL)
[DEMICAS, THINKING]
I HATE TO ADMIT IT,
BUT I WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO
BEAT HIM LIKE I AM NOW.
NO. I CAN'T FORGIVE
HIM FOR WHAT HE DID.
SOMEDAY I'M GONNA KICK HIS ASS.
EVERYONE'S GONNA SEE IT.
AND I'M GONNA LOVE IT.
I'M GONNA RIP HIS GLASSES OFF
AND SMASH THAT
SMUG FACE OF HIS...
THEN I'M GONNA TAKE A LITTLE NAP
AND CRUSH HIM ALL OVER AGAIN!
[ENKARTANTO] LOOKS LIKE WE'VE
GOT HIM DOWN TO HALF HIS HEALTH!
[TOKO] GREAT!
I THINK WE GOT THIS GUYS.
HEH...
[DEMICAS, THINKING]
I'M GONNA GET STRONGER.
AND GET EPIC ITEMS ON THIS RAID.
YOU JUST WAIT... YOU'RE GONNA
GET YOURS, AND GET IT GOOD!
SHIROE, YOUR DAY IS
COMING, ENCHANTER!
YOU'RE GONNA PAY, BOY!
69! 70‐‐HUH?!
(SCREAM)
UWAH!
EH‐HEH. EH.
[WILLIAM]
WHA‐?!
WHAT THA...
TARTAURGA?!
HUH?
(SCREAM)
AH?
(SCREAMS)
[ENKARTANTO]
IT'S IBRA HABRA!
[TOKO] THAT CAN'T BE RIGHT!
THIS IS RUSEATO'S ZONE!
(GROWL)
(ROAR)
(SCREAMING)
WHAT...? ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
COME ON, MAN!
ANOTHER RAID BOSS?
THIS ISN'T GOOD...
THERE ARE THREE OF THEM?
[PROROCCA] THEY CAN'T DO THAT!
THEY CAN'T DO THAT!
THERE'S ONLY SUPPOSED
TO BE ONE RAID BOSS‐‐
ONLY ONE BOSS PER ZONE!
NO. THIS ISN'T FAIR.
[ALL]
AGGGHHHHHHHHH!!!!
[WILLIAM] WHAT IS THIS...?
A QUEST THAT'S NOT MEANT
TO BE BEATEN?
WE'RE GOING TO LOSE...
(GASP)
[DEMICAS]
SHIROE! HAAAA!
[SHIROE] AHHH! UPH!
[NAOTSUGU] SHIROE!
[DEMICAS]
(RASPY INHALE)
YOU HAVE THE STUPIDEST LOOK
ON YOUR FACE RIGHT NOW.
[SHIROE]
LOOK OUT!
UWAH!
[BOTH]
HUH? (SCREAM)
[SHIROE]
HUH?
ISN'T THIS...
... MY HOMETOWN?
I WAS BORN AND RAISED HERE.
HUH?
I CAN'T READ IT... IT WAS A
RESTAURANT, RIGHT?
OH, I GET IT. THIS IS WHAT IT'S
LIKE TO LOSE ONE OF MY MEMORIES.
[SHIROE, THINKING]
THAT'S RIGHT. I DIED.
IT'S NOT LIKE THE TOWN I GREW UP
IN WAS ALL THAT SPECIAL ANYWAY.
YOU COULD EAT AND
SLEEP AND WORK HERE,
BUT IF YOU REALLY WANTED
TO GET SOMETHING,
YOU'D HAVE TO GO TO SHIBUYA
OR SOMEWHERE LIKE THAT.
I'M A NORMAL GUY,
FROM A SMALL TOWN.
NOT MUCH MORE TO IT
THAN THAT, REALLY.
(DOOR OPENING)
[SHIROE]
UH?
(KEYS JINGLING, DOOR LOCKING)
THAT'S ME.
SINCE BOTH OF MY PARENTS WORKED,
I HAD A TENDENCY TO
SNEAK OUT OF THE HOUSE
AND WALK AROUND TOWN AT NIGHT.
EVEN WHEN I WAS GOING TO BED,
I WAS DEALING WITH DEPRESSION
AND BAD FEELINGS
WHEN I WAS BY MYSELF.
I WAS AFRAID OF GOING
DOWNTOWN...
SO INSTEAD...
I SPENT A LOT OF SLEEPLESS
NIGHTS ON THIS BENCH.
WHENEVER I FELT BAD
ABOUT SOMETHING,
SPENDING THE NIGHT OUT HERE
WAS THE ONLY THING
THAT HELPED ME FORGET.
[SHIROE]
WAIT! THAT'S IT!
NOW I KNOW WHY I CAME HERE.
I'M DEALING WITH
ANOTHER FAILURE AGAIN.
[SHIROE, THINKING]
ALL THE ADULTS I KNEW
COMPLIMENTED ME
ON BEING "GROWN‐UP."
YEAH, I DID A PRETTY GOOD JOB OF
KEEPING QUIET
AND UNDERSTANDING
WHAT THEY SAID...
BUT WHAT DID I LOSE BY NOT BEING
LIKE THE OTHER KIDS AROUND ME;
ACTING HIGH AND
MIGHTY ALL THE TIME?
(SIGH)
[SHIROE, THINKING]
I'VE MADE SO MANY MISTAKES.
AND I PUSHED ALL MY
POTENTIAL FRIEND AWAY.
THEY OFFERED. I REFUSED, AND
CRAWLED FURTHER INTO MY SHELL.
AND I KEPT WALKING AWAY FROM
THE ONE PLACE
I NEEDED TO BE
PART OF THE GROUP.
MY FAMILY.
HOW HARD WAS IT ON MY PARENTS
TO WORK LIKE THEY DID
JUST TO HAVE A KID WHO WASN'T
REALLY THERE,
BECAUSE THEY WEREN'T THERE?
I MADE A LOT OF LITTLE MISTAKES,
BUT PUNISHED MYSELF FOR THEM
OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
I'D COME HERE TO CRY EVERY TIME
I SCREWED UP IN SCHOOL.
I SWORE EVERY SINGLE TIME NOT TO
REPEAT MY MISTAKES...
AND I DID, ANYWAY.
YOU LEARN A LOT
ABOUT YOURSELF...
YOU LEARN THINGS THAT YOU WANTED
TO KNOW AND DIDN'T WANNA KNOW.
AND IT DOESN'T GET EASIER EACH
TIME IT HAPPENS EITHER.
SO MOST OF US DON'T WANNA
GO THROUGH IT AGAIN.
[SHIROE, THINKING] OKAY, SO THIS
IS WHAT IT MEANS TO DIE HERE.
DEATH DOESN'T HAPPEN UNTIL YOU
ACTUALLY WANT TO DIE!
AND WELL, I CAN'T SAY I HAVEN'T
THOUGHT ABOUT IT A FEW TIMES.
I REMEMBER THROWING ALL MY
PRECIOUS NOTEBOOKS AWAY ONCE...
OR JUST ABOUT EVERY TIME I SAID
GOODBYE TO MY FOLKS
WITH THAT FAKE SMILE OF MINE.
OR THE NIGHT WE PARTED
AT THE LIBRARY.
I GUESS THAT MEANS,
I'VE DIED A LOT ALREADY.
WHAT WAS DEMICAS THINKING WHEN
HE KICKED ME OUT OF THE WAY?
WHY DID WILLIAM SAY YES TO ME
WITHOUT HEARING ME OUT FIRST?
AND YOU WOULD THINK NAOTSUGU
WOULD'VE HAD BETTER SENSE
THAN TO FOLLOW ME HERE!
I HAVE SO MANY FRIENDS,
NOT KNOWING WHERE I AM
OR WHAT I'M DOING.
THEY'RE JUST HANGING BY
A THREAD RIGHT NOW.
[MINORI]
THERE MIGHT BE A SPY FROM MINAMI
IN THE CITY SOMEWHERE.
A LEAK FROM ANY ONE OF US,
NO MATTER HOW "SMALL"
OR "HARMLESS,"
COULD CAUSE A PROBLEM.
[SHIROE]
THAT'S RIGHT.
[SHIROE, THINKING] HONESTLY,
IF THERE ARE SPIES FROM MINAMI,
THEY'RE THE LEAST
OF MY WORRIES.
SO FAR, I'VE ONLY SEEN
ADVENTURERS AND
PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
BUT THERE'S SOMEONE ELSE HERE.
THERE'S AN UNKNOWN THIRD PARTY
THAT BROUGHT US TO THIS PLACE
FOR SOME REASON.
I'VE BEEN USING THE CONNECTIONS
OF THE ROUND TABLE CONFERENCE
TO SNOOP AROUND AND
FIND OUT THE REAL IDENTITY
OF THE PERSON OR
THING THAT DID IT.
I ASKED RODERICK TO INVESTIGATE
WHAT MIGHT BE GOING ON
WITH FLAVOR TEXT IMBUING
OBJECTS WITH POWER.
AND I ASKED SOJIRO TO SEE IF
ANY OF THE MONSTERS
STARTED CHANGING BEHAVIOR.
I HAVE MICHITAKA EXAMINING
PLANTS TO THE SOUTH AND
KARASHIN IS COLLECTING
AND ASSEMBLING
A LIBRARY OF EASTAL'S FOLKTALES.
OF COURSE, ME BEING ME,
I NEVER REALLY TOLD THEM
WHY I WANTED IT DONE.
[SHIROE]
HMMM....
[SHIROE, THINKING]
AND AT LEAST, UP TO THIS POINT,
THERE'S NOTHING IN WHAT THEY'VE
GATHERED SO FAR THAT SHOWS US
THE FACE OF THE THIRD PARTY
I'M LOOKING FOR.
HOWEVER...
IT JUST SEEMS A LITTLE
TOO COINCIDENTAL
THAT ALL THE EVIDENCE
POINTS IN THE DIRECTION.
IT'S ALMOST AS IF
SOMEONE PLANTED IT.
[SHIROE]
MPH...
[SHIROE, THINKING] I SUPPOSE
THAT'S JUST AN EXCUSE, RIGHT?
EVEN THOUGH I KEPT IT TO MYSELF
SO THEY WOULDN'T WORRY,
I'M STILL PUTTING EVERYONE OUT.
(SIGH) I'M NOT SURE
I DESERVE THEIR TRUST.
NAOTSUGU AND AKATSUKI
WAITED FOR ME BACK THEN,
AND NOW EVERYONE ELSE
IS WAITING FOR ME.
IT'S MY FAULT THERE'S
A DISTANCE BETWEEN US.
I SHOULD HAVE INVOLVED THEM MORE
AND TOLD THEM
WHAT I WAS THINKING.
AND THEN THERE WAS KINJO...
I DIDN'T TRUST HIM EITHER.
SO I KEPT MY THOUGHTS BURIED.
I SHOULD HAVE TOLD HIM
WHAT I WANTED
AND LET HIM HAVE ALL THE FACTS.
HMPH...
YEAH...
I KNOW YOU'RE RIGHT.
I SHOULD BE GETTING OUT
OF HERE, SHOULDN'T I?
YOU CAN ONLY SPEND SO MUCH TIME
HANGING OUT ON A BENCH
WITH YOURSELF.
UH? OH...
EARTH...
SO I'M GUESSING THIS
IS THE MOON, RIGHT?
MARE TRANQUILLITATIS?
THE "SEA OF TRANQUILLITY."
IT REALLY IS THE MOON!
SO WHAT AM I DOING HERE, ANYWAY?
WAS THIS REALLY THE TEST SERVER?
MANAGEMENT FOR THE ELDER TALES
GAME WAS DIVIDED BETWEEN
THIRTEEN SERVERS THAT COVERED
ALL OF THE REGIONS.
THE TEST SERVER IS NOT
OFFICIALLY INCLUDED
IN THE THIRTEEN, MAKING IT
THE FOURTEENTH SERVER.
[SHIROE] I KNOW SOMEONE
ON THE INTERNET
SAID IT WAS ON THE MOON,
BUT I NEVER BELIEVED THEM.
[SHIROE] I REALLY DIDN'T THINK
IT WAS GONNA BE THIS QUIET.
[AKATSUKI]
YEAH...
OH...
AH!
I THINK I...
I LOST PART OF MYSELF.
DID YOU JUST SEE THAT?
OR FEEL IT, MY LORD?
[SHIROE]
HERE, AKATSUKI.
YEAH, OKAY.
INCREDIBLE, ISN'T IT?
[AKATSUKI] LOOK AT THAT.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
[SHIROE] YEAH.
[AKATSUKI]
THOSE ARE... THEY'RE MEMORIES?
[SHIROE]
EVERY TIME A PLAYER HAS DIED,
THEY'VE OFFERED A MEMORY
SO THEY COULD STAND UP
ONE MORE TIME.
SO I'M GUESSING YOU GOT
KILLED ON YOUR MISSION?
UH...?
[SHIROE] YEAH WELL... THE SAME
THING HAPPENED TO ME.
AND NOW WE'RE BOTH DEAD.
[AKATSUKI]
YOU TOO, MY LORD?
[SHIROE]
MM‐HM.
[AKATSUKI] THIS HAS TO BE
THE STRANGEST CHRISTMAS EVE
EVER, MY LORD. REALLY.
HUH? EH. EHEH...
[SHIROE]
I'VE COMPLETELY FAILED.
I DON'T THINK I
PLANNED WELL ENOUGH.
I DIDN'T TRUST ANYONE.
[AKATSUKI] I'M NOT REALLY SURE
I UNDERSTAND, MY LORD.
SOMEHOW I'M NOT ALL THAT
UPSET ABOUT LOSING MY BATTLE.
[SHIROE]
A MYRIAD OF THINGS
KEPT ME FROM DOING
WHAT I PLANNED TO DO.
AND IT WOUND UP
GETTING ME KILLED.
YOU MIGHT HAVE DIED OUT THERE
TONIGHT, AKATSUKI,
BUT I'LL TELL YOU THIS...
YOU STILL HAVEN'T LOST
YOUR FIGHT! NOT EVEN CLOSE.
IT'S OKAY.
I'M DISAPPOINTED, TOO.
BUT I KNOW YOU,
AND HOW HARD YOU WORK.
SO I KNOW YOU'RE GONNA
GET UP AND FINISH THIS!
[SHIROE, THINKING]
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK...?
I THINK WE'VE BOTH GOTTA GET UP
AND TAKE ANOTHER CRACK AT IT.
[SHIROE]
IT'S ALL SO STRANGE.
I NEVER IMAGINED I'D END UP
SEEING YOU OUT HERE LIKE THIS.
[AKATSUKI] HEH, YES, MY LORD.
IT IS STRANGE.
YOU KNOW, MY LORD?
I NEED TO GO BACK AGAIN.
I THINK I SHOULD GIVE IT
ANOTHER SHOT TOO,
AND USE EVERYONE'S EXPERIENCE.
[AKATSUKI]
SHALL WE?
MHM.
MPH...
[SHIROE, THINKING] AND THAT'S...
IS WHEN I CAME BACK TO LIFE.
[AKATSUKI, VOICEOVER]
RAW EMOTIONS ARE FULLY EXPOSED.
WHAT ELSE IS LEFT?
WHAT CAN BE DONE?
THE ANSWER IS SIMPLE: NOTHING.
NO MATTER WHAT ANYONE THINKS,
HE PUSHES FORWARD.
IT'S THE PATH HE CHOSE.
AND THERE IS NO WAY BACK.
HE WILL TRY AGAIN AND AGAIN
UNTIL HIS BANNER IS
PLANTED INTO THE SOIL.
[SHIROE]
STAND UP, ONE MORE TIME!