POOR AKATSUKI...
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
WHERE AM I?
WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
COME AND GET YOUR FRESH HOT
CHRISTMAS CAKES HERE!
AND REMEMBER, IF YOU DON'T
HURRY AND GET ONE TODAY...
NOM, NOM, NOM...
YOU CAN'T BLAME ME,
WHEN IT TURNS BACK INTO
A BORING OL' NORMAL CAKE.
AND THE KIDS WILL LOVE THIS!
IF YOU BUY YOURSELF A
CHRISTMAS CAKE RIGHT NOW,
YOU'LL GET A
REINDEER MASK FREE!
THAT'S RIGHT.
(GRUNTS)
[NERURESU]
DISGUSTING ADVENTURERS!
[RIEZE]
THERE'S NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
HENRIETTA IS AT THE CATHEDRAL,
AND SHE'LL LET US KNOW THE
MOMENT AKATSUKI WAKES UP.
KAY.
AREN'T YOU A BIT COLD, MILADY?
YOU'VE BEEN STANDING BY THE
WINDOW FOR A WHILE NOW.
YEAH, I SUPPOSE.
[RIEZE]
OF COURSE, I'M ALWAYS COLD HERE.
I DIDN'T GROW UP
ANYTHING LIKE THIS.
YOU MEAN, YOU'RE NOT FROM
AKIHABARA, LADY RIEZE?
NO, I'M FROM A TOWN
CALLED KIYOSE.
I BELIEVE YOU WOULD
RECOGNIZE IT
AS THE AREA AROUND
NOBIDOME DISTRICT.
UH, BUT WAIT, I THOUGHT THAT...
I THAT YOU WERE
DESCENDED FROM NOBILITY.
NO, NOT EVEN CLOSE.
MY FAMILY IS
WONDERFULLY AVERAGE.
UH?
[RAYNESHIA]
HM. I GUESS THAT MEANS,
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
ANYTHING, DO I?
[RIEZE] HUH...
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT YOU,
OR EVEN ANY OF THE PEOPLE
I'VE MET HERE.
NOT MISS AKATSUKI, OR LADY
HENRIETTA OR LADY MARIELLE.
I MEAN, MAYBE I...
WHAT I MEAN IS...
IT'S NOT THAT I DON'T KNOW YOU,
BUT RATHER, I'VE NEVER EVEN
TRIED TO LEARN ABOUT YOU.
I DIDN'T EVEN TRY TO
LEARN ABOUT MASTER KRUSTY.
[RAYNESHIA] MM?
[RIEZE] WELL ALLOW ME TO
SHARE SOMETHING WITH YOU.
I WAS AN HONOR STUDENT
AT SCHOOL, Y'KNOW.
[RAYNESHIA]
HM?
THE FACULTY TOOK A
LIKING TO ME,
I WAS EXCELLENT
IN MY CLASSES.
AND ALL I HAD TO DO
WAS ACT INTELLIGENT,
AND THEN I WAS
SHOWERED WITH PRAISE.
IT'S LIKE I'D BECOME ADEPT AT
PRETENDING I WAS SMART.
SO AS YOU MIGHT EXPECT,
I'M GLAD I FOUND MYSELF
IN A GUILD LIKE D. D. D.
I MET A LOT OF PEOPLE
THROUGH THE GUILD.
AND THEY SHOWED ME THAT I
REALLY NEEDED TO FOCUS ON
SOMEONE OTHER THAN MYSELF.
IF I DIDN'T LEARN THAT...
I CAN'T REALLY IMAGINE THE
NUMBER OF WONDERFUL THINGS
I WOULD HAVE MISSED
IN THIS WORLD,
OR THE AMAZING PEOPLE
I WOULD HAVE MET.
I CAN'T IMAGINE WHERE I'D BE.
HMMM... I CAN
RELATE TO THAT.
EVERYONE IS BEAUTIFUL AND
UNIQUE IN THEIR OWN WAY.
WE JUST DON'T ALWAYS
SEE IT DO WE?
AND WE DON'T ALWAYS KNOW HOW TO
RECOGNIZE IT WHEN WE DO SEE IT.
PERHAPS THAT'S THE REASON I FEEL
THE NEED TO ACT LIKE A PRINCESS.
'CAUSE MY STRENGTHS, THEY
NEVER SEEM LIKE ENOUGH.
I FEEL THE ONLY THING I REALLY
HAVE IS MY ROYAL HERITAGE
AND SO...
I WANT TO...
I NEED TO BE COMPLETELY OPEN AND
HONEST WITH YOU, LADY RIEZE.
IF I'M ANYTHING ELSE, THEN I
DO NOT DESERVE YOUR KINDNESS.
ANYTHING LESS IS NOT WORTHY OF
SOMEONE'S RESPECT OR FRIENDSHIP.
SO, YOU WANT TO BE
"OPEN"? ALL RIGHT.
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT, MY
FIRST BIT OF ADVICE IS SIMPLE.
BEING A PERFECTLY "OPEN"
PERSON IS ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE.
UH...
(EXHALE) LET'S JUST START BY
BEING FRIENDS, RAYNESHIA.
IF YOU WOULD BE OKAY
WITH THAT, OF COURSE...
I AM AN ADVENTURER AFTER ALL.
MPH.
(STREET NOISE AND CHATTER)
[ AKATSUKI, THINKING]
DON'T TELL ME...?
COULD IT... NO...?
[AKATSUKI]
MMNPH.
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
OKAY WHERE AM I TRYING TO GO?
I KEEP GETTING PUSHED AROUND,
RUSHED SOMEWHERE,
BUT I DON'T KNOW WHERE...
[AKATSUKI]
UH? MPH...
(RUNNING AND HEAVY BREATHING)
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
ALL RIGHT. WHERE AM I GOING NOW?
WHAT IF I, WHAT IF I'M
NOT GOING ANYWHERE?
MAYBE I'M JUST RUNNING
FOR THE SAKE OF RUNNING.
(SHATTERING)
[SHIROE] I REALLY DIDN'T THINK
IT WAS GOING TO BE THIS QUIET.
[AKATSUKI]
YEAH...
OH...
AH!
I THINK I... I LOST
PART OF MYSELF...
DID YOU SEE THAT?
OR FEEL IT, MY LORD?
HERE, AKATSUKI.
YEAH, OKAY...
UH...
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
AH SO THAT'S WHERE WE ARE.
[SHIROE]
INCREDIBLE, ISN'T IT?
[AKATSUKI] LOOK AT THAT...
IT'S... BEAUTIFUL.
YEAH.
[AKATSUKI]
THOSE ARE... THEY'RE MEMORIES?
[SHIROE]
EVERY TIME A PLAYER HAS DIED,
THEY'VE OFFERED A MEMORY SO THEY
COULD STAND UP ONE MORE TIME.
SO I'M GUESSING YOU GOT
KILLED ON YOUR MISSION...?
UH?
[AKATSUKI]
THAT'S RIGHT! I DIED. DIDN'T I?
(EXHALE)
YES, I DIED.
AND I WAS JUST ABOUT TO LEARN
SOMETHING VERY IMPORTANT!
YEAH, WELL... THE SAME
THING HAPPENED TO ME.
AND NOW WE'RE BOTH DEAD.
YOU TOO, MY LORD?
MM‐HM
THIS HAS TO BE THE STRANGEST
CHRISTMAS EVE EVER, MY LORD...
REALLY.
OH... UH?
HEH...
I'VE COMPLETELY FAILED...
I DON'T THINK I
PLANNED WELL ENOUGH...
I DIDN'T TRUST ANYONE.
I'M NOT REALLY SURE
I UNDERSTAND MY LORD.
SOMEHOW I'M NOT ALL THAT
UPSET ABOUT LOSING MY BATTLE.
[SHIROE]
A MYRIAD OF THINGS
KEPT ME FROM DOING
WHAT I PLANNED TO DO.
AND IT WOUND UP
GETTING ME KILLED.
IT'S ALL SO STRANGE.
I NEVER IMAGINED I'D END UP
SEEING YOU OUT HERE LIKE THIS.
HEH, YES, MY LORD.
IT IS STRANGE.
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
WAS THIS JUST COINCIDENCE?
NO, IT HAS TO BE BECAUSE
I WANTED SO BADLY
TO SEE HIM AGAIN.
I WAS ACHING TO FEEL
HIM NEXT TO ME.
BUT THERE WAS SOMETHING ELSE.
SOMETHING ABOUT TO CLICK.
I WAS ON THE VERGE OF
SOMETHING BIG.
[AKATSUKI] YOU KNOW, MY LORD.
I NEED TO GO BACK AGAIN.
I THINK I SHOULD GIVE IT
ANOTHER SHOT TOO,
AND USE EVERYONE'S EXPERIENCE.
SHALL WE...
MHM.
UH... MPH.
I WAS SOMEWHERE WITH MY LORD. IT
WAS COLD AND I REMEMBER THE SEA.
(SNIFFLE)
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
I HAVE...
I HAVE A FLEETING FEELING.
I ALMOST HAD SOMETHING.
ALMOST HAD IT IN MY HANDS.
THAT'S IT. I'M GOING
TO FACE HIM AGAIN.
AND NO MATTER WHAT,
I WILL NOT FAIL THIS TIME.
[HENRIETTA]
AKATSUKI!
[AKATSUKI] HUH?
[HENRIETTA] UHA!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
HE DIDN'T LEAVE ANY
SCARS ON YOU, DID HE?!
OH! YOU'RE JUST SO CUTE!
PLEASE DON'T DO THAT.
I THOUGHT IT WAS
ABOUT TIME FOR YOU
TO COME OUT OF THAT
SLUMBER OF YOURS.
[AKATSUKI] EXCUSE ME...
[HENRIETTA] (COOING) HMM?
[HENRIETTA] SORRY.
[AKATSUKI] IT'S PROBABLY
A BIT RUDE OF ME TO ASK,
BUT I REALLY NEED YOUR
HELP WITH SOMETHING.
COULD YOU PLEASE
TEACH ME THE ORAL ARTS?
I WANT TO DO WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO STOP THAT SERIAL KILLER
[NAZNA] HMMMM...
[RIEZE] DIDN'T MASTER SOJIRO
ALREADY USE HIS ORAL ART
AGAINST HIM, MISS NAZNA?
[NAZNA] HE DID.
AND THAT WASN'T ENOUGH
TO GET THE JOB DONE, WAS IT?
THAT'S RIGHT.
(EXHALE)
[RIEZE] THERE IS NO SENSE
OBSESSING OVER IT
KNOWING THAT IT
DIDN'T WORK BEFORE.
[AKATSUKI] WELL I MEAN,
I WANT TO STOP THIS MANIAC
FROM KILLING ANYONE ELSE.
IT DOESN'T HAVE TO
BE AN ORAL ART.
IT'S JUST...
IF ANY OF YOU KNOW
ANOTHER WAY TO END THIS...
I'M WILLING TO LEARN
ABOUT THAT TOO!
[NAZNA] YOU REALLY THINK YOU
HAVE A CHANCE TO BEAT HIM?
[AKATSUKI]
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW.
BUT I HAVE TO TRY, I CAN'T JUST
SIT BACK AND LET HIM KEEP GOING.
MASTER SHIROE'S
NOT IN THE CITY RIGHT NOW.
WE HAVE TO HANDLE THIS!
AH... DID I JUST
HEAR YOU CORRECTLY?
SHIROE ISN'T HERE IN THE CITY?
UH... LISTEN HE ASKED US TO
KEEP IT QUIET IF WE COULD.
BUT YES, SHIROE ISN'T HERE.
HE'S CURRENTLY ON A MISSION
OUTSIDE OF AKIHABARA.
[NAZNA]
WELL THAT EXPLAINS A LOT.
NOW I KNOW WHY YOU'VE BEEN
ACTING SO STRANGE.
AKATSUKI?
UH?
[NAZNA] YOU STILL HAVEN'T
ANSWERED MY QUESTION.
DO YOU THINK YOU CAN WIN?
CAN YOU STOP THIS GUY
FROM KILLING AGAIN?
UPH.
AND ARE YOU ABLE TO
DO IT ALL ON YOUR OWN?
[AKATSUKI] 'COURSE NOT ALONE.
[HENRIETTA] OH?
I KNOW I CAN'T HANDLE
THIS GUY BY MYSELF.
THAT'S WHY I'M HERE
ASKING FOR YOUR HELP.
PLEASE HELP ME END THIS!
(SHAKY BREATH)
[AKATSUKI]
OHH...
[RIEZE] I WOULD SAY YOU'VE
PASSED OUR TEST,
IF ONLY HALFWAY.
D. D. D. HAS BUT EIGHT
CONFIRMED ORAL ARTS
AMONG ITS MEMBERS
AT THE MOMENT.
LORD KRUSTY'S ALREADY
GIVEN US PERMISSION.
WE WILL SHARE EVERYTHING
WE KNOW WITH YOU.
UH...
GOODNESS...
THIS IS LIKE GOING THROUGH
MIDDLE SCHOOL ALL OVER AGAIN.
[MISA]
SEE FOR YOURSELF,
THERE DOESN'T SEEM TO BE
ANY MORE GOBLINS IN THIS AREA.
[KRUSTY]
YEAH...
[MISA]
MY LORD!
[KRUSTY]
HM?
YOU'RE GETTING BORED
AGAIN, AREN'T YOU?
AH... OKAY GUILTY AS CHARGED.
I'M COMING OUT OF MY SKIN.
YEAH WELL DEAL WITH IT.
LOOK I WOULDN'T BE HERE
IF I WASN'T ABLE TO
ENDURE SUCH THINGS.
(SIGH)
HM?
[KRUSTY]
WHAT'S GOING ON THERE?
MY WEAPON'S BEEN ACTING
A BIT STRANGE AS OF LATE.
WHY DON'T YOU HAVE SOMEONE
TAKE A LOOK AT IT, REPAIR IT?
YEAH, I GUESS I COULD, BUT IT'S
WORKING FINE OTHER THAN THIS.
[KRUSTY]
IF I'M NOT MISTAKEN,
YOU WEAPON IS NAMED
"DISASTER," YES?
YEAH, EVEN THE FLAVOR TEXT
ISN'T VERY FLATTERING
IN ITS DESCRIPTION
OF IT EITHER.
IT'S A LITTLE BETTER NOW.
SORRY FOR BRINGING IT UP.
(ELECTRIC SOUNDS)
(MUTTERING)
[ALI]
MMMMMM...
GLAD THAT'S OVER WITH...
I ALWAYS GET NERVOUS
WHEN I HAVE TO PRESENT
MY RESEARCH TO THE CLASS.
[AOMORI] WELL EVERYBODY
SEEMED TO BE PRETTY IMPRESSED
WITH YOUR WORK Y'KNOW.
IT WAS THE COOLEST THING TO COME
OUT OF RODERICK'S WORKSHOP...
AT LEAST IT
SEEMED LIKE IT TO ME.
IT'S ACTUALLY A PRETTY COOL
THING IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
NOT NEEDING A CHEF SUBCLASS
TO COOK ANYMORE.
[MIKAKAGE] YEAH WELL,
I WOULDN'T CALL MAKING A SALAD
A GRAND ACHIEVEMENT.
STILL I'M NOT SURE REALLY
HOW IT'S EVEN POSSIBLE
TO BEGIN WITH.
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
[ALL]
HM?
[AOMORI]
IT'S THE GUILD MASTER.
[RODERICK]
AH, CONTINUE EATING EVERYONE.
I'M PLEASED TO ANNOUNCE
SOME OF OUR LATEST FINDINGS
ON A FEW OF THE THINGS
WE'VE BEEN INVESTIGATING.
THERE ARE THREE TOPICS
I NEED TO SHARE WITH YOU
WHILE WE STILL HAVE THE TIME.
FIRST IS THE GENDER GAP THAT
GOES BACK TO OUR GAMING DAYS.
[AOMORI]
"GENDER GAP"?
YOU KNOW HOW SOME
PEOPLE PLAYED THE GAME
AS THE OPPOSITE GENDER?
THAT'S WHAT HE MEANS.
THE BODY INFLUENCES PERSONALITY,
BUT NOW IT APPEARS THOSE
GENDER CHARACTERISTICS
WILL ALSO BE PASSED TO
YOUR VOCAL CORDS.
THUS FURTHER ALTERING
ONE'S GENDER IN THIS WORLD.
IF YOU ARE CURRENTLY AN
ADVENTURER IN A FEMALE BODY,
YOUR VOICE WILL GRADUALLY
BECOME MORE FEMININE.
THOSE MALE PLAYERS
WILL CONTINUE TO ACQUIRE
FEMALE CHARACTERISTICS.
(SURPRISED GASP)
NEXT IS A
GEOGRAPHICAL OBSERVATION.
AND TO BE HONEST...
THERE ARE MORE QUESTIONS
THAN ANSWERS ABOUT THIS.
BUT IT LOOKS AS THOUGH THE
DISTANCE BETWEEN AKIHABARA
AND MT. FUJI IS
GRADUALLY INCREASING.
ACTUALLY IT'S THE DISTANCE
BETWEEN ANY TWO POINTS.
ALTHOUGH THE INCREMENTS
ARE RATHER SMALL FOR NOW.
[BLACKSMITH] EXCUSE ME!
[RODERICK] YES. GO AHEAD.
[BLACKSMITH] IS THAT GOING ON
EVERYWHERE, GUILD MASTER?
I MEAN, ARE THE MOUNTAIN RANGES
THEMSELVES ALSO GETTING BIGGER?
IS EVERYTHING GROWING?
YES, THAT APPEARS
TO BE THE CASE.
[RODERICK] THE LAST ISSUE WE'LL
BE ADDRESSING IS FLAVOR TEXT.
[RODERICK]
AS YOU'RE ALREADY AWARE,
FLAVOR TEXT IS JUST
AN EXPLANATION DESCRIBING
AN ITEM'S ORIGINS AND ABILITIES
ORIGINALLY WRITTEN BY
THE DEVELOPERS.
THEY CALLED IT "FLAVOR TEXT"
BECAUSE IT WAS ONLY THERE
TO ENHANCE THE EXPERIENCE
OF THE GAME PLAY.
OKAY, THEY'RE
THE LITTLE POP‐UPS
THAT ARE SUPPOSED TO
SET THE MOOD AND STUFF.
[RODERICK]
THAT'S RIGHT.
THESE BLURBS WERE NEVER MEANT TO
HAVE ANY REAL MEANING TO THEM.
BUT SOMETHING ABOUT THEM
SEEMS TO HAVE CHANGED.
ANYTHING WRITTEN ABOUT ANY
PERSON OR THING IN ITS TEXT
HAS A NEW RELEVANCE.
[MIKAKAGE] CRAZY...
[RODERICK]
IS IT SIMPLY COINCIDENCE
THAT ALL THESE RECENT PHENOMENA
HAVE BEEN HAPPENING LATELY?
PERHAPS WE SHOULD
CONSIDER THE POSSIBILITY
THAT THIS WORLD IS IN THE MIDDLE
OF A LARGE‐SCALE TRANSFORMATION.
IT APPEARS THE APOCALYPSE
ISN'T ANYWHERE NEAR COMPLETE.
[RIEZE]
I HAVE A REPORT ON HIM.
THE SERIAL KILLER IS
A PERSON OF THE LAND.
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
SHE TOLD THEM...
[RIEZE] IF THIS INFORMATION
BECOMES PUBLIC,
IT'S GOING TO DO
IRREPARABLE DAMAGE
TO THE RELATIONSHIP
BETWEEN BOTH OUR PEOPLES.
I CAN ONLY ASSUME
THAT'S THE REASON
YOU WENT OUT TRYING TO HANDLE
THIS MATTER ON YOUR OWN?
[RIEZE]
AM I RIGHT?
MM.
I UNDERSTAND WHY
YOU WANTED TO DO THIS...
BUT THE PUBLIC WOULD'VE
DISCOVERED THE TRUTH EVENTUALLY.
WELL NOT IF EVERYONE IN THE
PUBLIC IS ALREADY DEAD.
IS THE BRIGADE OF
THE WEST WIND
PLANNING TO RELEASE
THIS INFORMATION?
NO! SOJIRO SAID WE'RE GOING
TO STAY OUT OF IT FOR NOW.
HE'S WAITING FOR THESE
TWO TO FIX THIS MESS.
[RIEZE] MEANING?
[NAZNA] MEANING SOMEONE
NEEDS TO SET THEM STRAIGHT.
AND I DON'T THINK YOU WANT ME
TO BE THE ONE TO DO IT.
(SIGH)
[HENRIETTA] SO WHAT EXACTLY
WERE THE TWO OF YOU THINKING?
I'M GOING TO GUESS
YOU DECIDED ON YOUR OWN
THAT YOU SHOULD
HANDLE IT YOURSELVES.
EVEN THOUGH YOU ALREADY KNEW
THAT YOU COULDN'T DO THIS ALONE.
YOU WENT ANYWAY.
PERHAPS YOU DON'T THINK
VERY HIGHLY OF YOUR
FRIENDS' ABILITIES.
HOW LONG DO YOU PLAN ON
BEING A SOLO ACT?
SHIROE ISN'T THE ONLY ONE
OUT HERE THAT YOU CAN DEPEND ON.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO LEARN
TO RELY ON ONE ANOTHER.
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
SHE'S RIGHT.
THAT'S EXACTLY
HOW I'VE SEEN THINGS.
HE CASTS A BIG SHADOW.
AND I'VE BEEN HIDING IN IT
ALL THIS TIME.
I NEVER EVEN MADE AN ATTEMPT
TO GET TO KNOW ANYONE ELSE.
MUCH LESS LEARN TO TRUST THEM.
AS SOON AS MY LORD WAS GONE.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
I COULDN'T EVEN DO
WHAT HE ASKED ME TO...
[HENRIETTA] WEREN'T YOU
COMING TO THIS MANSION
TO BE A BODYGUARD
FOR THE PRINCESS?
UH!
YOU WEREN'T THE ONLY ONE
ASSIGNED TO SUIFUU.
DID YOU HONESTLY BELIEVE
THAT YOU WERE THE ONLY PERSON
GUARDING THE PRINCESS?
RIEZE AND I MIGHT HAVE
SOMETHING TO SAY ABOUT THAT.
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
I AM NOT THE ONLY PERSON
MY LORD COUNTS ON.
BUT... BUT WHEN I SAW HOW THAT
BURDEN WAS BEARING DOWN ON HER,
I HAD TO DO SOMETHING TO
MAKE IT LESS THAN IT WAS.
I HAD TO HELP THE PRINCESS.
[AKATSUKI]
I NEED YOUR HELP.
I CAN'T DO IT WITHOUT YOU!
[HENRIETTA]
OF COURSE WE'LL HELP YOU!
RIEZE AND I ARE HERE TO
HELP HOWEVER WE CAN.
BUT THERE IS SOMEONE ELSE
THAT CAN HELP YOU AS WELL.
[AKATSUKI]
SOMEONE ELSE...?
[HENRIETTA]
YES.
[RAYNESHIA]
SHE DOESN'T HAVE TO...
BECAUSE ABOVE ALL,
AKATSUKI IS MY FRIEND!
(EXHALE)
[AKATSUKI] RAYNESHIA'S DOING
THE BEST SHE CAN EVERYDAY.
WE CAN HELP HER.
ALL OF US.
TOGETHER WE CAN DO IT.
I ASK YOU...
I NEED YOU...
I NEED MY FRIENDS.
[MARIELLE] HMM...
[RIEZE] ALL RIGHT THEN.
LET'S STOP ENBART NERURESU.
I'LL MAKE UP THE PLAN.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
SO LET'S GET IT DONE.
[MISA]
MY LORD. IT'S DARK NOW.
LET'S GET BACK TO CAMP.
THIS SPEARHEAD IS A BIT STRANGE.
[MISA]
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
[KRUSTY] IT LOOKS LIKE
THIS AREA MIGHT'VE BEEN
A TRAINING GROUND FOR GOBLINS.
[MISA]
FOR GOBLINS YOU THINK SO.
I MEAN, WHEN DO GOBLINS
INVEST TIME IN COMBAT TRAINING?
[KRUSTY]
HM?
[MISA]
OH HERE WE GO,
IT'S ACTING UP AGAIN.
(GASP)
(SCREAM)
[KRUSTY]
MISA!
HEH!
(STRUGGLING)
(GRUNTING) AH HUH?
MILORD!
(STRUGGLING)
OH NO, KRUSTY!
(KRUSTY STRUGGLING)
(MISA SCREAMING)
(HEAVY BREATHING)
(ELETRIC SIZZLING)
MILORD...
[RIEZE] THE SWORD OF
THE COLD, BYAKUMARU?
ARE YOU SURE THAT'S THE
SERIAL KILLER'S KATANA?
I KNEW IT THE MOMENT I SAW IT...
UP UNTIL VERY RECENTLY
IT WAS IN AMENOMA.
[HENRIETTA]
MARIELLE, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
[MARIELLE]
UH... UH, I DON'T KNOW.
HE USUALLY CALLS RIGHT ON TIME.
BUT MAYBE TODAY,
HE'S JUST RUNNING LATE.
YEAH, WELL THEY'RE NOT
EXACTLY HAVING A CAMPOUT.
THERE MIGHT BE SOME DAYS
HE'S TOO BUSY TO CALL.
YOU MIGHT JUST HAVE TO WAIT
UNTIL TOMORROW, OKAY, MARIELLE?
YEAH, I GUESS
YOU'RE RIGHT.
[MARIELLE, THINKING]
OH NAOTSUGU.
WHY TONIGHT?
IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE ABOUT
HIM YOU THINK MIGHT BE HELPFUL?
(PING) OH?
I HAVE TO TAKE THIS...
I'M HERE.
OKAY...
(GASP)
[BOTH] HM?
OH NO!
[AKATSUKI, VOICEOVER]
AS A MAN LOSES HIS HEART,
THE SERIAL KILLER
BECOMES A REAL MONSTER.
MEMORIES OF A LEGENDARY
HERO RUN THROUGH HIS MIND.
WHILE RIEZE AND
HENRIETTA GET READY
TO STAGE A RAID TO CAPTURE HIM.
A WARRIOR DEDICATES HERSELF
TO LEARNING AN ORAL ART.
ALTOGETHER, 26 MAIDENS JOIN
TO STAND AGAIN THE MONSTER!
[SHIROE]
STAND UP, ONE MORE TIME!