[NERURESU]
UWAH!
HAAAA!
HWU‐HA!
[MARIELLE]
JUST REMEMBER THAT SWORD
CAN CAST THE BLIZZARD SPELL.
NOT TO MENTION HIS STATS
ARE OFF THE CHART,
THANKS TO HIM WEARING
THAT ROYAL GUARD ARMOR.
BE CAREFUL;
HE'S LIKE AN OP HACKER!
SORRY TO ASK THIS, BUT HAVE YOU
EVER BEEN ON A RAID BEFORE?
THIS IS MY FIRST ONE!
[AKATSUKI]
THAT MAKES TWO OF US.
IF IT'S ALL THE SAME TO YOU,
I DON'T WANT TO SPEND
NEW YEAR'S EVE ON THE
FLOOR OF THE CATHEDRAL.
DEFINITELY!
LET'S MAKE OUR FIRST
RAID A SUCCESS!
SOUNDS GOOD!
MMPH.
[RIEZE, VOICE CHAT]
WE'VE GOT A VISUAL ON HIM!
HE'S ON CENTRAL STREET
HEADED TO OLD OGAWAMACHI.
HE'S CAUGHT UP TO C‐SQUAD AND
THEY ONLY HAVE ONE HEALER!
D‐SQUAD, FALL BACK ON CENTRAL
AND BACK THEM UP!
ALL OTHER UNITS
HOLD YOUR POSITIONS!
ISN'T AKATSUKI IN
C‐SQUAD WITH MARIELLE?
YES. I WAS HOPING
HE'D RUN INTO THEM,
ESPECIALLY WITH HER ACUTE
RECONNAISSANCE SKILLS.
WE'RE GONNA GET THIS GUY!
KEEP YOUR FOCUS, KYOKO.
I'VE GOT A SCORE TO SETTLE
WITH THIS PIECE OF CRAP!
[RIEZE]
THEN LET'S TAKE HIM DOWN!
[KYOKO]
YOU'RE MINE, NERURESU!
(HEAVY BREATHS)
[RIEZE, VOICEOVER] YOU NEED
TO BE IN A CONSTANT STATE
OF EVALUATING YOUR OPPONENT.
KNOW WHAT YOU CAN DO AND BE
AWARE OF WHAT YOU CANNOT DO,
SO IT DOESN'T TAKE YOU
BY SURPRISE IN THE FIGHT.
(LAUGHTER)
[AKATSUKI, THINKING] I HAVE TO
FACE MY SHORTCOMINGS...
AND MAKE THEM WORK FOR ME!
NOW LET'S FIND A BLIND SPOT!
(BREATH)
[AKATSUKI]
MORBID STINGER SLASH!
GOOD HIT! THE POISON SHOULD
START WEARING HIM OUT!
[NERURESU]
HWAHHHH!
[AKATSUKI]
EH!
I'VE ALWAYS SEEN MY SHORT
STATURE AS A HINDRANCE.
BUT NOT ANYMORE...
NOT AT ALL.
HOW THICK IS YOUR BLOOD,
ADVENTURERS?! LET'S FIND OUT!
(SQUEAL)
(STRUGGLE)
(YELL)
(GASP)
(STRUGGLE)
(GRUNTS)
I'M GLAD EVERYONE SHARED
SO MUCH OF THEIR THINGS WITH ME.
AKATSUKI!
I'M FINE!
LET'S PUT AN END TO THIS.
YOU MUST BE STOPPED.
(LAUGHTER)
(BATTLE GRUNT)
[NERURESU] HUH?
[KAWARA]
HYA!
ORION DELAY BLOW!
(SCREAM)
(HEAVY BREATHING)
YOU'VE GOT AN OPENING NOW!
MOVE ON TO THE NEXT AREA!
[AKATSUKI]
THANK YOU, KAWARA!
[MARIELLE]
YOU'RE THE BEST!
HMM? RUNNING WON'T HELP,
LITTLE GIRLS.
[KYOKO]
A RAID INSIDE THE CITY...
[RIEZE]
THIS WOULD HAVE BEEN IMPOSSIBLE
BACK IN THE ORIGINAL GAME.
(GROWLING)
HWUA!
[SEINE]
VIPER SLASH! HA!
(GROANS)
[SEINE]
BLOODY PIERCING!
(HEAVY BREATHING)
[KYOKO] I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY THE ROYAL GUARDS
HAVEN'T COME AFTER HIM YET.
ACCORDING TO THE SYSTEM,
IF HE'S HERE AND SUITED UP,
IT MUST ASSUME
HE'S HERE PUNISHING US.
WHICH IS EXACTLY WHAT'S
ALLOWING US FIGHT IN THE CITY.
(GASP)
(EXHALE)
[NERURESU]
ALL RIGHT YOU LITTLE TROLLOPS.
ROUND TWO.
AH!
[AKATSUKI] EH!
(NERURESU GROANS)
WE'LL KEEP HIM OCCUPIED
AS LONG AS WE CAN!
GO TO THE NEXT AREA!
WE GOT MORE THAN ENOUGH
TO KEEP HIM BUSY!
GO GET READY TO SPANK
HIS NAUGHTY TUSHY GOOD!
WE'RE ON IT!
THANKS A LOT!
[RIEZE] IT LOOKS LIKE
THE BAKER WAS RIGHT.
LUGRIUS IS ALSO
BOOSTING HIS ABILITIES.
BASED ON THE FACT THAT EVERYONE
WITHIN 50 METERS IS BUFFING HIM.
[KYOKO]
IT WAS A SMART MOVE
GETTING EVERYONE
TO STAY INDOORS.
[RIEZE] WE'VE GOT TWENTY‐FOUR
PLAYERS OUT THERE
AND THEY'RE THE ONLY
ONES IN THE STREET.
I SPLIT THEM INTO SMALL GROUPS
AND SPREAD THEM OUT
AS THIN AS POSSIBLE.
AKATSUKI IS LEADING NERURESU
ALONG WITH HER.
RUNNING HIM THROUGH A GAUNTLET
OF EACH TEAM'S PATROL AREA,
WHERE THEY CAN
DEAL DAMAGE TO HIM.
A CLASSIC EXAMPLE OF KITING.
AS HE KEEPS HIS FOCUS
ON AKATSUKI,
THE OTHERS CAN ATTACK HIM
WHILE SHE GETS HEALED.
[KYOKO] WELL OKAY. I CAN SEE
THAT YAMATO'S CAPTAIN
OF TRAINING AND DEVELOPMENT
REALLY KNOWS HER STUFF!
I LIKE IT.
IT'S GONNA WORK.
[RIEZE] WELL... IT WOULD UNDER
NORMAL CONDITIONS...
UH...
(SCREAM)
[RIEZE] REMEMBER, THINGS
ARE DIFFERENT...
YOU CAN'T SIMPLY SET UP A RAID
AND EXPECT TO WIN ANYMORE.
[RIEZE] THAT SWORD IS
DANGEROUS ENOUGH.
PLUS NERURESU IS IN
ROYAL GUARD ARMOR.
HE CAN TRANSPORT
ANYWHERE IN THE CITY.
[KYOKO]
HE'S MOVED ON TO THE NEXT BLOCK!
[NERURESU]
THOSE DAMNED ADVENTURERS
ARE SCATTERED EVERYWHERE.
[LUGRIUS]
NOT SO FAST, MY FRIEND.
WE MUST HUNT DOWN THAT
LITTLE WENCH FIRST!
[RIEZE]
TO COMPLICATE MATTERS,
HE HAS THE COMBAT SKILLS
OF A ROYAL GUARDSMAN!
[RIEZE, THINKING]
THERE ARE STILL SO MANY THINGS
THAT CAN GO WRONG HERE.
ARE YOU OKAY?
[RIEZE]
MPH... SORRY ABOUT THAT.
KYOKO MAY I CONFIDE
IN YOU ABOUT SOMETHING?
[KYOKO] HM?
[RIEZE] SOMETHING ABOUT
THIS JUST HIT ME.
I'VE ENDANGERED MANY PEOPLE,
AND THERE'S NOTHING I CAN
DO FOR THEM RIGHT NOW.
AND THE THOUGHT OF THAT
OVERWHELMS AND TERRIFIES ME.
[KYOKO]
MMM...
[RIEZE]
AND THE PRINCESS...?
SHE HAS BEEN FORCED
TO DEAL WITH
SUCH DIRE CIRCUMSTANCES
HER ENTIRE LIFE.
I HAVE A NEW RESPECT FOR HER.
[KYOKO] YEAH, WELL EVERYONE IN
THE ROUND TABLE DEALS WITH IT!
AND THE SAME GOES FOR YOU.
HUH?
LIKE RIGHT NOW...!
WE ALL DO WHAT
NEEDS TO BE DONE.
YES... LET'S FINISH THIS THEN...
MPH...
[RIEZE, VOICE CHAT] AFTER
D‐SQUAD HAS FINISHED HEALING
GET BACK TO C‐SQUAD.
F‐SQUAD, I HAVE
AN UPDATE FOR YOU.
STANDBY, CHECKPOINT D.
[KINJO] ARE YOU SURE
YOU WANT TO DO THIS?
[RAYNESHIA]
I AM.
REMEMBER PRINCESS,
AKIHABARA WON'T HAVE IT'S
MAGICAL DEFENSES FOR DECADES.
AND WITHOUT THE ROYAL GUARD
TO KEEP THE PEACE,
IT COULD FALL INTO LAWLESSNESS.
[RAYNESHIA]
I KNOW...
HUH?
[HENRIETTA]
MM‐HM...
IT WASN'T JUST THE KUNIE.
ALL THE PEOPLE OF THE
LAND SHARE IN THE BLAME.
WE WERE RESPONSIBLE
FOR GUARDING THE ARMOR.
AND NOW WE SHOULD DO WHAT WE
CAN TO ASSIST THE ADVENTURERS.
WE OWE THEM DEARLY FOR OUR
FAILURES IN THIS MATTER.
THIS PARTICULAR SITUATION, NOW
CALLS FOR CUTTING OFF THE MAGIC.
[KINJO]
I REMIND YOU,
YOU COULD BE MAKING
THEIR BURDENS WORSE.
[HENRIETTA] YOU DON'T
NEED TO WORRY ABOUT THAT.
YOU MAY HAVE FORGOTTEN
MASTER KINJO,
THE ROUND TABLE CONFERENCE HAS
ALREADY PETITIONED THE PRINCESS
TO MAKE THIS HAPPEN.
[HENRIETTA] AND SINCE WE ARE
FELLOW RESIDENTS OF AKIHABARA,
WE'VE ALREADY PLEDGED OUR
SUPPORT IN REMEDYING THIS.
[KINJO]
IF YOU INSIST.
REGARDLESS OF THE CAUSE,
THERE'S NO DENYING ONE THING.
THERE WAS A FAULT IN MY TRIBE'S
SECURITY THAT MUST BE ADDRESSED.
IT'S BEEN HUNDREDS OF YEARS,
AND WE'VE ALWAYS DEFENDED
THE MAGIC CIRCLE FAITHFULLY,
THAT HISTORY IS TARNISHED.
WE MUST ATONE FOR THAT.
UH? WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
PRECISELY AS YOU SAID YOURSELF.
WE MUST DO EVERYTHING IN OUR
POWER TO ASSIST THE ADVENTURERS
AS THEY LEARN TO
LIVE IN THIS LAND.
WE SHOULD TAKE A NEW STEP
FORWARD, AND NOT REJECT THEM.
(EXHALE)
HMM.
I BELIEVE I OWE YOU AN APOLOGY
FOR THE WAY I'VE
TESTED YOU, PRINCESS.
FURTHERMORE,
AND I'M SURE OF THIS,
I SHALL BE IN YOUR DEBT
REGARDING THIS INCIDENT,
YOUR HIGHNESS.
AH.
BUT ON THE OTHER HAND,
I GET THE FEELING
I'M GOING TO BE CLEARING
THAT DEBT WITH SOMEONE ELSE.
HMMM?
[KINJO]
WELL, WE SHOULD BE GOING NOW.
IS THAT...?!
AFTER YOU, LADIES.
AH.
LET'S GO...
YAH!!!!
(GROANING)
(GROAN)
[RIEZE, VOICE CHAT]
J‐SQUAD, MOVE AWAY FROM HIM AND
GET TO SOMEWHERE YOU CAN HEAL!
(GROWL)
[RIEZE]
D SQUAD, HOLD YOUR POSITION.
[RIEZE] YOU'VE GOT LESS THAN
THIRTY SECONDS. GET READY!
[AKATSUKI]
ARE YOU OKAY, MARIELLE?
THIS IS A PIECE OF CAKE!
I CAN KEEP ON RUNNING
UNTIL DAWN IF I NEED TO!
EHEH...
[LUGRIUS]
WHY?
(GASP)
[LUGRIUS]
WHY DID YOU BETRAY ME, SUTUYNAW?
NO! SHUT UP! I'M NOT LUGRIUS!
FALL BACK NOW!
YOU GOT IT!
QUIET! HOW COULD YOU
BETRAY ME LIKE THAT!
I SAVED YOUR CITY AND
THIS IS THE THANKS I GET?!
[BYAKKOU]
COMPANION SUMMON: GOLEM!
I THOUGHT YOU GUYS
MIGHT NEED A HAND!
HYA!
[AKATSUKI] THANKS FOR THE HELP!
[NERURESU] ARRRRGGHHHH!
[AKATSUKI] EH!
[NERURESU] AHHHHH!
[MIKAKAGE]
HEARTBEAT HEALING! HERE!
I REALLY NEEDED THAT.
THANKS A LOT YOU GUYS.
YOUR INCANTATION IS
ADORABLE BY THE WAY.
[NERURESU] EYAHHHHH!
[AKATSUKI] HM?
[NERURESU] UWAHHH!
COMBAT COMPANION SUMMON:
DIESEL LANCER!
EH? AAAUGGGHHHHH!
[MIKAKAGE] GOOD LUCK!
[MARIELLE] THANK YOU!
(SMALL LAUGH)
(SQUEE)
(GIGGLE)
[MARIELLE] TEN METERS TO
THE NEXT BLOCK, RIEZE.
[AKATSUKI, THINKING] I'M CLOSE,
I'M SO CLOSE TO LEARNING
SOMETHING. I CAN FEEL IT!
(SCREAM)
(GROANS OF PAIN)
MARIELLE!
J‐SQUAD ISN'T GOING TO
GET THERE IN TIME!
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
I AM WEAK.
MY SWORD IS STARVING,
ADVENTURER.
LET'S GIVE IT A TASTE
OF YOUR BLOOD!
ENH!
HUAH!
UGHHH!
[NERURESU] UWHAAAA!
[AKATSUKI] AGGGGHHHHHH!!!
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
I MUST MOVE FASTER!
NO! FASTER THAN THIS!
FASTER, AKATSUKI!
EH!
EH?
WHAT THE HELL?! FWAH!
EHAAAUGHHHH!
(GASP) WHERE'D ALL THOSE
AKATSUKIS COME FROM?
[AKATSUKI]
WHAT A MINUTE...
DID I JUST RELEASE
THE HIDE SHADOW ABILITY
WHILE I WAS PUSHING
MYSELF BACK THERE?
MY DESIRE TO MOVE FASTER
MUST HAVE TRIGGERED IT SOMEHOW.
I MUST HAVE FORCED IT
TO MANIFEST.
I'VE GOT IT...
I'VE GOT MY ORAL ART.
IT'S MINE!
[RIEZE]
LOOKS LIKE SHE FINALLY GOT ONE.
[KYOKO]
YES! DO IT AKATSUKI!
[RIEZE, VOICEOVER]
AN ORAL ART ISN'T SOMETHING
ONE CAN SIMPLY BE TAUGHT.
YOU HAVE TO TRAIN,
UNDERSTANDING YOUR WEAKNESSES,
AND FIGHTING TO OVERCOME THEM.
[RIEZE] GET HIM AKATSUKI!
AND STAY IN HIS BLIND SPOTS!
EH!
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS!
I SPENT SO MUCH TIME DEPENDING
ON WHAT THE GAME WAS GIVING ME.
AND ALL I HAD TO DO
WAS REACH BEYOND THAT!
IT WAS THERE ALL ALONG
AND I DIDN'T SEE IT!
I SEE IT NOW.
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS
FREE MY EXPECTATIONS...
I USED TO BE JUST LIKE YOU.
HELD BACK BY MYSELF.
BUT IT'S OKAY IF I'M WEAK,
I CAN USE IT TO GET BETTER.
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING,
YOU MONSTER,
YOU CHOOSE TO NEVER
FACE YOUR DEMONS,
EMBRACING A CURSED POWER!
YOU DON'T HAVE ANYONE
TO BLAME BUT YOURSELF!
YOU MAY THINK YOU WIELD
OVERWHELMING STRENGTH.
... BUT IT'S NOTHING COMPARED TO
A WILL INSPIRED BY WEAKNESS!
AH!
GOT HIM!
YOU GO GIRL!
[AKATSUKI]
OH, NO!
(STRUGGLE) IT'S STUCK!
SO EASY TO LURE YOU IN,
ADVENTURER!
(GASP)
[KYOKO]
OH MY GOD!
AKATSUKI ONLY HAS FIVE
PERCENT OF HER HEALTH LEFT!
AND SHE DOESN'T HAVE
A SWORD ANYMORE!
TO MAKE THINGS WORSE, MARIELLE'S
RUNNING OUT OF MAGIC POINTS!
SHE CAN ONLY CAST LIGHT
HEALING SPELLS ON HER!
I'M SORRY AKATSUKI,
BUT I'M OUT OF POWER.
I DON'T HAVE ANY
MANA LEFT EITHER.
YOU NEED TO GET OUTTA HERE
BEFORE HE ENDS UP
KILLING US BOTH!
[RIEZE, VOICE CHAT] D‐SQUAD!
WE NEED YOU TO BACKUP C‐SQUAD!
[KAWARA]
WE'RE ALREADY ON OUR WAY!
NO, AKATSUKI!
I STILL HAVE TO HELP YOU!
MPH!
(PING)
[TATARA] DON'T GIVE UP!
[AKATSUKI] UH...?
[TATARA] FIND ME AS QUICK AS YOU
CAN, NO MATTER WHAT IT TAKES.
MOVE IT!
[RIEZE, VOICE CHAT]
WE'RE ON THE MOVE, PEOPLE!
C‐SQUAD IS TAKING CENTRAL STREET
TOWARD KANDAMYOJIN STREET.
COVER THEM!
ALL OTHER UNITS,
SET YOUR NEW PERIMETER LINE!
[LUGRIUS] SUTUYNAW,
FACE YOUR ACCUSER FOR ONCE.
STOP RUNNING FROM ME!
[NERURESU] THAT'S NOT HER!
THEY'RE THOSE
ADVENTURER MAIDENS!
LUGRIUS HAS TAKEN OVER HIS MIND!
MARIELLE, I'M GONNA
NEED SOME ROOM!
MPH.
[AKATSUKI]
NOW WAIT...
ISN'T THIS THE SCREAMING SWORD,
HAGANEMUSHI?
[TATARA] NO, NOT EXACTLY.
[AKATSUKI] OH...
[TATARA] I REFORGED IT INTO
HAGANEMUSHI‐TATARA.
I MADE IT SMALLER SO YOU
COULD HANDLE IT BETTER.
[AKATSUKI]
AH... UH, BUT...
[TATARA] IT LOOKED LIKE YOU
COULD USE A SWORD OUT THERE.
(EXHALE)
MAKE GOOD USE OF IT
AND FINISH HIM OFF.
(EXHALE)
WELL IF IT ISN'T
MAIDEN TWENTY‐SEVEN...
AND NOT A MOMENT TOO SOON.
MMMPH.
(GROWL)
(BATTLE GRUNTS)
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
EVEN IF I CUT THIS GUY DOWN,
THE MURDERS WON'T STOP.
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
I HAVE TO DESTROY THE SWORD!
MY HAGANEMUSHI HAS AN ABILITY.
IT DECREASED ENEMY
WEAPON DURABILITY
WITH EACH STRIKE
INFLICTED ON IT!
(CRACKING)
I'VE GOTTA FINISH THIS FAST,
SO THIS MANIAC DOESN'T
HURT ANYONE ELSE!
[NERURESU]
WHAT? THIS AGAIN?!
(CHUCKLE)
(GRUNT)
[NERURESU]
HAHHH!
[AKATSUKI]
NO!
(GASP)
[ISAMI]
FOX TORNADO!
[NAZNA] MAKE SURE YOU DON'T
TURN HIS ATTENTION TO YOU!
[ISAMI]
COUNT ON IT!
ISAMI! HOW MUCH IS HIS HP?
[ISAMI]
LEMME LOOK...
[ISAMI] HIS DISPLAY'S
GOING CRAZY,
BUT HE'S RIGHT AT 20 PERCENT!
I CAN'T GET A CLEAN READ!
[RIEZE, VOICE CHAT]
GOT IT.
C‐SQUAD, SWAP MARIELLE
OUT WITH NAZNA...
FIND THEM AND MAKE IT HAPPEN.
[MARIELLE]
ROGER!
[RIEZE]
IF THIS IS A RAID BOSS,
IT'S ABOUT TIME FOR HIS
ATTACK PATTERNS TO CHANGE.
WATCH YOUR BACK OUT THERE!
[NAZNA]
WILL DO.
[RIEZE] C‐SQUAD, START
HEADING INTO POSITION.
TAKE BACKUP PLAN 6'S ROUTE.
[AKATSUKI]
GOT IT!
[NAZNA]
OH MAN, HE WAS THAT FAST?
[AZUKIKO]
ENGAGE! THORN‐BIND HOSTAGE!
[TOWA]
WELL DONE! RAPID SHOT!
[NERURESU]
UH? UWAH...
(EXPLOSION)
UWAHHHHHHHH!
[NAZNA] SHIROE'S PROTEGE
IS MY PROTEGE TOO!
AND YOU LOOK LIKE YOU
COULD USE A HAND!
LET'S GET SOME DISTANCE!
HUH? IT'S NO TIME TO
FALL APART...
GET YOUR HEAD ON STRAIGHT!
(EXHALE, SNIFFLE)
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
SO THIS IS A RAID. AMAZING!
AKATSUKI, IT'S ABOUT TIME I
SHOWED YOU MY ORAL ART!
DIVINE STEP!
[AKATSUKI]
WHAT IS THIS?
WALLS OF PURIFICATION
ARE SUPPOSED TO KEEP YOU
FROM GETTING INJURED,
BUT YOU'RE ACTUALLY MAKING
STEPS IN THE AIR WITH THEM!?
IS THAT HOW YOU SAVED
ME EARLIER TONIGHT?
YOU GET A GOLD STAR!
YOU JUST HAVE TO CHANGE
HOW YOU SEE THE WORLD.
SO? MAKE YOU FEEL KINDA SILLY?
EHEH!
JUST A LITTLE.
[NAZNA]
WOW.
I DON'T KNOW IF HE'S
GOING TO ATTACK US AGAIN
OR JUST KEEL OVER AND DIE!
TIME TO PUT AN END
TO THIS LITTLE GAME.
[HENRIETTA]
THREE!
[KYOKO]
TWO!
[RIEZE]
ONE!
[HENRIETTA] TAKE IT DOWN!
[BOTH] MM.
[NERURESU]
HNH?
[KYOKO] YOU'RE JUST OUTSIDE
OF 50 METERS, RIEZE!
ALL RIGHT.
NOW LET HIM HAVE IT!
[RIEZE]
FREEZING LINER!
[NERURESU]
HUH?
HWAAAAA!
YOU'RE NOT SPILLING ANOTHER
DROP OF INNOCENT BLOOD!
[RIEZE] YOUR DAYS OF
TERRORIZING THIS CITY ARE OVER!
(GROANS)
[KYOKO]
IT WORKED!
(GRUNT)
[NAZNA]
YOU'RE NOT TELEPORTING ANYWHERE
WHEN YOU DON'T HAVE
ANY MORE MAGIC.
[NAZNA] THAT ARMOR OF YOURS
MEANS NOTHING NOW.
[NERURESU]
YOU FILTHY LITTLE TRAMPS!
EH!
(YELL)
[NERURESU]
AAUGH! THIS ISN'T OVER!
[LUGRIUS]
I SWEAR I'LL HAVE YOUR HEAD...
[AKATSUKI] HYAH!
[LUGRIUS]... ADVENTURER...
(SCREAMS)
(HEAVY BREATHING)
[AKATSUKI]
THE FLAVOR TEXT HAS CHANGED.
"HAGANEMUSHI‐TATARA.
THE SWORDSMITH TATARA OF
AMENOMA REFORGED THIS BLADE...
...FOR NONE OTHER THAN THE
QUIET AND ALOOF SWORDSWOMAN."
[TATARA] "MAY THE SERIOUS
MAIDEN NEVER FALTER NOR FALL
AS SHE PRESSES ONWARD.
MAY SHE DRIVE AWAY THE EVIL
CURSE AND TRAGEDY IN THIS WORLD,
ALLOWING THE PEOPLE
AND THE SWORD ALIKE
TO SUPPORT ONE ANOTHER
IN HARMONY"
MAY SHE WIELD THIS BLADE IN THE
DEFENSE OF ALL WHO NEED
ITS PROTECTION AND STEAL
HER HEART AGAINST DESPAIR.
(CHEERS)
[RAYNESHIA]
IT'S OVER, ISN'T IT?
[HENRIETTA]
YES.
IT REALLY DIDN'T MATTER
HOW MUCH HP HE HAD LEFT.
ALL WE HAD TO DO WAS FIND
A WAY TO SHATTER THAT BLADE.
A MASTERFUL STRATEGY!
[RAYNESHIA]
(PLEASED) OH... UH...
[HENRIETTA]
MPH...
(LAUGHING)
[RAYNESHIA]
MPH...
(GIGGLE)(HIVE FIVING)
[SOJIRO] CONGRATULATIONS!
YOU WERE AMAZING AS ALWAYS.
[NAZNA] YEAH, TELL ME
SOMETHING I DON'T KNOW.
[SOJIRO] WOMEN ARE REALLY
POWERFUL, AREN'T THEY?
RIGHT, SHIROE?
[KYOKO] CHECK IT OUT!
WE GOT NEW YEAR'S SOBA NOODLES.
[MIKAKAGE] AND I MADE A WHOLE
BUNCH OF SWEETS FOR US!
(HAPPY CHATTER)
GOD! I'VE NEVER SEEN
SO MUCH FOOD IN MY LIFE!
SO ARE ALL OF YOUR
PAJAMA PARTIES LIKE THIS?
[TATARA]
I THINK I LIKE IT!
I'D EAT EVERYTHING, BUT
I'D GET AS BIG AS A HOUSE!
BUT I'M NOT
GONNA STOP!
I WANNA HEAR SOME SINGING!
I'M GONNA SING ON
THE BOY'S TEAM
THIS TIME AROUND
TO MAKE IT FAIR.
(LAUGHTER, MERRIMENT CONTINUES)
WELL SINCE WE FINALLY
LIFTED THE CURFEW,
EVERYONE IS OUT IN
THE STREET DANCING.
WE CAN INVITE MINORI AND ALL
THE LOWER RANKS BACK HOME.
WHAT SHOULD WE DO
ABOUT... HENRIETTA?
SHE'LL BE ALL RIGHT
EVENTUALLY.
I'M SURE SHE
LOST HER MIND
WHEN SHE SAW EVERYONE
IN THEIR PAJAMAS.
[HENRIETTA] I'VE NEVER SEEN
SO MANY HOTTIE PATOTTIES!
[RAYNESHIA]
OKAY.
UM, AKATSUKI...
THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING.
I THINK I SHOULD BE THANKING
YOU INSTEAD, RAYNESHIA.
(GIGGLE)
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
I THINK I FINALLY
FIGURED IT ALL OUT,
MY LORD.
PROTECTING SOMEONE MEANS
GIVING THEM A HOME
TO COME BACK TO.
WHAT PEOPLE NEED IS A PLACE
WHERE THEY CAN LAUGH
WITHOUT FEAR.
I UNDERSTAND NOW.
IT'S THE REASON WHY
MY LORD WORKS SO HARD.
[AKATSUKI]
PLEASE HURRY BACK HOME...
(PING)
AH...
[SHIROE, VOICE CHAT]
AKATSUKI?
AKATSUKI? HELLO? YOU THERE?
UH, MY LORD?
WHAT'S HAPPENING OUT THERE?
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO CALL
UNLESS THERE'S A PROBLEM!
[SHIROE]
THAT WAS THE DEAL, BUT...
WOW, I'VE NEVER KNOWN YOU
TO BREAK THE RULES
LIKE THAT, MY LORD!
[SHIROE]
I AM THE VILLAIN IN GLASSES.
OH RII‐IGHT! YOU WOULDN'T BE
YOU WITHOUT A FEW SURPRISES.
[SHIROE]
SO HOW DID THE RAID GO?
[AKATSUKI] UH...
[SHIROE] AKATSUKI...
[AKATSUKI]
UH‐HUH?
[SHIROE]
GOOD JOB...
[AKATSUKI]
MY LORD...
WE'RE STILL FIGURING
THINGS OUT OVER HERE...
BUT WE'RE NOT GIVING UP.
IN FACT, WE'RE JUST ABOUT
TO GIVE IT ANOTHER GO!
[AKATSUKI, VOICEOVER]
ON CHRISTMAS EVE NIGHT,
SHIROE AND HIS COMPANIONS DIED.
THE RULES HAD CHANGED.
THIS ISN'T THE WORLD OF
ELDER TALES ANYMORE.
THEIR TIME IS OVER.
UPON LOSING HIS BODY,
SHIROE WANDERS THROUGH
A TOWN OF MEMORIES.
HE ALSO SEES A FRIEND AT
THE BEACH ON THE MOON.
[SHIROE]
STAND UP, ONE MORE TIME!