[DINKURON] ALL RIGHT!
LET'S GET THIS RAID STARTED!
[UKIYO]
YEAH, IT'S KINDA COOL TO THINK
WE'RE THE FIRST ADVENTURERS
TO BRAVE THIS CHALLENGE!
[JUNZO] DEFINITELY! BUT I'M
GETTING A LITTLE NERVOUS!
[PIANISSISSIMO] UH...
I'M GONNA TRY THE BEST I CAN.
[ENKARTANTO] WE'LL BE FINE!
JUST WAIT AND SEE.
[WILLIAM]
OKAY, GUYS...
I HOPE YOU'RE READY.
THIS ZONE BELONGS TO US...
WE SHALL TAKE IT AND
HOIST OUR FLAG HIGH!
[TOKO]
TWO GOT BY ME!
[DINKURON] I NEED A
RECOVERY SPELL OVER HERE!
[FEDERICO]
HIT THEIR FLANKS!
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
THIS IS THE RAID ZONE,
AT THE VERY BOTTOM
OF THE DEPTHS OF PALM.
IT'S KNOWN AS "THE PATH TO THE
ABYSS," THE "ABYSSAL SHAFT"
THIS WOULD'VE BEEN A
TYPICAL RAID DUNGEON
IF WE WERE PLAYING IT IN A GAME.
A "RAID DUNGEON," ‐ A POWERED UP
VERSION OF A NORMAL DUNGEON.
EXTRA HALLWAYS, ROOMS,
TRAPS AND PUZZLES.
IT IS COMPOSED OF SEVERAL
EXTENSIVE AREAS.
MORE PLACES TO GET HIT, GET
HURT, OR DIE FOR THAT MATTER.
YOU'VE GOTTA WATCH YOUR BACK
AND HAVE YOUR WITS ABOUT YOU
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS,
WHILE GOING AFTER YOUR
GOALS AND TREASURES,
AND IF YOU'RE LUCKY,
FINDING THE EXIT.
[HIGHLAND]
ENEMY CONTACT, FOUR O'CLOCK!
[DINKURON]
DIG IN, YOU GUYS!
[TOKO]
THREE ORKS' JELLIES! RAID CLASS!
[SHIROE]
NAOTSUGU!
[NAOTSUGU]
RIGHT! ON IT!
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
A FULL RAID IS COMPOSED OF
FOUR NORMAL PARTIES OF SIX,
MAKING A "SUPER‐PARTY"
OF TWENTY‐FOUR PLAYERS.
WE'VE STARTED OUT WITH
A CLASSIC BATTLE FORMATION.
PARTY ONE ARE THE TANKS,
PURE FIGHTERS
BIG ON MUSCLE,
HIT POINTS AND ARMOR,
TANKS MAKE UP THE FRONT LINES,
ABSORBING AND DISHING OUT
MASSIVE PUNISHMENT.
IF THE TANKS FAIL, THE REST
OF US ARE SUNK. PERIOD.
I'VE GOT THREE MONSTERS IN SIGHT
JUST SOUTHWEST OF HERE.
[NAOTSUGU]
NO PROBLEM!
ANCHOR HOWL!
WUAAH! FUUU!
[DEMICAS]
WYVERN KICK!
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
PARTY TWO IS THE REAR ECHELON.
IF ANYTHING GETS PAST PARTY ONE,
THEY'RE SUPPOSED TO
USE THEIR MOBILITY
TO ENGAGE THE STRAGGLERS
AND KNOCK THEM OUT,
WHILE STILL
SUPPORTING PARTY ONE.
FLEXIBILITY IS THE KEY
TO BEING IN PARTY TWO.
YOU CAN'T JUST
SIT STILL AND FIGHT.
[SHIROE] MORE JELLIES
ON OUR FLANKS, PEOPLE!
WE NEED BACKUP HERE AND QUICK!
I'VE GOT SIX OF THEM IN SIGHT!
PARTY FOUR, BLOCK THE EAST EXIT!
[WILLIAM]
RAPID FIRE!
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
PARTIES THREE AND FOUR
SPECIALIZE IN LONG‐RANGE
ATTACKS: ARCHERY AND SORCERY.
THEY'RE LIGHT ON ARMOR,
BUT HEAVY DAMAGE DEALERS
AT A DISTANCE.
THEY HAVE TO BE VERY CAREFUL
TO STAY OUT OF THE FRAY.
HIT AND DON'T GET HIT.
PARTY THREE ATTACKS WHILE
PARTY FOUR WATCHES THEIR BACK.
[JUNZO] GET BACK!
[PIANISSISSIMO] OKAY!
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER] THAT'S THE
BEST‐CASE SCENARIO, ANYWAY.
AND HONESTLY,
IT NEARLY ALWAYS WORKS.
WILLIAM AND I AGREED
ON THIS FORMATION
AND THE ROLES FOR
THE MOBILE UNITS
ONCE WE STARTED ENGAGING
THE ENEMY'S FORCES.
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER] "RAID CLASS"
MONSTERS ARE A LOT TOUGHER
THAN THEIR COUNTERPARTS
OUTSIDE OF A RAID ZONE...
AND THEY HAVE EXTRA
POWERS AS WELL.
SINCE THE APOCALYPSE,
THE LEVEL CAP HAS GONE
FROM NINETY TO A HUNDRED.
THAT INCLUDES MONSTERS.
SO WE CAN'T ASSUME WE'RE MORE
POWERFUL THAN THEM ANYMORE.
THIS RAID ZONE IS TOO FAR
FROM THE NEAREST CATHEDRAL,
SO IF WE DIE, WE COME BACK
TO LIFE AT THE FRONT DOORS.
[HIGHLAND]
HNGH... I BLEW IT THAT TIME...
[DEMICAS]
WYVERN KICK!
WATCH IT, MAN!
YOU NEED TO SLOW DOWN!
I CAN'T HEAL YOU FROM BACK HERE!
[DEMICAS]
EAT IT CHUMP! HAHAHA!
THESE GUYS'RE EASY!
HUH? WHAT'S THAT?
(GROWLS)
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER] THE UPSIDE
OF BATTLING RAID‐CLASS MONSTERS
ARE THE ITEMS THEY DROP.
THEY'RE SOMETHING SPECIAL.
[TETORA] HEAL! (LAUGHS)
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
YOU CAN EITHER MAKE
YOUR EXISTING WEAPONS
MORE POWERFUL,
OR BUILD SOMETHING
NEW FROM SCRATCH.
[TETORA] AND HEAL!
[TOKO] THANKS, TETORA!
(GIGGLE)
[TETORA]
ARE YOU OKAY, BIG GUY?
[NAOTSUGU] OF COURSE I AM!
JUST GIMME SOMETHING TO KILL!
HEY WAIT A SEC. ARE YOU
USING ME AS A SHIELD?! HUH?
JUST THINK OF ME AS YOUR
PORTABLE FIRST AID UNIT,
OKAY, NAOTSUGU?!
[NAOTSUGU] UGGHHH...
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
AND THEN...
UH? I THINK THAT'S IT...
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
RAID ZONES HAVE AT LEAST FIVE,
AND POSSIBLY TEN SUPER MONSTERS
CALLED RAID BOSSES. BAD NEWS.
[PROMETHEUS]
IT LOOKS JUST LIKE VENDEMIAIRE
FROM THE FIRST PRISON RAID,
DOESN'T IT?
[ELTON DISKA] THE NINE
DUNGEONS OF HEILOS, HUH?
NOW THAT WAS A HUGE RAID.
[ORDISSO] OH MY GOD!
IT LOOKS JUST LIKE HIM!
[SASAMEYUKI] IT'S A GAME,
SOMETIMES THE DATA
GETS USED OVER AND OVER.
(SCREECHES)
[BOLOGNESE MASTER]
OKAY... WE'RE ON!
[WILLIAM] WHATEVER YOU DO,
DON'T GET BUNCHED UP!
[ALL]
ROGER!
[WILLIAM] PARTY ONE, TAKE THE
RIGHT LEG FROM THE FRONT!
PARTY TWO, TAKE THE
LEFT LEG FROM THE SIDE.
PARTY THREE, TAKE THE
LEFT LEG FROM BEHIND!
PARTY FOUR, TAKE THE RIGHT LEG
FROM BEHIND! GET INTO POSITION!
[DINKURON]
ANCHOR HOWL!
[WILLIAM]
WELL DONE!
DO IT LIKE WE PLANNED
AND KEEP ON CHIPPING AWAY...
KEEP AT IT!
[ALL] GOT IT, BOSS!
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
SO WE HAVE HEAVY FIREPOWER
AND ARMOR FORWARD,
SUPPORTED BY HEALERS
AND PLAYERS WHO CAN CAST
REINFORCEMENT SPELLS
AND ATTACK FROM A DISTANCE.
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
TANKS ATTACK AND GET ATTACKED,
WHILE HEALERS MAKE SURE
THEY STAY HEALTHY
THROUGHOUT THE PROCESS.
THIS IS WHERE IT
REALLY PAYS OFF.
A TANK HAS TO KEEP ON INCREASING
A MONSTER'S "ATTRACT FIRE,"
IT KEEPS THE MONSTER
FOCUSED ON THE TANK
AND NOT THE OTHER PLAYERS.
[MOLLUSCA TYPE @ AKIBA]
WHAT'S IT DOING?
[PROMETHEUS]
IS IT MOVING AWAY?
[ORDISSO] NO, HE'S REDIRECTING
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT!
NO!
AH!
OH!
[TETORA] MASTER SHIROE?!
[SHIROE] HE'S NOT LOCKED IN
ON A SINGLE ATTACKER!
[WILLIAM]
SHIROE! I NEED A DAMAGE REPORT!
[SHIROE] FIVE PARALYZED,
FOUR PETRIFIED AND ONE DEAD!
[PROMETHEUS] GET US A HEALER,
NOW! WE NEED A RESURRECTION!
[NAOTSUGU]
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
[FEDERICO]
IT COULDN'T DO THAT BEFORE!
[WILLIAM] WE NEED THAT HEALER!
[VOINEN] HANG ON, DEMICAS!
[DEMICAS] I DON'T HAVE TIME
TO WAIT FOR THOSE PANSIES!
USE IT YOURSELF!
[DEMICAS]
YAH! TIGER ECHO FIST!
[NAOTSUGU]
ONE HANDED CROSS SLASH!
[PROROCCA] LOOK AT THAT!
[MOLLUSCA] WE'VE TAKEN
A TENTH OF HIS HEALTH!
[BOTH] AGGHHHHH!!!
[NAOTSUGU] WE'VE JUST LOST
A BUNCH OFF THE PLATFORM!
[SHIROE]
WE'VE GOT ONE FLAT ON HIS BACK!
AND ANOTHER TWO WERE
BLOWN OUT OF THE ZONE!
[WILLIAM] UH! QUICK! HE'S TRYING
TO GET TO HIGHER GROUND!
[DINKURON]
LET'S GET HIM!
[ALL] YEAH!
[TOKO]
WE'VE GOT TO BE CAREFUL, GUYS!
[UKIYO] THAT'S RIGHT.
IT CAN BREATHE FIRE.
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER] WHEN A
RAID BOSS' HEALTH GETS LOWER,
ITS ATTACKS BECOME
MORE INTENSE AND VARIED.
(HOWLS)
WOAH!
(SCREAMING)
IT DID NOT JUST CHANGE ITS
ELEMENTAL TYPE AND TIMING.
THIS IS GONNA BE REALLY ROUGH!
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
ALL THINGS CONSIDERED,
YOU CAN'T DEAL WITH A RAID BOSS
THE SAME WAY YOU DID WHEN
IT WAS A NORMAL BATTLE.
[ORDISSO] AGGGGGGHHHHHH!
[RAGOMARU] AGGGHHH...!
[NAOTSUGU/TETORA]
AHHHHHH!
[SHIROE]
NAOTSUGU! TETORA! NO!
(SCREECH)
[SHIROE VOICEOVER]
YOU WON'T WIN A BATTLE LIKE THIS
SIMPLY BY GROUPING A BUNCH
OF STRONG PLAYERS EITHER.
[RAGOMARU]
UWH! DINKURON'S BEEN PETRIFIED!
[FEDERICO]
AAAGH! WE'VE LOST ALL OUR TANKS.
[JUNZO]
WHERE ARE THE HEALERS?
[RAGOMARU]
THEY'RE ALL GONE! WE GOTTA MOVE!
[SHIROE]
MASSACHUSETTS...! LET'S GO!
[WILLIAM]
OKAY, FINE...
LET'S GET OUTTA HERE.
FALL BACK, PEOPLE!
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
IN A CASE LIKE THIS,
A TEAM ENDS UP FALLING BACK
AND DYING SEVERAL TIMES
UNTIL IT FIGURES OUT THE
BEST SET OF TACTICS TO USE.
AND THAT'S JUST WHAT WE DID.
VENDEMIAIRE,
OF THE FIRST PRISON,
DEFEATED US SEVERAL TIMES
BEFORE WE EVEN HAD A CHANCE.
(ROAR)
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
HE NEVER COMPLETELY WIPED US OUT
BUT HE CAME AWFULLY CLOSE.
[HIGHLAND] I REALLY DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'M DOING WRONG.
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
A RAID PARTY HAS TO LEARN
A RAID BOSS' PATTERNS
AND STRATEGIES
OR THEY'LL JUST KEEP DYING.
NOT ALL RAIDS ARE SIMPLE
IN‐AND‐OUT BATTLES.
SOME TAKE AS LONG AS
A MONTH TO FINISH,
IF YOU EVER
FINISH THEM AT ALL...
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
BUT EVENTUALLY...
[WILLIAM]
IT'S WHEN IT BLINKS.
[PROMETHEUS]
RIGHT AFTERWARDS.
AND IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHO'S FIGHTING IT,
IT PICKS TEN RANDOM PEOPLE.
IT PLACES STATUS‐EFFECTS OR
USES INSTANT DEATH SKILL.
[DINKURON] YEAH...
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO
FIGURE OUT THE TIMING ON THAT.
[SHIROE]
TWENTY‐SIX SECONDS.
[ALL]
HUH?
GUYS, IT'S TWENTY‐SIX SECONDS.
(SCREECH)
[WILLIAM] TIME IT NOW!
[ELTON DISKA] ALL RIGHT, GUYS...
GET AROUND THE FRONT!
[SASAMEYUKI]
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR...
[PIANISSISSIMO]
HURRY AND GET INTO POSITION!
[SASAMEYUKI]
... SEVEN!
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
LIKE THE REST OF US,
RAID BOSSES HAVE RE‐CAST
AND COOL‐DOWN PERIODS.
TIMING IS EVERYTHING.
KNOW THE TIMING, EVADE,
THEN COUNTERATTACK.
THEN DOING DAMAGE
IS ALMOST EASY.
[SASAMEYUKI]
SIXTY! GO!
[SHIROE]
WILLIAM!
[WILLIAM]
YEAH!
LET'S SEE WHAT YOU GOT!
(SCREECH)
[JUNZO] HEY! IT ISN'T
FLASHING THIS TIME!
[NAOTSUGU] YEAH, NO MORE GETTING
TURNED INTO STATUES!
[TETORA] LET'S GO GET HIM!
[WILLIAM] ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS!
DO SOME REAL DAMAGE THIS TIME!
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
IF THE TEAM ATTACKS BASED ON
WHAT THEY'VE LEARNED ABOUT THE
BOSS' STRENGTHS AND WEAKNESSES,
IT'S JUST A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE IT GETS
THE VICTORY IT WANTS.
(EXPLOSION)
BEAT A RAID BOSS,
AND YOU PRETTY MUCH
GET SHOWERED WITH GOLD
AND EPIC‐CLASS ITEMS.
THE SECOND RAID BOSS WAS
EL RAIDA OF THE FIFTH PRISON.
HER SPECIALTY WAS RESETTING OUR
ACCUMULATED FOCAL HATRED
AND SUMMONING GUARDIAN BEASTS
TO DEAL WITH US.
IT WAS BRUTAL.
(HEAVY BREATHING)
HWYA!
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER] HOWEVER,
WE FINALLY TOOK CARE OF IT
ON OUR ELEVENTH TRY.
WE'VE HAD A TOUGH GO OF IT,
BUT BY HITTING ALL THESE
RAID BOSSES ONE AT A TIME
EN ROUTE TO OUR GOAL,
SEEMS TO BE HAVING
THE EFFECT WE WANT.
NOW... THIS IS A
FULL RAID PARTY.
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER] WE'RE NOW
THREE WEEKS INTO OUR ASSAULT
ON THE ABYSSAL SHAFT,
GIVE OR TAKE A DAY.
[FEDERICO] NOT AGAIN.
[VOINEN] THERE HE GOES...
[DEMICAS] I'LL SHOW YOU
THE WAY TO HELL, MONSTERS!
[NAOTSUGU] HEY, WAIT!
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO HOLD OFF
ON THE TAUNTS, MAN!
YOU'RE DRAWING TOO MUCH
ATTENTION, DEMI‐POO!
SHUT IT YOU POT‐BELLIED
STOVE, I'M GONNA‐!
[TETORA]
WAAUGH! LOOK OUT! BEHIND YOU!
UWH! WYVERN KICK!
DOES HE ENJOY
GETTING HIMSELF HURT?
GUESS WE HAVE TO
BACK THAT MANIAC UP.
(RASPY BREATH)
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER] THE DEEPER
AND FARTHER WE GOT IN,
THE MORE VICIOUS
THE DUNGEON BECAME.
(LABORED BREATHING)
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
THE LEVELS OF THE MONSTERS GREW.
AND SO DID THE INTENSITY
OF THE BATTLES.
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
AND WE HAD TO FIGHT WITHOUT
ANY KNOWLEDGE OF THE
LAYOUT OF THE ZONE.
(GROANS)
[TETORA]
GET READY!
IT'S TIME TO HEAL!
NOW DON'T GO FALLING IN
LOVE WITH ME... OKAY?
CAST THE FREAKIN' SPELL ALREADY!
(GIGGLES)
OH. OH RIGHT!
HERE YOU GO!
OKAY! IT'S TIME FOR A LITTLE
MORE PEP IN YOUR STEP!
AURORA HEAL!
[ALL] AHHHHHH....
[MOLLUSCA TYPE @ AKIBA]
OH, SPLENDID!
[SHIROE]
CONCENTRATE YOUR ATTACKS!
BUT DON'T GET TOO CLOSE!
[ALL]
RIGHT!
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
WE DEFEATED TWO RAID BOSSES,
BUT WE'RE WONDERING WHY WE
HAVEN'T SEEN A THIRD ONE YET.
AND A LITTLE SNOOPING AROUND
HASN'T HELPED US, EITHER.
AS IT STANDS,
WE'RE COMPLETELY STUCK.
[WILLIAM]
HOW MANY DO YOU THINK ARE LEFT?
[SHIROE]
YOU MEAN RAID BOSSES?
THERE HAS TO BE
AT LEAST THREE OR FOUR.
[WILLIAM] WE CAN'T DO THIS...
NOT IN TEN DAYS.
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
SUPPLIES AND LOGISTICS
ARE GETTING REALLY PROBLEMATIC.
WE GET RESURRECTED IF WE DIE,
BUT FIXING WORN OUT
EQUIPMENT ISN'T EASY.
WE HAVE TO TAKE TIME OUT TO LET
THE PLAYERS WITH CRAFTING SKILLS
GET OUR WEAPONS AND
SHIELDS BACK INTO SHAPE.
OTHERWISE, WE CAN'T LAST LONG
ENOUGH TO DO ANY REAL DAMAGE.
AND WILLIAM ONLY HAS
A HANDFUL OF CRYSTAL COMET
ARROWS TO USE AT A TIME.
HE'S CONSTANTLY TAXING OUR
EPIC CRAFTSMEN
AND SUPPLIES TO
RESTOCK HIS QUIVER.
(HUMMING)
SO WE'RE RUNNING OUT?
THERE'S NO TELLING HOW LONG
OUR PROVISIONS WILL LAST.
YEAH, AND THIS
FULL‐RAID PARTY
IS BEATING THE GEAR UP
PRETTY BADLY.
NOT TO MENTION YOU CAN'T GET
A LOT OF THESE WEAPONS
OUTSIDE OF A RAID.
SAME WITH THE MATERIALS
FOR THE REPAIR WORK.
WELL THAT'S WHY OTHER RAID
GUILDS GO ON LOWER‐LEVEL RAIDS;
TO GET MATERIALS THEY NEED
TO BUILD AND MAINTAIN
BETTER WEAPONS.
EASIER SAID THAN DONE...
IT'S NOT LIKE WE CAN HIT ALL
THE RAID ZONES ALL THE TIME.
WELL, THAT'S JUST IT, ISN'T IT.
WE'RE A MASTER RAID GUILD.
WE DON'T DO LESSER RAIDS.
AFTER ALL WE DO HAVE OUR PRIDE
TO THINK ABOUT, DON'T WE?
IT'S NOT JUST THAT!
WILLIAM WOULDN'T WASTE
OUR TIME ON SUCH THINGS.
GOT THAT RIGHT.
THAT'S WHY WE DECIDED TO STAY
WITH HIM IN THE FIRST PLACE.
HE HAS OUR
BEST INTERESTS AT HEART.
I MANAGED TO GET SOME
PROVISIONS BEFORE WE LEFT.
HOW LONG WILL
THEY SUSTAIN US?
ALONG WITH EVERYTHING YOU
BROUGHT... TWENTY DAYS.
[WILLIAM]
HUH? TWENTY DAYS?
[SHIROE] I GUESS THAT
ISN'T MUCH HELP, IS IT?
[WILLIAM]
UH, NO...
NOT REALLY.
YEAH I KNOW...
[WILLIAM, THINKING]
SERIOUSLY?
LOG HORIZON HAS WHAT,
EIGHT PLAYERS IN IT?
NOT EXACTLY A "POWER GUILD"
HOW DID HE MANAGE TO GET ALL
OF THOSE SUPPLIES ON HIS OWN?
THIS GUY REALLY IS
SOMETHING ELSE, ISN'T HE?
AFTER I TOLD THE ROUND TABLE
I WASN'T INTERESTED
IN THEIR ENDEAVORS,
I LEAD SILVER SWORD AROUND
TO THE VARIOUS RAID ZONES
UNTIL WE GOT TO SUSUKINO.
I DON'T REGRET ANY OF THE
DECISIONS I'VE MADE TO GET HERE.
I FEEL NO SHAME,
BUT ... NONETHELESS.
[GUY A]
LOOK, I'M DONE WITH THIS...
[GUY B]
GOOD LUCK. SEE YA LATER!
[GUY C]
IT WAS FUN, GUILD MASTER!
THEY EVEN KNOW
WHERE THEY'RE GOING?
LET 'EM STARVE
OUT THERE.
[WILLIAM, THINKING]
AND WELL, HERE WE ARE,
EVEN THOUGH I DIDN'T
BOTHER TO ASK SHIROE
WHAT THE HELL IT WAS
HE WAS LOOKING FOR
AND HOW MUCH TROUBLE
IT WAS GONNA BE.
THEY JUST FOLLOWED ME...
I DON'T EVEN KNOW IF WE'RE
DOING THE RIGHT THING
OR THE WRONG THING OUT HERE.
OR WHAT TO TELL THEM
IF THEY ASK?
JESUS. I'M JUST A GAMER.
I'M NOT SOME GUY WHO JUMPED OFF
THE PAGES OF A COMIC BOOK,
FULL OF AMAZING FIGHTING SKILLS
AND BUILT‐IN LEADERSHIP.
BUT I MUST WONDER...
... WHAT'S GOING ON IN THAT
MIND OF YOURS, SHIROE?
[SHIROE, THINKING] HAVING A
NICE QUIET PLACE TO READ,
KINDA WORKS IN MY FAVOR.
BUT HE'S SURE TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT I'M UP TO SOONER OR LATER.
AND EVEN IF SOMEONE FROM MINAMI
DOESN'T CAUSE PROBLEMS,
SOMEONE ELSE MIGHT BE AFTER US.
(ROCK BREAKING)
[BOTH] HM?
THAT LITTLE RAT!
(GROWL) YOU LITTLE PUKE!
RAHHHH! (HEAVY BREATH)
[DEMICAS, THINKING]
DAMN YOU, SHIROE!
YEAH, THAT BIG MOUTH PUSSY CAT
AND THAT LOUD‐MOUTH KNUCKLEHEAD
I CAN DEAL WITH...
AT LEAST THEY GAVE ME A FIGHT.
I CAN RESPECT THAT.
(SNARL)
ALL HE DID WAS PLAY WITH HIS
GLASSES AND GIVE PEOPLE ORDERS!
AND ON TOP OF EVERYTHING ELSE,
HE DISRESPECTED ME.
[SHIROE] SO WHICH ONE
OF YOU FUTURE DEAD GUYS
IS DEMI‐DOOFUS OR WHATEVER?
UWAH?
PARDON ME...
YOU'RE DOOFUS.
(ANGRY SCREAM)
[DEMICAS, THINKING]
WAIT,
MY EXTRA FIGHTING POWER
WAS HIM BUFFING ME.
HE USED KEEN EDGE
TO BOOST MY STRENGTH
AND MIND SHOCK TO MAKE SURE
THE MONSTER DIDN'T MOVE.
THAT LITTLE CREEP TOUCHED ME
WITH HIS MAGIC AGAIN!
THAT KID... SAVED MY LIFE?!
UWAHHHHARRGGH!
(ROCK SMASHING) AHHHH!
I DON'T SUPPOSE
HE'S NOTICING
THAT I GAVE HIM MORE
VEGETABLES THIS TIME AROUND?
I DON'T THINK
THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
[FEDERICO]
HUMPH! WHAT A DRAMA QUEEN.
[VOINEN] YOU SAID IT...
BUT I'M GLAD HE'S ON OUR SIDE.
YEAH, AT LEAST YOU DON'T
HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT HIM
RUNNING AWAY IN A FIGHT.
[NAOTSUGU]
WOAH! THIS LOOKS AWESOME!
[BOTH]
THANK YOU FOR THE STEW YOU GUYS!
(LAUGH, MUNCH)
(BLOWING)
(CHEERFUL CRY)
(CHOMP) MMMMM!
OH WOW! THIS IS PRETTY GOOD!
HUH? YOU OKAY OVER THERE?
HMMM... SOMETHING'S UP WITH
SHIROE. I'M NOT SURE WHAT IT IS.
YOU KNOW HIM
PRETTY WELL, HUH?
I KNOW HE'S GOT A LOT
ON HIS PLATE RIGHT NOW
AND HE'S LOOKING
PRETTY STRESSED.
BUT BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
HE ACTUALLY ENJOYS OVERWORKING
HIMSELF AND STAYING BUSY.
OF COURSE,
HE'S ALWAYS LIKE THAT,
SO IT'S HARD TO TELL IF
HE'S IN GOOD SPIRITS OR NOT.
BUT SOMETHING SEEMS OFF.
OKAY, SO HIS FRIEND CAN
SENSE THAT HE'S STRUGGLING.
YEAH.
YOU THINK HE NEEDS
A BEAUTIFUL STARLET?
YEAH MAYBE, BUT HE
DOESN'T NEED YOU.
DO YOU THINK I SHOULD
SHOW HIM MY PANTIES?!
[NAOTSUGU]
WELL MAYBE IF I SAW 'EM FIRST‐
UWH‐WAHAHAHOHH!
HEY! YOU STAY OUT
OF THIS, PIP‐SQUEAK!
(SNEEZE)
LOOK, SHIROE'S HARDER
TO CHEER UP THAN I AM.
SO IF HE'S ALREADY DOWN
IN THE DUMPS ALL THE TIME,
WHY WOULD HE COME
TO THIS AWFUL PLACE?
UH... HMMM...
THAT'S A GOOD POINT.
I'M NOT SURE, BUT I'D SAY
HE'S HERE TO PROTECT HIS HOME.
HIS HOME, YOU SAY?
I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT AN
ACTUAL HOUSE OR BUILDING.
IT'S MORE LIKE
WHAT OUR GUILD IS...
THE CITY... OR MAYBE
EVEN THE WORLD.
[TETORA] THE WORLD?
[NAOTSUGU] WELL, YEAH.
YOU KNOW HOW PEOPLE
NEED TO EAT AND SLEEP.
AND DON'T FORGET OUR FRIENDS.
WE HAD FAMILY
WHERE WE CAME FROM.
I MEAN IN THIS WORLD, NOW...
OUR GUILD'S KINDA LIKE A FAMILY.
[TETORA] HMMM...
[NAOTSUGU] AND ALL THOSE
PEOPLE YOU CARE ABOUT
NEED A PLACE TO STAY. YOU KNOW?
SO LIKE, AKIHABARA IS
ESSENTIALLY THE HOME
FOR OUR HOME.
IF THE PEOPLE OF THE CITY
CAN'T BE HAPPY,
THEN NONE OF THE GUILDS
REALLY HAVE A CHANCE.
IF YOU DON'T FEEL SECURE
ABOUT YOUR CITY,
THEN YOU WORRY ABOUT YOUR GUILD.
AND FROM WHAT I'VE SEEN,
SHIROE WON'T THINK TWICE
ABOUT GOING NOSE TO NOSE
WITH AN ENTIRE CITY
OR EVEN THE WORLD ITSELF
TO PROTECT HIS HOME.
OKAY... WHERE'S HOME?
[NAOTSUGU] AKIHABARA.
[TETORA] HM?
[NAOTSUGU, THINKING] I REALLY
OUGHTA GIVE MARIELLE A CALL...
I GUESS IT'S STILL
A LITTLE EARLY...
I PROBABLY SHOULDN'T...
AHHHEEEEEEEUAHHHHH...
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOUR
FACE, NAOTSUGU? (GIGGLE)
ACK! N‐NOTHING!
MY FACE IS JUST FINE, ALRIGHT!
MY FACE IS THE
BEST FACE EVER.
WHY DON'T YOU WORRY ABOUT
YOUR OWN STUPID FACE!
HM? (GIGGLE)
(MINORI HUMMING)
SO IS THERE EVEN A DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN CHRISTMAS AND
SNOWFELL, ANYWAY?
SNOWFELL'S THE BIG
WINTER CELEBRATION
FOR THE PEOPLE OF
THE LAND, RIGHT?
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK...?
IS MASTER SHIROE GONNA MAKE IT
BACK IN TIME FOR CHRISTMAS?
I DUNNO,
BUT I SURE HOPE SO.
HUH?
OH, MAN... I MISS THE
HOLIDAYS BACK HOME.
(SOBBING)
[LYCOPENE] AW, WHAT'S
THE MATTER, KATSUOMARU?
[KATSUOMARU] THIS IS THE
FIRST TIME I'VE SPENT CHRISTMAS
AWAY FROM MY FAMILY.
I... I'M... I JUST
FEEL LOST, YOU KNOW?!
[SMASH] (SNIFFLE) WHY'D YOU
HAVE TO BRING THAT UP?!
SO LET'S SPEND IT
TOGETHER THIS YEAR.
(CRYING TOGETHER)
[RUDY] SANTA CLAUS?
WE GET TOGETHER AND
EXCHANGE PRESENTS
AROUND SNOWFELL TIME, TOO.
[TOYA] AT CHRISTMAS, SANTA
DELIVERS PRESENTS TO EVERYONE.
RIGHT! HE RIDES ON A REINDEER.
(GIGGLE) NO THE REINDEER
PULL HIS SLEIGH.
[MINORI] OH YEAH...
[RUDY] I CAN'T WAIT!
I WONDER WHAT HE'LL
BRING US THIS YEAR.
TELL YOU WHAT!
IF HE'S GOT A SCROLL FOR ONE OF
THOSE ORAL ARTS, THEN I WANT IT!
DID SOMEONE SAY ORAL ART?
HOLY CRAP!
AKATSUKI, WHEN DID YOU GET HERE?
YOU NEVER CEASE TO
AMAZE ME AKATSUKI!
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU...
COME ON DOWN!
CHIEF...
HMM, NOTHING LIKE COMING
HOME AFTER A HARD DAY.
HAVE YOURSELF SOME TEA
AND A SNACK, HMMM.
I APPRECIATE IT.
OKAY... WHAT'RE
THEY TALKING ABOUT?
UH... THE ORAL ARTS...
THEY'RE LIKE THE TALK
OF THE TOWN THESE DAYS.
I HEAD SOME TALK
ABOUT THAT MYSELF...
IT'S A NEW WAY FOR SOMEONE
TO GO OUT AND GET A NEW
SKILL RANK FOR THEMSELVES.
AS YOU ALREADY KNOW,
THE STRENGTH OF A FIGHTING SKILL
IS DIRECTLY PROPORTIONAL
TO THE STRENGTH OF
THE PERSON USING IT.
[ISUZU] 'CAUSE THE NEW SKILLS
AREN'T PART OF YOUR
EXISTING SKILLS.
YOU GOT IT.
AND THEY WORK LIKE THIS:
INTRODUCTORY, MID‐CLASS,
MASTER, AND SECRET.
AS THE SKILL PROGRESSES,
IT BECOMES INCREASINGLY
HARD TO BEAT, Y'KNOW.
IT SAYS HERE YOU NEED TO GET
A SCROLL FROM AN ADVENTURER
IN YOUR CLASS TO
LEARN A MID‐CLASS.
AND IF I'M NOT MISTAKEN,
YOU NEED A SCROLL THAT
USES RARE MATERIALS
IN ORDER TO LEARN A MASTER ART.
[NYANTA] THE SCROLLS
AND MATERIALS
ARE REALLY EXPENSIVE TO OBTAIN,
MYAH... HOWEVER...
IF YOU'RE DEAD SET ON GETTING
TO THE SECRET LEVEL OF YOUR ART,
YOU'LL NEED TO DO
SPECIAL QUESTS.
SO YOU'LL HAVE TO PLAY CATCH UP.
IF YOU HAVEN'T DONE ANY
RAIDS YET, BABY.
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
RAIDS...
[RUDY]I'VE HEARD THAT ORAL ARTS
ARE SUPERIOR TO SECRET ARTS.
IS THAT TRUE, CHIEF?
BUT THAT'S ONLY
A RUMOR, RIGHT?
THERE AREN'T A LOT OF PEOPLE
I'VE TALKED TO
THAT'VE ACTUALLY SEEN
ONE IN ACTION,
LET ALONE OBTAINED ONE
FOR THEMSELVES.
WELL BROTHER SHIROE
SAID THEY EXIST!
HUH? HE REALLY DID?
[TOYA] YEAH, HE SAID THEY'RE
TOTALLY LEGIT.
WOULDN'T YOU LOVE TO
MASTER JUST ONE OF THEM?
MHMMH!
[AKATSUKI, THINKING] BACK WHEN
WE WERE JUST PLAYING THIS,
ORAL ARTS WEREN'T AVAILABLE
FOR US TO MASTER.
BUT NOW...
COME GET YOUR CRISPY, JUICY
CHRISTMAS CHICKEN RIGHT HERE!
JUST SIX DAYS TILL
CHRISTMAS EVERYONE!
[NERURESU] HOW WEAK AND
SHALLOW CAN YOU FOOLS BE!
WE'RE NOT A PACK OF LAPDOGS
BEGGING AT YOUR FEET!
IT'S TIME YOU
LEARNED YOUR PLACE...
ADVENTURERS, YOU HAVE
WORN OUT YOUR WELCOME!
[AKATSUKI, VOICEOVER] WHILE
SHIROE IS AWAY FROM AKIHABARA,
A WARRIOR TRIES TO
FIND HER OWN WAY.
WHY WAS SHE LEFT BEHIND?
IS IT INEXPERIENCE? WEAKNESS?
MEANWHILE, RAYNESHIA HAS
GIVEN HERSELF TO RESIGNATION.
SHE DOESN'T BELIEVE THE
ADVENTURERS AND HER PEOPLE
WILL EVER AGREE.
[SHIROE]
STAND UP, ONE MORE TIME!