[AKATSUKI]
MY LORD... WHAT'S GOING ON?
[SHIROE]
THEY'RE ALL PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
[SHIROE] SHE'S SLEEPING?
THEY'RE ALL SLEEPING!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
HMM... WINGS...
GLITTERING... A MOTH... MM
[REGAN]
"GLITTERING... WINGS"?
[SHIROE] WE'RE TAKING CARE OF
THE FIFTY‐FOUR
PEOPLE OF THE LAND
WHO HAVE FALLEN ASLEEP
AT THE GUILD BUILDING.
[RIEZE] THE SAME THING
HAPPENED IN MAIHAMA.
AND LORD SERJIAD STILL
SLEEPS AT THIS VERY MOMENT.
I TALKED TO SILVER SWORD,
THERE'S NOTHING LIKE
THIS IN SUSUKINO.
SO BASICALLY IT'S ONLY PEOPLE
OF THE LAND WHO ARE AFFECTED?
[RODERICK] YES. THEIR MAGIC
POINTS DROP TO ZERO,
AND THEIR RESTORATION CAN'T
COUNTERACT THE DRAIN.
[MICHITAKA] WHICH MEANS THIS
THING DRAINS MAGIC POINTS.
ACCORDING TO A WITNESS,
IT LOOKED LIKE A MOTH
EXCEPT REALLY HUGE AND
WITH GLITTERING WINGS.
SO WE'RE DEALING WITH
SOME KIND OF SPIRIT MOTH?
I DON'T REMEMBER THE GAME HAVING
A MONSTER SUCH AS THIS ANYWHERE.
NEITHER DO I, BUT IT'S HERE.
AND WE NEED TO TIGHTEN
OUR DEFENSES UP, QUICK.
[EINS] WHAT DO WE DO ABOUT
SHIBUYA? [SHIROE] HUH?
[SOJIRO]
SHIBUYA?
[EINS]
I HEARD RECENTLY,
REGAN REPORTED THAT SHIBUYA'S
OLD RADIO AND TELEVISION
CENTER IS STILL WORKING.
[EINS] SHOULDN'T THAT BE OUR
HIGHEST PRIORITY, MASTER SHIROE?
SO YOU'RE SAYING WE LET
THE MOTH RUN LOOSE?
THIS MIGHT BE COLD OF ME,
BUT IF THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND
ARE THE ONLY ONES ASLEEP...
EINS, NO!
[EINS]
LOOK. THESE ARE DESPERATE TIMES.
YOU HAVE TO SEE THAT.
FIRST, THERE WAS THE ROGUE
ROYAL GUARD INCIDENT,
THE EMPOWERING OF FLAVOR
TEXT AND NOW, THIS?!
THERE ARE RUMORS OF THE PEOPLE
OF THE LAND PREPARING FOR WAR.
HOW MUCH OF THIS ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO LET HAPPEN, MARIELLE?
[WOODSTOCK] LOOK, I UNDERSTAND
WHAT YOU'RE TRYING TO SAY.
HOWEVER...
[MICHITAKA] YEAH. EVEN IF WE CAN
GO HOME, IT'S NOT LIKE WE CAN
JUST PACK UP AND
LEAVE RIGHT AWAY.
RIGHT, SHIROE?
[SHIROE]
YES, I AGREE.
MM?
[SHIROE] BUT WE CAN'T JUST
IGNORE WHAT'S GOING ON, EITHER.
KEEP YOUR EYES PEELED AND LET'S
COME UP WITH SOME OPTIONS.
[AKATSUKI] THERE AREN'T
MANY PEOPLE OUT TODAY.
[SHIROE]
THE MOTH IS ON EVERONE'S MIND.
(EXHALE)
[TOYA] NGHHH!
[MINORI] TOYA?
[TOYA] WHAT DID CHIEF
NYANTA HAVE TO SAY?
THAT WE'RE GOING OUT
ON PATROL TONIGHT...
AND THE CHIEF TOLD ME THAT
HE'LL BE COMING OUT WITH US.
I SEE.
[MINORI]
IT TURNS OUT NONE OF
THE PEOPLE OF THE
LAND WHO FELL ASLEEP
ARE SHOWING ANY SIGNS
THEY'RE GONNA WAKE UP SOON.
[TOYA]
WELL THAT'S NOT GOOD.
I WOULD IF I COULD.
(EXHALE)
[RUDY] YOU THINKING ABOUT YOUR
HOME AGAIN? [ISUZU] OH...!
HEY RUDY.
[RUDY]
YOU KNOW, I WAS GIVING ALL OF
THIS SOME THOUGHT...
I DON'T THINK ALL
THAT MUCH WOULD CHANGE BETWEEN
US IF YOU WENT BACK HOME.
BUT IF I DO, WE MAY NEVER
SEE EACH OTHER AGAIN.
[RUDY] IF YOU HAVE A
PLACE TO CALL HOME,
YOU SHOULD AT LEAST
TRY TO GET THERE.
I GUESS MAYBE WHAT
I'M TRYING TO SAY IS,
NOT EVERYONE HAS A
PLACE TO GO BACK TO.
(EXHALE)
[ISUZU]
RUDY...
[NYANTA] ALRIGHT, IT'S TIME
FOR US TO START OUR PATROLS.
[SHIROE] MM‐HM! NYANTA, KEEP AN
EYE ON EVERYONE FOR ME, OKAY?
[NAOTSUGU] SHIROE!
[SHIROE] UH?!
[TETORA]
OVER THERE! LOOK!
[NAOTSUGU]
THEY'RE COMING RIGHT AT US!
IT'S A SWARM OF
THOSE MOTH‐JERKS!
[SHIROE]
ETERNAL MOTHS?
(TERRIFIED)
[SHORYU]
THERE'S SO MANY OF THOSE THINGS!
[MARIELLE]
THIS IS REALLY BAD YOU GUYS.
[HENRIETTA]
I DO NOT LIKE THE LOOKS OF THIS.
[ISAAC] HOLY CRAP...! MAN,
DO I FREAKIN' HATE BUGS!
[KAZUHIKO]
THE HELL'S GOING ON HERE?
[DINKURON] ALL THE SCALE
DUST FROM THESE MOTHS
IS GETTING PAST THE
CITY'S MAGIC CIRCLE!
[WILLIAM] JUST KEEP
ATTRACTING THEM.
PUSH THEM BACK
OUTSIDE THE WALLS!
[BOLOGNESE MASTER] THEY'RE ABOUT
TO BREACH
THE SOUTHWESTERN CORNER!
[WILLIAM] SECOND UNIT,
COVER THE OTHER SIDE!
[PROROCCA] ROGER THAT!
[WILLIAM] DON'T YOU NEED TO BE
GETTING BACK TO YOUR
WIFE, DEMICAS?!
[DEMICAS] UWAH! I'VE
GOT HER IN CHARGE
OF EVACUATING THE
PEOPLE OF THE LAND!
I'M NOT LETTING A SINGLE MOTH
GET PAST ME! NOT ON MY WATCH!
[WARRIOR]
ALL THE ROYAL GUARDS ARE ASLEEP!
[KAZUHIKO] WHO COULD'VE THOUGHT
OF SOMETHING LIKE THIS,
LAUNCHING AN ATTACK FROM
OUTSIDE OF THE ZONE.
GET THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND
EVACUATED NOW! [ALL] YES SIR!
THIS IS GOING TO GET
REAL UGLY, REAL FAST.
[SERARA]
MARIELLE, OVER HERE TOO!
[HENRIETTA]
ADVENTURERS NOW?!
[MARIELLE] SO IT'S NOT
JUST PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
[SHORYU] WE NEED TO
FIND COVER RIGHT AWAY!
[SHIROE]
RUN!
GO! GET TO THE GUILD BUILDING!
[AKANEYA] SO NOW ADVENTURERS
ARE FALLING TO THESE THINGS?
[SHIROE] THE SCALE
DUST IS THE KEY.
ANYONE WHO COMES INTO
CONTACT WITH IT
IS VULNERABLE TO THE
SLEEPING SICKNESS.
PERHAPS, THE LOSS OF MAGIC
POINTS IS
CAUSING THE SOUL TO
EVACUATE THE BODY.
ALMOST LIKE A "SOUL
EXPULSION DISEASE."
[MARIELLE] MAYBE, BUT NOT
EVERYONE HAS PASSED OUT.
[RODERICK] I HAVEN'T
BEEN ABLE TO DETECT
A DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
THOSE WHO FALL ASLEEP
AND THOSE WHO DON'T, BUT...
[AKANEYA] IS THERE A
CHANCE OF DYING FROM THIS?
[RODERICK]
DOESN'T LOOK LIKE IT.
SO ANYONE WHO PHYSICALLY DIES
CAN COME BACK AT THE CATHEDRAL.
IN THAT CASE, SLEEPING LIKE
THIS MIGHT ACTUALLY BE WORSE.
(PING)
WHAT'D YOU FIND OUT?
[SOJIRO, VOICE CHAT]
BAD NEWS, SHIROE. I THINK...
I THINK I FOUND THEIR NEST.
[SHIROE, VOICE CHAT]
OKAY, SO WHY'S THAT BAD?
[SOJIRO] IT'S IN SHIBUYA.
[SHIROE] UH?
[SOJIRO]
BETWEEN US AND THE TRANSMITTER.
THE CITY'S BEEN
TURNED INTO A DUNGEON
AND THAT'S NOT THE WORST OF IT.
[SHIROE]
SO WHERE EXACTLY IS THE NEST?
[SOJIRO] THE OLD TV AND RADIO
CENTER,
THE ENTIRE COMPLEX
IS A RAID ZONE NOW.
I TOOK A LOOK AT THE FLAVOR
TEXT, IT'S CHANGED.
NOW IT'S THE
"FORTRESS OF CALLS."
[REGAN]
AH, AND THIS IS?
[RODERICK] A PROTOTYPE BASED ON
HOW SCREEN‐CAPTURE USED TO WORK.
JUST BE CAREFUL.
IF YOU TRY USING IT FOR
MORE THAN TEN MINUTES,
THE WHOLE THING'LL BLOW UP ON
YOU AND THAT'D RUIN YOUR DAY.
[SHIROE] WHOA. DIDN'T
LOOK LIKE THIS LAST WEEK.
[AKANEYA] LOOKS LIKE THERE'S A
MAGIC SEAL ON THE ENTRANCE.
[REGAN] PERHAPS THE "ANTENNA"
DEVICE IS
ACTUALLY A HOMING BEACON
BRINGING ALL THOSE MOTHS
DOWN FROM THE MOON,
ALONG WITH THEIR
EGGS AND COCOONS.
FROM THE MOON, THAT
DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
[MICHITAKA] THERE ARE SOME
OBSERVERS ON THE MOON
WE'VE BEEN TRYING TO CONTACT,
WE'RE HOPING THEY HAVE A
FEW ANSWERS FOR US UP THERE.
DON'T THOSE "GENIUS" OR
"COLLECTOR" MONSTERS
HAVE A BASE THERE TOO?
[MARIELLE] I GUESS IT'S SAFE TO
SAY THAT THOSE ETERNAL MOTHS
ARE ALSO A TYPE
OF GENIUS AS WELL.
BUT WHY WOULD THEY TAKE MP
IF THEY DON'T USE MAGIC?
[SHIROE] ROE2'S LETTER
STATED THAT GENIUSES ARE
IN THE PROCESS OF HARVESTING
SOMETHING CALLED "EMPATHIUM."
I DIDN'T REALLY UNDERSTAND
WHAT THAT MEANT AT TIME, BUT...
[RIEZE] IS IT POSSIBLE
EMPATHIUM IS OUR MP?
IT APPEARS THAT
COULD BE THE CASE.
[AKANEYA] THE ETERNAL MOTHS
HAVE BEEN SHOWING UP
AT THE SAME TIME OVER
THE LAST TWO DAYS.
THEY'VE BEEN
TIMING THEIR ATTACKS
ALONG WITH THE MOON RISE.
BOTH OF THE ASSAULTS TOOK
PLACE AT 18 TO 22 HOURS.
AND WE CAN PROBABLY COUNT ON
THE SAME THING HAPPENING AGAIN
AT THE SAME TIME TONIGHT.
FIRST THEY TOOK OUT PEOPLE
OF THE LAND,
THEN WENT AFTER THE ADVENTURERS.
AND THERE'S MORE EACH
TIME THEY ATTACK.
THIS MIGHT BE UNPOPULAR,
BUT DESTROYING THE ANTENNA
COULD BE THE BEST WAY
TO GET RID OF THEM.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?! THAT'S THE
ONLY ANTENNA ON THE SERVER!
YES... AND ACCORDING
TO ANCIENT LEGEND,
SOMETHING LIKE THIS IS
ONE OF THE ONLY THINGS
WE COULD USE TO COMMUNICATE
WITH THE HEAVENS.
IT MIGHT VERY WELL STOP THE
MOTHS, BUT WITHOUT THE ANTENNA,
YOU WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO
CARRY OUT SHIROE'S PLAN.
[EINS]
WHAT...?
[MARIELLE]
WHAT ABOUT THE OTHER SERVERS?
[MICHITAKA]
I DON'T KNOW.
WE DON'T HAVE A LOT OF
INFORMATION ON OVERSEAS SERVERS.
[RODERICK] AND BESIDES, IT'S NOT
LIKE WE CAN GUARANTEE
THEY'LL WORK, EVEN IF
WE COULD GET THERE.
[AKANEYA] IT CAN'T BE IGNORED...
OR FINDING ANOTHER WAY TO
COMMUNICATE
WITH THE MOON WILL BE THE
LEAST OF OUR PROBLEMS.
I SUPPOSE WE'RE JUST GONNA
HAVE TO LEAVE IT BE FOR NOW.
(EXHALE)
ALL RIGHT, SO WHAT'S
THE PLAN THEN?
THE OLD COMPLEX IS A RAID ZONE.
LAUNCHING AN ASSAULT FROM THE
OUTSIDE TO DRAW THEM AWAY
ISN'T GOING TO BE AN OPTION
FOR US AT THIS POINT.
WE'LL NEED TO GO IN BY
WAY OF THE MAIN ENTRANCE
AND ENGAGE POCKETS OF RESISTANCE
EN ROUTE TO THE ANTENNA.
I'LL GET A RAID TEAM
TOGETHER IMMEDIATELY.
[AKANEYA] SOME PEOPLE
ON THIS TEAM HAVE
PRETTY LOW STATS, YOU KNOW.
[SHIROE] YES, BUT I THOUGHT
WE SHOULD USE THE PEOPLE
WHO STAYED AWAKE DURING
THE LAST ATTACK.
I KNOW THAT'S NOT
EXACTLY A GUARANTEE,
BUT IT'S OUR BEST
BET, I'M AFRAID.
[MICHITAKA] YOU MIGHT
BE BETTER OFF IF YOU
SCOUTED IT OUT BEFORE GOING IN.
WE DON'T HAVE THE TIME.
THAT'S ONE HELL OF A
RISK, MASTER SHIROE.
[REGAN]
SORRY I KEPT YOU WAITING!
[NAOTSUGU] HUH?
[TETORA] OH...!
[NAOTSUGU]
YOU'RE COMING TOO?
[REGAN]
YES, INDEED.
THE ENTRANCE TO THE FORTRESS
OF CALLS SEEMS
TO HAVE A SPECIAL
SEAL THAT WOULD
OTHERWISE KEEP YOU
FROM GETTING IN.
SO MASTER SHIROE
ASKED ME TO TAG ALONG
SO THAT I COULD
REMOVE IT FOR YOU.
THAT'S NOT THE ONLY
REASON YOU'RE COMING.
I WOULDN'T MISS IT
FOR THE WORLD.
IT'S THE FIRST TIME AN EVENT
LIKE THIS HAS EVER HAPPENED.
AS MAGE OF MIRROR LAKE, IT IS
MY DUTY,
AND A RESPONSIBILITY I RATHER
ENJOY. [TETORA] HEH.
WELL MAKE SURE YOU
STAY OUT OF THE WAY...
I DON'T KNOW IF I'LL
BE ABLE TO PROTECT YOU.
[REGAN] I WOULDN'T WORRY
ABOUT THAT IF I WERE YOU...
IN MATTERS SUCH AS THIS,
I CAN TAKE CARE OF MYSELF.
[KINJO] ALL FACILITIES
HAVE CEASED FUNCTIONING.
AND I HAVE HEARD ABOUT
SHIBUYA AS WELL.
I'M CURIOUS TO SEE HOW THE
ADVENTURERS RESPOND...
I WISH YOU THE BEST.
[SHIROE] PLEASE LOOK AFTER
THE CITY FOR USE, KINJO?
[KINJO]
BE CAREFUL, MASTER SHIROE.
[SHIROE]
OH UH, AND EINS.
[EINS]
YES?
I'M CONFIDENT
THAT YOU WILL KEEP YOUR FAITH
IN US THROUGH THE END OF THIS.
(EXHALE)
[SHIROE] OUR TARGET IS THE RAID
ZONE INSIDE THE SHIBUYA DUNGEON,
THE FORTRESS OF CALLS.
IF WE DESTROY THE ANTENNA,
THAT SHOULD KEEP ANY MORE
ETERNAL MOTHS FROM SHOWING UP.
WE MAKE SURE WE DON'T
HAVE ANY MORE COMPANY...
THEN WE TAKE OUT THE REST.
[AKATSUKI] UH...
[MINORI] OH...
[NAOTSUGU] MPH...
LET'S FINISH THIS
BEFORE MOONRISE!
[RIEZE] SIX HOURS AND
THEN THE MOON COMES UP.
[MINORI]
IVE GOT EIGHT MOON RABBITS
FROM THE FORMER DOGENZAKA
DIRECTION!
AVERAGE LEVEL 91!
[SHIROE] KEEP THEM IN CHECK AND
MAKE FOR THE FORMER
CENTER‐GAI STREET!
[RIEZE] SIX MORE RABBITS,
EACH FROM TWO O'CLOCK
AND TEN O'CLOCK!
[SHIROE, THINKING]
I DON'T LIKE THIS...
IT'S A LITTLE TOO CONVENIENT
THIS HAPPENS RIGHT
WHEN WE START TRYING TO
COMMUNICATE WITH THE MOON.
[NAOTSUGU] SHIROE!
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD!
[AKATSUKI]
SOME UP AHEAD OF US!
[NAOTSUGU]
WE GOT NINE MORE!
HEY! PARTY 2 DRAW
THE MONSTER IN FRONT!
[SHIROE] PARTY 1 FRONTLINE!
GO FORWARD AND...
WAIT! SPLIT UP THE
BUNCH IN THE REAR!
[BOTH]
HYAHHHHH!
MR. RICHO AND TOYA,
BACK UP PARTY 1!
[BOTH]
ROGER!
YUZUKO! YOU AND MISS OLIVE
GO AND SUPPORT
THE OTHER PARTIES!
PARTY 4 FRONTLINE, I NEED YOU TO
MAKE A PATH FOR US! [ALL] ROGER!
[KURINON] IS THAT
YOUR FRIEND MINORI?
SHE'S SO CUTE AND ADORABLE!
[RUDY] YOU CAN THANK A LITTLE
MAGICAL SPELL CALLED
THE FULL CONTROL ENCOUNTER.
[ISUZU] SHE LEARNED IT
DIRECTLY FROM SHIROE HIMSELF.
THERE'S TOO MANY OF THESE
STUPID MOON RABBITS!
[MARIELLE] HANG ON!
[NAOTSUGU] AH...!
[MARIELLE] GIMME A MINUTE,
NAOTSUGU AND YOU'LL BE FINE.
[TETORA] HEY! IF YOU
WANNA GET YOUR POWER UP
AND STAY STRONG, JUST LET
TETORA‐BABY DO THE HEALING.
[SHIROE, THINKING]
IF THEY'RE READING US,
WE'RE PLAYING RIGHT
INTO THEIR HANDS.
OLIVE, FALL BACK TO THE
REAR! NO! NO WAIT! RICHO'S
RIGHT FLANK'S EXPOSED!
[OLIVE] ERK! HUH? WHAT? AH...!
[RICHO] BE CAREFUL.
[SHIROE]
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?!
UH, SORRY...
[SHORYU]
MASTER SHIROE!
WE GOT MORE ENEMIES!
NOW THEY'RE COMING AT US
FROM EIGHT O'CLOCK!
[ISUZU] SHIROE! I'VE GOT A
MINOTAUR OVER HERE!
[RUDY] WELL I WAS
NOT EXPECTING THAT!
THAT'S WHY THEY CALL
IT AN AMBUSH, RUDY!
[ISAMI] WAAAAHHHH!
[KURINON] OMIGOD, OMIGOOOD!
[SHIROE, THINKING] AT THE RATE
WE'RE GOING WE'RE NEVER GONNA
FIND OUT HOW TO GET BACK HOME!
[HENRIETTA] MASTER SHIROE?!
WE'VE GOT TWO MINOTAURS
OUT HERE! WHAT DO WE DO?!
[SHIROE, VOICE CHAT] UH... FORCE
YOUR WAY UP THE FORMER SPAINZAKA
WITH PARTIES 2 AND 4 AT THE
CENTER! [SOJIRO] HYAHHHH!
(SERARA GASPS)
[NYANTA] HANG ON! I'VE GOT YOU!
[SERARA]
CHIEF NYANTA!
[REGAN] OH, MY! I'VE NEVER
SEEN A MELEE LIKE THIS BEFORE!
IT IS MOST UNUSUAL IF
I DO SAY SO MYSELF.
(GROWLING)
EH?
OH DEAR HEAVENS!
[NAOTSUGU]
WATCH IT, OLD TIMER! HYAHH!
PARTY 1, YOU NEED TO FALL BACK
AND FOCUS ON YOUR HEALING!
[SHIROE, THINKING] THERE IS NO
WAY I CAN LEAVE THIS WORLD
BEHIND. NOT WITH
THE SHAPE IT'S IN!
[SHIROE, VOICE CHAT]
KEEP YOUR RANKS STRAIGHT
AND PUSH FORWARD, PEOPLE!
NO. TURN RIGHT AT
THE NEXT CORNER!
[KOZARU]
DOES HE KNOW WHAT HE'S DOING?!
[NAZNA] HE'S USUALLY A
LOT BETTER THAN THIS.
[SOJIRO] IT'S NOT LIKE WE HAD A
CHANCE TO DO A LOT OF SCOUTING.
WE'VE JUST GOTTA SUCK IT UP.
[HENRIETTA]
WHATEVER...
[RIEZE]
HOW DISAPPOINTING.
[MINORI]
HUH?
MY LORD TOLD ME HE WAS AN
OUTSTANDING STRATEGIST.
I WAS EXPECTING A
LITTLE MORE FROM HIM.
MPH.
[TOYA] SO THIS IS THE
FORTRESS OF CALLS...
[RIEZE]
FOUR HOURS, SEVEN MINUTES.
[REGAN] THIS REALLY IS A
COMPLICATED SEAL, ISN'T IT?
AND THERE! SORRY FOR THE WAIT!
[BOTH]
AW YEAH! NICE PANTIES!
[TETORA]
WAY TO GO, MISTER CREEPY GUY!
[REGAN] I'M MERELY A CONDUIT
FOR MY AWESOMENESS!
[SHIROE] LET'S GO.
[BOTH] ROGER!
[SHIROE, THINKING] WE DID MANAGE
TO USE SOME MYTHICAL BEASTS
AND FIND OUT A LITTLE
BIT ABOUT THE LAYOUT.
BUT WE'LL STILL NEED TO
TAKE THE FLOORS ONE BY ONE
TO GET ALL THE WAY
UP TO THE ROOF.
EACH PARTY'S REARGUARD
WILL NEED TO BE READY.
(ROAR SQUEALS)
[SOJIRO] VOTIVE SWORD,
KOGARASUMARU! HWAH!
[OLIVE] OH, COME ON! I
CAN'T SEE MASTER SOJI!
[YUZUKO] ENEMY CONTACTS!
SIX MOON RABBITS!
[ISAMI] I'M NOT LETTING MASTER
SOJIRO HAVE ALL THE GLORY!
SAMURAI'S CHALLENGE!
OH WOW! I COULD
GET USED TO THIS.
LADIES... IN COMBAT.
ALL OF YOU GUYS SURE DO LIKE
EACH OTHER, DON'T YOU?
[ISAMI] OF COURSE WE
ARE. WE'RE GUILDMATES
[KURINON]
OH, AND SO MUCH MORE! WHOO!
[REGAN]
OMIGOODNESS!
[NAOTSUGU]
YOU ALL RIGHT, GRANDPA?
YES, I'M FINE. DON'T
WORRY ABOUT ME.
[RUDY] ALL THE PASSAGES
LOOK THE SAME TO ME!
[ISUZU] THIS MAZE COULD TAKE
US SOME TIME TO GET THROUGH.
[SHORYU]
ANOTHER DEAD END?!
[HIEN]
IT'S BLOCKED OFF BY COCOONS!
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD, IT'S
BLOCKED OFF OVER HERE!
[TETORA] I CAN'T SEE THROUGH IT!
[MINORI] MASTER SHIROE!
THE WEST CORRIDOR IS
SWARMING WITH MOON RABBITS!
[SHIROE, THINKING] AS FAST AS
WE'RE MOVING, WE'RE
GONNA WIND UP BURNING
THROUGH OUR MAGIC POINTS.
NO, WAIT A SEC...
[SHIROE] EVERYONE! BACK TO THE
FIRST FLOOR! [NAZNA] HUH?!
WHAT?! BUT WE'VE
ALREADY GOTTEN SO FAR?
YOU SURE?
[SHIROE]
BACK TO THE COURTYARD, NOW!
AS LONG AS WE KEEP AN
EYE ON THOSE DOORS,
WE CAN FUNNEL THE MONSTERS
INTO A KILL ZONE.
TAKE TURNS. THAT'LL LET
EVERYONE RECOVER THEIR MAGIC.
[HIEN] I'D STILL BETTER
IF THIS WAS A SAFE ZONE.
[SHORYU] THE RAID MOB
LEVELS ARE TOO HIGH...
I WASN'T REALLY COUNTING
ON IT BEING THIS TOUGH.
(RIEZE GASPS)
[SHORYU/HIEN] HUH?
[RIEZE]
SHIROE!
[TOYA] MINOTAURS!
(ROAR)
TWO OF EM? AGAIN?!
[NYANTA] SIX BLACK
OGRES ARE ON TOP OF US!
[NAZNA] TWELVE MOON
RABBITS FROM THE WEST!
SET YOUR FORMATION, GUYS!
I GUESS WE'RE NOT
GETTING A BREAK.
[KUSHIYATAMA] OH COME ON,
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE IT
ANY OTHER WAY
WOULD YOU?!
[KOZARU] AS SOON AS I FOUND OUT
I WAS TEAMING UP WITH
MISS VANGUARD DUTY
I KNEW I WAS GONNA
WIND UP LIKE THIS.
WHY AM I ALWAYS FIGHTING
FOR MY LIFE AROUND YOU?!
ARE YOU TRYING TO TELL ME I'M
BAD LUCK OR SOMETHING, ZARU?
Y'KNOW WHAT I THINK...
YOU'RE PROBABLY THE REASON
YOU'RE ALWAYS FIGHTING
FOR YOUR LIFE!
[NYANTA] SERARA!
[SERARA] HUH?
(SERARA SCREAMS)
[NYANTA] UGH! UWAH!
[TOYA] (GASP) CHIEF!
(SNARLING)
[SERARA]
NO! SAY YOU'RE OKAY!
[MINORI]
NO! TOYA! DON'T DO IT!
[SHIROE]
WE CAN'T STOP THEM FAST ENOUGH!
ALL RIGHT, WHO NEEDS SOME
AURORA HEALING TO... OOF!
GRR, YOU CAN'T JUST SHOVE A
FAMOUS STARLET LIKE TH‐! OH!
[MARIELLE] TETORA, DO WHAT YOU
CAN TO HEAL EVERYONE!
AHH!
[TETORA] NO! NO! NO! NO! NO! NO!
[NAOTSUGU]
MARIELLE!
[REGAN] UWAH!
[NAOTSUGU] NO!
[HIEN] OH CRAP,
OH CRAP, OH CRAP!
[TOYA] ARGH!
[RIEZE] ANOTHER ONE!
A FOURTH QUARTER
VENOMOUS HYDRANGEA!
[MINORI]
MASTER SHIROE! WE'VE LOST THREE!
[KUSHIYATAMA]
I DON'T HAVE ENOUGH MP!
I'M GOING TO PRIORITIZE
RICHO AND THE OTHERS.
YOU'LL HAVE TO DO WHAT YOU
CAN ON YOUR OWN, ZARU!
[KOZARU] YOU GOT IT, BOSS!
[SHIROE]
LOOK! IT'S WIDE‐RANGE!
EVERYBODY SCATTER!
NO WAIT! MAIDENS,
FOUR‐QUARTER PRAYER!
[NAZNA] AIN'T NOBODY GOT
ENOUGH POINTS FOR THAT!
(GASP)
[KOZARU]
ARRGH!
(OLIVE COLLAPSING)
[KUSHIYATAMA] ZARU!
[YUZUKO]
AHHHH!
[ISUZU]
STATUS AILMENTS!
WE'RE STARTING TO FALL APART!
(COLLAPSE)
[RUDY] IT'S NO GOOD! WE'RE
LOSING HIT POINTS TOO FAST!
[RIEZE]
THREE LOST, FIVE DEAD!
WE'VE LOST A THIRD OF OUR PEOPLE
IN ONLY A COUPLE OF MINUTES...
WE DON'T STAND A
CHANCE OUT HERE!
WE DON'T HAVE ANYTHING LEFT!
[SOJIRO]
HELP US, SHIROE!
[NAZNA]
WE CAN'T KEEP THIS UP!
[SHIROE]
UH...
[NAOTSUGU]
SHIROE!
[AKATSUKI]
NO, MY LORD...
[SHIROE]
HA... HM.
QUANTUM GATE!
[SHORYU]
THIS IS... A RECORDING STUDIO?
[YUZUKO] SO I GUESS THIS IS THE
DUNGEON'S RESURRECTION POINT
INSTEAD OF THE ENTRANCE.
[NAOTSUGU] MARIELLE, I'M
SORRY. I DIDN'T CATCH YOU.
[MARIELLE] IT'S NOT
YOUR FAULT, BABY.
ONCE THE HOLE OPENED
UP AND I FELL IN,
I ENDED UP BEING
TRANSPORTED HERE.
DOES IT HURT? YOU
WANNA SEE MY UNDIES?
[REGAN] I'M GOOD. I'M NOT
SURE HOW THAT WOULD HELP. HEH.
[TETORA] MARIELLE, THANKS FOR
LOOKING OUT FOR ME BACK THERE.
[MARIELLE] HM? DON'T YOU WORRY.
IT ALL BOILED DOWN TO YOU HAVING
MORE MAGIC POINTS THAN I DO. YOU
WOULD'VE DONE THE SAME FOR ME.
[KOZARU] MAN, I
HAVEN'T BEEN IN A RAID
THIS TOUGH IN A LONG TIME.
[NAOTSUGU] GET OFF HER,
YOU LITTLE PARASITE!
[SHIROE] UM!
[BOTH] HM?
HEY GUYS, I'M SORRY.
MASTER SHIROE...
[HENRIETTA]
MASTER SHIROE.
HM?
(SLAPPING)
[BOTH] OH...
OH, MISS HENRIETTA?
[AKATSUKI]
MY LORD...
(EXHALE)
[MINORI]
(GASP) UM, MASTER SHIROE!
WE DECIDED, WE'RE GONNA STAY
IN THIS WORLD, NO MATTER WHAT!
[SHIROE]
HUH...?
[MINORI]
WE KNOW YOU'RE WORRIED.
YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT
GETTING BACK.
YOU'RE WORRIED IF WE BREAK
THE ANTENNA WE WON'T GET HOME,
OR WE'RE GONNA BE
STUCK IN A WAR.
IT'S NOT LIKE WE DON'T WANT TO
GO BACK HOME, MASTER SHIROE.
BUT WE HAVEN'T MADE UP OUR MINDS
ABOUT IT EITHER. [RUDY] MM‐HM.
SO IF WE ACTUALLY HAVE SOME
TIME TO THINK ABOUT IT,
THAT MAY NOT BE A BAD THING,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
YEAH! THE ANTENNA
CAN'T BE THE ONLY WAY
TO FIND OUR WAY BACK HOME.
BESIDES, Y'KNOW,
I CAN'T JUST LEAVE THE
PEOPLE OF THE LAND LIKE THIS.
SERIOUSLY,
WHEN WE WENT TO SAPHIR,
WE WEREN'T A LOT OF HELP.
[SHIROE]
OH...
[TOYA] EVEN IF THEY WERE
GRATEFUL FOR WHAT WE DID,
SOME PARTS OF THAT TOWN
WON'T EVER RECOVER.
I DON'T KNOW WHETHER WE'LL BE
ABLE TO GO BACK HOME AGAIN.
BUT IF WE DO, IT SHOULD BE
A JOYFUL THING, RIGHT?
FOR BOTH OF US AND THE ONES
WHO WERE ALREADY HERE.
WE CAN WAIT TO MAKE
THAT HAPPEN CAN'T WE?!
(GASP)
IT'S OKAY TO MAKE THE DIFFICULT
CHOICE, WE'RE WITH YOU.
IF YOU CAN'T DO TWO THINGS AT
ONCE, DON'T. DO WHAT YOU CAN.
[MINORI] KNOWING WHO WE CAN
REALLY HELP ISN'T EASY...
BUT WE'RE NOT GONNA LET YOU
DO IT YOURSELF, MASTER.
WE'RE GONNA HELP YOU, ALL OF US,
BUT YOU HAVE TO LET US!
PLEASE, MASTER!
HUH?
SO WHADDYA SAY?
(CHUCKLING)
SHIROE‐ECCHI.
BUT STILL...
[AKATSUKI]
DON'T WORRY.
I GUARANTEE MY LORD
WILL BE JUST FINE.
[SHIROE]
AKATSUKI...
HMPH.
(PING)
[RIEZE] YES, IT'S ME.
[WOODSTOCK, VOICE CHAT]
OH, THANK GOODNESS YOU'RE SAFE.
THE TELEPATHIC LINK
WASN'T WORKING,
SO I GOT WORRIED
AND CAME TO SEE‐
HMM? HANG ON A SECOND!
THERE'S SOMEONE IN
FRONT OF THE ANTENNA!
HE'S TOO FAR AWAY TO
SEE HIS STATUS BAR.
BUT I'VE GOT MY GUESS.
[RIEZE]
UNDERSTOOD. MR. WOODSTOCK,
PLEASE RETURN TO AKIHABARA AND
DO WHAT YOU CAN TO STRENGTHEN
OUR DEFENSES.
[SOJIRO]
A RAID BOSS...
[ISAMI] HE WASN'T THERE WHEN
WE INVESTIGATED BEFORE, RIGHT?
[NAZNA] MAYBE HE DOESN'T GO INTO
ACTION UNTIL THE MOON COMES UP?
[OLIVE]
HE CONTROLS THE MOTHS?
[KURINON]
UGH, I HATE HIM ALREADY.
[MARIELLE] WE NEED TO FOCUS
ON DEFEATING THAT JERK!
[TETORA] THEN MAYBE
THE MOTH'LL FLY BACK
TO WHERE THEY CAME FROM!
[NYANTA] YOU REALLY
THINK THESE CATS ARE GONNA
MAKE IT THAT EASY?
MAYBE, A LOT OF THINGS
AROUND HERE STILL ACT
LIKE THE GAME IN
THE WEIRDEST WAYS.
[SHIROE]
THANK YOU, HENRIETTA.
[HENRIETTA] UH? YOU'RE VERY
WELCOME, MASTER SHIROE.
[SHIROE]
THE ANTENNA, MAGIC POINTS,
AND A RAID BOSS, HUH?
[NYANTA]
YEAH...
[NAOTSUGU] MM‐HM.
[TETORA]
AH!
(PLEASED)
[RIEZE] EVERYONE, WE'RE
DOWN TO 34 MINUTES,
THAT'S NOT A LOT OF
TIME FOR US TO...
[SHIROE] IT'S MORE THAN
WE'LL NEED. [RIEZE] HUH?!
[SHIROE] I WAS TRYING TO CHOOSE
BETWEEN THIS WORLD
AND THE ANTENNA TO
GET US BACK HOME.
AND ULTIMATELY, THAT'S
AN IMPOSSIBLE CHOICE.
SERIOUSLY. TRYING TO PICK ONE
OVER THE OTHER WOULD
BE AN ACT OF FUTILITY.
SO WE DON'T MAKE THAT CHOICE!
WE'LL JUST TEAR OUR WAY
THROUGH EVERYTHING
THAT TRIES TO STOP US,
YOU GOT IT?!
WE DON'T HAVE TO DECIDE,
BECAUSE WE'RE TAKING THEM BOTH!
THE ANTENNA AND THIS WORLD.
MPH.
[SHIROE]
WE CAN DO IT.
WE'LL GET WHAT WE WANT AND
DO IT ON OUR TERMS.
[AKATSUKI, VOICEOVER]
THE COUNTERATTACK HAS BEGUN.
HIS GLASSES GLEAM. HIS
STRATEGIZING, INGENIOUS.
WITH HIS TRUSTWORTHY
COMRADES AT HIS SIDE,
THERE IS NO MORE WAVERING.
SHIROE WILL PROTECT IT ALL.
IT'S THE ONLY ANSWER.
THE BATTLE TAKES SHIROE
TO A FINAL DESTINATION,
WHERE HE RESOLVES TO
TAKE ON A NEW QUEST...
[SHIROE]
THE HORIZON IS NOT THE LIMIT!