[WILLIAM] WHAT IS THIS? A QUEST
THAT'S NOT MEANT TO BE BEATEN?
(EXHALE)
(GRUNTS AND GROANS)
[WILLIAM, THINKING]
WE LOST...
(EXHALE)
[WILLIAM, THINKING]
WE WERE COMPLETELY DESTROYED!
YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME...
I DON'T UNDERSTAND...
I'VE NEVER HEARD OF THREE
RAID BOSSES AT ONCE.
THAT WAS INSANE...
WHAT HAPPENED
BACK THERE ANYWAY?
[PIANISSISSIMO]
D‐DO YOU THINK...
THAT THAT'S ONLY
IN THIS RAID ZONE?
HMMM...
THAT'S A GOOD
QUESTION...
WE'RE IN REAL TROUBLE IF ALL
THE RAID ZONES ARE LIKE THIS.
[ENKARTANTO] WE'RE NOT GONNA BE
ABLE TO GET VERY FAR, ARE WE?
[BOLOGNESE MASTER] I DON'T
THINK WE'D EVER BEAT
ANOTHER ZONE AGAIN. WE'D HAVE
TO STICK TO LOWER RAIDS.
(SNIFFLING)
WE POURED OUR LIVES INTO
LEARNING HOW TO PLAY THIS GAME.
BUT EVERYTHING, ALL
THE HOURS OF TRAINING.
IT ALL SEEMS LIKE IT
WAS FOR NOTHING NOW.
[AZAREA]
WE HAD BEEN DOING SO WELL.
SEEMED LIKE WE NEVER LOST,
MADE ME FEEL LIKE WE
WERE ACTUALLY IMPROVING.
[ELTON DISKA] WELL I
HATE TO BREAK IT TO YOU,
BUT THE DAYS OF
EASY RAIDS ARE OVER.
(SNIFFLE)
(SIGH)
YOU GOT THAT RIGHT...
IT'S ALL A BIG WASTE OF
TIME NOW IF YOU ASK ME.
[PROMETHEUS] THE GAME'S GIVEN UP
ON US NOW THAT WE'RE HERE.
ELDER TALES... HAS ABANDONED US.
(WILLIAM GASPS)
[CLASSMATE A]
REALLY? A COMPUTER GAME?
[CLASSMATE B] IT'S LIKE YOU'RE
AN EXPERT AT WASTING YOUR LIFE.
[CLASSMATE D] SERIOUSLY, ARE YOU
COOPED UP AT HOME ALL THE TIME?
[CLASSMATE C] DO YOU DO ANYTHING
ELSE? CAN YOU DO ANYTHING ELSE?
[WILLIAM] GO TO HELL!
[CLASSMATE E] THAT'S WHY YOU
NEVER GET INVITED TO PARTIES.
[CLASSMATE F] YOU ACTUALLY
TALK TO YOUR COMPUTER? CREEPY!
[CLASSMATE G] WHY DON'T YOU TRY
DOING SOMETHING
THAT COULD ACTUALLY BE USEFUL
SOMEDAY?
[CLASSMATE H] WHO CARES,
JUST LEAVE HIM ALONE.
SOME PEOPLE WERE JUST
BORN TO BE LOSERS.
[WILLIAM]
SHUT UP!
[JUNZO] HUH?
[BOLOGNESE MASTER] HM?
[WILLIAM]
UH...
[WILLIAM, THINKING]
WHAT THE HELL DO I TELL THEM?
[ALT WILLIAM] "WE'LL DO IT
NEXT TIME, SO LET'S GET 'EM!"
"I'M SURE THE OTHER
RAID ZONES ARE FINE!"
[WILLIAM, THINKING] I CAN'T TELL
THEM SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
I DON'T EVEN BELIEVE IT MYSELF.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT DOES IT MEAN?
[FEDERICO] IS THIS IT? IS THIS
AS FAR AS WE GO?
[WILLIAM, THINKING] DOES THIS...
ARE WE...?
[WILLIAM]
UH...?
(EXHALE)
(BREATH)
HMM. GUESS IT'S TIME
TO GO ON BACK HOME...
AND GET BACK TO OUR JOBS OF
KEEPING THE PEACE IN SUSUKINO.
PROBABLY, MIGHT ACTUALLY
HAVE FUN BACK THERE.
EZZO HAS MORE THAN ITS
FAIR SHARE OF MONSTERS.
PEOPLE OF THE LAND
APPRECIATE OUR PRESENCE.
YEAH, I'VE BEEN TRYING TO
FIND A GIRLFRIEND ANYWAY.
PROBABLY THE SMARTER WAY TO
LIVE THAN DOING THIS EVERYDAY.
MAYBE THEY'RE RIGHT.
[WILLIAM, THINKING] BUT IF WE
DID THAT.
THEN WE'RE NO DIFFERENT
THAN EVERYONE ELSE!
WE'D BE TAKING THE EASY ROAD...
OFFERING NOTHING BUT CORDIAL
COMPANY AND A LITTLE SHALLOW
"VALUABLE" ADVICE.
YOU MIGHT BE RIGHT...
[ALL] MM?
IN FACT YOU'RE
ABSOLUTELY RIGHT...
BUT YOU WANNA KNOW WHAT
I THINK ABOUT IT? IT'S BULLSHIT!
HUH?
ARE YOU OKAY?
WE JUST GOT OUR BUTTS
KICKED... WE LOST ONE.
MAYBE WE SHOULD ALL JUST
QUIT, MAYBE WE'RE WASHED UP.
IT COULD BE A BIG WASTE OF TIME.
IT'S WHAT WE'VE ALWAYS
BEEN TOLD, RIGHT?!
I GUESS ALL THOSE PEOPLE KNEW
WHAT THEY WERE TALKING ABOUT.
WE'RE A BUNCH OF GAME JUNKIES
LOCKED IN OUR ROOMS,
ADDICTED TO WASTING TIME.
AND SO WHAT IF WE ARE, GUYS?!
I MEAN IT'S NOT LIKE WE
DIDN'T ALREADY KNOW IT!
WE ALL KNEW EXACTLY WHO
WE WERE AND STILL.
WE KEPT LOGGING BACK IN.
WE ALL DID THE SAME THING.
[ALT WILLIAM] IF THEY
WANNA QUIT, SO BE IT.
BUT I WILL NOT STOP!
I'M NOT BACKING DOWN
JUST BECAUSE
I GOT PUNCHED IN THE FACE!
[WILLIAM] I GET IT. WE LOST.
IT'S SOMETHING
THAT'S NEW FOR US.
BUT IT PROBABLY WON'T BE THE
LAST TIME!
THERE'S NO NEED TO START PACKING
IT IN AFTER ONE DEFEAT!
I MEAN, OUR WIN‐TO‐LOSS RATIO IS
WHAT COUNTS, RIGHT?
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS TAKE A LOOK ON
THE SERVER AND SEE
IT FOR YOURSELF.
YOU'RE GREAT AT THIS,
EVEN IF IT'S MEANT FOR KIDS!
[ALT WILLIAM]
IT'S MORE THAN THAT.
IT'S SOMETHING SPECIAL TO US.
[WILLIAM] I'M NOT SAYING GROW
UP AND GO BACK TO SUSUKINO...
I WON'T TELL YOU
SOMETHING LIKE THAT...
BECAUSE WE'RE ALL
THE SAME IN HERE.
LOOK WE ALL MIGHT FEEL LIKE
WE'RE WORTHLESS FOR
LOSING THIS QUEST...
BUT THERE'S NO WAY THAT'S GOING
TO KEEP ME FROM DOING IT AGAIN!
[ALT WILLIAM] FOR ME... THIS
IS THE CENTER OF MY UNIVERSE.
[PIANISSISSIMO] UH...
[WILLIAM] ARE WE ALL JUST
BITS AND BYTES OF WORTHLESS
INFORMATION ON SOME SERVER NOW?
I DON'T THINK SO!
BECAUSE YOU'RE HERE!
AND YOU'RE WORTH
SOMETHING. ALL OF YOU!
YOU MIGHT FEEL LOST
AND STUCK IN HERE...
BUT I'M THAT YOU'RE WITH ME!
THE IDIOTS OUT THERE TOLD YOU
THAT GAMES WERE WORTHLESS.
WELL I'M TELLING YOU,
THAT THEY WERE WRONG!
NEVER ALLOW SOMEONE WHO
DOESN'T UNDERSTAND YOU
TELL YOU WHAT TO DO!
I MIGHT LOOK A LITTLE
RIDICULOUS RIGHT NOW.
JUST SOME SHUT‐IN
PLAYING A SILLY GAME!
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT? IF IT'S
SOMETHING THAT INSPIRES ME,
AND DRIVES ME ‐ WHAT'S
WRONG WITH THAT?!
IT'S MY CHOICE! AND
THAT'S ALL THAT MATTERS.
ALL OF US DECIDED WE
WANTED TO BE HERE!
[ALT WILLIAM]
I DON'T CARE WHO YOU ARE,
I WON'T LET ANYONE
MAKE LIGHT OF THAT!
[WILLIAM] JUST LOOK
AT ALL THE TIME
WE'VE INVESTED IN ELDER TALES.
SERIOUSLY, IT WAS A WHOLE
HELL OF A LOT OF TIME.
WHEN A RAID BOSS SHOWED HIS
FACE... WE'D GRAB OUR WEAPONS
AND LAY A BEATING ON HIM!
WE COULDN'T BE STOPPED!
AND YEAH! WE GOT ALL EXCITED
AND SOUNDED LIKE A
BUNCH OF GIDDY KIDS!
SURE, MAYBE IT WAS NOTHING BUT
A BUNCH OF ONES AND ZEROES
ON A COMPUTER SOMEWHERE
MILES AWAY.
BUT SINCE THE BEGINNING, WE
LOVED IT. AND SOMETIMES WE WON,
AND SOMETIMES WE LOST.
BUT WE CAME BACK EITHER WAY.
SO WHAT IF WE'VE ACTUALLY LET
THIS GAME CONSUME US...?
EVERY MINUTE'S BEEN
WORTH IT, RIGHT?!
YES. WINNING IS THE BEST
PART. WE'D CELEBRATE,
SPLIT UP ALL THE EPIC ITEMS
AND TOAST OUR VICTORY.
AND WHEN WE LOST, WE'D
PICK OURSELVES UP,
HAVE AN EVALUATION MEETING AND
TRY TO FIND A BETTER WAY.
IF YOU WANNA SIT THERE AND
TELL ME IT'S A WASTE OF TIME.
GO RIGHT AHEAD, LIKE I
SAID THIS IS YOUR CHOICE.
BUT I DON'T CARE IF
IT'S A GAME ANYMORE!
AND IF WE DO PUT OUR
TIME INTO THIS PLACE...
THEN WE MAKE IT WORTH IT!
(EXHALES)
[ALT WILLIAM]
OKAY, WE LOST.
AND FOR SILVER SWORD,
WINNING RAIDS
WAS LIKE DOING SOMETHING SACRED.
SO WHAT DO I DO NOW?
WHAT... WHAT ELSE
DO I TELL THEM?
WHAT ELSE CAN I SAY?
WHAT I MEAN, IS THAT
WE'RE NOT LIKE THEM.
AREN'T WE ALL THE SAME HERE!
IT'S JUST US, I
REALLY DON'T CARE
ABOUT ANYONE ELSE AT THIS POINT!
[ALT WILLIAM] HEY GET IT
TOGETHER! WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
[WILLIAM] UH. I JUST MEAN
I KNOW IT'S EASIER
TO GIVE UP AND MOVE ON!
AND YOU'RE ALL FREE
TO DO JUST THAT.
SO THEN WHY AM I GOING
OFF LIKE THIS ANYWAY...?
[ALT WILLIAM] YES, WILLIAM.
WHAT'S THE POINT HERE?
[WILLIAM] SO, LOOK, IT'S
LIKE THIS! I DON'T KNOW!
[ALT WILLIAM]
YOU GOT THAT RIGHT.
DO IT FOR YOU!
ANYTHING THAT HELPS YOU MAKE A
FRIEND
HAS GOTTEN BE WORTH SOMETHING!
[ALT WILLIAM] I GUESS, THIS IS
REALLY ALL I CAN TELL THEM.
[WILLIAM] IT'S FINE IF
IT'S YOUR GOOD LOOKS.
OR IF YOU'RE CLEVER OR SMART.
YOU'RE THE LIFE‐OF‐THE‐PARTY,
OR MAYBE
YOU'VE GOT A GOOD
SENSE OF HUMOR.
BUT I'VE GOTTA ASK YOU THIS:
DID YOU REALLY HAVE ALL THOSE
THINGS IN YOUR PERSONALITY
WHEN WE WERE IN REAL LIFE?
I KNOW I DIDN'T. AND I ADMIT
IT! I WAS VERY AWKWARD!
[WILLIAM] LOOK, YOU GUYS...
[DINKURON] AH...
[WILLIAM] I KNOW I'VE NEVER SAID
THIS BEFORE...
COULDN'T BRING MYSELF TO...
BUT YOU GUYS ARE
ALL MY FRIENDS.
[PIANISSISSIMO]
HUH?
[WILLIAM]
AND YOU KNOW WHAT...
WITHOUT THE GAME, I
WOULDN'T HAVE ANY FRIENDS.
I'M JUST A NOBODY. I'M A LOSER!
I JUST... I JUST HID MYSELF
AWAY AND LIVED INSIDE A GAME.
NOT EVEN SURE WHY.
I GUESS I JUST NEEDED A
PLACE TO HEAL OR SOMETHING.
AND INSIDE THE GAME, I'D SAY
I FOUND THAT.
THERE'S A WAY TO FALL
BACK AND GET HELP.
AND A WAY TO HELP OTHERS.
I FOUND A GUY WHO THOUGHT HE
BELONGS ON THE FRONT LINES,
BUT DIDN'T HAVE TO STAY THERE.
INSTEAD HE LEANED ANOTHER
WAY TO BE VALUABLE.
HE MAY HAVE BEEN
QUIET AND RESERVED,
AND DIDN'T GET ALL
THE ATTENTION HE WANTED.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
TURNED OUT HE WAS THE ONE HIS
FRIENDS COULD ALWAYS COUNT ON.
HE WAS TERRIFIED, BUT
HE DIDN'T LET IT SHOW.
HE'S DEAD TIRED FROM DAILY LIFE,
BUT HE MADE IT
A POINT TO LOG IN EVERY SINGLE
DAY. I SEE IT! I REALLY DO!
I MEAN IT. AND THAT'S
WHAT THIS IS ALL ABOUT.
[WILLIAM, THINKING]
YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
THIS GAME HAS TAUGHT ME A
LOT ABOUT PEOPLE. AND MYSELF.
I HEARD IT ALL IN THE OUTSIDE
WORLD. "YOU JUST DON'T GET IT."
"YOU'RE SELF‐RIGHTEOUS."
"YOU'RE INCONSIDERATE."
"YOU'RE A LOUSY TEAM PLAYER."
"YOU DON'T HAVE ANY PATIENCE."
"YOU CAN'T TAKE A HINT."
"YOU DON'T BELONG ANYWHERE."
YOU CAN ONLY HEAR SO MUCH OF
THAT OVER AND OVER
BEFORE YOU JUST SHUT EVERYONE
OUT OF YOUR EXISTENCE.
ELDER TALES WAS DIFFERENT.
IT WAS A PLACE WHERE, SOMEHOW,
I ACTUALLY STARTED
FEELING CONNECTED.
I CHERISHED THOSE BONDS WITH
EVERY OUNCE OF MY BEING.
AND IN RETURN, MY NEW FRIENDS
SHARED SO MANY SECRETS WITH ME!
THE FIRST THING I LEARNED WAS
TEAMWORK.
THERE WERE A FEW PEOPLE
I WORKED WELL WITH,
BUT OTHERS, NOT SO MUCH.
SOME PLAYERS GOT IT,
AND OTHER JUST DIDN'T.
BUT LEARNING HOW TO WORK
WITH OTHERS WAS THE
BEST REWARD OF ALL.
I SOON FIGURED OUT THE SOME
PARTNERSHIPS DIDN'T WORK OUT,
ONLY BECAUSE THEY DIDN'T
KNOW WHAT I WAS AFTER.
AND THEN, I FINALLY
STARTED RAIDING.
AND BEFORE YOU KNOW IT,
I BECAME A GUILD MASTER.
NEXT I LEARNED THAT
OUR WIN/LOSS RATIO
MAGICALLY INCREASED ON
NIGHTS WE WERE ALL HYPED UP.
SOMETIMES ABOUT LITTLE
STUPID THINGS.
SOME PARTY MEMBERS PLAYED
FEELING GREAT, AND OTHERS LOUSY.
I MEAN, WE ALL HAD OUR OWN
PERSONAL PROBLEMS
GOING ON IN THE REAL WORLD.
I QUICKLY REALIZED THAT EVERYONE
IN MY GUILD WAS JUST LIKE ME.
I STARTED ASKING THEM ABOUT
THEIR LIVES AND
WHAT THEY WANTED FROM
ME AS THE LEADER.
I FINALLY LEARNED PATIENCE, AND
HOW TO ASK THE RIGHT QUESTIONS.
IT'S REALLY AN ART
FORM, YOU KNOW?
AND, AFTER A WHILE, EVERYONE
STARTED
TO PUT UP WITH MY SHORT FUSE.
MOST RAID GUILDS
DON'T LAST VERY LONG.
EVERY RAID WILL COME ACROSS
SOMETHING THAT EVERYONE WANTS,
AND NOT EVERYONE GETS TO HAVE
IT.
ESPECIALLY IF THERE'S
ONLY ONE ITEM.
PEOPLE IN YOUR
PARTY FEEL CHEATED,
AND THEY LET YOU KNOW ABOUT IT.
EVERYONE GETS TICKED
AT EACH OTHER
AND EVENTUALLY IT
ALL BREAKS APART.
BUT SOMEHOW, WE MANAGED
TO ALWAYS WORK IT OUT.
I TRIED TO BE COMPLETELY OPEN
WITH MY GUILDMATES
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
THEY FORGAVE ME FOR GETTING
PISSED OFF ALL THE TIME
AND STARTED TO TRUST ME.
AND THE WORD OF OUR GUILD GREW,
AND IT WASN'T LONG BEFORE
EVERYONE KNEW WE WERE A
FORCE TO BE RECKONED WITH.
EVERYONE IN ELDER TALES
KNEW THE NAME SILVER SWORD.
[WILLIAM] I MEAN COME ON. I KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
IT'S NOT THAT HARD
TO FIGURE OUT.
YOU THINK THIS IS IT,
DON'T YOU? GAME OVER!
ADMIT IT. YOU'D RATHER
JUST GO BACK HOME
AND FORGET THIS EVER HAPPENED.
AND YEAH WELL MAYBE
THAT IS AN OPTION!
BUT I LIKE BEING HERE!
[ORDISSO] HUH?
AND I KNOW THAT AT LEAST A FEW
OF YOU ENJOY THIS TOO.
WE ALL ENDED UP IN THIS PLACE
BECAUSE WE LOVED THE GAME.
I MEAN. IS IT REALLY SO
BAD THAT WE'RE HERE?
THIS IS THE WORLD
OF ELDER TALES!
WE OBSESSED OVER IT DAY AND
NIGHT AND NOW WE'RE HERE!
THIS IS THE WORLD WHERE
WE ARE AT OUR BEST!
YOU CAN'T TELL ME THIS
ISN'T A BLESSING!
[DINKURON]
WILLIAM!
[ELTON DISKA]
GUILD MASTER!
[WILLIAM]
HUH?
HEY...
[WILLIAM, VOICEOVER] THE THING
THAT MADE ME THE HAPPIEST...
WAS SEEING THAT EVERYONE
ELSE WAS IN HERE WITH ME.
YOU GUYS... YOU'RE
JUST LIKE I IMAGINED!
AND I HOPE I'M THE SAME TO YOU.
MAYBE THAT'S BESIDES
THE POINT...
BUT I'M JUST GLAD WE
COULD DO THIS TOGETHER!
AND THERE'S NO ONE TO TELL US
WE'RE LOSERS HERE, RIGHT?
BUT NOW, WE WILL... WE WILL BE
A BUNCH OF LOSERS IF WE LEAVE!
MAYBE WE CAN'T WIN!
MAYBE THIS IS IMPOSSIBLE
THE ODDS ARE
DEFINITELY AGAINST US!
BUT WHO CARES?
WHO CARES IF WE LOSE AGAIN!
CAN YOU LOOK YOURSELF IN THE
MIRROR IF YOU DON'T TRY?!
WHAT DO YOU THINK WE'LL BE DOING
IF WE JUST GO BACK, HUH?
WHAT'S LEFT FOR US?!
TAKE THIS AWAY, AND
WHAT DO WE HAVE LEFT?
I PLAYED ELDER TALES SO MUCH
THAT EVERYONE THOUGHT
I WAS A FREAK.
I'VE GIVEN TWO YEARS OF
MY LIFE TO THIS PLACE!
I COULDN'T THINK OF ANYTHING
ELSE WHENEVER I PLAYED IT!
WHEN I ATE, SLEPT, AND BATHED,
MY HEAD WAS IN THE GAME!
EVERY SINGLE THING
I DID IN LIFE!
EVERYTHING I DID WAS
FOR ELDER TALES!
[ENKARTANTO] YEAH. SAME HERE.
[VOINEN] MM‐HM...
[WILLIAM] YOU CAN CALL
ME CRAZY IF YOU WANT...
THAT'S FINE.
I'M USED TO THAT!
YEAH, I'M A GAMER DORK WHO
SPENDS HIS NIGHT WITH FRIENDS
HE'S NEVER EVEN SEEN TO
WIN SOME IMAGINARY PRIZES!
BUT I'M GOING TO DO
IT THE BEST I CAN!
SO I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE...
I'M GOING TO TURN AND RUN AWAY
FROM AN EXTRA RAID BOSS OR TWO.
WHERE WOULD I GO IF I
DIDN'T TAKE THIS ON?
WHO WOULD I BE IF
I WERE TO SCOFF AT
ALL THIS LIKE THE
JERKS BACK HOME?
SO IF YOU CHOOSE TO WALK AWAY...
THEN YOU WILL JOIN
THE VERY PEOPLE
THAT LAUGHED AT US
AND PUT US DOWN.
AND THEN I SAY
THE HELL WITH YOU!
[DEMICAS]
YOU GUYS ARE A BUNCHA MORONS!
[ALL] HUH?
[DEMICAS] LISTEN TO YOU.
YOU JUST WANNA KEEP
ON GETTING KILLED.
HEY I LIKE A GOOD FIGHT, BUT
ENOUGH IS ENOUGH YOU KNOW?
WHAT'RE YOU SAYING?
I'D BE RIGHT BEHIND YOU
IF WE STOOD A CHANCE...
BUT WE'RE GONNA GET
CREAMED IN THERE AGAIN.
AT THE END OF THE DAY ALL WE'RE
DOING
IS PLAYING SOME KIND OF GAME!
AND THE RULES ARE
STARTING TO CHANGE.
FACE IT, MAN! WE'RE
ALL A BUNCH OF
CLUELESS AMATEURS
AGAINST THIS THING.
WE'RE BANGING OUR HEADS
AGAINST THE WALL. WE'RE LOST!
AND YOU JUST WANT US TO KEEP
AT IT. TO KEEP GOING BACK?!
[WILLIAM] WELL I... I
HAVE RUN FROM SOMETHING.
[WILLIAM] AND IT'S
BEEN BOTHERING ME.
IT WASN'T LONG AGO.
AT THE FIRST ROUND TABLE, I
RAN AWAY FROM HELPING THE CITY.
I WAS MORE INTERESTED IN MY
OWN PLANS.
I WANTED TO COMPLETE THE RAIDS I
HADN'T DONE YET. PRETTY SELFISH.
GOD, IT WAS SO STUPID!
AND SHORT SIGHTED!
HEH! WHAT A WASTE!
I THOUGHT I HAD
BETTER THINGS TO DO!
I HAD CONVINCED MYSELF THAT
THEY WERE THE ONES FIGHTING A
LOST CAUSE
AND THEY WERE A BUNCH
OF IDIOTS FOR TAKING IT ON!
I'D BE LYING IF I SAID I DIDN'T
LOOK DOWN MY NOSE AT THEM.
SOUNDS FAMILIAR, RIGHT?
IT'S NOT EASY TO ADMIT.
I HAD LOST WHO I WAS
AND BETRAYED MYSELF.
I HAD BECOME THE VERY
THING I HATE SO MUCH.
[ALT WILLIAM] BUT I REMEMBER,
THERE WAS SOMEONE
WHO NEVER RAN AWAY.
I... I HAD ALWAYS ADMIRED HIM.
THERE WAS A LEGENDARY PARTY
THAT COMPETED
WITH MAJOR GUILDS ON
HIGH‐LEVEL QUESTS,
BUT NEVER FORMED A
GUILD OF THEIR OWN.
THEY REFERRED TO THEMSELVES AS
THE DEBAUCHERY TEA PARTY.
I ALWAYS LOOKED FORWARD TO
SEEING WHAT THEY WOULD DO NEXT!
AND I TOLD MYSELF THAT I
WOULD JOIN THEM SOMEDAY!
BUT THEN, THEY BROKE UP
BEFORE I HIT LEVEL 90.
AND INSTEAD OF MAKING
GUILDS OF THEIR OWN,
THEY JUST WENT THEIR
SEPARATE WAYS.
I MEAN, IT WAS CRAZY, RIGHT?
YOU'RE OUT THERE AND
BETTER THAN EVERYBODY.
YOU GET EVERYONE
TALKING ABOUT YOU
AND THEN YOU JUST DISAPPEAR?!
YOU KNOW WHAT... TO BE HONEST...
I DIDN'T THINK THE ROUND TABLE
WAS EVER GOING TO WORK!
BUT SHIROE MADE IT HAPPEN, LIKE
HE DID THE TEA PARTY.
BUT INSTEAD OF BEATING BOSSES,
HE CREATED A CITY! AND IT'S
NOTHING SHORT OF A MIRACLE.
[ALT WILLIAM] SHIROE TOOK
CONTROL AND
MADE THE IMPOSSIBLE POSSIBLE.
I ADMIRE HIM FOR THAT. IT'S
WHY I FOLLOWED HIM OUT HERE!
[WILLIAM] ALL OF YOU WERE THERE
WHEN HE ASKED US
TO COME WITH HIM...
I WAS ACTUALLY FLATTERED
THAT HE ASKED ME!
WE MIGHT NOT HAVE A
CHANCE OF WINNING THIS...
BUT I WILL TRY AS LONG AS THE
VILLAIN IN GLASSES NEEDS ME!
I WILL BE READY TO SUIT
UP AND ENJOY THE RIDE!
LOOK, WE ALL KNOW THIS GUY IS AS
SADISTIC AND CRAZY AS THEY COME!
AND YET, WE ALL
JOINED HIM ANYWAY.
BECAUSE WE KNEW IT'D BE
FUN AND THAT WE COULD WIN!
YOU KNOW WHY?! WE'RE GAMERS!
AND SHIROE HAS FAITH IN US!
MPH!
WHAT'RE WE WAITING FOR?
HUH?
LET'S DO IT, THOSE BOSSES
NEED A GOOD BEATING!
EH?
MMM!
UH?
HMMM!
MPH...
MPH.
MMM...
EH...
(GRUNT)
EH!
HMM...
(GRUNT)
MPH...
HMPH...
(GRUNTS)
HMMM...
MHMMMM...
HMPH...
[WILLIAM, THINKING]
YEAH, OKAY, I WAS STUPID.
BUT I'M READY TO GO BACK IN
THERE
AND TAKE THESE BOSSES DOWN.
AND MOST OF ALL.
I WANT TO WIN.
AND I WANT TO DO IT WITH
MY FRIENDS, MY FAMILY.
[DEMICAS]
GUILD MASTER... (SCOFFS)
[NAOTSUGU] HEY, SHIROE!
YOU DONE SNOOZIN'?
[SHIROE] UH... HUH?
MM‐HM.
UH...?
(SHAKY HUMMING AND GIGGLES)
[SHIROE]
UH...
[NAOTSUGU] SILVER SWORD'S A HELL
OF A GUILD, AREN'T THEY?
[SHIROE]
YEAH...
[SHIROE, THINKING]
SERIOUSLY...
COULD I PULL OFF
SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
IF MINORI AND TOYA WERE SAD...?
IF ISUZU AND RUDY
WERE CRYING...?
IF IT CAME DOWN TO IT, I
DON'T KNOW IF I COULD FIND
THE WORDS TO TELL THEM WHAT
I'M REALLY FEELING...
WHAT IF AKATSUKI‐‐
DON'T WASTE TIME
WORRYING ABOUT ME.
I'M PROTECTING YOU, REMEMBER?!
MPH...
[TETORA] I WANNA HELP THEM WIN.
[SHIROE] UH...
[TETORA]
WELL? DON'T YOU, TOO?
[NAOTSUGU] I COULDN'T HAVE
SAID IT BETTER MYSELF!
YEAH, IT'S EASY FOR
A STARLET, YOU KNOW?
(EXHALE)
[NAOTSUGU] HMM? SO...
YOU GOT SOMETHING BREWING IN
THAT NOGGIN? MASTERMIND?
THERE IS SOMETHING I NEED TO
TELL YOU ABOUT, NAOTSUGU.
[NAOTSUGU] HUH?
[SHIROE] YOU TOO, TETORA.
[TETORA] HUH?
[SHIROE] AND I NEED TO TELL
SILVER SWORD AS WELL.
I SHOULD HAVE TOLD ALL OF YOU
WHY WE NEED TO FINISH THIS RAID,
WHAT THE ACTUAL PAYOFF IS,
AND WHY I NEED TO
GET MY HANDS ON
SUCH A HUGE STOCKPILE OF GOLD.
INSTEAD, I TOOK ADVANTAGE OF
EVERYONE'S TRUST IN ME.
YOU FOLLOWED ME, YET I
TRIED TO DO IT WITHOUT YOU.
IF YOU'RE WILLING TO FORGIVE
ME...
I THINK I HAVE ANOTHER IDEA...
AND IT MIGHT JUST GIVE
US A BETTER CHANCE.
[TETORA]
HOW MUCH BETTER?
[NAOTSUGU]
UH...
FIFTEEN PERCENT.
[NAOTSUGU] SO YOU'RE
SAYIN' THERE'S A CHANCE!
WORKS FOR ME!
AND LASTLY,
I'LL NEED TO TALK TO
KINJO AND HIS TRIBE...
ABOUT OUR REQUEST AND
ALL OF YAMATO'S LAND.
NEXT TIME,
I WILL LOOK HIM STRAIGHT IN THE
EYE AND TELL HIM WHAT WE NEED!
[NAOTSUGU] TOTALLY, I'LL TRY AND
MAKE IT BACK AS QUICK AS I CAN.
[MARIELLE, VOICE CHAT] I CAN'T
WAIT TO SEE YOU! I'LL HAVE
OZONI CHICKEN SOUP WAITING FOR
YOU. [TETORA] NAOTSUGU COME ON!
[NAOTSUGU]
WELL THAT'S QUITE AN INCENTIVE!
[SHIROE]
IT'S BEEN A WEEK, WE'RE ALL SET.
IT'S OUR LAST BATTLE OUT HERE.
MAYBE WE'LL HOLD OFF ON
THE NEW YEAR'S NOODLES THEN!
[SHIROE] (EXHALES) LET
THE CHIEF KNOW THAT
I'LL DEFINITELY BE
BACK BY THE SEVENTH.
I'VE ALSO GOT A FEW THINGS I'D
LIKE TO SHARE WITH EVERYONE.
THAT'S GOOD... MY LORD,
I'LL BE WAITING FOR YOU.
MM‐HM. I PROMISE, OKAY?
I'M COMING HOME...
HM?
[WILLIAM]
ALL RIGHT!
THERE'S NOTHING TO STOP US.
LET'S PLANT OUR BANNER,
AND CLAIM THIS ZONE AS OUR OWN!
(CHEER)
[SHIROE, THINKING] THAT'S RIGHT,
WE ARE GOING TO MAKE
IT HOME THIS TIME...
AND I MEAN, ALL THE WAY HOME!
[AKATSUKI]
1, 2, 3, 4...
THE COUNT STARTS AGAIN.
FOR THE THREE RAID BOSSES.
THE PLAYERS ARE READY WITH
WEAPONS IN HAND,
A MENTAL IMAGE OF THE MAP AND
THE PLAN BURNED
INTO THEIR MEMORY.
THE CHANCE OF SUCCESS
IS ONLY 15%,
BUT COMRADES‐IN‐ARMS ARE
FIGHTING AT THEIR SIDES.
[SHIROE]
STAND UP, ONE MORE TIME!