[AKATSUKI] THE RAID BOSS IS ON
THE OTHER SIDE OF THAT DOOR.
[NAOTSUGU]
SURE LOOKS THAT WAY.
YOU GO AHEAD AND
WAIT HERE, OLD TIMER.
YEAH, WE'VE GOT A JOB FOR
YOU ONCE WE'RE DONE..
[REGAN] YES. I'LL EAGERLY
AWAIT YOUR RETURN.
[RIEZE] MOONRISE IN...
FIFTEEN PLUS THIRTY‐TWO!
ALRIGHT GUYS, LET'S GO!
[TARICTON]
SO YOU'VE MADE IT THIS FAR.
PREPARE TO ENGAGE!
ALL PARTIES, FORMATION B!
GOT SOMETHIN' FOR YA, SHIROE!
SHIELD OTHER STANCE!
REACTIVE HEALING!
PURIFICATION WALL!
[SOJIRO]
DO IT, SHIROE!
[AKATSUKI]
MY LORD!
[SHIROE]
MANA CHANNELING!
[TARICTON]
HMM?
AN EMPATHIUM SURGE...!
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER] ETERNAL
MOTHS ARE CREATURES
THAT STEAL MAGIC POINTS.
SO I'M GONNA USE MANA CHANNELING
TO TAKE THE MAGIC POINTS FROM
ALL THE MEMBERS OF PARTY ONE
AND GIVE THEM AN EQUAL SHARE.
ALL THE SURPLUS MAGIC POINTS
SHOULD ACT LIKE A BEACON
TO THE MOTHS. AND LEAVE THE
OTHER PARTIES FREE TO ATTACK.
[RICHO] THERE THEY GO.
SURE ARE A LOT OF THOSE THINGS
OUT THERE.
IT WOULDN'T BE A PROBLEM IF WE
WERE FACING JUST ONE AT A TIME.
THEY'VE BEEN BEATING
US USING SHEER NUMBERS
AND FORMATION STRENGTH.
[SERARA] MASTER SHIROE
AND PARTY ONE ARE
DRAWING THE MOTHS AWAY
FROM THE REST OF US...
[KURINON] AN ENCHANTER
DOING TAUNTS...?!
HE ISN'T GONNA
LIVE VERY LONG!
[ISAMI]
THEY'RE LINED UP SINGLE FILE!
[NYANTA] IT'S TIME TO WRECK
THESE FOOLS! YAHAA!
HAHHH! ROUND WINDMILL!
SHORYU, YOU'RE LIKE A MAD MAN!
[SHORYU] HOW ELSE AM I GONNA
CATCH UP TO HIM!? HWAH!
COMING, NAOTSUGU?!
[ISUZU]
MAESTRO ECHO!
[RUDY]
LIGHTENING NEBULA!
[RIEZE]
FREEZING LINER!
[YUZUKO]
COMPANION SUMMON, PHOENIX!
[NAOTSUGU]
EAT THAT, NERDS!
WE WENT AHEAD AND TOOK OUT MOST
OF THEIR FRONT LINE, NO SWEAT!
[TETORA] YOUR ARMOR ISN'T
STRONG ENOUGH TO STICK
YOUR NOSE IN BATTLE
LIKE THAT, OKAY?!
[SHIROE] LOOK I KNOW WHAT I'M
DOING, ALL RIGHT, TETORA?
PROMISE I'LL FIGURE IT OUT.
[MARIELLE] WE MIGHT NOT BE AS
GOOD AT AGGRO AS DEMICAS,
BUT WE'LL DO OUR BEST!
HUH?
INCOMING FROM FOUR O'CLOCK!
SIX MOON RABBITS!
[NAOTSUGU]
YOU GOT THIS, STUMPY?
[AKATSUKI] DON'T CALL ME
STUMPY, YOU MEAT HEAD!
[NAOTSUGU]
SHIELD SWING!
[AKATSUKI]
ACCELERATOR FANG!
[HIEN]
MAN LOOK AT HER GO!
A COMBINATION ATTACK?
[AKATSUKI]
MY LORD IS UNDER OUR PROTECTION!
(GIRLS SQUEALING)
(NAOTSUGU PANICKING)
[TETORA] OH! THROW ME NEXT!
THROW ME NEXT!
[KOZARU]
AKATSUKI'S COOL!
SHE'S EVEN TOUGHER THAN
THE LAST TIME I SAW HER!
[NAZNA]
YEAH, SHE IS!
[SOJIRO]
MM‐HM!
NOW THAT SHIROE'S FINALLY
GOTTEN SERIOUS,
IT'S ABOUT TIME I ADDED
SOMETHING TO THE PARTY.
SOLO DASH!
[NAZNA]
I'M FEELING GOOD TODAY, BABY!
ALRIGHT, SOJI! GET 'IM!
AH!
HYA!
HU! HA! AHHHH!
[HENRIETTA] THE RAID BOSS
CHANGED LOCATIONS!
[HENRIETTA] THE PARTY 2 ASSAULT
TEAM HAS ENGAGED THE ENEMY BOSS!
[NAOTSUGU]
FINALLY, THE HEAD HONCHO!
[SHIROE] LET'S PUSH OUR
WAY TO THE ROOF, YOU GUYS!
HUWU! AH.
[SHIROE]
SOJIRO!
[SOJIRO]
NICE WORK BACK THERE, SHIROE!
[NAZNA] FOR A MINUTE I THOUGHT
YOU WERE GONNA MISS IT!
[TETORA]
UGH, THAT'S HIM?!
[MARIELLE]
HERE WE GO!
[AKATSUKI] HIS NAME... IS
TARICTON, THE SUMMONER GENIUS.
AT LEVEL 86, HE'S RAID RANKED.
[RIEZE]
HIS LEVEL ISN'T ALL THAT HIGH...
BUT THE PROBLEM IS
WE'RE A MAKE‐SHIFT TEAM
OF DIFFERENT LEVELS WHO'VE
NEVER FOUGHT TOGETHER BEFORE.
AND SOJIRO'S TEAM GOT HIT WITH
A WIDE‐RANGE ATTACK ALREADY.
[SHIROE] I NEED YOU TO
HEAL THE ASSAULT TEAM!
PARTIES TWO AND FOUR FALL BACK!
[NAOTSUGU] ANCHOR HOWL!
[MINORI] SO THAT'S THE GENIUS...
[OLIVE] GAIA BEAT HEALING!
[RIEZE] WE'VE GOT NINE MINUTES
AND FORTY‐SEVEN SECONDS!
[TARICTON] IT'S TIME FOR YOU
TO SLEEP, MORTAL CHILDREN.
TELL ME! WHY'RE
YOU DOING THIS?!
[TARICTON] IT'S TIME FOR YOU
TO SLEEP, MORTAL CHILDREN.
[SHIROE] THERE MUST BE
SOMETHING YOU WANT!
[TARICTON] IT'S TIME FOR
YOU TO SLEEP, ADVENTURERS!
[SOJIRO]
HE'S JUST LIKE KAMAISARU.
[NAZNA] HE'S NOT GONNA
LISTEN TO ANYONE...
[NYANTA] HE WAS CREATED TO DEAL
WITH THE WORLD IN THIS WAY.
[MARIELLE] SHIROE, W‐WE
CAN'T HOLD OUT MUCH LONGER!
[NAOTSUGU]
WHAT DO WE DO, SHIROE?!
[SHIROE]
EVERYONE, TAKE HIM OUT! HUH?
[TARICTON] IT'S TIME FOR YOU
TO SLEEP, MORTAL CHILDREN.
ALL MORTALS MUST
EMBRACE YOUR SLUMBER!
IT'S TIME TO SLEEP!
[RIEZE] O‐OH NO!
[MINORI] WHAT IS THAT?
‐HERE THEY COME!
‐OKAY GUYS, GET READY. (YELLING)
[WILLIAM]
ALL PARTIES GET IN FORMATION!
THE MOON ISN'T UP YET, BUT
THEY'RE ALREADY OUT ANYWAY.
THEY SPRINKLE SCALE DUST
WITH A DIFFERENT EFFECT
ON THOSE WHO DON'T GO TO SLEEP,
SO WATCH OUT!
(GUT WRENCHING SCREAM)
[WILLIAM] HUH?
KEEP IT DOWN, DEMICAS!
YOU NEED TO GO...?
[DEMICAS] HWAH! HURRY THE HELL
UP AND GET THIS OVER WITH
SHIROE! COME ON LET'S GO!
(CHEERS) (COLLAPSE)
[KNIGHT]
AW YEAH! BRING IT ON!
[KAZUHIKO]
ODYSSEY KNIGHT IDIOTS!
DAMMIT, YOU'RE ONLY MAKING
THINGS MORE DIFFICULT FOR US!
[TARICTON] TIME FOR YOU TO
SLEEP, MORTAL CHILDREN!
TIME FOR YOU TO SLEEP!
[TOYA] SHIROE!
[RUDY] LOOK! IF WE LET
HIM KEEP DOING THIS,
THE ANTENNA IS GONNA BREAK
BEFORE WE EVEN GET A CHANCE
TO TALK TO ANYBODY!
WE GOTTA TAKE HIM DOWN!
ALRIGHT PARTY ONE! KEEP FIRING
AND KEEP YOUR AGGRO UP!
THEN LURE HIM AWAY,
DOWN TO THE HALL BELOW!
TWO, THREE, AND FOUR, ELIMINATE
THAT RAID MOB AND MEET US LATER!
[KURINON] IS THAT WHAT
HE'S TALKING ABOUT?!
[HIEN]
THAT'S A LONG WAY DOWN...
[NAOTSUGU]
ANGER EXCHANGE!
[SHIROE]
NOW! PARTY 1, TO THE HALL!
[TETORA]
LOOK AT ME!
I'M A SHOOTING STAR!
(MARIELLE SCREAMS)
[RICHO] WE'VE TAKEN DOWN 40
PERCENT OF HIS HIT POINTS.
[KUSHIYATAMA] MAYBE, BUT LOOK AT
HIS EVASION RATE. IT'S INSANE.
[TARICTON] SLEEP AND THEY SAFETY
IS GUARANTEED, CHILDREN.
WAVES TO WAVES,
PARTICLES TO PARTICLES...
OFFER UP THY SOULS TO ME.
THIS IS THE ONLY WAY TO
FIND SAFE PASSAGE HOME.
[SHIROE] SLEEP FROM THE ETERNAL
MOTH WILL DO THAT?
JUST WHAT DO YOUR
PEOPLE KNOW, EXACTLY?
[TARICTON] THOSE WHO OFFER THEIR
SOULS ACCEPT ACCESS,
AND SELECT STANDBY MODE
FOR THEIR ETERNAL SLEEP.
[MARIELLE]
THAT LIGHT, WE NEED TO GET AWAY!
[SOJIRO]
IT'S WIDE‐RANGE! INSTANT DEATH?!
[SHIROE]
MOVE IT!
(SCREAMING)
NYANTA!
WHAT IS THIS?!
DO WHAT HE SAID AND
STAY AWAY FROM IT!
[NAZNA]
CAREFUL, GUYS.
THIS IS THE ATTACK
THAT GOT US BEFORE!
[RIEZE] THERE'S NO EVADING IT,
AND IT TARGETS AT RANDOM?!
[TARICTON] GO TO SLEEP, AND MAKE
THY CHOICE, ADVENTURERS!
(YELLING)
(TARICTON GROWLING)
[NAOTSUGU] CRAP!
UWAH!
WAUGH!
[NAOTSUGU] THANKS
FOR THE SAVE, HOLMES!
[SOJIRO] JUST DOING MY DUTY!
[MINORI] ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
[KOZARU] SORRY 'BOUT THAT...
[SHIROE] MARIELLE, CAST REACTIVE
HEALING ON EVERYONE!
[MARIELLE] GOT IT!
[SHIROE] TETORA, NOW!
[TETORA] JUST LEAVE IT TO MOI!
I'M JUST GETTING STARTED!
HANG IN THERE,
I'VE GOTCHA COVERED.
AURORA HEAL!
[SHIROE] PARTIES ONE AND TWO,
HIT HIM WITH MAXIMUM DPS!
EVERYBODY ELSE, CAST BARRIERS
ON PARTIES ONE AND TWO.
[NAZNA] GOTCHA!
[ALL] ROGER THAT!
[RIEZE]
WHAT'S SHIROE TRYING TO DO?
(BATTLE GRUNTS)
[SHIROE] OKAY, GUYS, REMEMBER
TO RESTORE YOUR HIT POINTS
IMMEDIATELY AFTER YOUR ATTACKS!
[TARICTON] SLUMBER,
CHILDREN, I SAID GO TO SLEEP.
(BATTLE CONTINUES)
[SERARA] HE'S ONLY GOT ABOUT 30
PERCENT OF HIS HIT POINTS LEFT!
[TARICTON] EYAHHH! SLUMBER,
CHILDREN,
AND ENSURE SAFE PASSAGE TO THE
PLACE FROM WENCE YOU CAME.
HE'S REVVING UP TO
LAUNCH HIS ATTACK AGAIN!
(RIEZE GASPS) [RIEZE, THINKING]
IF I GET HIT NOW...!
[RIEZE] AH!
(MINORI GASPS)
[RIEZE]
OHH... HUH?
[RIEZE, THINKING] THE BARRIERS
AND REACTIVE HEALING
KEPT THEM FROM
GETTING HURT THIS TIME.
[RIEZE] YOU KNEW WHICH ONE OF
OUR PARTY MEMBERS WOULD GET HIT?
[SHIROE] LET'S JUST
SAY HE GAVE ME A HINT.
THE ATTACK DEAL
A PENETRATING BLOW
TO THE TOP FIVE ON
HIS AGGRO LIST.
[NAZNA]
WHILE IT'S WAITING TO RECAST,
IT SELECTIVELY ATTACKS THE
PLAYER WHO RACK UP THE MOST.
IT'S A PRETTY EFFECTIVE DEFENSE.
[RIEZE, THINKING]
HE'S IN THE MIDDLE OF A FIGHT,
AND HE MANAGED TO KEEP
TRACK OF ALL THE PLAYERS,
WHAT THEY CAST, AND
HOW HEALTHY THEY WERE?
HOW CAN HE KEEP TRACK OF IT ALL?
(SNARLS)
[SHIROE] PARTIES 3 AND 4,
ATTRACT ITS LIMBS!
PARTIES 1 AND 2
FOCUS ON THE BODY!
[RIEZE, THINKING] WE LOST FAR
FEWER MAGIC POINTS
THAN I
WOULD'VE EXPECTED.
(WOLF‐CHAN HOWLING)
(TARICTON GRUNTING)
[RIEZE, THINKING] SO THIS...
THIS IS THE TEA PARTY'S
LEGENDARY
MANA CONTROLLER AT HIS
FULL POTENTIAL...
THIS IS HIS FULL
CONTROL ENCOUNTER!
[TOYA]
WE GOT IT COVERED.
[RUDY] WE'VE GOT EVERYTHING
UNDER CONTROL,
WE'RE READY WHENEVER YOU ARE.
[ISUZU] YOU'RE CLEAR FOR
THE FINISHING BLOW.
DO IT MASTER!
[SHIROE] MINORI! TAKE CONTROL
OF PARTIES THREE AND FOUR!
[MINORI]
(GASP) RIGHT!
[RIEZE] (GIGGLE, GASP)
I THOUGHT I WAS SO GOOD AT THIS.
[HENRIETTA] ARE YOU OKAY, RIEZE?
[RIEZE] I WAS PRAISED
AS A STRATEGIST AND
THE CAPTAIN OF THE DEVELOPMENT
AND TRAINING SQUADRON,
BUT GOODNESS, I GUESS I DIDN'T
KNOW SO MUCH AFTER ALL!
MM‐HM.
[RIEZE]
IT'S ALL SO EXCITING!
I GUESS I SHOULD JOIN IN!
LAMINATION SYNTAX!
FROST SPEAR!
[TARICTON]
SLEEP, CHILDREN...
[BOTH] HYAHHH!
(GRUNTING)
[TARICTON] STANDBY MODE
IN PEACEFUL SAFETY...
[AKATSUKI] ON THE BEACH
WHERE I WALKED WITH MY LORD.
OUR MEMORIES, THEY WEREN'T
WEREN'T TAKEN AWAY FROM US.
WE GAVE THEM UP WILLINGLY!
SO WE COULD FACE THE WORLD
ONE MORE TIME!
SHATTERING BITS OF OUR PAST,
TO GET A GRASP OF THE FUTURE!
[TARICTON] YOU'RE NOTHING BUT
EMPTY VESSELS TO ME, CHILDREN!
[NAOTSUGU] ANCHOR HOWL!
[SHIROE, THINKING] WE'RE
RESILIENT. AND QUICK TO ADAPT.
WE RELISH THE CHANCE TO MAKE
SOMETHING FROM NOTHING.
SINGULARITY!
[SHIROE, THINKING]
I HAVE MY COMRADES,
AND A DEFINITE GOAL TO REACH!
[SHIROE]
NOW, INFINITY FORCE!
[NAOTSUGU]
ALL RIGHT!
[SHIROE, THINKING]
WE HAVE PEOPLE WAITING FOR US!
[SHIROE]
AND THORN‐BIND HOSTAGE!
[NAOTSUGU]
HWAH! MERCILESS STRIKE!
[AKATSUKI]
ASSASSINATION!
(GROWL)
(DEATH SCREAM)
[KR] OH‐HO! THERE YA GO,
LOOKS LIKE THEY FINISHED IT.
OF COURSE THEY DID, IT'S
THE VILLAIN IN GLASSES.
[WILLIAM]
OKAY, I SEE.
YEAH, WELL WE TOOK CARE
OF THINGS HERE.
SO IT'S THE FORTRESS
OF CALLS, THEN, HUH?
(ROUSING) [WILLIAM] SOUNDS LIKE
SOMETHING WORTH TAKING ON.
[UPASHI]
UH... HUH?
[DEMICAS] BABY, ARE YOU OKAY!
(SOBBING)
[UPASHI] OH HONEY!
WHY ARE YOU CRYING?
[DEMICAS] ERR... I'M NOT CRYING!
IT'S JUST DROOL, I SWEAR!
DROOL FROM MY EYES! (SOBBING)
[UPASHI] (GIGGLING)
OKAY, WHATEVER YOU SAY.
[WILLIAM] SERIOUSLY, DON'T
EMBARRASS YOURSELF, MAN?
[TETORA, YELL SINGING] THE
PERPLEXED PINKIE HAS A HANGNAIL!
[ISAMI] SOMETHING'S CHANGED
BY DEFEATING THE RAID BOSS...
IT'S ALMOST LIKE THE
AIR IS DIFFERENT NOW.
[NAOTSUGU]
MAN WE ARE FREAKIN' AWESOME...
WE SAVED THE ANTENNA AND
THE WORLD AT THE SAME TIME!
[NYANTA] WE KILLED TWO
BIRDS WITH ONE STONE...
SHIROE‐ECCHI'S DONE IT AGAIN.
[MARIELLE] IT'S CRAZY TO THINK
THERE USED TO BE A BUNCH OF TV
[MARIELLE] AND RADIO STATIONS
HERE. (REGAN MUTTERS TO SELF.)
[HENRIETTA] IT PROBABLY
WOULDN'T HAVE MADE
AN APPEARANCE UNTIL
WE BEAT TARICTON.
[ALL] IT ACTS LIKE A GAME IN
THE WEIRDEST WAYS, DOESN'T
[NAOTSUGU]
YEAH, YOU KIDS ARE REAL FUNNY!
[AKATSUKI] BITTER? YOU'RE
ACTING LIKE A FIVE‐YEAR OLD.
[NAOTSUGU] NUH‐UHH?
(REGAN HUMMING)
[SHIROE] HOW'S IT GOING?
[REGAN]
JUST ANOTHER MINUTE HERE.
THERE! THAT SHOULD DO IT.
[HENRIETTA] YOU MEAN,
WE'RE CONNECTED?!
[MARIELLE]
WE'RE TALKING TO THE MOON?
[SHIROE] HUH?!
[KANAMI] HELLO? HELLO?
CAN... ANYBODY HEAR ME?
[KANAMI] HELLO! NI HAO!
[SERARA] OH WOW!
IT'S PRINCESS KAGUYA!
[KANAMI] BONJOUR? ALOHA! GUTEN
TAG? HOLA?
[SHIROE] HELLO? CAN YOU HEAR
ME?! HELLO?!
[KANAMI] HUH? I KNOW THAT
VOICE! SHIROE, IS THAT YOU?!
[ALL]
HUH?
HOLY CRAP, NO FREAKIN' WAY?
[KANAMI] OMIGOD! IT IS YOU!
I DON'T BELIEVE IT!
(DISBELIEF)
[SHIROE] KANAMI?!
[MINORI]
HUH? SO THAT'S KANAMI?
[AKATSUKI]
NOT THAT KANAMI?
(SHOCKED) [TETORA] THE BOSSMAN'S
FORMER FLAME'S ON THE PHONE?!
[KANAMI] LONG TIME NO SEE! SO,
HOW HAVE YOU BEEN DOING?!
[SHIROE] I... I CAN'T
BELIEVE IT'S REALLY YOU.
[KANAMI] OHH! HEARD
THAT YOU'VE BEEN BUSY!
THAT YOU'RE DOING SOMETHING
VERY INTERESTING IN AKIHABARA.
IT'S... IT'S SOMETHING LIKE...
THE "ROUND CABLE CIRCUMFERENCE?"
[SHIROE]
"ROUND TABLE CONFERENCE."
WHO TOLD YOU ABOUT
THAT, ANYWAYS?
ALSO, WHEN DID YOU
COME BACK TO THE GAME?
AND WHERE ARE YOU CALLING FROM?
[NAZNA] DON'T TELL ME
SHE'S ON THE MOON...
[SOJIRO]
WOULDN'T PUT IT PAST HER.
[KANAMI]
EEHEHEEE! WHAT?
I'M ON THE CHINA
SERVER, SILLY!
[LEONARDO]
OKAY, THAT'S THE LAST OF THEM.
YOU GUYS OKAY?
HEY, KANAMI! IT'S
ALL CLEAR OUT HERE!
[KANAMI] SO LIKE WE WERE ON THE
ROAD,
AND I STUMBLED ON
THIS OLD TV STATION.
AND THIS THINGY
LOOKED KINDA COOL,
SO I STARTED TINKERING
WITH IT AND GOT A CONNECTION!
[SHIROE]
I SEE YOU HAVEN'T CHANGED...
[KANAMI]
OH, BY THE WAY, SHIROE!
I HAVE A DAUGHTER, SHE'S
THREE YEARS OLD NOW.
UHH...
[MINORI]
HER "DAUGHTER"?
[AKATSUKI]
WAIT SO SHE HAS A CHILD?
[SHIROE]
I KNOW SHE IS.
I'M SORRY I NEVER
CONGRATULATED YOU.
[KANAMI] HMM? I DON'T
REMEMBER TELLING YOU.
[SHIROE] YOU DIDN'T,
BUT I HEARD ABOUT IT.
WELL ANYWAY... CONGRATULATIONS.
[KANAMI]
THANK YOU, SHIROE!
[LEONARDO]
A KID?! SERIOUSLY?!
[KANAMI]
ANYWAY, SHE IS SO SUPER CUTE!
SHE RUNS OVER AND SLAMS INTO
ME, AND WHEN I HUG HER
SHE JUST CLINGS ON WITH HER
TINY LITTLE HANDS
REALLY REALLY TIGHT!
[SHIROE]
THAT'S ADORABLE.
I GUESS, YOU REALLY NEED TO GO
BACK TO OUR WORLD, I MEAN.
[KANAMI]
YEAH? WHAT FOR?
[SHIROE]
HUH?
[KANAMI]
OH! SHIROE!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I WANNA SHOW HER WHAT
THIS WORLD IS LIKE.
I THINK SHE'D LOVE IT!
[SHIROE]
HUH?
IT'S BIG AND MAJESTIC!
AND YOU KNOW THE BEST PART?
ALL OF MOMMY'S FRIENDS ARE HERE!
NOW YOU'VE GOTTA ADMIT THAT
IS REALLY SUPER FANTASTIC.
I WANT HER TO GO ON AN ADVENTURE
AND MEET PEOPLE FROM
ALL OVER THE WORLD!
[SHIROE]
UH...
[KANAMI]
AND SHE LOVES HIGH PLACES.
I COULD TAKE HER ON A GRIFFON!
I WANT TO SHOW HER THE GREAT
FORESTS,
THE OCEANS, AND THE DESERTS!
I WANT TO TEACH HER THAT
THIS WORLD IS A REALLY
BEAUTIFUL PLACE!
(INHALE) HMPH.
[SHIROE]
OK... YEAH, SURE... I GUESS SO.
HONESTLY I DID GIVE THIS
SOME THOUGHT ALREADY...
BUT STILL I JUST ASSUMED IT
WASN'T POSSIBLE.
NOT JUST GOING
BACK TO OUR WORLD,
OR STAYING IN THIS WORLD,
FOR THAT MATTER...
BUT RATHER A THIRD OPTION.
THAT THIS WORLD AND
OUR OLD WORLD...
THAT WE COULD CONNECT THEM AND
MAKE IT POSSIBLE
TO TRAVEL BETWEEN THEM.
[HENRIETTA] IT SOUNDS
INCREDIBLE. BUT COULD WE DO IT?
[SHIROE] I THINK IT'S
WORTH A TRY, HENRIETTA.
[TETORA] YEAH... BUT
DIDN'T YOU SAY SOMETHING
ABOUT THE PRESENCE
OF ADVENTURERS
POSSIBLY BEING THE CAUSE OF
ALL THE TROUBLE AROUND HERE?
[SHIROE] YES, I DID, BUT I DON'T
KNOW
IF LEAVING THINGS IS
THE BEST THING TO DO.
THAT'S MASTER SHIROE.
THAT'S MY LORD, WOULDN'T
EXPECT ANYTHING LESS!
[KANAMI] COME ON, SHIROE!
LET'S FIND OUT IF WE
CAN MAKE IT HAPPEN!
[SHIROE]
YOU MEAN, LIKE A QUEST?
[KANAMI]
DEFINITELY! MAKE IT A QUEST!
[SHIROE]
WELL, SORTA.
[KANAMI]
HUUH?! AW, SHIROE!
LOOK KANAMI, IT'S JUST...
I FOUNDED A GUILD, SEE?
IT'S CALLED LOG HORIZON.
AND I MADE A LOT OF FRIENDS
SINCE I'VE BEEN HERE.
[KANAMI]
OH, YEAH?
SO WHEN IT COMES DOWN TO THIS
QUEST, WE'RE ALL TAKING IT.
[KANAMI]
HUH?
THAT'S RIGHT,
WE'LL BE THE FIRST PEOPLE
HERE TO SEE WHAT'S NEXT...
AND SINCE WE'RE OLD
FRIENDS AND ALL...
IF YOU MAKE IT IN TIME, I'D
LOVE FOR YOU TO SEE IT TOO.
[KANAMI]
I'VE MISSED YOU.
[SHIROE] IT'S A SOLUTION THAT
DOESN'T ABANDON OUR OLD WORLD
OR MAKE US LEAVE THIS ONE.
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
FIND IT. PROMISE ME!
[SHIROE] WE'LL TAKE IT,
KANAMI... LOG HORIZON...
WILL COMPLETE THIS QUEST.
[KANAMI] I'D EXPECT NOTHING
LESS FROM MY TOUR GUIDE!
[SHIROE] HUH?! YOU JUST HAD TO
BRING THAT UP, DIDN'T YOU?
[KANAMI] OH, YEAH.
I ALMOST FORGOT,
YOUR LITTLE PAL KRUSTY
IS OVER HERE.
[SHIROE]
HUH?
WAIT KRUSTY'S IN CHINA?!
[RIEZE]
WHAT? Y'MEAN MY LORD?!
[ALL]
WHAT?!
[SHIROE] DID I HEAR YOU RIGHT?
(RIEZE IN SHOCK)
DID YOU REALLY JUST SAY KRUSTY'S
THERE WITH YOU?!
[KANAMI] YEAH! TOTALLY!
BUT YOU KNOW, KRUSTY,
HE'S ALWAYS TRYING TO‐
(EXPLOSION)
[SHIROE] D'AHHH!
[REGAN]
HMM. I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED,
I SWEAR I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
MPH...
[KANAMI] HEY? WHAT HAPPENED?
YOU THERE SHIROE?
[LEONARDO, STRUGGLING]
YOU ARE GOING TO BREAK IT.
[KRUSTY] WELL WELL, SHIROE'S
THE SAME AS HE EVER WAS.
[KRUSTY]
ALWAYS ENTERTAINING...
[LEONARDO]
"ENTERTAINING"?
[KRUSTY]
SO THEN...
I CAN'T HELP BUT WONDER
WHICH ONE OF MY SECONDS
WILL BE COMING TO GET ME.
MISA OR RIEZE?
[LEONARDO] KANAMI IT LOOKS
LIKE YOUR FRIENDS ARE
JUST AS SCREWED UP AS YOU ARE.
[RAYNESHIA]
UNBELIEVABLE.
COME ON, KRUSTY!
AT THE VERY LEAST YOU
COULD'VE BEEN HERE FOR THIS.
I SWEAR THE NEXT TIME I SEE THAT
MONSTER HE IS REALLY IN FOR IT.
AND YOU BETTER BELIEVE HE'S
GONNA GET A PIECE OF MY MIND.
[INTIX] YOU'RE SAYING WE SHOULD
ADVISE THE WESTELANDE
ARISTOCRATS
TO STABILIZE RELATIONS
WITH EASTAL?
[KAZUHIKO] THE SWARMS OF ETERNAL
MOTHS
WERE A PRODUCT OF
THE GENIUSES, YES?
INFIGHTING WILL ONLY
WEAKEN US, INTIX.
[INTIX]
IF I UNDERSTAND YOU,
YOU'RE SUGGESTING WE ALLY
OURSELVES WITH THE ROUND TABLE.
[KAZUHIKO]
IF WE NEED TO, OF COURSE.
WITH THAT TRAITOROUS PIG?
YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
WE'RE NOT ALIGNING
OURSELVES WITH HIM,
AND WE'RE NOT LETTING
HIM GO HOME.
[NUREHA]
AND I COMMAND THE SAME.
SUSPEND PLANS FOR GOING
TO WAR WITH EASTAL.
[INTIX]
WHAT'S THAT?
THAT'S CUTE, YOU'RE
GIVING ME ORDERS NOW?
YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING,
YOU'RE NOTHING BUT FILTHY
SEWER RAT AND A MINDLESS PUPPET!
YOU'RE GIVING ME
COMMANDS?! HUHH...?
(BREATH) UNBELIEVABLE...
MY DEAR, DO I NEED TO
REMIND YOU... HEH...
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU SASS ME?!
[KAZUHIKO]
THAT'S QUITE ENOUGH, INTIX.
[INTIX]
(BREATH) UH...
[NUREHA] I'M THE ONE WHO
MADE THE PROMISE, INTIX.
YOU WILL NOT BE THE
ONE TO FACE SHIROE.
YOU UNDERSTAND THAT, YES?
(ANGRY EXHALE)
[KR] THE ROUND TABLE CONFERENCE
WILL CONTACT US SOON ENOUGH.
I'M SURE HE'S GOING OVER A
HUNDRED SCENARIOS IN HIS MIND
FOR NEGOTIATING WITH US, HE'S
NOTHING IF NOT THOROUGH!
WE'LL JUST HAVE TO
WAIT AND SEE...
I'M SURE HE'LL COME UP WITH
SOMETHING TO THROW AT US.
WHATCHA SAY, INTIX?
[INTIX]
MPH.
[KR] WHEN YOU STEP
BACK AND LOOK AT IT,
I'M NOT LIKE KANAMI
OR LEONARDO.
I'M MORE LIKE KAZUHIKO,
DESTINED FOR THE SIDELINES.
BUT WHILE THAT'S TRUE,
GIVING UP THIS CHANCE TO SHINE
ISN'T REALLY AN OPTION FOR ME.
IF I WANT TO SEE
THE BLUE SKY AFTER
THIS STORM FINALLY PASSES BY.
I NEED TO... I NEED
TO GET STRONGER.
[ROE2] PERHAPS MY BIG BROTHER
WILL HAVE SOME USE FOR THIS...
LITTLE SISTERS, BIG SIS
IS DOING HER BEST, TOO!
[TOYA]
(SIGH) I'M SO HUNGRY!
[RUDY]
AH! SO AM I!
[ISUZU] WE HAVEN'T EATEN
ANYTHING
SINCE YESTERDAY, AFTER ALL.
[SERARA]
I MISS MAYONNAISE.
[AKATSUKI] RED BEAN BUNS ARE
JUST THE THING
WHEN YOU'RE TIRED.
[MINORI]
FLAN, AKATSUKI! FLAN!
IT SOUNDS LIKE I'VE GOT A
BUNCHA HUNGRY GUILDMATES
TO FEED WHEN WE GET HOME.
I'LL PULL OUT ALL THE STOPS TO
PROVIDE MY CULINARY BEST!
(CHEER)
THEN IT'S ABSOLUTELY
POSITIVELY GOTTA BE CURRY!
RIGHT, CHIEF?!
(EVERYONE YELLING OUT ORDERS)
[AKATSUKI]
HEY UH... MY LORD!
[SHIROE]
HM? WHAT IS IT? AKATSUKI?
YOU WERE GREAT,
I JUST KNEW YOU WOULD BE.
UH...?
AND SO WERE YOU... REALLY?
[AKATSUKI]
UHH...
[ALL]
THANKS FOR THE FOOD!
[MINORI] DID THE FLAN
MAKE IT TO THE TABLE?
[NAOTSUGU] HANG ON. WHERE
DID OLD DUSTY‐BUTT GO?
[SHIROE] HE'S TRYING TO GET
THE TRANSMITTER RUNNING AGAIN.
[ISAMI] SO WE'RE JUST HERE TO
KEEP AN EYE ON MISTER REGAN?
[OLIVE]
I WANT TO TAKE A BATH!
[NAZNA]
OH, DON'T REMIND ME.
[SOJIRO] WELL WE HAVE SOME
TIME, WHY DON'T WE TRY
GETTING A LITTLE
TRAINING IN YOU GUYS?
(MOOING)
[KURINON] HEY!
THAT STUPID OLD FART JUST RAN
OFF AND LEFT US ALL HERE!
[MINORI] THERE'S STILL
MORE MAPO TOFU LEFT!
[AKATSUKI] WHATEVER. MY LORD
NEEDS ANOTHER HELPING OF CURRY!
[SHIROE] LADIES, I REALLY
THINK I MIGHT PUKE.
[REGAN]
NOW THAT LOOKS SCRUMPTIOUS!
[ALL]
HUH?
WOULD YOU MIND IF I...
JOINED YOU FOR A
BITE OR TWO? MMM?