(STAGGERED GROANS)
[ROE2]
UH?
AH, THE SUN...
THE SUN'S
KILLING ME! UGH!
[TOYA] HMMM... IT LOOKS LIKE
WE'VE MADE IT TO ZOOLAND.
[MINORI] UM... WE SHOULD BE ABLE
TO SEE IT PRETTY SOON NOW.
(GASP) THERE IT IS!
UH! OH MY GOD! MT. FUJI!
[ISUZU]
HUH?! WHERE IS IT, TOYA?!
[RUDY]
HMMM, OH THE SACRED MT. FUJI.
[SERARA]
IT'S BIGGER THAN I REMEMBER.
[ISUZU] OMIGOSH! LOOK! THOSE
THINGS TOTALLY LOOK LIKE COWS!
[SERARA] WHAT?!
[MINORI] WAIT. WHERE?
[SERARA] OH, I THINK THAT'S A
HERD OF GREEN ELK
OUT THERE YOU GUYS!
HOW COOL!
[ISUZU]
ARE THEY DANGEROUS?
[SERARA]
WE'LL BE FINE.
NONE OF THEM ARE
CLOSE TO THE ROAD.
AND BESIDES, THEY DON'T
REALLY LOOK FOR TROUBLE.
MOO...
AW, THEY'RE SO CUTE!
THEY REALLY DO
LOOK LIKE COWS.
NOT TO MENTION THEY
MAKE TASTY BARBECUE!
[ALL]
EH...?
[SERARA]
MMMM...
[TOYA] (EXHALES) THERE'S
BEEN A LONG SLIGHT CURVE
IN THE ROAD AROUND THESE PARTS.
[MINORI] THAT'S BECAUSE THE ROAD
RUNS AROUND THE SHORELINE.
[TOYA] OH YEAH? THEN
HOW COME ALL I'M SEEING
ARE BUSHES AND TREES?!
[MINORI] (BIG INHALE)
IF YOU TAKE A DEEP BREATH,
YOU CAN SMELL THE OCEAN TOYA.
(SNIFF SNIFF)
[TOYA] NOT GETTING ANYTHING.
WELL EXCEPT FOR
THOSE HORSE BUTTS.
(MINORI GIGGLES)
[TOYA]
NOW IF I REMEMBER RIGHT,
BROTHER SHIROE TOLD
US ABOUT THIS ROAD.
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
"THE TOKAIDO"
THAT'S WHAT PEOPLE CALLED
IT A LONG TIME AGO.
IT WAS ONE OF THE ORIGINAL
FIVE ROUTES.
STARTING AT THE NIYONBASHI
BRIDGE IN TOKYO,
IT BECAME A PIVOTAL
POINT OF TRADE.
[TOYA]
UH‐HUH...
IN THE REAL WORLD,
THE TOKAIDO ROUTE
IS PRIMARILY USED AS
A MAJOR HIGHWAY.
IT'S CALLED NATIONAL ROUTE ONE.
IT GOES ALL THE WAY INTO OSAKA.
[TOYA]
OSAKA?!
[RUDY]
AH... THE PLACE WE CALL MINAMI.
[MINORI] DOES THAT
MEAN ALL THE ROADS
ARE CONNECTED HERE
AS WELL, SHIROE?
[SHIROE] THAT'S RIGHT... THIS IS
PROBABLY GONNA BE THE FASTEST
WAY THROUGH THE
REDSTONE MOUNTAINS.
[MINORI] MPH.
[TOYA] HM?
IT'S FUNNY. I NEVER REALLY PAID
A WHOLE LOT OF ATTENTION
TO THE ROADS BEFORE
WE WOUND UP HERE.
[TOYA] UH... YEAH, I GUESS
I COULD SAY THE SAME THING!
BROTHER SHIROE'S LIKE A
WALKING, TALKING ENCYCLOPEDIA
WITH ALL THE CRAZY
STUFF HE KNOWS!
OH MAN! I'M GONNA LEARN A
WHOLE BUNCH OF STUFF
WHILE WE'RE ON THIS
TRIP, AREN'T I!
(STOMACH GROWLING)
[BOTH] HUH?
MAYBE WE SHOULD WAIT UNTIL
WE'VE HAD LUNCH FIRST!
[ALL]
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA!
[TOYA]
MMM‐MMMMM, YUM!
THE CHIEF MAKES THE BEST HAM
SANDWICHES IN THE UNIVERSE!
[RUDY] MM. YES, HE DOES!
THE MAN IS A MAGICIAN!
[ISUZU]
DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT IT!
[BOTH]
HUH?
[ISUZU]
NOT EVERYONE HAS HAD THEIRS YET.
[SERARA]
YEAH. YOU HEARD HER!
[SERARA] AH...?
YOU ALMOST BIT MY HAND.
WE SHOULD BE COMING UP ON
CALVET VILLAGE.
YOU WANNA STOP?
... OR GO ON?
WELL, IT'S SUCH
A NICE DAY OUT
I DON'T KNOW WHY WE
CAN'T KEEP ON GOING.
I'M BETTING DANISH AND
CROISSANT CAN DO THIS ALL DAY
IF THEY WANT TO.
(HORSE NEIGHS AND WHINNIES)
[SERARA] YOU HEAR THAT! THEY SAY
THEY CAN GO AS LONG AS WE CAN.
[ISUZU] SOUNDS TO ME LIKE
THEY'RE UP FOR IT.
[SERARA] I KNOW
I CAN KEEP GOING!
[MINORI] YEAH! ME TOO!
[RUDY]
ROADS UNIMAGINED ALWAYS
APPEAR BEFORE RUNDELLHAUS KODE!
[TOYA] ALL RIGHT! WE'D BETTER
GET MOVING
BEFORE IT STARTS
GETTING DARK OUT HERE!
[ALL]
YEAH!
(HORSES WHINNY)
[ALL] WAUUGHHH!
(DISORIENTED GROANS)
[TOYA]
OKAY... WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT...?
[ISUZU] WAUUUGHHH!
[ALL] HUH?
[ISUZU]
THEY MUST'VE RUN OUT OF TIME.
THE TWIN HORSE FLUTE
ONLY LASTS A FEW HOURS.
[SERARA]
WELL I GUESS THAT EXPLAINS IT.
THAT'S RIGHT. THEY'RE
ONLY SUPPOSED TO GIVE US
SIX HOURS A DAY.
(DISAPPOINTED)
(LAUGHTER)
WELL I GUESS WE'RE NOT ALL THAT
WORRIED ABOUT IT ARE WE GUYS?
[MINORI]
YEAH, TOTALLY!
YOU HAVE TO ADMIT THAT WAS
STILL A PRETTY QUICK DEPARTURE.
I MEAN SERIOUSLY, WHY DIDN'T
THOSE TWO MOVE THAT FAST BEFORE.
[RUDY]
GOOD QUESTION!
THAT IS JUST RUDE,
AND AFTER THEY ATE CARROTS
RIGHT OUTTA MY HANDS!
[ISUZU] NOT TO MENTION THE
CABBAGE! [RUDY] HUH...?
THEY DON'T HAVE A SINGLE
SHRED OF HUMAN DECENCY!
THAT'S BECAUSE THEY'RE HORSES.
WELL THAT'S NO EXCUSE...
YOU KNOW... EVEN
HORSES SHOULD KNOW
IT'S NOT RIGHT TO EAT AND RUN.
(LAUGHTER)
[RUDY] OKAY, WE LOST THE HORSES.
BUT THAT JUST GIVES US
ANOTHER ADVENTURE, RIGHT?
[TOYA] YOU BET...!
SO WHERE ARE WE, ANYWAY?
[MINORI] WELL WITH TRAVEL TIME,
WE'RE SOMEWHERE BETWEEN
CALVET AND WILLISTORIA.
[ISUZU] WE'RE NOT GONNA GET
ANYWHERE VERY FAST
WITHOUT A SET OF FRESH HORSES.
(DEFLATED)
GUESS THIS MEANS
WE'RE CAMPING TONIGHT!
WELL I DON'T SEE A
HOTEL OR ANYTHING.
JUST AS LONG AS EVERYONE
LEAVES THE COOKING TO ME.
NOW THIS IS WHERE ADVENTURERS
ARE AT THEIR BEST!
WE'RE NOT ALL
OUTDOORSMEN, YOU KNOW?
[BOYS]
LET'S PITCH CAMP!
[GIRLS]
YEAH!
[RUDY] HMM. HEH.
(CLAPPING)
[TOYA]
PERFECT.
[BOTH]
WAUUUGHHHH!
(HAPPY SOUNDS)
(HUMS A TUNE)
(SURPRISED)
[ALL] THANK YOU FOR THE FOOD!
(EATING)
[TOYA] IT'S REALLY... GOOD.
[SERARA] HM?
[MINORI] OH YEAH, THIS
IS, DEFINITELY GOOD.
[ISUZU]
IT'S JUST... A LITTLE...
[RUDY]
IT'S REALLY BLAND... AND BITTER
[ISUZU]
RUDY!
(GASP AND SCREAM)
[SERARA]
I'M SORRY! I'M SORRY! I'M SORRY!
[SERARA] WHENEVER I'M
COOKING WITH CHIEF NYANTA,
IT ALWAYS COMES OUT THE
WAY IT'S SUPPOSED TO...
[TOYA] HEY, THE
MORE YOU DO IT,
THE BETTER YOU'LL GET!
DON'T SWEAT IT!
IF THE CHIEF WERE
HERE RIGHT NOW...
HE'D TELL YOU TO TAKE IT EASY,
BABY. YOU CAN TOTALLY DO IT!
[RUDY] KEEP WORKING TO
IMPROVE, YOU'LL BE FINE.
[MINORI] I WISH MORE OF US
HAD THE COOKING SKILL,
SO WE COULD ALL HELP COOK!
[ISUZU] SORRY WE'RE
COUNTING ON YOU
FOR ALL THE GRUB,
LITTLE DUDE‐ETTE!
(INHALE) YOU'RE
ABSOLUTELY RIGHT!
I'VE GOTTA KEEP TRYING FOR
EVERYONE IN MY GUILD!
[SERARA] I'M THE ONE WEARING
THE NEWLYWED WIFE'S APRON!
IT'S TIME I LIVE UP TO CHIEF
NYANTA'S LEGACY OF AMAZING FOOD!
(CHEERS)
(STRUMMING LUTE)
[MINORI] SO IT LOOKS LIKE THE
NEXT BEST PLACE
TO STOP IS SAZAN VILLAGE.
[TOYA] HOW LONG WILL
IT TAKE TO GET THERE?
WELL IF WE CAN'T
GET MORE THAN
SIX HOURS A DAY
OUT OF THE HORSES...
IT'S PROBABLY GONNA TAKE
US ANOTHER THREE DAYS.
AHHH! WHY IN THE HECK ARE WE
RUNNING INTO ALL THIS TROUBLE
ON OUR FIRST JOURNEY?
WHY CAN'T IT BE A NORMAL
ADVENTURE LIKE IT USED TO BE?
S'NOT SO BAD...
WE'VE GOT OUR GUILDMATES WITH
US KEEPING US COMPANY...
IT KINDA MAKES THE WHOLE
THING MORE FUN, Y'KNOW.
I'M SURE THAT'S WHY SHIROE AND
THE OTHERS SENT US
IN THE FIRST PLACE
TO TEACH US TO TAKE CARE OF EACH
OTHER. AND TO TRUST EACH OTHER.
HMPH. LOOK AT
YOU, MINORI.
HUH?
IT SURE IS STRANGE
TO SEE MY BIG SISTER
ALL GROWN UP LIKE THIS.
MM? ALL GROWN UP?
I KINDA ALWAYS THOUGHT YOU
AND I WERE GONNA GROW UP AT
THE SAME SPEED. BUT YOU'RE
MOVING PRETTY FAST.
[MINORI]
YOU'RE EXAGGERATING.
WHICH ONE OF US WAS STRONGER
WHEN THIS APOCALYPSE
MESS GOT STARTED?
HEH. THERE'S NO WAY I WOULD HAVE
GOTTEN THIS FAR IF I DIDN'T
HAVE YOU HERE TO HELP
ME THROUGH ALL THIS.
WELL, I AM YOUR BIG
BROTHER YOU KNOW.
HUH? UH... I'M
THE BIG SISTER HERE
[TOYA]
NO, I'M DEFINITELY OLDER!
[MINORI]
YOU HAVE LOST YOUR MIND.
[TOYA] NO, I AM! I'M
EVEN TALLER THAN YOU ARE!
[MINORI] OH WHATEVER. THAT
DOESN'T MEAN ANYTHING.
[TOYA]
UH, IT SURE DOES!
[MARIELLE] THE KIDS LEFT FOR
THEIR EXPEDITION THREE DAYS AGO.
AWW... I HOPE THEY'RE
NOT GETTING HOMESICK...
[HENRIETTA] I DOUBT IT!
I BET THEY'RE ROMPING ABOUT
LIKE IT'S A SCHOOL TRIP.
THEY MIGHT EVEN START TELLING
THEMSELVES
THEY DON'T WANT TO COME BACK!
[AKATSUKI] HMN... THAT WOULDN'T
BE GOOD EITHER, WOULD IT?
(SIGH)
[HENRIETTA] YOU'RE LOOKING
PALE AGAIN, RIEZE.
HUH? I'M ALL RIGHT,
IT'S NOTHING.
HM‐MM. YOUR EYES ARE STARTING
TO LOOK STERN, LIKE MY LORD.
INTENSE AND SEVERE.
HUH?
YOU DON'T NEED TO PUSH YOURSELF
AS HARD AS YOU HAVE BEEN.
[RIEZE]
OKAY...
THE ABSENCE OF KRUSTY MUST
BE TAKING ITS TOLL ON YOU.
THAT'S TRUE, IT'S BEEN
DIFFICULT.
WORKING WITHOUT HIM OR TAKAYAMA
HAS BEEN VERY HARD FOR ME.
D. D. D. IS STILL FUNCTIONING
PROPERLY FOR NOW,
BUT THERE ARE A LOT OF UNKNOWN
FACTORS FACING US AT THE MOMENT.
AND IT'S TROUBLING.
(EXHALES)
I'M SORRY TO BE SUCH A
THORN IN EVERYONE'S SIDE
AND I'M AFRAID, THAT WON'T
BE CHANGING ANYTIME SOON.
[HENRIETTA] GO AHEAD AND BE
A PAIN IF YOU NEED TO BE!
WE KNOW THINGS HAVEN'T BEEN
GOING SMOOTHLY FOR YOU.
I BET SHIROE CAN WORK SOMETHING
OUT TO HELP YOU RUN YOUR GUILD.
[AKATSUKI] HE DEFINITELY WON'T
CONSIDER IT AN INCONVENIENCE.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS SAY THE
WORD AND HE'LL BE HERE,
AND OF COURSE I WILL TOO.
THAT'S RIGHT! JUST ASK
US FOR ANYTHING, 'K?
WE'LL BE HERE FOR YOU!
'CAUSE WE'RE FRIENDS,
ALL RIGHT?!
(GIGGLING) [AKATSUKI] GRR...
HEY! WHAT IS SO FUNNY?!
I THOUGHT THAT'S THE STUPID
CRAP FRIENDS SAY TO EACH OTHER.
I'M SO LUCKY TO HAVE YOU.
(AKATSUKI GRUMBLING)
HUH?
[BOTH]
UH?
IF WE'D NEVER COME
TO THIS PLACE...
THEN THERE'S A GOOD CHANCE NONE
OF US WOULD HAVE EVER MET.
(EXHALE)
YOU MIGHT BE RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
OH NO! I'M NOT BUYING
THAT FOR ONE MINUTE!
HOTTIES ATTRACT OTHER HOTTIES
SO NATURALLY WE'D END UP
FINDING EACH OTHER EVENTUALLY!
I'M HAPPY TO BE FRIENDS
HENRIETTA!
BUT I THINK YOU'RE TAKING
IT A BIT TOO FAR!
I DON'T THINK THAT MADE
THE LEAST BIT OF SENSE!
HEH!
OH MY AKATSUKI! COME BACK TO
MAMA YOU LITTLE DARLING!
WAS THAT AN ORAL ART, LIKE
THE NINJA REPLACEMENT
MANEUVER, AKATSUKI?
[AKATSUKI] NO. THAT WAS
NOTHING, JUST A DOLL.
[ISUZU]
AHH!! LOOK AT THAT SUNSET!
IT'S REALLY PRETTY,
ISN'T IT?
[TOYA] THERE IT IS, YOU
GUYS! SAZAN VILLAGE, HO!
(GASP)
LOOKS LIKE WE MADE IT!
[RUDY] OUR BARD HERE WOULD LIKE
TO PLAY AT
YOUR FINE ESTABLISHMENT TONIGHT.
SHE'S A FINE MUSICIAN,
AND SHE'S LOOKING FOR A
PLACE TO PERFORM HER SONGS.
[BARTENDER]
OKAY KID, LOOKIE HERE.
I'LL TELL YOU RIGHT NOW I
CAN'T AFFORD 42.
WE'RE JUST A LITTLE
PLACE Y'KNOW.
YEAH, BUT I DON'T
WANT THE MONEY!
ALL I WANT IS THE
OPPORTUNITY TO PERFORM!
[RUDY]
HUH? PLEASE LET HER!
[ISUZU]
PLEASE LET ME!
(GRUNT)
[TOYA]
WAY TO GO, RUDY!
A CHANCE TO PLAY! FREE ROOM!
[TOYA] THAT WAS PRETTY
SLICK NEGOTIATING!
HMPH! THIS IS WHAT
I WAS MEANT TO DO!
AT LEAST I WISH
I COULD SAY THAT,
BUT MISS ISUZU'S PASSION
WON HIM OVER.
ARE YOU OKAY?
THERE'S NO NEED TO
WORRY ABOUT ME!
JUST USE THIS OPPORTUNITY TO
PLAY! BOTH YOU AND ISUZU!
OH... YEAH, SURE!
(BACKGROUND SINGING BEGINS)
[TOYA, THINKING] I SWEAR, I
NEVER THOUGHT I WAS GONNA LEARN
SO MUCH ON THIS TRIP!
(BAR ROOM BUZZ)
[TOYA, THINKING]
EVEN RIGHT FROM THE BEGINNING ‐
ON THE ROAD WE TOOK TO GET HERE.
I MEAN I WAS REALLY
STARTING TO WONDER
WHY IT HAD ALL
THESE TWIST TURNS.
BUT THE FURTHER WE WENT,
THE MORE I REALIZED IT
WAS THE BEST WAY TO GO.
STRAIGHT LINE TO THE VILLAGE
WOULD'VE BEEN SHORTER.
BUT A LOT BUMPIER.
SOMEBODY ALREADY TRIED TO DO IT
THAT WAY
AND THEN CREATED THE CURVES
AROUND THE TROUBLE SPOTS.
AND THEN, JUST WHEN I WAS
STARTING TO GET TIRED,
THERE WAS A VILLAGE.
THAT'S PROBABLY WHY IT'S
HERE IN THE FIRST PLACE.
[TOYA, THINKING] THAT RUDY ‐
HE'S SOMETHING ELSE.
SO FULL OF ENERGY.
REMINDS ME OF BEING BACK IN
THE REAL WORLD,
WATCHING FROM THE SIDELINES.
EXCEPT THEN, I HAD A HARD TIME
SEEING PEOPLE LIKE THAT.
I WONDER WILL ALL
MY TRAVELING LAND ME
IN A VILLAGE LIKE THIS SOMEDAY?
[TOYA]
UGH! MAN I AM BEAT!
[RUDY] DUDE! EVERYONE
LOVED YOU OUT THERE!
SERIOUSLY, THEY WERE SCREAMING
FOR ENCORE AFTER ENCORE
LIKE YOU WERE NEVER GONNA STOP!
YOU WERE GREAT, TOYA!
[TOYA]
UH‐HUH...
(DISTANT LAUGHTER AND CHATTER)
[TOYA] UH? HUH?
[TOYA] WHOA...
THEY'RE STILL HYPED!
[RUDY] TOO HYPER FOR ME...
BUT IT DOES MAKE ONE
WONDER WHAT THEY'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
[TOYA] RUDY! YOU
REALLY WANNA KNOW?
NO, OF COURSE NOT...!
I'M FAR TOO REFINED
OF A PERSON, TOYA...
TO RESORT TO EAVESDROPPING.
BUT YOU KNOW... I CAN STILL
MARVEL AT THE AMOUNT OF
CHATTERING THEY DO. I MEAN
HOW CAN THEY TALK SO MUCH?
IT'S BECAUSE
THEY'RE GIRLS, DUDE.
VERY WELL. A GIRL THING... I
SUPPOSED I CAN UNDERSTAND THAT.
AND I MUST ASSUME IT'S A GIRL
THING FOR ISUZU TO ACT
AFFECTIONATELY TOWARDS ME, YES.
HUH? SHE'S
AFFECTIONATE WITH YOU?
LIKE ALL THE TIMES
SHE BRUSHES MY HAIR!
IT DRIVES ME ABSOLUTELY
CRAZY INSIDE!
UH... YEAH...
[TOYA, THINKING] SOUNDS LIKE
SHE'S TREATING YOU LIKE A DOG.
HMPH... IT'S NOT LIKE I'VE SEEN
MISS ISUZU TREATING YOU THAT.
IT'S JUST TO ME.
I'M GETTING THE FEELING MAYBE
SHE ISN'T TAKING ME SERIOUSLY.
UH... (LAUGHING)
HUH?! KNOCK IT OFF, TOYA!
I'M TRYING TO BE SERIOUS!
TAKE IT EASY, WILLYA?! TRY
THINKING OF IT LIKE THIS...
SHE'S TREATING YOU
LIKE YOU'RE SPECIAL.
HMM? "SPECIAL"...?
MM‐HM!
(PANTING)
[ISUZU] SHAKE!
[RUDY] W‐WOOF! (PANTS)
[ISUZU] OH RUDY‐BOOBY, YOU'RE
THE SWEETEST LITTLE PUPPY...
(MUFFLED LAUGHS)
OK?! SO WHAT'S FUNNY NOW!
SHE'S TOTALLY HAVING
FUN WITH YOU, DUDE!
AND WHEN SHE DOES THE DOG THING
WITH YOU THAT'S
HOW SHE'S LETTING YOU KNOW!
[RUDY] (SIGH) YOU SURE ABOUT
THAT? [TOYA] OH, YEAH!
BUT HERE'S THE THING... DOES
SHE THINK I'M A MANLY MAN?
DOES SHE THINK I'M AMAZING?
DOES SHE THINK I'M AS
MAGNIFICENT AND AS
STRONG AS I REALLY AM?
REALLY. WHAT DOES MISS
ISUZU THINK OF ME?
(YAWN) MAYBE
YOU'RE THINKING ABOUT
THIS TOO MUCH? NIGHTY NIGHT!
WHAT?! WELL IF YOU'RE
NOT GOING TO HELP ME...
THEN I'M GOING TO
SLEEP! (SNORING)
WHATEVER. GOOD NIGHT, RUDY.
[RUDY]
G'NIGHT.
[MINORI] TODAY WE'LL BE
HEADING TO THE SAKAWA ZONE!
[TOYA]
SAKAWA?
[MINORI] BACK IN OUR WORLD,
IT'S SOMEWHERE NEAR ODAWARA.
[SERARA] AREN'T THEY FAMOUS
FOR ITS STEAMED FISH PASTE?
[ISUZU] REALLY? I
DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
[MINORI] OH AND IT LOOKS LIKE
THE ABANDONED ARIBA CASTLE'S
ON THE WAY THERE, TOO.
AND AFTER WE GET THROUGH
THERE, WE'LL HAVE TO BREAK
FROM THE HIGHWAY TO REACH
THE REDSTONE MOUNTAINS.
WE'LL NEED TO DECIDE WHETHER
TO TAKE THE SMALLER ROAD
OR THE ROAD THAT'S LIKE
A MOUNTAIN TRAIL.
THIS AREA IS A PADDY FIELD ZONE
WITH NATURE‐ TYPE MONSTERS.
IT'S GOT FERAL DOGS...
ALONG WITH MONSTROUS BOARS...
AND EVEN THE PLANTS
GET PRETTY VICIOUS,
BUT ONLY IF YOU PROVOKE THEM.
BIG BROTHER SHIROE
TOLD US ABOUT THIS,
BUT THE MONSTERS ON THE ROAD
AREN'T AS POWERFUL AS SOME
OF THE OTHERS WE'VE FACED.
[MINORI] MM‐HM!
AND THAT MEANS WE SHOULDN'T
HAVE A PROBLEM HANDLING
A BUNCH OF THEM AT ONCE!
THEN IT'S TIME FOR
US TO HIT THE ROAD!
[TOYA]
LET'S DO THIS, GUYS!
[ALL]
WOOHOO! YEAH!
[ISAAC]
SO, IS THIS GONNA WORK?
[SHIROE]
YEAH, IT SHOULD BE FINE.
I'M SORRY ABOUT THIS... BUT I
NEEDED SOMEONE TO TRAIN THEM.
YEAH WELL DON'T
WORRY ABOUT IT.
MISTER ISAAC IS REALLY LOOKING
FORWARD TO GETTING THIS GOING.
HEY! DON'T CALL ME
THAT, ALL RIGHT?
OKAY, SO NOW THAT WE'RE
GOING TO BE TRAINING THEM,
HOW MANY LEVELS SHOULD
WE BE SHOOTING FOR?
[SHIROE] WE'RE DOING THIS AS A
GOODWILL GESTURE
FOR OUR FRIENDS IN EASTAL.
JUST GET THEIR KNIGHTS
UP A COUPLE LEVELS.
THAT'S NOT VERY AMBITIOUS.
REMEMBER THESE ARE NPCS... TRY
NOT TO SLAP 'EM AROUND TOO MUCH.
WHAT? WHERE'S
THE FUN IN THAT?
[SHIROE] ISAAC...
[BOTH] HM?
[SHIROE]
PLEASE TELL ME,
YOU WON'T TRY TO JUST
POWER‐LEVEL THEM THROUGH THIS.
OF COURSE! THAT'S THE
EASIEST WAY TO DO IT, RIGHT?!
[ISAAC] ALL THEY HAVE
TO DO IS FOLLOW ME...
I DO THE FIGHTING
AND THEY LEVEL UP!
SEE, EVERYBODY WINS, AND EASTAL
GETS A BUNCHA TRAINED TROOPS!
THAT'S NOT TRAINING,
IT'S CHEATING,
YOU'LL JUST BE INFLATING THEM.
YOU ARE SERIOUSLY UPTIGHT, MAN!
CAN'T WE JUST DO COMBAT
DRILLS OR POWER‐LEVELING?
AH WELL, I'LL JUST RUN 'EM
TIL THEY DROP! (LAUGHS)
[SHIROE, THINKING] OK. MAYBE I
PICKED THE WRONG PERSON
FOR THE JOB. OH WELL, LET'S
JUST HOPE FOR THE BEST.
ALSO, DOES ANYBODY
KNOW WHAT'S BEEN
GOING ON WITH KRUSTY LATELY?
NO... AND HIS FRIEND'S
LIST ISN'T ANSWERING.
TELL YA WHAT; THE WAY HE'S
BEEN BLOWING OFF HIS GUILD
IS UNFORGIVEABLE. THEY'RE
GONNA FALL APART WITHOUT HIM.
I HEARD D. D. D.'S BEEN LOSING
MEMBER AFTER MEMBER
SINCE HE WENT AND
BAILED ON THEM.
[REZARICK] ON THE OTHER HAND,
THEY'VE STILL STUCK TOGETHER
THROUGHOUT THE WHOLE ORDEAL.
GUESS THAT'S A TESTAMENT
TO THEIR LOYALTY.
(EXHALES)
[ISAAC] YOU'RE NOT REALLY
WORRIED, ARE YOU?
WELL SHOULDN'T I BE
WORRIED ABOUT HIM?
AH, IT'S JUST KRUSTY.
HE GETS BORED AND
RUNS OFF, YOU KNOW?
HE'S HAVIN' THE
TIME OF HIS LIFE!
YEAH...
[SHIROE, THINKING] FINE, BUT I'M
STILL WORRIED ABOUT D. D. D.
[EINS] HONESTY'S MEMBERSHIP IS
NOW OVER 1800 GUILD MEMBERS.
THAT'S BETTER THAN WE EVER
ACCOMPLISHED IN
THE PEAK OF OUR GAMING DAYS.
[TOSHI] MAYBE, BUT THE MAJORITY
OF NEW MEMBERS
ARE JUST HERE TO SAY
THEY'RE IN A GUILD, EINS!
THEY DON'T LEAVE THE CITY LIMITS
TO HUNT OR GATHER, AND I DON'T
THINK THEY'RE CRAFTING OR
SELLING ANYTHING EITHER!
[HARUHARU]
HEH... NOTHING BUT PARASITES...
TRUE, WE DIDN'T PICK UP A LOT OF
CONTRIBUTORS... HOWEVER...
[HARUHARU] "HOWEVER" WE DON'T
NEED A BUNCH OF LEACHES
MAKING OUR GUILD SOFT AND LAZY!
THE PEOPLE ARE STARTING
TO NOTICE, IN THE GUILD,
IN THE CITY AND THEY'RE
NOT HAPPY ABOUT IT.
IT IS ONLY A MATTER OF
TIME BEFORE IT BLOWS UP!
I'M DOING EVERYTHING I CAN
AT THE ROUND TABLE
CONFERENCE MEETINGS!
[TOSHI] AND HOW ARE THEY
SUPPOSED TO FIX THIS?
WE JUST NEED TO KICK THEM
OUT LIKE WE USED TO!
[EINS] UH!
[HARUHARU] OR AT THE LEAST
RESTRICT ENTRY INTO THE GUILD!
I COULDN'T DO THAT!
THE SOURCE OF OUR POLITICAL
CLOUT AT THE ROUND TABLE
IS THE NUMBER OF
MEMBERS WE HAVE.
RIGHT NOW, WE'RE THE THIRD
LARGEST GUILD IN AKIHABARA.
WE CAN'T LOSE THAT.
IF WE DON'T TRY TO
KEEP OUR NUMBERS UP
THEN WE WON'T HAVE ANY SAY IN
WHAT GOES ON IN THOSE MEETINGS!
[TOSHI]
WELL, I'LL TELL YOU THIS...
I THINK OUR GUILD, AND
THE CITY AS A WHOLE
WOULD BE BETTER OFF WITH FEWER
WELFARE CASES... "GUILD MASTER."
[EINS]
MMM...
[MINORI]
HUH?!
(GASPING)
[ISUZU]
ARE THOSE CHERRY BLOSSOMS?
[SERARA] I THINK... I THINK
THEY'RE PLUM BLOSSOMS!
[RUDY]
AH... THEY SMELL HEAVENLY!
[TOYA]
YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME!
AW, MAN! WE'RE NOT GETTING
ACROSS HERE ANYTIME SOON.
[MINORI]
WE GOTTA FIND ANOTHER WAY.
[MAN A] HELP! HELP US PLEASE!
(BOTH SURPRISED)
(SCREAMING AND BREATHING HEAVY)
[TOYA]
UH...!
LOOK AT THAT!
WE'VE GOT SOME OGRES!
LET'S GET 'EM OFF THEIR BACKS!
[ALL]
LET'S DO IT!
(SCREAMING)
(GROWLS)
[TOYA] NONE OF 'EM ARE OVER
LEVEL 22! THIS OUGHTA BE EASY!
TOYA!
[TOYA]
YEAH! I'M ON IT!
TIME TO DIE YOU
UGLY PIECE‐A‐CRAP!
(DEATH YELL)
HMPH! SPEARS OF ICE!
(FRIGHTENED)
(GRUNTS)
HMPH!
[TOYA] ARE YOU GUYS
ALL RIGHT? YOU OKAY?
[ROE2, DISTANT] YOU'VE GOT
COMPANY, LITTLE MAN! WATCH OUT!
[TOYA]
HUH? WHA...?
(STARTLED)
[MINORI]
NIGHTSHADE SERVANTS!
THEIR AVERAGE LEVEL IS...
FORTY?! AND THERE'S
FIFTEEN OF THEM!
SPIRIT MONSTERS:
RESISTANT TO ATTACKS USING
POISON AND MENTAL POWERS,
AND THEY'RE IMMUNE
TO INSTANT DEATH.
FIGHTING THEM OFF
IS GONNA BE HARD!
[MINORI, THINKING]
IF WE'RE NOT CAREFUL,
SOME OF US COULD
GET SERIOUSLY HURT.
[TOYA]
I'M GOING IN!
(BATTLE GRUNT)
[TOYA]
DID I EVEN DAMAGE THE THING?!
WAUGH!
[MINORI]
TOYA!
(PAINFUL GRUNTS)
(GROWLS)
[MINORI] HUH?
(WINCE)
[ROE2]
PRINCESS WRAITH!
HWWAAH.
EH.
(GASP)
WHAT THE...
UM... EXCUSE ME...
BUT WHO ARE YOU?
[ROE2]
MY NAME... IS ROE2
I'M A SUMMONER BY TRADE
AND SINCE I AM CURRENTLY
HEADED TO IKOMA,
IT WOULDN'T BE TOO
MUCH OF A STRETCH...
IF YOU CALLED ME A
TRAVELING VAMPIRE.
ANOTHER VILLAIN IN GLASSES...
[ALL]
MM‐HM!
(ROE2 COLLAPSES)
[ALL] HUH?
[ROE2] OH... THE SUN...
[ALL] HUH?!
[ROE2] OH..THE SUN...! (MOANING)
[ALL] WHOA!
[ROE2]
OHHH...! (MOANING)
[AKATSUKI, VOICEOVER] THE NEW
MYSTERIOUS COMPANION IS ROE2.
SHE FINDS JOY IN BEING
TREATED LIKE AN OLDER SISTER.
TOYA AND THE OTHER JUNIOR
MEMBERS CONTINUE
THEIR QUEST IN
SPITE OF HER ANTICS.
ALONG THE WAY, THEY FIND
A GROUP OF ADVENTURERS WHO
FIGHT MONSTERS TO PROTECT
THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
[SHIROE] MY COMRADES
ARE ALWAYS BESIDE ME.