(DISTANT MUTTERINGS)
(CHEERS AND CLAPPING)
[ISUZU]
HM?
[TOYA]
(CHUCKLE)
(INHALE, SIGH)
(MUSIC AND SINGING)
(MUSIC FADING)
[SERARA]
IT WOULD'VE BEEN BETTER
IF MINORI WAS HERE, YOU KNOW?
SHE WANTED TO
COME OUT TONIGHT...
BUT UNFORTUNATELY
SHE HAD TO WORK.
MISS MINORI IS TURNING OUT TO BE
QUITE THE WORKING GIRL NOWADAYS.
DON'T CALL HER THAT, RUDY...
IT MEANS SOMETHIN' ELSE.
(LAUGHTER)
[RUDY]
(LAUGHING) HM?
MISS ISUZU, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU'RE LOOKING A LITTLE DOWN.
UH...? MM‐MM! I'M FINE!
I AM VERY EXCITED!
[EXHALE] ARE
YOU SURE?
YEAH!
YOU WERE WONDERFUL TONIGHT!
REALLY! IT WAS LIKE
LISTENING TO A REAL PRO!
C'MON, SERARA!
THE MANAGER WAS HAPPY
TO HAVE YOU TONIGHT!
HE WAS TOTALLY PATTING HIMSELF
ON THE BACK FOR FINDING YOU!
IT ISN'T THAT BIG OF
A DEAL, TOYA!
HE'S GONNA HAVE ME IN ONE
NIGHT A WEEK AND THAT'S IT!
ALL I'M REALLY DOING ARE
COVERS OF STUFF ANYWAY.
WELL EVERYBODY IN THERE
CERTAINLY ENJOYED IT.
YOU WERE JAMMIN', LITTLE LADY.
MISS ISUZU! YOUR PLAYING IS
BREATHTAKING AND INSPIRING
LIKE THE GREATEST MUSES OF OLD.
GIVE IT A REST, WILLYA?
WE BOTH KNOW I'M
NOT ALL THAT GREAT.
WE JUST ALWAYS HAD INSTRUMENTS
LYING AROUND THE HOUSE,
AND I'D PICK 'EM UP AND PLAY.
YOUR EXQUISITE MELODIES
ENRICHED THE CITY NIGHT!
AND YOUR VOICE
LIFTED MANY HEARTS...
BIRDS AND BEASTS ALIKE
WERE MADE HAPPY.
YOU WERE WONDERFUL.
[ISUZU, ANNOYED] DIDN'T I SAY
TO KNOCK IT OFF RUDY?
HEY! WHY CAN'T I SAY HOW
MAGNIFICENT YOU ARE,
IT IS THE GOD'S HONEST TRUTH?!
I'M GONNA PUNCH YOU
IN YOUR DUMB MOUTH!
[ISUZU] GET BACK HERE
SO I CAN HIT YOU!
[RUDY]
AH! I'M PAYING YOU A COMPLIMENT.
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?!
ON A QUEST?
YEAH, TOYA AND
THE OTHER YOUNG ONES
NEED TO GAIN
SOME EXPERIENCE.
I'D ALSO LIKE TO HAVE
SERARA GO WITH THEM
SO THEY'LL HAVE
ANOTHER HEALER.
IF SHE WANTS TO
GO WITH THEM
I'M PERFECTLY FINE
WITH LETTING HER GO.
WHAT'S THE QUEST FOR?
RIGHT THERE.
[MARIELLE]
HUH? THE MAGIC BAG?
YEP, NONE OTHER THAN
DAZANEGG'S SATCHEL.
THEIR QUEST IS TO FIND THE
PIECES AND PUT THEM TOGETHER.
OH! I TOTALLY REMEMBER THAT ONE.
COOL. YOU HUNT DOWN A WYVERN
FOR ITS LEATHER.
[SHIROE] EXACTLY! AND ALL
OUR JUNIOR MEMBERS
ARE OVER THE MINIMUM LEVEL
TO TAKE THE QUEST.
OH YEAH! THEY'RE ALREADY
LEVEL 45! HOW EXCITING!
MM‐HM. TOYA'S BEEN
ASKING ABOUT IT.
AND LET'S JUST SAY
HE HASN'T BEEN
WHAT I'D CALL "SUBTLE" EITHER.
SO HERE WE GO.
YEAH, WELL, YOU KNOW.
IT IS THE MAGIC BAG!
YOU CAN CARRY ANYTHING
AND EVERYTHING!
[SHIROE] WELL, I DON'T THINK
IT'S JUST THE BAG THEY WANT.
THEY'VE BEEN HERE
ALL THIS TIME
AND THEY STILL HAVEN'T HAD
THE CHANCE TO GO OUT AND
COMPLETE ANY OF THE
LARGER QUESTS.
D'YOU... DO YOU THINK
THEY'LL BE OKAY?
YOU MIGHT BE ASKING A LOT.
[BOTH]
HUH?
[MINORI]
EXCUSE ME!
[MINORI] THOUGHT YOU
COULD USE A REFRESHMENT.
WOW! THANK YOU!
SO, YOU'RE ALREADY DONE WITH
YOUR WORK? THAT WAS FAST.
YEAH!
THANKS A LOT. ACTUALLY
THAT WORKS OUT PERFECTLY.
HUH?
(EXHALES)
[ISUZU, THINKING]
IT'S REALLY NICE FOR EVERYONE
TO SAY ALL THAT STUFF
ABOUT ME...
MUSIC HAS ALWAYS BEEN SUCH A
BIG PART OF MY LIFE, BUT...
I MEAN, I'M GLAD NO ONE
EVER SAID I WAS BAD,
BUT NO ONE'S GONE
SO FAR OUT OF THEIR WAY
TO GIVE ME A COMPLIMENT, EITHER.
SURE, I MEAN I HAVE WHAT IT
TAKES TO BECOME A PRO LIKE DAD,
BUT IT WOULDN'T HURT
IF I PLAYED FOR FUN
FROM TIME TO TIME, WOULD IT?
IT SEEMED LIKE THEY
ALL ENJOYED THE SHOW!
[TOYA]
WOW, SOMEBODY LOOKS LIKE
THEY'VE BEEN UP TO NO GOOD, HMM?
[ISUZU]
EHHHH!
[TOYA]
EHEHEHEH!
(GASP) WAIT WHAT?!
AM I REALLY STILL SMILING?!
[TOYA]
IT'S ALL OVER YOUR FACE!
YOU MUST'VE REALLY
ENJOYED YOURSELF.
YOU SOUNDED REALLY GOOD.
MMMM... THANKS...
HMFPH! IT WAS GREAT!
AND I NEVER THOUGHT
IN MY WILDEST DREAMS
I'D GET TO GO UP ON STAGE
AND LAY DOWN SOME BEATS!
YOU WERE REALLY
GOOD AT IT!
WHATEVER!
SERIOUSLY,
THE BARD CLASS
IS AMAZING TO ME!
I MEAN ABOUT IT, ALL I HAD
TO DO IS BE IN YOUR AURA
AND RIGHT THEN AND THERE
I SUDDENLY KNEW
HOW TO PLAY THE DRUMS.
WELL, HERE'S THE THING.
IT WON'T WORK IF YOU
DON'T ALREADY HAVE
SOME KIND OF TALENT.
AND IF YOU DON'T BELIEVE ME,
JUST ASK RUDY.
BO‐BA‐PFFT!
CHECK IT OUT!
I'M GETTING BETTER, RIGHT!
[RUDY] WHADDYA THINK?!
GETTIN' FUNKY NOW!
[RUDY] AHHH! OH GOD!
(TOYA LAUGHS)
I'M SORRY, SOMEBODY HELP ME!
[TOYA] OH WELL, NICE TRY RUDY.
SO I... I SUPPOSE
THAT MEANS YOU MUST HAVE
A REALLY GOOD EAR
FOR MUSIC, HUH, ISUZU?
UUUH NO, NOT NECESSARILY!
IT'S JUST THAT I'VE BEEN
DOING THIS SORTA THING
EVER SINCE I WAS A KID.
[TOYA] I GET IT...
[ISUZU] UH?
[TOYA]
I PLAYED SOCCER. A LOT.
I PRACTICED ALL THE TIME.
BUT THERE WAS NO WAY I WAS EVER
GONNA BE BETTER THAN THE GUYS
WHO JUST HAD THE KNACK FOR IT.
YOU CAN TELL WHEN SOMEONE'S A
NATURAL, EVEN WHEN HE'S A KID.
BUT YOU KNOW,
I STILL HAD FUN PLAYING EVEN
THOUGH I WASN'T ALL THAT GOOD.
JUST LIKE YOU'RE
STILL HAVING FUN
PLAYING YOUR MUSIC, AREN'T YOU?
UUUH...? MM‐HM.
OF COURSE YOU ARE.
MM‐HM.
SO IF YOU GET A CHANCE
TO PLAY OUT THERE,
WHAT'S THE BIG PROBLEM?
OH...
(ISUZU EXHALES)
I WAS JUST THINKING...
REMEMBER WHAT IT WAS LIKE AFTER
WE GOT SAVED FROM HAMELIN?
[TOYA] HUH?
[ISUZU] I'D BEEN WITH
CRESCENT MOON FOR QUITE A WHILE.
AND THEN, YOU AND ME AND MINORI
ALL JOINED LOG HORIZON
AROUND THE SAME TIME.
BUT, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I SUDDENLY HAD MY FREEDOM,
AND I REALLY DIDN'T KNOW WHAT
I WAS GONNA DO WITH MYSELF.
IT WASN'T LONG AFTER THAT,
I FOUND THIS LUTE.
IT WAS JUST SITTING THERE.
IT WAS ENGRAVED WITH A
MOTHER‐OF‐PEARL DESIGN
THAT FOR SOME REASON,
REMINDED ME OF A DOLPHIN.
IT WAS BEAUTIFUL!
IT TURNS OUT THAT MARIELLE
MADE IT A LONG TIME AGO,
SO I ASKED IF SHE WOULDN'T
MIND GIVING IT TO ME.
IT MODIFIED IT
A COUPLE TIMES MYSELF...
IT'S LIKE MY BABY...
MY ONE AND ONLY,
MY FLYING DOLPHIN.
THIS INSTRUMENT OF MINE,
IT'S ALL I REALLY NEED.
IT MOTIVATES ME TO KEEP PLAYING.
AND PLAYING, IN TIMES LIKE
THESE, IS A REAL BLESSING.
MPH.
[MINORI] TOYA! ISUZU!
[BOTH] HUH?
HUH? HEY!
BACK ALREADY?
[MINORI] SO UH... SHIROE NEEDS
TO TELL US SOMETHING?
NOT SURE WHAT ABOUT,
BUT HE SAID IT'S IMPORTANT.
[BOTH]
HUH?
[TOYA]
WE'RE GOING ON A QUEST?!
REALLY? THAT'S AWESOME!
THOSE ARE THE REDSTONE MOUNTAINS
AROUND NAGANO, AREN'T THEY?!
THERE'RE GONNA BE ALL KINDS OF
MOUNTAINS, RIVERS, AND FORESTS!
ON TOP OF THAT, WE'RE GONNA
MEET A WHOLE BUNCHA NEW PEOPLE!
[MINORI] TOYA! YOU NEED TO
FOCUS ON PACKING.
AND DON'T FORGET YOUR UNDERWEAR!
COME ON! I CAN ONLY JAM
SO MUCH STUFF INTO MY BAG.
IF WE'RE LUCKY WHILE
WE'RE OUT THERE,
MAYBE I'LL GET THE MAGIC BAG.
FORTUNATELY, YOU HAVE
A WELL‐SEASONED
TRAVELER EXTRAORDINAIRE
IN RUNDELLHAUS KODE!
OH YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT!
YOU'VE ALREADY DONE A LOT OF
TRAVELING HAVEN'T YOU RUDY?!
YES! WHILE IT WAS TRUE
I TRAVELED WITH AN ADVENTURER
TO BOGPORT, I MADE THE REST
OF THE JOURNEY A' SOLO.
I HAVE A WEALTH OF EXPERIENCE!
HUH?
AAAUUGHHHHH!!!
HUH? RUDY, YOU OKAY?
WHERE IN GOD'S NAME
IS MY HAIRBRUSH!
I CAN'T MAINTAIN MY
INCREDIBLENESS
WITHOUT MY DIVINE COIFFURE!
MY ELEGANT STRANDS WILL
BE BUT A NEST OF RATS!
[RUDY] BY THE GODS,
WHY HAVE I BEEN BROUGHT
THIS VILE PUNISHMENT!
[ISUZU] WHOA, EASY. FOUND IT.
[RUDY] OOOH! UH?
[ISUZU] HERE. UH?
AAAH! MISS ISUZU!
YOU'VE SINGLE‐HANDEDLY
SAVED MY MANLINESS!
[ISUZU] UHAH! OKAY,
WELL USE YOUR MANLINESS
TO PICK ALL THIS CRAP UP.
(GIGGLES)
ARE YOU PIPSQUEAKS
READY TO GET AFTER IT?
[TOYA]
YOU KNOW IT, MASTER NAOTSUGU!
[NAOTSUGU] MAKE SURE YOU GET
A FEW BARRELS OF AGUA
LOADED UP ON THE WAGON.
[TOYA]
WE GOT IT COVERED!
GOOD JOB.
HUH? WHAAA?!
[TETORA] HOW'S EVERYBODY DOIN'?!
ARE YOU OKAY?!
HEY! GET YOUR SCRAWNY
BUTT OUTTA MY SHIRT!
[NAOTSUGU] I'M NOT KIDDIN'!
[TETORA] IF YA WANT ANY
ADVICE ON THE BESTEST AND
SAFEST WAYS TO TRAVEL,
TETORA‐BABY'S GOT THE 411!
AFTER ALL, THERE'S NO ONE BETTER
TO ASK THAN A WORLD RENOWNED...
[TETORA] STARLET!
[NAOTSUGU] GET OFF ME
OR I'M GONNA BREAK YOU
IN HALF, I SWEAR TO GOD!
[TETORA] OH, WHO'RE YOU KIDDING
YOU KNOW YOU LOVE IT,
MR. MUSCLES! WHEE! SEE YA!
[NAOTSUGU] (GRUNTS)
GET BACK HERE, YOU HUSSY!
[MINORI] UH... HUH?
(LAUGHTER)
[AKATSUKI] MPH...
[MINORI] UH...
[SERARA] HM?
THAT WAS KINDA WEIRD...
I THINK THEY'RE WORRIED
ABOUT US, YOU GUYS.
THAT'S NOT REALLY NEW.
THEY'VE BEEN LOOKING OUT
FOR US SINCE WE GOT HERE.
IT MIGHT SOUND CRAZY, BUT I
THINK THEY'RE GONNA MISS US.
MM‐HM, AND I GUESS THEY'RE
TRYING TO BE SUBTLE ABOUT IT.
AND IT'S NOT WORKING.
I GET THE FACT THAT THEY
WANNA KEEP US SAFE...
BUT I WANNA DO THIS ONE
ON MY OWN, YOU KNOW.
(EXHALES)
[ISUZU] HEY, YOU WANNA BET ON
WHO'S COMING NEXT? WHADDYA SAY?
[SERARA] NYANTA!
[MINORI] MAYBE MASTER SHIROE?
[SHIROE] SO HOW'S IT GOING,
YOU GUYS?
[ISUZU] YOU WIN, MINORI!
(SNICKERING)
[SHIROE]
HM? WHAT'S GOING ON?
[MINORI]
OH! UH, NOTHING!
YEAH, WE SHOULD HAVE ALL OUR
STUFF PACKED AND READY TO GO
IN JUST A FEW MINUTES.
ALL WE REALLY HAVE LEFT
IS PROVISIONING,
AND ACQUIRING SOME
WEAPONS AND A WAGON.
OH, AND CHIEF NYANTA'S
HELPING US PICK ONE OUT!
'KAY...
HOPEFULLY THIS MAP I DREW UP
WILL BE HELPFUL.
(GASP)
LATER.
[MINORI] THANKS!
[RUDY] ALL RIGHT!
LET'S GET THIS MESS CLEANED UP
AND DO SOME SHOPPING.
[ALL] MM‐HM!
YEAH...
UH... HEY... YOU GONNA
PACK THAT MAP OR WHAT?
(GASP)
(EXHALE)
[TATARA]
WELCOME.
[RUDY] HELLO!
[TOYA] HEY, THERE!
[RUDY] WE NEED TO GET
SOME SHIELDS AND ARMOR
AFTER WE STOCK UP ON WEAPONS...
WE MIGHT END UP GOING
TO ANOTHER STORE OR TWO.
UHN...
[RUDY]
OH, HO! NOW THAT'S A SAMURAI!
YOU HOLD THAT KATANA
LIKE YOU'RE THE REAL DEAL!
[TOYA]
YEAH! WHILE WE'RE IN THE STORE,
I WANTED TO GET
ANOTHER SWORD, YOU KNOW?
BUT I'M KINDA LIMITED.
I CAN'T GET SOMETHING THAT'S
HIGHER THAN MY CURRENT LEVEL.
[AKATSUKI] YOU MIGHT
WANNA TRY CROW'S FEET.
[AKATSUKI] YOU SPREAD
THEM ON THE GROUND
AND THEY IMPALE
YOUR OPPONENT'S FEET.
[NAOTSUGU]
YOU LOOKING FOR MORE GEAR?
SQUIRTY PANTS HERE DRAGGED
ME OUT WEAPON'S SHOPPING.
[AKATSUKI]
HMM...
MAYBE YOU'D BE BETTER OFF
USING SHURIKEN.
[TATARA] TRUE, ANY CLASS CAN
USE THEM AS A THROWING WEAPON.
THEY CAN BE MASTERED QUICKLY.
YOU ALSO MIGHT
WANNA TRY A KUNAI.
YOU CAN USE
THEM AS TOOLS...
AND FOR STABBING PEOPLE.
UUUH... OKAY...
YEAH, IT'S NOT ALL ABOUT YOUR
WEAPONS, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
YOU HAVE TO HAVE YOUR NOGGIN ON
STRAIGHT AND YOUR BODY IN SHAPE!
LISTEN! A REAL MAN WILL RISK
HIS LIFE TO PROTECT PEOPLE,
Y'UNDERSTAND?
[TOYA]
MM‐HM! I GOT IT, MASTER!
UHUH! AND IF YOU EVER FEEL
LIKE THINGS ARE TOO MUCH...
JUST IMAGINE SOME
PANTIES AND...
WAAAAAAUGH!
[NAOTSUGU]
LIKE NOW'S A GOOD TIME!
(HAPPY NOISE)
AHHH!
AWWW!
[ALL] THEY'RE SO CUTE!
[ISUZU] SO THESE FLUTES
ARE FOR SUMMONING HORSES?
THAT IS SO COOL!
YOU CAN SUMMON ALL KINDS
OF THINGS WITH THESE!
EVERYTHING FROM VICIOUS BEASTS
TO CUTESY CRITTERS! UH?
GROSS! YOU CAN EVEN SUMMON NASTY
STUFF LIKE RATS AND SNAKES!
GOT ANYTHING FOR
A GRIFFON IN HERE?!
I'D REALLY LIKE ONE OF THOSE!
[SHOPKEEPER]
YOU CAN'T GET A FLUTE LIKE THAT
UNLESS YOU CLEAR AN EXTREMELY
DIFFICULT QUEST, YOUNG LADY!
IT'S THE ONLY WAY TO GET
A GRIFFON OR A PEGASUS.
AWWW! NOW I WANT ONE!
MY OWN WHITE PEGASUS!
JUST RIDING THROUGH THE BREEZE!
[NYANTA]
NYA?
WILL THIS GET ME
A PEGASUS?
[NYANTA] THAT'S RIGHT, I
COMPLETED A DEATH‐DEFYING QUEST
TO GET THAT FLUTE
JUST FOR YOU DARLIN'.
(INHALE) OH MY GOSH...
YOU'RE THE BEST! (SQUEAL)
[NYANTA] LET'S GO FOR A RIDE,
GO AHEAD, AND SUMMON IT.
OKAY!
[SHOPKEEPER] NO, WAIT!
[MINORI] AH! NO!
[ISUZU] OH GOD,
WHAT'VE YOU DONE?
(TRILLING AND GROWLING)
(SCREAMING)
[SERARA] SORRY GUYS...
ONE THING'S FOR SURE,
RODERICK'S MERCHANT GUILD
SURE HAS A LOT OF WAGONS!
CHECK IT OUT! THAT'D BE
LIKE RIDING IN A TANK!
THIS ONE'S A LEVEL 80...
FIRE RESISTANT, STANDS UP
WELL TO LIGHTNING. YEAH.
I TOTALLY WANT THIS!
OH? (NERVOUS LAUGHTER)
YEAH, THAT LOOKS
PRETTY EXPENSIVE.
[RODERICK]
HMMM...
[TOYA]
OHHH (ADORING)
[RODERICK] THIS IS
WHAT IT'LL RUN YA.
[MINORI] D'AHH!
[MINORI] LET'S FIND
SOMETHING ELSE, TOYA!
[TOYA] AW COME ON.
I WAS JUST LOOKIN'!
[RODERICK] HUH?
[MINORI] EH...
(EXHALE) S'NOT
QUITE OUR STYLE...
NOW, SOME OF THESE WERE
PIMPED OUT BY WAGON FANATICS.
[RUDY] THAT'S THE ONE!
[BOTH] HUH?
[RUDY]
I AM A NOBLE, MY FRIENDS.
NOT ONLY THAT,
I AM ALSO AN ADVENTURER!
MEANING, THIS MIGHTY WAGON
IS PERFECT TRANSPORT FOR
MY FEATS OF DARING DO!
(HORN BLOWING)
(EXHALE)
[ISUZU] DOWN, BOY.
WE CAN'T AFFORD IT.
WELL NOW, I BET THIS'LL
BE A BIT MORE REASONABLE.
[TOYA]
MMM... IT'S REALLY NICE!
[RUDY]
MM‐HMM!
YEAH, YOU CERTAINLY HAVE
A GOOD EYE, YOUNG MAN.
NOW IT MIGHT LOOK LIKE A SIMPLE
WAGON BUT WE'VE IMPROVED
THE UNDERCARRIAGE
AND THE SUSPENSION.
IT'S LIGHTWEIGHT,
HIGHLY DURABLE,
AND THE STEERING ASSEMBLY
HAS A TURNING RADIUS OF...
UH... ARE YOU TRYING TO
HIKE UP THE PRICE ON US?
I THINK I'LL LEAVE
THE HAGGLING TO MINORI.
[RODERICK] I STILL OWE
CHIEF NYANTA A FAVOR
FOR SHOWING ME THE
BEST PLACE TO HAVE
A BOWL OF RAMEN
A WHILE BACK.
I COULD PROBABLY
SWING A DISCOUNT.
[ALL] SCORE! WOOHOO!
(HORSES GRUNTING)
(SERARA BREATHING QUICKLY)
OOH! DANISH AND CROISSANT,
YOU MUST BE REALLY HUNGRY!
(GIGGLE) SERARA NAMED THEM,
CAN'T YA TELL?
[RUDY] MM‐HMM...
ISUZU! YOU WANNA GIVE THE
HORSEYS SOME CABBAGE?!
YEAH! THAT'D BE GREAT!
RUDY, COME HELP ME!
OH! HEH! I'VE SPENT
TOO MUCH TIME
WITH THE BEASTS
TO SIMPLY PLAY!
I KNOW I'VE NEVER SAID THIS,
BUT I'M ACTUALLY
A COMPLETE PROFESSIONAL WHEN IT
COMES TO WORKING WITH HORSES!
GRR... OH, COME ON! COULD YOU
STOP BEING SUCH A PRISS
AND FEED THE STINKIN' HORSES?!
[SERARA] UH...?
[ISUZU] OH? UH...
MISS ISUZU! HORSES
ARE VERY SENSITIVE,
THEY PICK UP ON SUCH TALK!
HAVE YOU NO COMPASSION
FOR THEIR FEELINGS?
UH...! SORRY HORSEYS!
I'M SORRY!
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO DO
BETTER THAN, THAT MISS ISUZU.
[ISUZU]
UH! I'M REALLY SORRY!
OKAY! IT'S YOUR TURN NOW!
WHADDYA MEAN IT'S
"MY TURN"?! D'AHH!
AH! I'M SO SORRY!
I'M REALLY SORRY, OKAY?! ER...
YEAH! IT'S ALL DONE!
[RUDY]
WOW, THAT'S STUNNING.
[ISUZU]
YEP, IT'S REALLY COOL!
[MINORI] ALL THIS PUPPY
NEEDS IS A PERSONAL TOUCH!
[ALL] AHHH!
[RUDY] PLEASE, PLEASE STOP,
I'M BEGGING YOU!
(DINNER TABLE CHATTER)
THE GRAB TONIGHT COMES TO US
COURTESY OF SERARA.
(GIGGLE) CHIEF NYANTA'S
PUT IN A LOT OF TIME
TRYING TO TEACH ME THE FINER
POINTS OF BEING A CHEF;
HE LET ME DO
THE COOKING THIS TIME.
YEAH OKAY, AND THAT APRON
DRESS IS REALLY NICE!
I BORROWED IT ONCE MYSELF...
BUT YOU LOOK LIKE YOU
JUST GOT MARRIED!
HUH?! I‐ I REALLY ‐
LOOK LIKE I'M MARRIED?
I REALLY DO LOOK
LIKE I'M MARRIED?!
OH MY GOODNESS. OHHHH...
[TETORA] SAFE! GOTCHA...
[ALL]
THANK YOU FOR THE FOOD!
MMMM! DELICIOUS!
YEAH IT IS!
AND HERE I WAS WORRIED THAT
IF WE WENT OUT ON THE ROAD
WITHOUT CHIEF NYANTA, WE'D BE
STUCK WITH TERRIBLE FOOD.
MM‐HMM! YEAH, YOU NAILED IT!
[SERARA] HM.
[NYANTA] UH‐HUH.
(SERARA GIGGLING)
(NYANTA CHUCKLING)
[TOYA] NOW THAT I
THINK ABOUT IT, ISUZU,
AREN'T YOU KINDA BUMMED
ABOUT LEAVING?
HUH? WHY'S THAT?
YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE ABLE TO
HAVE ANY PERFORMANCES OUT THERE.
YEAH, BUT... WE CAN
MAKE THE WHOLE TRIP
LIKE OUR OWN
LITTLE TOUR, Y'KNOW?
A TOUR?
THAT'S WHEN A ROCK BAND
HITS THE ROAD,
MAKES OUT WITH ALL THE LOCALS
AND PUKES IN THE HOTEL.
UH HUH! YOU GOT IT!
GET YOUR TICKETS NOW FOLKS!
WHOA! YEAH! WE CAN PLAY A
WHOLE BUNCH OF SHOWS ON THE WAY!
[ALL] HUH?
[TOYA] MM‐HM!
GOING ON TOUR!
(SINGING) WE'RE GONNA ROCK
THE ENTIRE WORLD!
JUST TRY NOT TO BE OVERSHADOWED
BY MY SHINING AMAZINGNESS!
THEIR DESTINATION
LIES BEYOND IZU.
HUH?
GOING ON TOUR WITH YOUR MUSIC!
THAT'S FANTASTIC!
ARE YOU GONNA DO ALL 42
WHEN YOU'RE OUT THERE?
FORTY‐TWO? I DON'T THINK WE'RE
GONNA HIT THAT MANY VILLAGES.
NO, "THE 42" IS
WHAT WE'VE ALWAYS‐
ON THE ROUTE WE'RE TAKING
TO THE REDSTONE MOUNTAINS,
WE'RE PROBABLY ONLY GONNA COME
ACROSS FOUR OR FIVE VILLAGES.
THIS IS GONNA BE SO COOL!
WE'LL BE LIKE
ROCK STARS ON TOUR!
I MEAN WE'LL HAVE TO STOP
AT EVERY VILLAGE FOR WATER
AND SUPPLIES ANYWAY!
UH‐HUH, IF IT'S ALL RIGHT
WITH YOU, SHIROE?
MM‐HM... DEFINITELY.
DON'T GO TRYING ANYTHING
STUPID OUT THERE...
JUST CALL US IF
THINGS GET HAIRY.
WHOA, I THINK
IT WOULD BE BETTER
IF THEY STAYED OFF THE
TELEPATHIC NETWORK.
[ALL] OHHH...?
[NAOTSUGU]
UH... YOU SERIOUS?
IT'S THE POINT OF THEM
GOING OUT ALONE, NAOTSUGU...
THEY NEED TO SOLVE
PROBLEMS ON THEIR OWN.
ALL OF YOU SHOULD THINK
OF THIS WHOLE JOURNEY
AS AN EXTENDED EXERCISE
IN CRITICAL THINKING.
NOT TO MENTION
MEETING NEW PEOPLE,
AND SEEING AND
DOING NEW THINGS.
THAT'S RIGHT! AND YOU
SHOULD DEFINITELY ALLOW ME
TO HANDLE NAVIGATION
AND NEGOTIATIONS!
YEAH! THIS'LL BE A GREAT
EXPERIENCE! WHAT'DYA SAY ISUZU?!
OKAY...
HM? AREN'T YOU EXCITED?
(UNCERTAIN)
UH, SURE...
I'M THRILLED BEYOND WORDS!
I MIGHT HAVE TO GET RUDY HERE
TO FETCH ME SOME EXTRA STRINGS
WHENEVER THEY BREAK ON ME!
(LAUGHTER)
[RUDY] OW, THAT HURTS!
LET GO, MISS ISUZU!
[ISUZU] OH, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE A MANLY MAN.
YOU SHOULD BE ABLE TO
HANDLE ONE LITTLE BARD.
(HORSES NEIGHING)
[MINORI] AND WE'RE OFF!
[TOYA] WELL WE'RE OFF!
[SERARA] SEE YA LATER!
(LAUGHTER)
REMEMBER MAINTAINING
YOUR WEAPONS IS CRUCIAL.
IF YOU EVER START
FEELING LONELY,
REMEMBER YOU CAN ALWAYS
JUST THINK OF ME!
BE SAFE OUT THERE, HM.
(CRYING)
AHHH!
WE'RE FINALLY DOING IT!
MM‐HM! THERE'S A
LOT OF ROAD AHEAD.
THE START OF OUR WORLD TOUR!
IT'S ADVENTURE TIME!
LET'S DO THIS?!
[MINORI, THINKING]
WELL MASTER SHIROE, HERE I GO!
WITH A BUNCH OF ADVENTURES,
JUST WAITING FOR ME!
[TOYA] LET'S GO! WE'RE HEADED
INTO THE WEST YOU GUYS!
[AKATSUKI, VOICEOVER]
MINORI AND FRIENDS
ARE FULLY ENJOYING
THEIR JOURNEY.
FROM FUN EXPERIENCES
TO DIFFICULT TRIALS,
EVERYTHING ENCOUNTERED
IN THIS NEW WORLD
MAKE THEIR HEARTS DANCE.
HOWEVER, THEIR JOURNEY BEGINS
TO FEEL STRANGE AND UNEASY.
A MYSTERIOUS FIGURE
APPEARS BEFORE THEM.
A NEW STRANGER IN GLASSES
GREETS OUR YOUNG ADVENTURERS.
[SHIROE] MY COMRADES
ARE ALWAYS BESIDE ME.