[opening theme song]
SOICHIRO (ON PHONE):
Light, there's
another message from
the second Kira.
It was sent to Sakura TV
and we intercepted it.
I'm told it's a video
and a journal this time.
Anyway, I figured
I should tell you.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): A journal?
What is that idiot up to now?
Why can't he just wait?
-He wanted the
journal shown on TV?
-Yes.
This is it.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Hmm.
2006?
These entries are
from last year.
-Please take a look at the
entry he made on the 30th.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Hmm.
"Confirmed our shinigami
at the Tokyo Dome."
This is probably
supposed to mean
that he plans to do
this on May 30th.
If this were aired
on TV, his intentions
would be obvious to
anyone who sees it.
-[laughs]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Besides,
he can't see my shinigami
unless he touches my Death Note.
How's he planning to do that?
-Hey, Rem?
REM: Hmm?
-I forget.
Why can't I see my
own lifespan even
though I have shinigami eyes?
Do you think you
could tell me again?
-Humans with shinigami
eyes only need
to know the lifespan
of their victims.
And just as we can't see the
lifespan of others of our kind,
humans who possess a
Death Note cannot see each
other's lifespan,
even with the eyes.
-Hmm.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): "May 22nd.
My friend and I showed off
our notebooks in Aoyama."
If by "notebooks" he's
referring to our Death Notes,
that's something that could
only be understood by me.
And as for the
police, they'll be
distracted by the
May 30th entry.
"We confirmed our shinigami
at the baseball game
in the Tokyo Dome.
It must've been
intended for them.
I'm almost positive that the
real message from this diary
is the one regarding Aoyama.
But if that's the case-- hmm.
-What do you think?
Is it real?
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): I have to
be careful not to say too much.
Better to wait and hear
his opinion, first.
-At this point in time,
all I can say for sure
is, he must be stupid.
-Yeah, I agree.
I mean it's
completely obvious he
wants to meet Kira
at the home game.
-Doesn't he
understand what would
happen if we aired this message?
It would create an
immediate panic,
and the game would
have to be canceled.
-To be honest, it's so
stupid, I'm not even sure
how to deal with this
whole situation anymore.
If we make the diary
public, then we'll
be forced to make some kind
of televised announcement
canceling the game on the 30th.
But if we don't
broadcast it, we can
be sure the second
Kira won't do anything.
-Won't canceling the
game make him angry?
There's no telling
what he'll do.
-Frankly, that's
not a big concern.
From what we've witnessed,
it's safe to say
the second Kira
admires the real one.
He gave his word to
the Kira we invented
that he'd refrain from
killing aimlessly.
I'm inclined to believe that.
I say we make it
public, and we air
an announcement
canceling the game.
At the same time we'll
announce that, on May 30th,
we're going to
set up checkpoints
on all roads leading
to the Tokyo Dome.
And finally, we'll
send a response
from our invented Kira.
Something like, I understand,
and I agree to meet you there.
-Ryuzaki, you don't honestly
expect him to go there
if we set up checkpoints
around the dome, do you?
I don't think that Kira
would even consider it.
But it's possible
the other one might.
It all depends on how
stupid he really is.
However, assuming he's not
actually the idiot we think is,
there could be
another message hidden
in this diary, one
that's not so obvious.
If there's a message
written in some code
that only people who have this
shinigami power can understand,
there'd be no way for
me to decipher it.
Still, it would only
make sense for us
to look into all the places that
were mentioned in the journal.
Uh, 22nd, he's meeting
a friend in Aoyama.
24th, meeting another
friend in Shibuya.
We have to be prepared
for the possibility
that all of our efforts
will be fruitless.
Let's keep an eye out for
people with notebooks in Aoyama
and people in clothing
stores in Shibuya.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
It's as I thought.
If this phony Kira slips
up and gets apprehended,
at the very least I have
to obtain his notebook.
And in the worst
case, I may end up
having to kill everyone there.
-All we can do is place
more surveillance cameras
in Aoyama and
Shibuya in the hopes
that we might capture somebody.
We should also arrange to
have undercover officers
in both locations
on these dates.
I should probably go
to Aoyama and Shibuya
since I blend in with
the crowd there, ya know?
-I'll go, too.
-But, Light--
-I'll be all right.
Don't worry.
Aoyama and Shibuya are
places I'd go anyway.
Not to mention,
out of all of us,
I'd probably look the most
natural hanging out with Matsui
there.
Besides, the second Kira
will be there looking
for Kira, not for the police.
LIGHT: OK, we'll talk more
about our trips tomorrow.
MATSUDA: Sounds good, Light.
See you tomorrow.
Careful getting home.
[phone ringing]
-Uh?
[sighs] It never fails.
The second I'm out the door,
my phone starts ringing.
Yes?
L (ON PHONE): It's Ryuzaki.
When you two are
working together,
I want you to keep a close
eye on Light the entire time.
And please keep this
between you and me.
-Uh, sure.
Yeah, I understand.
I guess he still plans
to investigate Light
until the probability that
he's Kira reaches zero.
-I'm home.
-Hello, dear.
You're back quite late today.
-Yeah.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): I'm supposed
to keep the fact that I'm
helping with the Kira
investigation a secret.
-Uh, It's because I was
hanging out my girlfriend.
-Your?
SAYU:
[excited scream and giggle]
What?
Light, you have a
girlfriend, now?
What's her name?
-It's not that surprising.
I'm 18 and I'm in
university now.
Of course I have a girlfriend.
You should look for
a boyfriend, Sayu.
-Huh?
A boyfriend?
What's that supposed to mean?
-Light, aren't you going
to have any dinner?
-Actually, I'm still full from
room service at the hotel.
--[squeal] I can't believe
you just said that to Mom.
So what's this about a hotel?
Sounds pretty suspicious.
-OK, Ryuk.
We need to have a little talk.
-Ah, should've known.
-And I'd appreciate an
answer, if you could.
If two shinigami happen to
meet in the human world,
are they allowed to
speak to each other?
-Hard to say.
As long as I'm
attached to a human,
I'd say it's against
the rules, unless I
had their permission, first.
But there's no laws
against it either,
so I guess it's possible
that another shinigami might
talk to me.
-So does that mean that if
this fake Kira's shinigami were
to see you, there's
a chance he might
mention the fact
that you're with me
and reveal that I'm Kira?
-They probably wouldn't, but it
depends on their personality.
-And if this kind of
situation did arise,
I can assume that you'll
act the way you normally do?
-Yeah.
Even if I see another
human with a shinigami,
I'm not going to tell you.
-Well, I definitely think
you've got the right approach.
-Meh.
Thanks.
-Huh?
There's no way.
Did he really think
this far ahead?
-What is it?
-Aoyama is a big area.
I was searching for
possible meeting places
when I stumbled across this.
On the 22nd, there's
a big event going
on at a club in Aoyama
called the Note Blue.
Aoyama-- "blue mountain."
"Note" and "blue"-- it's a code.
-Well, well.
If you ask me, that's
pretty elaborate.
-He might be smarter
than I thought.
Which means I'll have to be that
much more careful from now on.
In any case, this
Note Blue place
is definitely
worth checking out.
-What's the point in
going there if you
don't want him to find
out that you're Kira?
You really think
it's worth the risk?
-Uh, excuse me, Light?
So what's going on here?
-Oh.
These are some of my
friends from school.
[shy laughter]
-Nice to meet you.
-This is my cousin, Taro.
It's his first
time ever in Tokyo,
and he wants to see
Aoyama and Roppongi,
so I figured the least we could
do is show him a good time.
I'm counting on you guys.
Oh, yeah.
He also told me he's
looking for a girlfriend,
so does anyone
want to volunteer?
-Hey, I never said that.
MATSUDA (VOICEOVER):
I'm impressed, Light.
I doubt that anyone would ever
suspect that there was a police
detective hanging around
with these students.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): With all of
us walking together like this,
even if Ryuk is
seen, no one would
be able to tell which
one of us he's following.
It's also a defense against
L's surveillance cameras.
Not such a bad way to
investigate, really.
I just have so stay
relaxed and keep an eye
on the entrance of the
Note Blue when it opens.
MISA (VOICEOVER): Found you!
Moon Yagami, is it?
You're the only one whose
lifespan I can't see.
He's Kira.
I can't believe it.
I never thought it would
be this easy to find him.
-All right, Rem.
Time to go.
-Huh.
You finally found him and
now you just want to leave?
-Well, I can't go up to
him and say, "Hi, Kira!
Nice to meet you.
I'm the one who sent
you the messages,"
with all these people around.
I know his name now, so I can
easily find out all about him.
After all, it's
such a unique name.
[music playing]
-Ohh, It's written as
"Moon" but read as "Light."
Light Yagami.
He sure is amazing.
Look at all this stuff.
He won the national
tennis championship
when he was in his second and
third years of junior high.
He gave an address as freshman
representative at this year's
entrance ceremony
at To-Oh University.
I can't find a picture
of him, but there
won't be anyone else with
a name like Light Yagami.
MISA (VOICEOVER): Who
would've ever thought
that Kira would be so
young and handsome?
Everything about him is
better than I imagined.
I can't believe how easy it was
to purchase this information.
The world sure is a scary place.
I even know his
home address now.
-So we were there both days, in
Aoyama on the 22nd and Shibuya
on the 24th, and we observed
nothing of significance
on either occasion.
That leaves us with only
the Dome on the 30th.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
I didn't notice
anyone who looked
suspicious at the Note Blue.
Was he serious about the Dome?
[beeping]
WATARI (ON LAPTOP): Ryuzaki,
apparently Sakura TV has just
received another message
from the second Kira.
It was postmarked on the 23rd.
-I'm happy to say that
I have found Kira.
To all the people at
the television station
and the police department, I'd
like to thank you very much.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Huh?
I- Impossible!
Where, in Aoyama?
His shinigami.
It must have seen Ryuk and
picked me out of the crowd.
No!
No, there's no way he could've
known who Ryuk was attached to.
I checked repeatedly that
no one was following me.
L (VOICEOVER): If this is
true, the only possible event
that would correspond with this
tape being mailed on the 23rd
is the entry regarding
Aoyama on the 22nd.
The only ones from the
taskforce who went to Aoyama
are Matsuda and Light Yagami.
Is Light really Kira after all?
Still, there's no proof it
even happened in Aoyama.
-This is a disaster
if he found him.
-Yeah.
It most likely means that
the two Kiras are now
cooperating with each other.
-At this point, I don't think we
should jump to any conclusions.
The second Kira is
only saying that he
found him, nothing more.
He may not have
made contact yet.
Now that it's come
to this-- --we
have no choice but to
communicate as the police
directly with the second Kira.
-You want to send a message?
-Yes.
The police need to
reach out to the copycat
and offer him a deal.
We need to negotiate
with him to see
if we can get Kira's real name.
--[laughs] That's the last thing
you wanted to hear, right?
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
This isn't good.
I have no idea how the fake
Kira will react to this.
But I have no means
of stopping the police
from sending this message.
TV ANNOUNCER: If Kira
doesn't yet know your name,
it may not be too
late for you, provided
you are willing to cooperate.
Whatever you do, you must not
approach Kira out of curiosity.
Make no mistake-- Kira will
kill you if you contact him.
You'll be used and disposed of.
Consider your own
life for a moment.
Yours, like every other
life, has an intrinsic value.
Now is your chance
to right past wrongs
by sharing what you
know about Kira.
Only you can help us bring
his reign of terror to an end.
-Hmm.
-Where are you going?
-To introduce myself.
REM: So this is what you meant.
-Oh.
Could that be your father?
-Coming!
Welcome h-- uh, hi.
-Hello and good evening.
My name is Misa Amane.
I just came by to give
Light an important notebook
he left at school earlier today.
-Could you wait
here for a second?
Light!
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Notebook?
Could it be?
MISA: Um, pleased to meet you.
I'm Misa Amane.
I thought you might get worried
if you saw that message on TV.
I just couldn't take it anymore,
so I brought this notebook.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
[inward shudder] A Death Note.
A shinigami.
She's the fake Kira.
LIGHT: Please, come in.
MISA: Are you sure it's OK?
Thanks.
Mom, she came all this
way to return my notebook.
Could you make us some tea?
-Sure, I don't see why not.
-Hmm?
I already told you about her.
LIGHT: Have a seat.
-Oh.
Um, thank you.
-How did you find me?
-I knew it.
You never made the
shinigami eye deal.
When you have the
shinigami eyes like I do,
you can see most people's
name and lifespan
just by looking at them.
However, you can't
see the lifespan
of any person who
possesses a Death Note.
-No kidding.
I have to admit, even I wasn't
aware of that little detail.
Well, now you've
managed to find me.
But you were careless.
What if you were
caught by the police?
Then they'd know
everything about Kira.
-It's all right.
Because the police
didn't catch me,
and if I do as you say from now
on, they'll never be able to.
So we're safe.
After all, don't you need
someone to see L's name?
If you want, I
could be your eyes.
So--
-Yeah?
So what?
-Would you please make
me your girlfriend?
-Girlfriend?
-Yes.
RYUK: [laughs]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): If she
finds out I'm manipulating her
and gets hurt, she'll
probably kill me.
But still--
-Impossible.
The day that you and
I were in Aoyama,
there were three
times the usual number
of surveillance cameras around.
Anyone who was in
Aoyama on the 22nd
would've definitely been caught
on camera-- that includes me.
If you and I were seen together,
it wouldn't look very good.
In fact, even being
here together right now
is a problem.
I wish you'd understand that.
-But look-- these
are pictures of me
when I went to Aoyama that day.
-Well, I'm sure no one would
recognize her from this.
-And what about
your fingerprints?
All those tapes you
sent to the TV station.
They all had the same
fingerprints on them.
-Yeah, but those
aren't my fingerprints.
It's not like I do these things
without thinking about them
first.
Up until recently, I lived
in the Kansai region,
and I had this friend
who was into the occult.
I suggested that we distribute
this fake poltergeist
video I had made to a bunch
of different TV shows,
sort of as a prank.
And she agreed to
help me with it.
I had her take care
of all of the dubbing
so my fingerprints
wouldn't be on the tapes.
Then I took them from her
added the Kira graphic
and recorded the message
with that voice effect.
-And this friend you made the
tapes with, where is she now?
-Why are you doing this to me?
If you want me to kill her,
just say so and I'll kill her!
If you really still can't
trust me, then here.
I'll even let you hold
onto my Death Note.
But you'd just be holding it.
So I'd still be the
rightful owner of it
and that means I get to
keep my shinigami eyes.
Isn't that right, Rem?
-Yes, that's right.
-Now there's no way I
could possibly kill you.
And if I become a burden to you,
then you can just kill me, OK?
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Why
would she go this far?
-But you might have
removed several pages
from your Death Note.
You could be hiding them
somewhere for all I know.
-Why are you so
suspicious of me?
I already told you, I don't care
even if all you do is use me.
Believe me.
-How can you say that?
-Exactly one year
ago, my parents
were killed in a robbery.
I was home with
them at the time.
It happened right
in front of me.
I wanted that man to
pay for what he did.
But the trial
dragged on forever.
Opinion started surfacing that
he was being falsely accused.
Then it happened.
Kira punished him for
what he did to my parents.
And that's why Kira
means everything.
Kira means everything to me.
All I-- All I wanted was a
chance to meet you one day,
so I could thank you
for what you did.
[sobs]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): So all
these irrational moves, they
were just a means
for her to meet Kira.
Still, she got around the
surveillance cameras with ease
and managed not to leave her
fingerprints on the evidence.
She's not as stupid
as I thought.
And she has promised
to obey me from now on.
-I understand.
I can't be your boyfriend,
but I can act like it.
The lengths you went to meet
me, to be of help to me.
Those eyes of yours that you
sacrificed half your life
to get will become my weapon.
-Thank you so much.
I'll try my hardest to make
you love me, I promise.
[sighs]
[ending theme song]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): That's
good to know, Ryuzaki.
I also consider
you a close friend.
It'd be a shame if you no
longer came to university.
I was looking forward to
playing tennis against you
one last time.
L will die.
That's all it took.