[theme music]
-I think we should
do this every day.
The sun will do you good.
-What in the world am
I supposed to do now?
-Ah.
Mm.
Mm-hm.
-Hi, Ryuk.
-Sidoh?
Wh- What are you doing here?
Hey.
Quit following me.
-I want my notebook.
RYUK (VOICEOVER): Damn.
Guess I shouldn't be surprised.
Too bad.
Things got a little
complicated recently.
I have no idea where it is.
-Why am I not surprised?
-Look!
I told you.
Stop following me!
-Then give me back my notebook.
-I don't know where it is.
If you want it
back, you're gonna
have to look for it yourself.
-Moron.
-Wammy's House isn't
exactly a normal orphanage.
It's like a school
for gifted children.
But here's the crazy part.
Its real purpose is to groom
these kids so that one of them
could become the next L.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
L's successor?
-Apparently, the one
most likely to succeed
L is this kid named Near.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Near.
Is that N?
-Also, we found some leads on
Mello, the one N mentioned.
He's smart too, but he
always came second to Near.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): So Near
was meant to be L's successor.
There's no mistake.
He has to be N. He's the
one commanding the SPK.
As for Mello, he would've
wanted to become L's successor,
but he probably
lost out to Near.
That gives him a
motive for wanting
to get his hands on
the notebook first.
It all adds up perfectly.
This guy is definitely the same
Mello that N told us about.
-These are sketches
of both of them.
We couldn't find any photographs
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
L's successors.
It looks like I'm still
fighting L after all this time.
First thing's first.
I have to find out where
Mello and his mafia associates
are hiding themselves.
I already had Misa check a list
of known mafia syndicates using
her Shinigami eyes.
-Look!
I found him!
I can't see his lifespan.
He's number 105.
They have him listed
as Jack Neylon,
but his real name is Kal Snydar.
He's got the notebook.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
After that, it
was a simple matter of
using the Death Note
to make Snyder
send a letter to me
with the location of
the gang's hideout.
It should be arriving soon.
-Hi Light!
Great news.
The letter arrived.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): He's in LA.
I did it.
I outmaneuvered
both Near and Mello.
Guess it's no surprise.
As long as I have the
notebook and Misa's eyes,
I'm unstoppable.
-So, Light.
I guess this means I was helpful
to you again, doesn't it?
-Yeah.
I love you, Misa.
-Los Ang-- Ah huh.
MELLO: The next step
is for me to figure out
just how much I can control
people with this thing.
-Aw.
They're gonna have
to be able to see me
before I can even talk to them.
What a drag.
Looks like Snyder's
the owner right now.
Guess I'll have to make him
touch the notebook first.
Oh well.
Tag, you're it.
-The, uh-- The
notebook just flew.
-Ha.
It's a notebook
that kills people.
Hell, nothing
surprises me anymore.
[scream]
-Boss!
Who is this?
The guy in the freaky costume?
Who the hell is he?
Who brought him here?
-I came here on my own.
I'm actually a Shinigami.
-A Shinigami?
[scared laughter]
-If you don't want everyone
to think you're crazy,
pass the notebook around,
so they can see me too.
-He says you can see him
if you touch the notebook!
Please.
Everyone touch it.
I swear I'm not crazy!
-Fine, whatever.
Come on, guys.
Touch the notebook.
[shouting]
-He wasn't there the
last time I touched him!
-Should I kill him?
-Nice try.
You humans can't
kill a Shinigami.
-Jack's right.
That ain't no costume.
That's a real, live Shinigami.
So now what do we do?
LIGHT: Ryuk.
As of now, I'm going to forfeit
ownership of this notebook.
All I ask is that
you agree to follow
whichever person I give it to.
-What?
You're giving up
ownership again?
-But wait.
Won't you lose all your
memories if you do that?
-Misa, lend me your notebook.
-I'll keep it on me like this.
That way, even if I forfeit
ownership of my notebook,
I won't lose my memory.
I'll give you as many
pages as you need.
From this moment on,
you're going to be Kira.
Can you do that?
-Of course.
But I don't get why
you're doing this.
-I'll explain everything
to you right now.
I won't forgive any mistakes.
-Chocolate is so good.
-Hey.
What about that
stuff you told us?
Is it true?
If the person using the note
fails to consecutively write
names of people to be killed
within 13 days of each other,
then the user will die.
If you make this note unusable
by tearing it up or burning it,
all the human who have touched
the note until then will die.
Are you saying those
two rules are made up?
-Oh yeah, those rules
are definitely fake.
My guess is, some Shinigami
wrote those down as a joke
before giving the
notebook to a human.
MELLO (VOICEOVER): As
for the 13 day rule,
we can test that out by
using one of our people.
But the real
question is, was this
the notebook that
was used by Kira?
And if so, was he aware that
these two rules were false?
If he did know, he could've used
these rules to his advantage.
In particular, the
13 day rule would've
allowed him to prove his
innocence in only 13 days.
Sidoh, go keep watch outside.
It'll be very convenient
for us that you
can't be seen be humans.
Go outside and keep watch.
Got it?
-What's with this guy?
He's human, but he's scary.
[phone ringing]
-Yagami speaking.
MODIFIED VOICE: This is Kira.
LIGHT: What did he say?
Kira?
MODIFIED VOICE: I
understand the notebook that
was in your possession has
fallen into criminal hands.
CHIEF YAGAMI:
Can-- Can you prove
that you are the real Kira?
MODIFIED VOICE: Prove it?
Now that there are others
using the notebook,
there's no point
predicting killings
in order to identify myself.
They could just as easily
kill the same targets.
But don't worry.
I've already taken
this into account.
I've sent you something
that will clearly
prove to you that I am Kira.
It's my own notebook.
-Wha-- What do you mean?
MODIFIED VOICE:
The notebook I've
sent you gives me the power to
know a person's name by seeing
only their face, and you will
be able to gain that same power.
Do you understand?
MISA: Please stay calm
and listen carefully.
(MODIFIED VOICE) I've
gathered information
from the FBI and other sources.
On November 10 at
exactly 11:59 PM,
arrangements have been so
that all known associates
of the mafia will die.
It's already been
written in my notebook,
so it's impossible for
me to make any changes.
You will not be able to
prevent these deaths.
I already know their location.
I will hand over
that information
along with the
notebook, so remember.
November 10th, 11:59 PM.
That's when it all happens.
That moment is your
best and only chance
to get the notebook back.
It's up to you.
-What should we do?
If the mafia members
are going to die
on the day Kira
specified, it would
be a chance to get
the notebook back.
I don't like the idea of
following Kira's plan,
but it's our best option.
RYUK: Exactly.
-But still, knowing the
time of death for these guys
isn't going to be enough
for us to make our move.
-Ide, I think we both know
what needs to be done.
We get the Shinigami
to follow us in,
and then we do the deal
for the eyes, and make sure
they're all dead.
Right?
-I will make the
deal for the eyes.
-No way, Chief.
Let me be the one to do it.
-I was responsible
for handing over
the notebook in the first place.
Since that moment, I've
been unable to live
with what I've done.
I've even thought
of killing myself.
I'll use the notebook to
kill any criminals who
try to stop this.
And then, after 13
days, I'll die as well.
-(VOICEOVER) If Dad writes a
name in the notebook, then,
when the time comes-- Report.
Is everybody ready to move in?
MEN: Roger.
-All right.
Deputy director, make the
eye deal with the Shinigami.
-All right, Ryuk.
I'm ready.
-Sure thing, boss.
-Once you're
finished, I want you
to take a look at
the photographs
of the criminals I gave you.
Can you see their
names and lifespans?
-Yes.
I can.
-Their names should
disappear soon.
That's your cue.
[screaming]
-Everyone, move in!
-So, Kira is involved after all.
I didn't think he'd go this far.
My plan was supposed
to be perfect.
Damn!
What the hell is Sidoh doing?
-Relax, Sidoh.
Just shut up and
watch, all right?
All you have to do is
sit here and do nothing.
If you can do that, you'll
get your notebook back.
-Roy, Skiier, the
notebook's under Rod's body.
Bring it to the
surveillance room upstairs.
-Don't move!
-L, w apprehended
two of the criminals.
We've also been able
to secure the notebook.
MATSUDA: We'll begin
withdrawing now.
-Not yet.
Keep going.
-Huh?
-What?
LIGHT: We still
haven't found anyone
who resembles our
picture of Mello.
That means he must be hiding
somewhere in the building.
We've come this far.
Let's finish this.
Do a thorough search.
-Ah!
-What was that?
-An explosion.
MELLO: Don't move.
I've already blown up the
two entrances to this place.
This will be your only warning.
The next explosion will take out
the entire building, as well as
all your men inside.
So you'd better do as I say.
-It's Mello.
[laughter]
-Hm?
-Yagami again, huh?
Maybe I should have killed
you when I had the chance.
History repeats
itself, but I never
dreamed in a million years I'd
be bargaining for the notebook
with you again.
M-I-H-A-E-L K-E-E-H-L.
Your real name.
It's Mihael Keehl.
-(VOICEOVER) What the hell?
How did he--
-I did it.
-It's over, Mello.
It's time to turn yourself in.
If you give up,
I won't kill you.
You have my word on that.
-(VOICEOVER) What are you doing?
Don't be stupid.
Write his name
down and kill him!
Now!
-You know how this works.
I write your name,
and you will die.
Let go of that trigger and
put your hands in the air.
Yagami--
-Don't move!
I've written your first
name, and it will only
take me a second to
write your surname.
-(VOICEOVER) You idiot!
Just write it!
Kill him!
-I'm truly sorry.
For what it's worth,
I give you my word
that I never wanted to kill you.
-Hm?
-But tell me, Yagami, you've
never killed someone before,
have you?
-Gunfire?
-What was that?
-Jose!
The notebook!
-Damn!
-This guy he-- he won't
let go of the thing.
Son of a--
-Hm?
MATSUDA: Deputy Director!
-It's all over, Mello!
Put your hands up and surrender!
Matsuda!
Are you all right?
MATSUDA: No.
I don't think so.
AIZAWA: I'm sure you'll live.
L, I don't see
any sign of Mello.
-(VOICEOVER) Dammit.
After all that, he got away?
That's why you should
have just killed him.
[beeping]
-Come on!
Please, Dad!
You can't die on me like this.
-Light.
-Yeah, Dad?
Thank goodness.
-You'll be fine.
It's OK.
-Light.
I still have them.
I still have the Shinigami eyes.
According to that
Shinigami, Ryuk,
I can't see the lifespan of
someone who owns a notebook.
But I can see the
numbers above your head.
Light-- you really aren't Kira.
I'm so glad, my son.
-Don't tell me you're still
worried about that, Chief.
Of course he's not Kira.
-Come on.
You shouldn't talk so much, Dad.
(VOICEOVER) That's
important, but I've
got bigger things to
deal with right now.
I've got to get him to write
Mello's name in the notebook.
-I-- I'm so sorry, but-- in
the end, I couldn't do it.
I couldn't bring
myself to kill him.
-(VOICEOVER) I can't just come
out and say, it's not too late.
No.
Wait, maybe I can.
It all depends on how I do it.
No one will think it's weird
if I get upset and panic.
Come on.
Dad, write his name.
You can't let him
beat you like this.
Write his name down!
With your last bit of strength.
Do you want to die in vain?
D-- Dad, no!
-Light--
[steady beep]
-I'm sorry for your loss.
-Dad.
Wake up!
Come on, damn it!
Don't you die on me, you idiot!
Dad!
-You are the Shinigami
who came here
to take back this
notebook, aren't you?
-Yes.
-The notebook might be helpful
to the Kira investigation,
but we really only
need one of them.
I'll give this one back to you.
RYUK (VOICEOVER): Humans
who use the notebook are
cursed with fear,
pain, and misery.
Of course, Soichiro
didn't use the notebook.
He got to die believing
that his son wasn't Kira.
I guess that means he was happy.
[theme music]
LIGHT: If Kira gets
caught, then he is evil.
If Kira rules the world,
then he is justice.
From now on, the world will
start leaning in favor of Kira.
Kira will be justice.