[theme music]
-L. I want to meet you.
Daikoku Wharf, an
abandoned warehouse
known as the Yellow Box.
How about three days from
now, on the 28th at 1:00 PM?
-That's fine by me.
MIKAMI: Take off
everything you're wearing
and put it all in that box.
You can use this blanket.
MAN: Ms. Takada,
are you all right?
-Light.
I did exactly what
you told me to.
I made survival my first
priority and-- and I did it.
Come quickly.
Save me.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Kiyomi Takada.
Suicide.
January 26th, 2013.
2:32 PM.
Burns to death by setting
fire to everything around her,
including everything
she wrote on.
-It is with great sorrow
that I must announce
the passing of one of
our very own colleagues.
The police have identified
one of the bodies found
at the scene as NHN's
Ms. Kiyomi Takada.
A two ton truck and a
motorcycle were also
found in the ruins of
the burned out church.
Investigators suspect gasoline
was used to start the fire.
-What I really want
to know is who's
going to be Kira's
next spokesperson.
Kira's message still
needs to be spread,
and someone's gotta do it.
-The death of newscaster
Takada was a horrible tragedy,
but I can't help but think
that if she was that careless,
she couldn't have taken her
position as Kira's spokesperson
that seriously.
-It needs to be said.
This is not a woman's job.
Kira.
Please make me your
new representative.
-No!
Give the honor to
Sakura TV again!
-Disgusting.
-Yeah, I know.
I mean, they just
announced her death,
and already it's started.
Every TV station
airing its own segment
on who should replace her.
It's like she never existed.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Last night's judgments
unfolded just as planned.
That means Takada
and Mikumi have
had no problems
contacting each other.
There's nothing to worry about.
[beeping]
-It's near.
-Hello L.
-Yes?
NEAR (ON COMPUTER): I don't
mean to keep bothering you,
but with regards
to our meeting, I
wanted to confirm
that we are still
set for the 28th at
1:00 PM, all right?
-Yes.
It's just as I predicted.
He's sticking with
the original time.
There's no doubt about it.
-Very well.
The 28th.
The day after tomorrow.
-Right.
-So, the day of tomorrow, huh?
Finally.
Isn't it getting exciting?
-Y-- Yeah.
I can't help but wonder
what Near wants to show us.
-(VOICEOVER) Matsuda Ide.
When the day comes,
there's a good chance
we might all be killed.
Don't you understand that?
NEAR: Giovanni.
-Yes?
NEAR: Will you be able
to make it in time?
GIOVANNI: Yes.
I'll be there for sure.
-Commander Rester,
Lidner, Giovanni.
Let's put our best
into this, shall we?
NEAR (ON COMPUTER):
Good morning, everyone.
-Uh, good morning.
-First of all, in
regards to Misa Amane,
we've already set her free.
You may call her to confirm it.
MISA: I don't know
what's going on,
but this must be some sort
of compensation or something!
They totally put me up
in the penthouse suite
of the Teido Hotel.
Can you believe it?
Now, this is more like it!
-I understand.
All right, Misa.
Please stay there for a little
while longer until I call you.
MISA (ON PHONE): OK!
-All right, Near.
I need you to
connect me with Mogi.
We have the notebook
locked away here,
and in order to open
the safe it's kept in,
we'll need the pin number
from each member of the team.
NEAR (ON SPEAKER): Understood.
I'll connect you
to him immediately.
-This is Mogi.
Number is 62-324.
-(VOICEOVER) All that's
left is my number.
The killer notebook.
How to use it.
The human whose name is written
in this notebook shall die.
This note will not take
effect unless the writer has
the person's face in their mind
when writing his or her name.
Therefore, people sharing the
same name will not be affected.
If the cause of death is written
within 40 seconds of writing
the person's name,
it will happen.
If the cause of death
is not specified,
the person will simply
die of a heart attack.
After writing the cause of
death, details of the death
should be written in the next
six minutes and 40 seconds.
Near, it's me.
We've discussed
it, and it's been
decided that I'll be the
one to carry the notebook.
-L, are you sure it's
all right with you
if Mr. Aizawa carries it?
Be honest.
-Of course.
I chose Aizawa for
the job because we
knew you'd prefer that.
I have no problems with it.
NEAR (ON SPEAKER):
I appreciate it.
Thank you.
Well then, we'll
see you shortly.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Looks
like this is the end.
No.
More like the beginning.
The perfect world of Kira.
And those who know of the
notebook's existence, all
of them will die.
-There's no mistake,
Near's inside.
I checked it out.
All right.
Let's do this.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Near.
You're far inferior
to L. You have
no right to be
wearing a mask of L.
-It's them.
Those four are the SPK.
And the one wearing
a mask is Near.
-Hang on.
Am I the only one who
sees something wrong?
He can go around accusing
people of being Kira,
but the fact that
he's wearing a mask
says he's only trying
to protect himself.
Not anyone else.
-It's just a precaution.
There's a good possibility
that Kira has already
seen the faces of everyone
in this warehouse,
except for mine.
In fact, he may be writing
down your names as we speak.
So I'd like to wait for one
hour-- No, make it 30 minutes.
That should give us
more than enough time
to see if anyone is being
controlled before they die.
-Huh?
What?
You're gonna wait
and see if we die?
-No.
It's not impossible that
Light really is Kira,
especially since the rest of us
are of no use to him anymore.
-(VOICEOVER) This is all just
a front to buy some time,
isn't it?
I never thought it would
be this hard to keep myself
from laughing out loud.
Near must be waiting
for him to come.
It's all just as I predicted.
MATSUDA: Near!
It's already been
over 30 minutes.
Nothing's happened yet.
-Of course not.
That's because Kira's
not here with us.
-Very well.
Everyone seems to be safe.
I'll remove my mask now.
-You're quiet, Near.
What's wrong?
Are you still waiting
for something?
-Waiting.
That's an excellent
choice of words.
Yes, I am waiting,
for the arrival
of the one who will solve
everything once and for all.
-Someone else is supposed
to clear this up?
NEAR: He'll be here soon.
It's only a matter of time.
There's only one entrance
to this building,
and the only way to look
inside is by opening that door.
That means he'll either
walk through that door,
or at the very least,
open it and peek through.
-And just who is
this person, anyway?
-X Kira, the one who is
currently using the notebook
and killing people
on Kira's behalf.
He's bound to come here and
bring the notebook with them.
And then he'll see me, and
write down my real name.
Or rather, he'll write down the
names of everyone here knows
about the notebook,
and kill them.
-Huh?
-What?
What are you saying?
This doesn't make any sense.
What are you trying
to tell us, Near?
That some other guy's going
to drop by with the notebook,
poke his head in,
and kill us all?
-And you want us to sit
back and let it happen?
-NEAR: Yes.
That's correct.
Now, listen carefully.
If someone comes into the
warehouse through that door,
just let him in
without resisting.
If a door opens
slightly, simply act
as if you don't
notice anyone there.
-But-- but that's just crazy!
NEAR: He's already here.
-God!
Delete!
Delete.
-Hold it!
Don't do anything.
-Everything is fine.
You won't die.
IDE: How can you
be so sure, Near?
-Because I modified
the notebook.
-Huh?
NEAR: We took brief
possession of the notebook
and replaced the pages.
The person behind
the door has been
doing the killings for Kira.
He has also been using
exactly one page every day.
Based on that, I was
able to replace the page
he would use today, as well
as all subsequent pages,
so that no one else would die.
-Delete.
Delete.
Delete!
[laughter]
NEAR: On the other side
of that door is X Kira.
My guess is in
roughly 40 seconds,
he'll look inside to
see if we're dead.
That's when we'll restrain
him and seize the notebook.
Whoever's name is not
written down must be Kira.
-It's true.
Kira would be the only one
that guy wouldn't try to kill.
But still--
-(VOICEOVER) I knew it.
I knew it.
I knew it!
I knew all along you had
tampered with the notebook.
Near, you've been
completely defeated.
The notebook you
altered was nothing more
than a forgery I
had Mikami prepare.
On the other hand, the one
Mikami is writing their names
in is the real notebook, which
had been kept hidden until now.
[laughter] I had Mikami create
a fake notebook for himself.
He also sent Takada several
pages from the real one,
so in fact, it was
Takada, not Mikami,
who was doing the killings.
As for Mikami, I
had him write names
in public several times
using the fake notebook.
That way he'd be noticed by
anyone who was following him.
But Takada was the
one behind the deaths.
Mikami simply sent the names
and faces by cellphone.
This little
performance was how I
made the SPK believe that
the notebook Mikami used
was the real one.
Mikami's daily behavior
is so methodical,
it's almost obsessive.
He always fills exactly one
page with names, every day.
And Near, you noticed
this little habit
and though you could use it
to tamper with the notebook.
All you had to do was
count ahead to the page
he'd use on the day
of this meeting.
Then you replaced all the
pages from that day onwards.
You were confident you could
prevent anyone from dying.
That was your big plan.
That's why you couldn't
change the date
and time of our meeting.
But I was one step
ahead of you, Near.
I always knew you were going to
try and alter the Death Note.
That's why I had Mikami
check the notebook every day
for signs of tampering.
-I've confirmed it.
LIGHT: (VOICEOVER)
I knew I'd won
this game as soon as
I got that message.
Mikami brought a different
notebook today, the real one,
which had been kept
hidden up until now.
But you know, Near, you
did have a chance to win,
if only you'd taken it.
You were just too naive.
You're nothing compared to
L. L would have considered
the possibility
of a fake notebook
from the very beginning,
and he would have tested it.
You had the chance,
but you squandered it.
I've gotta say, I'm so
disappointed in you.
This victory was no fun.
You tried too hard to
win in a noble way.
Well, that's fine.
Everyone here dies
today, thanks to you.
And as for me, I, Kira, will
have my perfect victory.
-You there, outside.
-Huh?
-Have you finished writing
down the names in the notebook?
-God.
Yes.
I've written them.
[stifled laughter]
-(VOICEOVER) No.
I can't laugh yet.
I've got to hold it in.
They're all gonna die.
40 seconds after he
wrote down their names.
35 seconds.
I'll claim my victory then.
-Don't you think
it's rather odd?
-Hm?
-Why would he answer
you so quickly, calmly,
and honestly when you asked
him if he had written down
our names yet?
-Who knows?
Maybe he's just honest.
Or confident that he'll succeed.
Or perhaps he's seen
through your brilliant plan.
-Huh?
In that case, we're
in big trouble.
-Teru Mikami.
If it's not too much trouble for
you, won't you please come in
and join us?
I already know that
you're the one who's
been judging and
executing people for Kira.
If you've already
written down our names,
then there shouldn't be
anything to be afraid of.
You can come right on in.
-Teru Mikami, is it?
He's correct.
There's no reason
to hide from us.
You can come in.
-God.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
You've done well, Mikami.
How many seconds has it
been since you wrote down
the first name?
-30 seconds.
31, 32, 33, 34,
35, 36, 37, 38, 39!
-Well Near.
Looks like I win.
-40!
[theme music]
[maniacal laughter]
-That's right.
I am Kira.