[theme music]
-Huh?
-What is this?
[groaning]
-Everyone, the Shiniga--
L: Now, try to kill me.
Although this was announced
as a worldwide broadcast,
the truth is we are
only broadcasting
in the Kanto region of Japan.
In actuality, the
fist of your victims
was a suspect in Shinjuku.
Furthermore, his crime was only
ever reported inside Japan.
I used that information
to deduce this much.
You are in Japan, and your
first victim was little more
than an experiment,
which means that you
haven't been killing
for very long.
Kira has found a way to obtain
information from the task force
headquarters.
There are 141 people
in the police force
who have acces to classified
information regarding
the investigation.
I am sure that somewhere in
this list of police officers,
and the people closest to
them, we will find our suspect.
On December 14th, 12 FBI
investigators entered Japan.
Here are are on December 19th.
Using prison inmates,
Kira conducts experiments
manipulating his victim's
actions before they die.
He needed to know how much
control he had over his victims
before he could use it
against the 12 agents.
I suspect Kira had to be one of
the people being investigated
by the FBI between the 14th
and the 19th of December.
In fact, I have no doubt.
Raye Penber's fiance?
Naomi Misora.
So it's her.
She was working under me.
I guess she must have come
to Japan with her fiance.
I heard she was
seen with Penber.
It's possible that she
may have found a lead.
If that's the case, did Kira
manage to get to her first?
Everyone, at this point I'd
like to focus our investigation
on only those people who
Raye Penber was tailing.
There are two groups.
Deputy Director
Kitamura, as well as
Detective Superintendent
Yagami and their families.
At this stage I'd like to
place wiretaps and surveillance
cameras in both households.
-That's my son
you're talking about.
-Are you honestly telling
me that you suspect him?
-I do suspect him.
I want to you, I'm
L. Relax, Light.
While it's try that
Kira hates losing,
it's also true that most people
would rather win than lose.
It's human nature.
Look at that.
He's going for the win.
I suspect that you, Light
Yagami, are in fact Kira.
-You think I'm Kira?
Ryuga, what would
it take to get you
to believe that I'm not Kira?
Please, isn't there something?
-If you are not Kira, that
truth will be revealed.
Just let things
run their course.
-Four days ago--
-Our audience rating
should go up 60%-- no,
more like 70%
percent after this.
NEWSCASTER: --contained a
prediction of two deaths,
proving that he is Kira.
We understand that the second
tape contains a message
to all people of the world.
DISTORTED VOICE: I am Kira.
The news anchor,
Mr. Kazuhiko Hibima,
will die of a heart
attack at exactly 6:00.
-Stop this broadcast!
We can't let him finish!
You idiots!
-You told us that Kira
couldn't kill without a name!
L: But from what
we've just seen,
I'd say it's not
entirely impossible
that Kira can kill
with only a face.
-This is the police.
Stop this broadcast now!
L: There's a strong possibility
that this Kira's a fake.
No, we should think of
him more as a second Kira.
Mr. Yagami, I'd
like your permission
to ask your son to cooperate
with us on this investigation.
-At the very least,
I'd say this isn't
the Kira we're familiar with.
-That's almost exactly how
L-- I mean, Ryuzaki said it.
DISTORTED VOICE:
When we meet, we
can confirm our
identities by showing
our Shinigami to each other.
[scream]
L: If there's a message
here written in some code
that only people who have this
Shinigami power can understand,
there'd no way for
me to decipher it.
Still, it would only
make sense for us
to look into all
of the places that
were mentioned in the journal.
When you two are
working together,
I want you to keep a close
eye on Light the entire time.
It's only a slim chance,
but if Light is Kira,
then there's still a
possibility that the second Kira
may try to contact him somehow.
Also, Mr Yagami, please ask Mr.
Mogi to start following Light,
so he can keep tabs
on what he's doing.
-Light, there you are.
Hi there.
I'm Light's
girlfriend, Misa Amane.
Nice to meet you.
-I'm Hideki Ryuga.
-Huh?
Hideki Ryuga?
-I'm not exactly sure
how you'll take this,
but regarding Misa
Amane, there's
something you should know.
We've taken her into
custody under suspicion
of her being the second Kira.
We gathered physical evidence
from the envelope sent
by the second Kira, and
particular hairs and fibers
used in the masking
tape used to seal them.
They matched what we
found in Misa's room.
CHIEF YAGAMI: Ryuzaki,
what's the meaning of this?
-Now hurry up and kill me!
If you wanted to, you could
kill me right now, couldn't you?
L: Does this mean you admit
to being the second Kira?
Is this the reason
you wish to die?
-No.
I don't know anything
about the second Kira.
-Ryuzaki, like I said over
the phone, I could be Kira.
-Why come here to announce
that you could be Kira?
It's an act.
There's no could be about it.
You are Kira.
Light, are you feeling OK?
-Yeah.
I know I must look pretty
bad in here, but this useless
pride-- I suppose I'll
have to get rid of it.
Ryuzaki, I realize that
I was the one pushing
for confinement, and that
I asked you put me in here,
but this whole thing's
completely pointless.
I'm not Kira.
You have to get me out of here!
-I just heard.
Two weeks' worth of criminals
were just murdered all at once.
It happened yesterday.
-I don't understand
what's going on here.
-I'm not sure how much more
of this the three of them
can take.
-Ryuzaki, you have no reason to
keep Light locked up anymore.
It's already been 50 days.
-I'm going to kill you
here, and then kill myself.
-What?
What are you talking about, Dad?
You can't, that's crazy!
-How can you even say that?
-It's too late.
-Please, don't, Dad!
I'm not Kira!
-Light, my son-- from
one murderer to another--
-No, Dad!
-I'll see you in hell.
-No!
Stop it!
[gunshot]
L: It was a convincing
performance.
As we discussed, I will end
their confinement immediately.
As for your part in
this agreement, Light,
you and I will be
together 24/7, and that's
how it will remain until
we've brought Kira to justice.
LIGHT: Their deaths have all
worked in Yotsuba's favor.
Looking back, there have
been 13 similar deaths
in the past three months.
L: Is Kira someone from Yotsuba?
Or is Kira simply using Yotsuba?
I haven't figured that
out yet, but we'll
proceed under the assumption
that this is Kira's doing.
We will focus on Yotsuba.
Please be sure not
to act impulsively,
out of panic or haste.
And don't take matters
into your own hands.
-I'm an agent with
Yoshida Productions.
Would you be interested
in using Misa
Amane as your new spokesperson?
Ryuzaki, are you watching this?
The eight men who came
here were having a meeting
to decide who they get
Kira to kill for them.
L: If Matsuda dies,
our suspicions
about the Yotsuba group
would be confirmed
MATSUDA: Do you think
there's anything
I can do to save myself?
MAN: Matsuda, you idiot.
-Good luck, Misa Misa!
I'll be here ready to celebrate
when they decide to hire you!
-It's always been my dream
to become Kira's wife.
I know he'll need me by
his side And you know why?
Because I'm the second Kira.
-Well, since I
happen to be Kira,
does that mean you'll
marry me, Misa?
-So, based on what he
said, Higuchi is Kira.
-So, what are you doing to do?
-I'm going to trick
Higuchi secret Sakura TV.
-Like a hidden camera show!
-Higuchi, we've got a problem.
Turn on the television.
-Huh?
-So you're saying one of
those people is Kira, right?
-Yes.
I've got a lot of
evidence to prove it, too.
-It's-- it's him!
Why is he still alive?
-I see Higuchi.
I'm in pursuit.
-We're heading after him.
[siren]
POLICE OFFICER:
You in the red car!
Pull over to the
side of the road.
Now!
HIGUCHI: Rem.
Let's make the deal.
-A deal?
-You were speeding.
License, please?
-Yeah.
No problem.
-Hey!
-Higuchi ditched the cop.
He's driving away.
This is Traffic Control--
-Everyone!
It's too dangerous to allow
further action by Higuchi.
Let's bring him in.
I believe he has the same
powers as the second Kira.
He is able to kill just by
looking at someone's face.
Please keep this in mind when
you move in to arrest him.
-Stop right there.
-Stay back!
Stay back or I'll
shoot, I swear!
Ah!
L: Higuchi, how were
you able to kill people?
-You probably won't
believe me, but I've
got a special notebook.
If I write someone's name in it
while thinking of their face,
that person dies.
-It was in one of the
compartments of Higuchi's bag.
[scream]
L: What is it, Mr. Yagami?
-It's a monster!
-A Shinigami.
There have to be two notebooks.
Possibly more.
This isn't over yet.
-How to use it.
It says the human whose name
is written in this notebook
shall die.
And then there's this last rule.
According to this, if
the person using the note
fails to consecutively
write names
of people to be killed
within 13 dayf--
-Of each other, then
the user will die.
Light Yagami and Misa
Amane are both still alive.
13 days.
That's the only problem.
The following is
the record which
contains everything I have
investigated on the Kira
incident.
That fact that now you
are reading this message
means I am no longer
alive at this moment.
I hereby leave this record
as my firm achievement.
That is all.
[beep]
MATSUDA: It's been 10 days
since Ryuzaki's funeral.
Look like we're not
gonna die after all.
-We know Watari's
true identity now,
but we never found out anything
about who Ryuzaki really was.
-Yeah, that's true.
Who could have guessed
that Watari was actually
a famous inventor?
-The paper says he
founded orphanages
around the world
using the fortune he
inherited from his patents.
-He was a fine man.
A hero.
-But it doesn't help us now.
We can't continue
investigating using this place
as our base with
L and Watari gone.
This is tough.
CHIEF YAGAMI: Light,
how's it going?
-I should be able to
transfer the system and most
of the information out
of here by tonight.
It's weird, though.
I almost feel as
if I'm stealing.
I've created a voice filter
identical to the one reason
Ryuzaki used.
We can use it to make the
police think he's still alive,
and give them orders like
we've been doing so far.
But who is going to
take the place of L?
Where will he work
from, and what will we
do with the notebook?
-Come on.
What are you talking
about, Light?
You're the only one who
can take on the role of L.
-Huh?
I don't know.
Ryuzaki was killed by Kira
because he challenged him.
That's not something
I'm eager to do.
Besides, I would be fooling
the people of the world.
-I can understand how you
feel, but you're really
the only one of us
who can do this.
-That's right.
Even Ryuzaki said so himself.
You would be capable
of succeeding L.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Just as I thought.
It's too simple.
It's no fun without
Ryuzaki here.
I understand.
All right, I'll do it.
But I won't be like Ryuzaki.
I won't take big risks like
challenging Kira directly
to gather clues.
it's just not me.
-Yeah.
It's probably better
if we play it safe.
Ryuzaki may have been a
little too confrontational.
-In that case, I'll be able to
do the same sort of work using
both this computer and my own.
In fact, it'll be
possible for me
to act as L in the
comfort of my own room.
I can be Watari, as well.
But it'll be difficult to pull
off with Mom and Sayu around.
Things would be
easier if I could
rent a one bedroom apartment.
-Well, considering
your age, it certainly
wouldn't look odd to anyone if
I let you move out on your own.
-Hey, yeah.
And then we'll be able to
use Light's new apartment
as our task force headquarters.
That's a great idea.
[sigh]
-All that's left
to figure out now
is what to do with the notebook.
LIGHT: It's really
not that difficult.
There's five of us here.
And we know none of us
will ever use the notebook.
We'll just have one of us
take it and hide it somewhere
where no one else
could ever get to it.
-Please, Chief.
It's got to be you.
-Uh, yeah, Chief.
We can count on you.
You're a pillar of
justice, after all.
-You want me to-- all right.
-We'll avenge Ryuzaki together.
-Yeah.
Kira is still out
there somewhere.
We'll catch him.
That's a promise.
-Well then, why don't
we have a little party
to celebrate Light
becoming L number two?
AIZAWA: Quit fooling around.
Now's not the time
for stuff like that.
CHIEF YAGAMI:
Let's take it easy.
-Light.
This is our first
date in forever.
Can't you enjoy
yourself a little more?
-Misa, let's move in together.
[gasp]
-Do you mean it?
-Yeah.
I've already rented a place.
-Yay!
Victory is mine!
Misa wins!
-Victory?
Over Kiyomi, and Mari, and Yuri.
But it's all right now.
Don't worry.
I knew you were just
using those other girls
to trick L. You
don't have any reason
to see them anymore, right?
LIGHT: Right.
-Hey.
Now that L's dead,
does that mean
you've finally settled
the score with him?
-Yeah.
-So in that case,
I guess things are
gonna get pretty
boring from now on.
-That's not true, Ryuk.
-Huh?
-From this moment
on, I'll show you
the creation of the new world.
-Ah!
[groan]
-Daddy!
Daddy?
-Hm?
-This will be the
rebirth of Yotsuba.
-Yeah.
It's a new start.
Huh?
Hey-- Namikawa!
What's wrong?
That's impossible--
MAN: In April 2012,
Light Yagami, age 23,
joined Japan's
National Police Agency.
In the summer of
2012, Kira's killings
increased at an
unprecedented rate.
Numerous people around the
world were terrified of Kira,
and yet, there were just
as many cheering him on.
Gradually their private
thoughts became public opinion,
and soon, certain nations began
to accept Kira's judgement.
The world was heading
into a dark age
in which Kira's will
was the only law.
[beeping]
MELLO: What is it, Roger?
-It's L. He's dead.
[theme music]
MELLO: L's death?
Where'd they hear it from?
Who told them?
Who is this guy?
Is he joking?
What's with this
strange feeling?