[theme music]
SOICHIRO YAGAMI: I
can't believe my son is
looking at those magazines.
-Hey, Light!
Come on!
Dinner's ready.
[laughing]
LIGHT YAGAMI (VOICEOVER):
I'll solve equations
with my right hand and
write names with my left.
I'll take a potato
chip-- and eat it!
And the witness to my
alibi is L himself.
Are you sure about this?
Ryuk.
-Yeah, I'm sure nobody's
following you, OK?
Now hurry up already, will you?
The symptoms are getting worse.
LIGHT YAGAMI: I
really hope you're not
saying what you think
I'd want to hear just
to get some apples.
RYUK: Whoa!
Hold it right there.
I just flew out and checked a
100-meter radius around you,
and there was no one
there. (TESTILY) So yeah,
for the last time, I'm sure.
OK?
-All right.
But on the news, they
said they were dispatching
1,500 investigators to Japan.
-They're bluffing.
You said so yourself.
If it were really
happening, they
wouldn't announce their arrival.
Instead, they'd come and
investigate secretly.
-I suppose you're right.
Well, then, I'll
buy you some apples.
-Nice.
[laugh]
-Here you are.
Please come again.
-Light, come on.
Hurry up.
You know, you really haven't
been that nice to me.
You have me looking
all over for cameras,
telling me that I can't even
eat apples in the house anymore.
It's not right.
[bones popping]
-Make sure you eat
the core as well.
[chomping]
-You know, I might actually
write your name in my Death
Note and kill you,
just like that.
LIGHT YAGAMI: [laughing]
RYUK: I wouldn't
laugh if I were you.
LIGHT YAGAMI: Right.
That reminds me, I've got one
finishing touch left to add.
-Hmm.
Hey, Ryuzaki.
RYUZAKI: Yes?
-I've been thinking
about the purse snatcher
and the embezzler's heart
attacks two days ago.
It seems my family couldn't
have had any knowledge of them
before they died.
Shouldn't that resolve
any doubts you have?
-You may be right.
Even though Kira can
control the time of death,
I don't think there's any
way he could have arranged
their debts without having
seen the broadcast first.
Hmm?
Your son has come home.
-Huh.
-Heh.
So you're going to
keep quiet and pretend
to study again, huh?
LIGHT YAGAMI (VOICEOVER):
I have a good grasp
of where all the
cameras are placed,
but I only managed to kill a
purse snatcher and an embezzler
using that trick with
the potato chips.
Both of them were guilty
of much lesser crimes
than my previous victims.
NEWS ANCHOR (TV):
Next, in local news--
-Huh?
You're watching TV?
LIGHT YAGAMI (VOICEOVER): I
made sure to kill criminals
whose names and faces were
broadcast when I didn't have
access to TV or the internet.
But there's a chance I'll look
even more suspicious if only
these lesser
criminals end up dying
while I'm not
receiving information.
In other words, if I kill other
petty criminals whose names
and faces are broadcast
as I watch TV,
I won't draw unnecessary
attention to myself.
For this to work, all
I really have to do
is remember the identities
of the criminals
I either see on TV
or while I'm online,
regardless of the
severity of their crimes.
That way, whenever I go out, I
can use that piece of the Death
Note I keep in my wallet to
kill them at random times.
Just like that.
It's the perfect way to deal
with these hidden cameras.
L: In the past few
days, I've listened
to all of our audio
recordings and reviewed
the video footage we captured.
I've gone over them many times.
And I've come to a conclusion.
Our surveillance of the
Kitamura and Yagami households
has revealed--
[gasp]
--nothing.
[sigh]
(WHILE EATING) We will remove
the cameras and wiretaps.
--[sigh] All that, and we
still don't have any suspects.
-It's OK, Matsuda.
We'll have to pursue other
leads, but we'll get him.
L: Please don't
get the wrong idea.
-Huh?
-I only said that we were unable
to reveal anything suspicious
based on our surveillance.
-What?
L: Even if Kira
was among them, I'm
sure he wouldn't
make it obvious.
No, in fact, it
could mean he was
able to continue killing
without doing anything outwardly
suspicious.
-Well, then you
believe that Kira
is among one of those families.
-As I've said,
there's a 5% chance.
(VOICEOVER) Kira never
stopped killing people,
even while the surveillance
cameras were in place.
I still have no
idea how he's been
able to commit these
murders, but let's say
he could kill someone simply
by wishing death upon them.
You'd think that any
human being would
have shown at least
some emotion, some sign
that they were knowingly
committing an act of murder.
So the obvious
conclusion is that Kira
couldn't be one of them.
However, what if he
is one of these people
we've been watching?
If he is, we have to assume
that his psyche has reached
godlike proportions, punishing
evildoers without the slightest
change of expression.
It almost makes me want to
believe that Kira doesn't
exist, that this is just
the wrath of a vengeful god.
But that idea is
completely absurd,
to think that God would need
a person's face and name
to kill them.
No, these aren't acts
of God, but someone
very childish and immature who
wants to pretend they're God.
That's what's going on here.
A mass murderer who calls
himself Kira exists somewhere,
I'm sure of it.
And I will catch him.
But I can't count on
Kira making any mistakes.
It doesn't matter how
long we watch him.
He's not going to
expose himself to us.
So what should I do?
Ideally, I ought
to get to know him
well enough that he'd admit
to me that he was Kira
and show me how he kills.
Would that even be possible?
-[grunting] Hey, Light.
I just checked, and all the
cameras have been removed.
All of them, every single one.
Hello?
Are you listening to me?
Hey, Light.
Oh, good point.
We still don't know if they've
removed all the wiretaps
from the house.
LIGHT YAGAMI
(VOICEOVER): I suppose
this means I'm no
longer a suspect.
Everything's going as planned.
But I'm sure L won't
give up that easily.
If he's still working
with the Japanese police,
chances are my father is working
with him, or under him, anyway.
If that's the case, I'll have
to use my father to find out
L's true identity, and
I"ll eliminate him.
Once I get rid of L,
Kira w be one step closer
to becoming the god
of the new world.
SACHIKO YAGAMI: Light, hurry up.
You don't want to be late.
Do your best.
-I know you don't need
it, but good luck.
[laugh]
-I really don't
see why you two are
making such a big
deal out of this.
-I'm relieved.
We don't have to deal with
wiretaps in the house anymore.
LIGHT YAGAMI
(VOICEOVER): Well, it's
nice to know that
one cause of stress
was resolved before my exam.
And once I get into
university, I'll
have a lot more
room to act as Kira.
Then I can focus on finding
out who L really is.
-You there.
The exam will be
starting in 10 minutes,
so you better hurry up.
-It's fine.
I planned to get here three
minutes before the test.
I hate waiting.
I'm here too early.
-Well, well.
Confident.
[bell ringing]
-And begin.
-Hmm?
You there, student number 162.
Sit properly in your chair.
-Hmm?
[groan]
-It seems like a
lot of Shinigami
are observing the
human world lately.
Uh, what's with that, anyway?
-It turns out that Ryuk
is being kept by a human.
-Ha, what's he thinking?
Seriously.
-He's a disgrace to the
pride of the Shigiami.
-No, I'm talking about the
human who's keeping Ryuk.
-Huh?
-Who would want him as a pet?
Aren't pets supposed to be cute?
[laughter]
-When you're right,
you're right.
-So what's the story
on this human, anyway?
Is it a male or a female?
-Who knows?
-In that case, I think I'd
better go take a closer look.
-Oh boy.
[crowd noise]
-You're a college student now.
That's kind of exciting.
I'm filled with joy.
-Now for the freshman
address, freshman
representative Light Yagami.
-Yes.
-Ooh.
Wow.
-And freshman
representative Hideki Ryuga.
MALE SPEAKER: Oh, uh, here.
--[gasp] Is that Hideki
Ryuga, the pop idol?
-That guy?
There's no way
he's got the brains
to get into a school like To-Oh.
-Yeah, you're right.
He doesn't look anything
like the real Hideki Ryuga.
LIGHT YAGAMI
(VOICEOVER): I knew I'd
be giving the address
with one other student.
But I never expected this.
I remember him from
the exam center.
He got into trouble for
sitting oddly on his desk.
It seemed like he was
off in his own world.
As all of us embark on this
new chapter of our lives--
STUDENT 1: The student who
scores highest on the test
is supposed to give
the speech, right?
STUDENT 2: I guess
both of them must
have had the high
score this year.
STUDENT 3: I heard they
both had perfect scores
for all subjects.
STUDENT 1: Seriously?
STUDENT 2: It's hard to
believe there are actually
people like that.
-I think I like the
little one on the right.
-What?
You're so weird, Kyoko.
Look at how he's dressed.
KYOKO: Mmm.
-Man, these two are
total opposites.
-Yeah.
STUDENT 1: This one looks
like a sheltered genius
who's been groomed for
success his whole life.
But the other one--
-(MONOTONE) As we embark on
this new chapter in our lives--
STUDENT 1: There's something
not right about him.
He's just freaking weird.
STUDENT 2: This guy must be
what they call a mad genius.
STUDENT 1: Coming to
the To-Oh entrance
ceremony dressed like that?
Unbelievable.
Either he's crazy, or
he's just toying with us.
---your freshman
representative, Hideki Ryuga.
L: Light.
Light Yagami?
Your father is Cheif
Soichori Yagami of the NPA.
Your respect for your
father is matched only
by your strong sense of justice.
LIGHT YAGAMI (VOICEOVER):
Who the hell is this guy?
-You're planning
to join the police
agency when you graduate.
And you've already
got experience,
seeing as you've
helped the police solve
a number of cases in the past.
Now you're showing an
interest in the Kira case.
I'm impressed by your abilities
and your sense of justice.
If you promise not to
tell anyone about this,
I have important information
concerning the Kira
investigation that I'd
like to share with you.
LIGHT YAGAMI (VOICEOVER):
Where's this coming from?
And who is he?
Is it safe to just ignore him?
But I wonder what this
information actually is.
I won't tell anyone.
What is it?
-I want to tell you
(WHISPERING) I'm L. And
LIGHT YAGAMI (VOICEOVER): What?
There's no way!
What's he talking about?
If he really was L,
he'd never admit to it.
I thought this guy
was a bit strange,
but this is pretty extreme.
Nn-- stop.
This isn't good.
Don't act surprised.
On the off chance
that he really is L,
I have to act how Soichiro
Yagami's son, Light Yagami,
would act in this situation.
There'd be no reason
for him to be afraid.
If you are who you
say you are, then you
have nothing but my
respect and admiration.
-Thank you.
The reason I chose to
reveal my identity to you
is because I think you
could be of some help to us
on the Kira investigation.
(VOICEOVER) Light Yagami.
The likelihood that you
are Kira is just under 5%.
Even so, something tells me
I'm not wrong to suspect you.
But you're just too perfect.
If you are Kira, I
can't think of anything
that would put more pressure on
you than this little scenario.
--[laughing] If this guy
is really L like he says,
then consider be impressed.
LIGHT YAGAMI
(VOICEOVER): Indeed.
If this guy really is L--
no, even if he's not L-- I--
I can't do anything to him.
Huh.
If what he's saying
is true, i-it probably
means he's already shown
his face to my father.
What now?
If he were to die right
after telling me who he was,
it would only confirm
their suspicions.
Although it's obvious
Hideki Ryuga is nothing
more than an absurd alias,
it still complicates things.
Even if I get lucky
and it isn't an alias,
if I try to kill him by simply
writing his name in the Death
Note, I might
accidentally picture
the face of Ryuga the pop star
and end up killing him instead.
And if this guy doesn't
die, he'll know for a fact
that I'm Kira.
Is he really L?
Does he already
suspect that I'm Kira?
It's hard to say
how much he knows,
but I must be under suspicion.
What other reason could he have
for telling Soichiro Yagami's
son that he's L?
Does this mean that he's
still suspicious of the people
that Raye Penber was
investigating before he died?
Even so, I still don't see
why he would reveal himself
to me directly.
I can't let him see
any signs of distress.
It's better if I
just clear my mind.
[crowd murmuring]
-Ha, I didn't think the ceremony
would be so interesting.
L: Hey, Light.
-You hear that?
I think it's your new friend.
-Uh, nice meeting you.
-No, the pleasure was mine.
-What an amazing car.
-A limousine?
-Well, I'm sure I'll
see you on campus.
LIGHT YAGAMI: Yeah, take care.
STUDENT 4: That kid must
come from some serious money.
STUDENT 5: Plus he's at
the top of the class?
Where's the justice?
[tv blaring]
-Huh?
Hey, welcome home, Mr. To-Oh!
RYUK: Hmm?
-Damn it!
He got me!
-Uh, what do you mean?
I
-Damn L!
I've never been so
humiliated in my life.
-Uh-- hey, why don't you just
do the Shinigami eye deal thing?
You should have no problem
killing him, right?
-And what good
will Shinigami eyes
do me if this is just a trap?
If I kill him, and it turns
out he's not really L,
that would be like announcing
to the real L that I am Kira.
-Uh, sorry.
-Don't think that Shinigami
killing people and humans
killing people are the same
thing, because they're not.
I want nothing more
than to kill him.
But if I do, it's like
asking to get caught.
Unfortunately, the
Death Note can only
kill the person whose
name is written in it,
so it's not like I can arrange
for someone else to kill him.
It's inconvenient.
That's the flaw
with the Death Note.
RYUK (VOICEOVER): Light
is usually so calm,
but he's snapped.
This must be getting to him.
-At first, I thought once
I found out his name,
I'd have him die in an
accident or kill himself.
However, none of that
will do me any good
unless I know with
100% certainty
that this guy is L. No, it's
already too late to do anything
about it since he's approached
me and introduced himself as L.
It doesn't matter how sure I am.
Regardless of the cause
of death, if L dies now,
the police are
going to suspect me.
I underestimated him.
I'd never even considered
the possibility
that he would reveal his
identity to me on purpose.
He could be telling all the
suspects the same thing.
In fact, it doesn't
even have to be him.
He could have sent
a double instead.
For L, this strategy
acts as a solid defense,
and it allows him to
confront Kira directly.
He can defend and attack.
He got me.
It was a good move.
I'm sure I haven't
seen the last of Ryuga.
He'll keep trying
to move in on me,
playing the
absent-minded genius,
and we'll pretend like
nothing's going on.
[laughing]
-Huh?
-This is perfect.
There's no reason
for me to be worried.
After all, this is proof that
they don't have anything on me
yet.
So this whole thing
is nothing more
than a contest between L and me.
A match of wits.
On the surface, we'll be
two friendly classmates.
But in reality, we'll actually
be investigating each other.
This is interesting, Ryuga.
If it's my friendship you
want, I'll gladly accept it.
In time, I'll earn your trust.
And once you've told
me what I want to know,
there'll be no point
keeping you alive.
Then I'll kill you, with
my hands if I have to.
Hmm.
[theme music]
LIGHT YAGAMI (VOICEOVER):
I don't see any way
that Ryuga, or L, can profile
me based on a tennis match.
So I have to assume he has
some other goal in mind.
Either way, I'm not
going to let him win.