[theme music]
MAN: Hey.
I thought we were supposed to
be meeting every other week.
Not this often.
-It can't be helped.
We just received a
new report from Coil.
He says that Misa Amane might
know L. According to Coil,
L once questioned Amane as
part of his Kira investigation.
But see, here's the problem.
He says, I've been
able to deduce
that Amane worships Kira.
At the moment,
Yoshida Productions
is trying to promote Amane
as the new face of Yotsuba.
My recommendation is that
Yotsuba use her for the next ad
campaign and take
the opportunity
to extract information
about L. Personally,
I don't like the idea.
It's unacceptable,
if you ask me.
-Oh really?
It seems like a
perfectly good plan.
-I don't think that's what
Ooi was trying to say.
It's supposed to be Coil's job
to investigate L's identity.
It doesn't make sense for him to
leave all the hard work to us,
in my opinion.
-Exactly.
We're paying him to uncover
L's identity, after all.
-Why don't we contact Coil
and see what he has to say?
MAN: Yes.
That's a good idea.
-Mr. Kida.
I thought we agreed
before that you'd only
call me if it was urgent.
So, is it an emergency?
Yes, I understand.
In that case, I think I
have an even better idea.
HIGUCHI: Even after
those meetings are over,
I have to come home
to punish criminals.
Being Kira is so time consuming.
But things sure have become
more interesting lately.
It's pretty clear that Misa
Amane was the second Kira,
and that L must've
caught her at some point.
The only way she could've
gotten out of that situation
is by forfeiting ownership
of her Death Note
and losing all memories
of what she did with it.
I'm not about to leave
things as they are.
I'm going to make
Misa Amane my wife.
-Huh?
-Everything I could ever want.
Money, power, and
a beautiful wife.
That'll be enough to
make anyone envious.
Once we're married, I'll
just invest a large lump sum
in her life insurance.
REM (VOICEOVER): She would never
marry such a disgusting fool.
-Rem.
Make sure you hide the
notebook in the usual place.
REM (VOICEOVER): Right
now, this is the only thing
I can do, for Misa's sake.
L: All right.
Let's try again, from the top.
-Tell me, Misa.
Is it true you once said that
you came to Tokyo in order
to meet Kira?
-What?
-Misa.
Please stop overacting.
It looks too cheesy,
not to mention fake.
-Huh?
But I thought that was
a realistic performance.
-Just do it again.
-Whatever you say,
oh so great director.
-If you don't get serious
about this, I'll kick you.
-Hmph.
-Uh, Misa Misa?
-You're not smiling
enough, Motchi!
And you can just call
me Misa, you know.
MOGI (VOICEOVER): I'm
not cut out for this,
but it's part of my
job, so-- Misa-Misa!
-What is it, Motchi?
-(EXCITEDLY) Today you have
an interview with the Yotsuba
group to see if they'll use
you in their new ad campaign.
But remember, this is also
an infiltration mission,
so stay sharp!
-Don't you worry.
I already know about that.
And of course, that
means you can't
let your cover fall either.
You're gonna play the character
of the hyper-energetic manager,
OK?
-Right!
Bring it on!
Hooah!
MAN: Sorry to keep you waiting.
-Good morning!
I'm Misa Misa's manager, Kanichi
Moji, also known as Motchi!
-Mr. Ooi, Mr. Shimura.
It's so nice to see you again.
-Good luck, Misa Misa!
MISA (VOICEOVER):
Way to go, Motchi.
You're a natural.
-I'll be here ready to celebrate
when they decide to hire you!
I don't think I'm
cut out for this.
-Now then.
I don't believe you and I
have met before, have we Miso?
My name is John Wallace.
I'm the executive adviser for
the advertising department.
Nice to meet you.
-Thank you!
I'm very pleased
to meet you too!
-Well, this might seem
a little bit sudden,
but I'd like to be
honest with you.
We've been talking about
it, and we've pretty much
decided to hire you already.
But before we make
it official, we'd
like to clarify a few things.
-Yes?
-We've been doing a little
background check on you,
and according to our
sources, a burglar
killed your parents
during a robbery.
You worship Kira because
he killed the suspect.
Isn't it true that
you came to Tokyo
in hopes of finding
and meeting Kira?
-Uh, what?
Who did you hear that from?
-I'm afraid I can't answer that.
The information is reliable,
and now I'd say it's confirmed.
The look in your face tells
me that these are the facts.
-Coil.
I never thought you
investigated that far.
-Also.
You're still hiding something
from us, aren't you?
Something you'd prefer
the world not to know.
MISA (VOICEOVER): OK.
Here's where I pause
and look nervous.
-It seems you were
detained by the detective L
for a short period of time.
We'd like you to tell us
the full story of what
really happened.
It would be a problem if
the new face of Yotsuba
turned out to be Kira.
-Yes.
We would appreciate it if
you were honest with us.
-All right.
I understand.
I'll tell you everything.
Yes.
I was held for questioning.
I didn't think it
was L, but he did
ask me lots of
questions about Kira.
But I'm not the second
Kira, and I never was.
I was released because he
realised I didn't have anything
to do with Kira after all.
-Did you manage to see who it
was that was restraining you?
-No.
I was blindfolded
the whole time.
-But if he asked you
questions, surely you
heard his voice, right?
-Only through a speaker
and voice filter, so--
-Come on.
What the hell is this anyway?
A job interview or a
police interrogation?
How long are we
gonna keep this up?
I'm going to the bathroom.
-He has a point.
It seems the interview
veered a little off track.
We're very sorry.
Excuse me, but would you mind if
I went to the bathroom as well?
This is getting exhausting.
But everything's
going well so far.
I just have to keep it up.
REM (VOICEOVER): Being
touched by this scrap of paper
alone will not restore her
memories of the Death Note,
but at least now Misa
can see me once again.
MISA (VOICEOVER):
What is this thing?
Some kind of monster?
-Misa.
You're in a dangerous
situation right now.
There are people within Yotsuba
who can easily have you killed.
I've come here to warn you.
Calm down and listen to me.
MISA (VOICEOVER): Calm down?
How can I?
This thing looks like
it's gonna kill me.
-Please believe me.
I'm your ally.
MISA (VOICEOVER): My ally?
-Oh, man, I wonder if
Misa Misa's all right.
Maybe we should've wired
her or used something
to track her movements.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Just as I thought.
The Kira before I was
detained and the one that
surfaced afterwards.
They must be two
different people.
The MO clearly doesn't match.
This Kira is killing
criminals as soon as they've
had their crime broadcast on
TV, regardless of the situation.
He's punishing people who
never intended to kill.
Those who sincerely regretted
their crimes or people
with excusable circumstances.
To original Kira would've never
punished those kinds of people.
That's the sort of distinction
I'd make if I were him.
The way the original
Kira acted is
disturbingly close to my ideals.
What the hell am I thinking?
I'm not Kira.
Something's got to
be wrong with me
if I'm seriously comparing
myself to that murder.
-Light Yagami is Kira.
Tell me.
What is Light doing
at the moment?
[mumbling]
-Wha-- What are you?
I mean, I can tell
you're not a stalker,
but-- but you don't look
like a human at all.
-No, of course not.
I am a Shinigami.
Before you were
captured by L, you and I
worked closely together.
-What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
You know me and Light is Kira?
-The Death Note.
It grants its owner the
power to kill someone simply
by writing that
person's name in it.
Light Yagami took
it upon himself
to punish criminals
using that notebook.
He soon became known
to the world as Kira.
You also possess
that same power.
In fact, your ability was
even greater than his.
You managed to find
Light by using your power
to determine that he
was, in fact, Kira.
-Light is Kira?
And I'm the second Kira?
REM: That's right.
Or rather, that
used to be the case.
Light arranged it so you
would both lose this power.
This was all
according to his plan.
-He did?
Then Ryuzaki was right.
-Misa, do you still love
Light enough to die for him?
-Unbelievable.
You've got to be
telling the truth.
You already know
everything about me.
I totally believe you now.
And yes, I do love him.
To death.
Not to mention how amazing
it is that Light and I were
both Kira.
Of course I'd want to
believe something like that.
I only wish I could remember it.
-You haven't changed, Misa.
And it seems your
feelings for Light
will never change, either.
It's enough to convince me that
the only way you can be truly
happy in life is if you can
support him in his plan.
-Thank you, Shinigami.
-It's Rem.
The current Kira is a vile
and pathetic human being.
I don't know what
he's capable of.
Be careful, and beware of
the others from Yotsuba.
Trust Light.
Let him do whatever
he feels necessary.
-OK.
I got it.
I guess I should just act normal
in the meantime though, right?
REM: That's right.
When you go back
to the interview,
you will be able to see for
yourself who the real Kira is.
Be on your guard,
and do not trust him.
-Oh my gosh, I'm so
sorry I took so long.
I was just fixing up
my makeup a little.
REM: Listen.
When you return, I
will be in the room.
The man sitting in front
of me will be Kira.
-(VOICEOVER) The person
in front of you is Kira.
Higuchi's Kira?
That bastard!
-Misa Misa sure is late.
[door closing]
-Hm?
-They're back.
-Hey!
I'm exhausted.
-Hey.
-How did it go?
-Yotsuba agreed to hire Misa
on as their spokesperson
for the new ad campaign.
L: I see.
That's good to hear.
-And I made sure to give
them my cell phone number.
Would you believe three out of
seven guys already messaged me
asking for a private date?
-What?
-So now I accept
their invitations
and investigate them, right?
Oh, it's going
exactly as I planned.
LIGHT: No.
The plan's getting
canceled right now.
-Huh?
But why.
Everything's been going
so smoothly up until now.
-If w go any further,
you'll be in danger.
You can still appear
in their commercials,
but from now on you should
deny that you were suspecting
of being the second Kira,
and was detained by Lo.
Mogi will continue
being your bodyguard,
but you'll be working
solely as a celebrity.
-If that's what you want,
Light, then that's what I'll do.
Oh, well.
I'm feeling pretty tired.
Tomorrow's shoot is
bright and early,
so I'd better get some sleep.
(VOICEOVER) Thank you, Light.
You're so sweet to
be worried about me.
But I've thought of
the best plan ever.
I'm gonna be useful to you.
I promise.
Hey, Light?
Wanna come sleep
with me tonight?
-Wh-- what are
you talking about?
-Just kidding.
You're saving it for after
we catch Kira, right?
You don't have to
be shy about it.
-Hm?
-Yes, Light.
There's no need to be shy.
-I'm not being shy.
-No need to be so
serious, either.
DIRECTOR: Cut!
OK, that's a wrap.
-Good work, everyone!
-Good job!
Thanks a lot, Miss Amane!
-Great job, Misa Misa.
-Thanks, Motchi.
Can you take me to the
restroom in that hospital?
-No problem.
I'll be waiting!
-I'll be sure not to
take too long, OK?
WOMAN: Yes?
Misa.
You actually made it.
-Nori, you look so cute
in that nurse's outfit.
-You really think so?
-That went well.
What an amazing car.
-If you like it, I'll
give you a ride anytime.
Or buy you one of your own.
By the way, loving that
nurse's outfit, Misa.
MISA: I'm glad you like it.
-That took a while.
[giggling]
-Ah!
Where's Misa?
-She's on a date.
-You've got to be kiddin'.
-(VOICEOVER) Kyosuke Higuchi.
The sleazy pervert
who's been sending me
text messages ever
since that party.
He's been even more persistent
than any of the other guys.
He's Kira?
It can't get any
worse than that.
HIGUCHI: Hey, Misa?
-Huh?
HIGUCHI: How about we
grab a bite to eat?
-Are you planning to take me
somewhere and do pervy things
to me?
Well, even if you
are, that's OK.
I'll be fine.
Since I can kill people.
(VOICEOVER) What are
you saying, Misa?
Is this part of
Light Yagami's plan?
Is this what he wants you to do?
Or is this your
way of telling me
that you want me to kill
Higuchi the moment he
tries to do anything?
-Come on you're just getting
with me, aren't you, Misa?
-You can kill people?
-Yep.
It's true.
And you know why?
Because I'm the second Kira.
-(VOICEOVER) That can't be.
Even if she was the
second Kira before,
there's no way she still is.
She's not supposed to have
any memory of it, either.
What the hell's going on?
(OUT LOUD) Oh, Misa.
You don't have to make up stuff
like that to feel safe with me.
I'm sure you'll find that
I'm quite the gentleman.
-MISA: Yeah, maybe.
Anyway, I'll only prove
that I'm the second Kira
to the real Kira.
-You'll only show proof to Kira?
Why?
MISA: I'd show him
because it's always
been my dream to
become Kira's wife.
I know he'll need me by
his side once I tell him.
-(VOICEOVER) If she
really is the second Kira,
then it's pretty clear from the
Sakura TV incident that she has
the Shinigami eyes.
If that's the case,
I need to make
sure I keep this
girl by my side.
At all costs.
I've got to test her, first.
Well, since I happen to be Kira,
does that mean you'll marry me?
Hm?
-Really?
-Yeah.
I mean it.
-What?
Then prove it to me.
Come on, let's prove
it to each other.
-I can't do that.
It'd be a pretty bad idea
to let someone witness how
I kill people.
-You think so?
-I dunno.
I thought someone
was Kira, I think
I'd be willing to show them.
We'd never get
anywhere if I didn't.
-Then why don't
you kill someone?
After all, I could
be the real Kira.
-All right.
But I only kill bad people, OK?
-That's right.
Bad person, huh?
This is Ginzo Kaneboshi,
president of a major finance
company.
He's infamous for his
immoral collection methods.
Sometimes he even makes people
pay with their insurance money.
How about him?
MISA: Would you be able to
confirm his death right away?
HIGUCHI: Yeah.
As soon as I call him.
MISA: OK, then.
Could you turn around
for just a sec?
-(VOICEOVER) Misa.
You want me to kill Ginzo
Kaneboshi, don't you?
Then Higuchi will
believe your claim
about being the second Kira.
Very well.
-All right.
He should be dead by now.
HIGUCHI: Hello, this is
Higuchi from Yotsuba--
MAN: Sorry.
Our president just collapsed
and stopped breathing.
Call back later.
[beeping]
-Told ya.
-She killed him.
The same guy I chose
just a minute ago.
It would've been
impossible to do
that unless she had the power.
This proves it.
So.
If I'm Kira, you'll
marry me, right?
-Wha-- Hey, why are you getting
so serious all of a sudden?
-Because I'm Kira.
-Then prove it.
-Hm.
I'm not going to be able
to kill until I get home.
You understand?
-Oh, well, that's no good then.
For all I know, you're
just making all this up
so you have an excuse to
take me to your place.
Wait!
I know.
-Huh?
-Why don't you stop killing
the criminals on TV.
That should prove it.
If you're Kira, it
should be no problem.
You can start killing
again when I tell you to.
If all the times
and deaths match up,
then I'll believe you.
After all, killing
criminals in that way
is something that
only Kira can do.
-I see what you mean.
That's a good idea.
All right, Misa.
I'm Kira, so in order to
make you trust me and prove
that I'm him, I'll stop killing
criminals for the time being.
Then, once you're fully
convinced I'm the real thing,
you and I can get married.
-And so, based on what
he said, Higuchi is Kira!
-Now we not only
know Kira's identity,
but all those deaths that
were worrying the chief
are gonna stop!
That's amazing, Misa Misa!
[theme music]
HIGUCHI: It's been
three days since I
stopped killing criminals.
That should be good enough.
Now if I marry Misa
Amane, the second Kira,
I'll have the Shinigami eyes.
With that power, Yotsuba
will be under my control.