[MIKURU sings]
[KYON] Her name is Mikuru
Asahina. On the outside,
she seems like a normal,
kind, and extremely cute girl.
But in reality, she's a battle
waitress from the future.
Don't ask me why she's from the
future or why she's a waitress
'cause that's not
important right now.
It's just a couple
of minor details
you need to have
shoved down your throat
before this particular
story can kick into gear.
Um... Not to bother
you people or anything.
We got a lotta good,
crispy nappa cabbage
in the store today.
Uh... Did I mention that
for the next hour only,
all nappa cabbage is
on sale for half price!
[KYON] By the way,
earlier I mentioned she
was a battle waitress,
so you're probably wondering
why she's wearing a
bunny girl costume here.
You see, that's
because during the day,
she has a part-time job
attracting customers
to the store in the
local shopping area.
I can't believe it.
Look, the nappa
cabbage is cheap today.
Yes, we should hurry
up and buy some.
Hi, Mikuru! Looks like you're
workin' hard out here today.
Why, yes! I'm trying my best!
[KYON]
Mikuru answers cheerfully,
in an outfit that screams
"trying too hard."
And so, thanks to
her innocent charm,
the nappa cabbage
sold out in record time.
You worked so hard.
Sorry this isn't much,
but I want you to have it.
Oh, no! I'm sure it's
more than enough!
I should be the one
apologizing to you.
This is pretty much
all I can do anyway.
See you later.
I have to head over
to the butcher shop
right away now,
without delay.
Accuse me-- Ah!
Excuse me.
[KYON] The girl had
become a sort of mascot
for the local retailers.
And she was loved
by all the people
who lived in the neighborhood.
You can do it, Mikuru!
Bring back the customers
who flock like lemmings
to that huge mega-warehouse
store that opened last year.
The fate of this neighborhood
and its mom and pop stores
is riding on your
shoulders, Mikuru.
Unfortunately, none of this has
anything to do with the story.
[KYON] Anyway, getting
back to the story,
she's actually
a battle waitress.
She was sent back in time to
secretly watch over someone,
and make sure no
harm came to them.
[KYON] And that someone's
name is Itsuki Koizumi.
Looking at him, you'd think
he was your average,
carefree high school student.
In reality, he's an ESPer.
Unfortunately, he's not
aware of his powers yet.
It seems he needs
a catalyst or trigger
to awaken all the super,
incredible powers
lying dormant within him.
[KYON] She looks like she's
got a high school crush
on a boy who she can't
express her true feelings to.
But, we'll just say that
was a little sigh of relief
because she saw
Itsuki was safe.
Mikuru finishes her
other part-time job,
which also requires
her to be scantily clad,
and goes home
to her tiny room
at the back of the
stationery store.
Aah, welcome back. My,
Mikuru, you seem a bit tired.
Oh, well, I'm fine. Really.
There were a lot
of customers today.
It was quite a busy day!
Aah, that's good.
Have a good evening.
[KYON] With her work
done for the day,
Mikuru can finally take
off that sleazy outfit,
change into something comfier,
and settle down for
a good night's sleep.
[KYON]
Okay, we stopped the camera
just before she took
her clothes off.
So, don't bother asking
us for the footage
'cause we don't have it. Honest!
[KYON] Yuki Nagato
stands here dramatically.
Although we don't
really know why,
you could say she's
not an ordinary girl,
and maybe she's a little weird.
Well, you're right
because she's actually
an evil witch
who's also an alien.
Okay, at this point,
you're supposed to get that
Yuki's planning something
diabolical that involves Itsuki.
But there's no reason
for her to be hanging out
at the high school
after he's gone home.
Also, the lighting's changed.
It was early evening
in the last scene.
But now, it's obviously
the middle of the day!
I mean, you can do
whatever you want,
but inserting cut
scenes like this
makes it really
hard for the editor.
Moving right along,
we've got the first battle scene
between Mikuru and Yuki.
All the stuff about them
meeting for the first time,
and the reason why
they're fighting,
I guess that's all gonna be left
up to the viewers' imagination
for various reasons, which
shall remain unexplained.
In fact, with the way
this has been going,
we'll be lucky if this movie
makes any sense at all.
Koizum-- Uh, I mean Itsuki,
is not a person that
you can control!
I'll protect him
with all I've got!
--[whimpers]
--[gunshots]
[KYON]
Allow me to explain:
The, uh, staff with
the creative design?
It's called the
Starring Inferno,
and it's supposed
to be a magic wand.
It's time to use
my secret weapon!
[grunts]
--Mi-Mi-Mikuru Beam!
--[zap]
[KYON]
Huh?
Let me explain.
The Mikuru Beam is a
super dangerous laser beam.
that shoots out of
Mikuru Asahina's left eye.
[HARUHI]
Cut! Cut!
[KYON] I'm literally
on the edge of my seat
wondering what's
gonna happen next.
Will Mikuru escape?
And why has Itsuki
suddenly shown up?
Th-This store is... Uh...
The owner's a really
friendly person!
He's a really nice guy!
They've been in
business ever since
Mr. Eijiro's grandpa opened it.
Uh... It's all right here!
Batteries to refrigerators,
they have it all!
Uh... And they...
have a lot of things...
J-Just hope on down
to Ohmori Electronics,
where good deals
are made every day!
[KYON]
Following her defeat,
Mikuru walks the
streets alone, deep in thought.
The Mikuru Beam had no
effect on that alien witch.
What will I do now?
[KYON] Other heroes can
transform into their alter egos,
but Mikuru has to
change her clothes.
You see, she's off
to work again today,
and mustn't be late.
Meanwhile, Itsuki was
walking along,
staring blankly at the
world as he always does.
Ahh!
And who might you be?
I am an alien from
beyond the stars
that uses the art of magic.
Well, is that so?
It is.
And what do
you want with me?
I have come from outer
space with only one goal:
To take your hidden
powers from you.
What would you do if I said
you were being a nuisance?
I am prepared to use
force if I have to
to take your hidden
powers away from you.
Just how would you use
force to obtain my powers?
Like this.
[MIKURU]
Look out!
Ow!
[MIKURU]
Owie...
Uh... I will never let
you get away with him,
you alien witch, you.
You have won today's round,
Battle Waitress.
And I promise you won't
be so lucky next time.
Please make your
funeral arrangements,
for when next we meet,
it will be the last.
Next time, you may
be certain that
I will intend to take you down
and destroy you with no mercy.
And who might you be?
[MIKURU]
Huh?! Uh...
Just an innocent bunny
girl passing through here.
That's all I am. Well, goodbye!
Just who in the world, is she?
[KYON] With a forced
look of awe on his face,
Itsuki watches
Mikuru run off.
And what's with the
camera tilting up like this?
Once again, a huge chunk of
the story has been left out.
After this and that,
involving you-know-what,
uh... the flames of battle
have burst up again.
I think.
E-E-Even in times like this,
I won't ever run away!
Y-You're an evil,
bad alien...
...and now, you'd better
leave this planet at once!
[music plays]
But it is you who should leave
this time plane
immediately, not I.
For we shall seize him
and his hidden powers.
For he is very valuable
to us, you see.
And while we're seizing
him and his hidden powers,
we will also
invade the Earth.
I-I won't let you
get away with that!
I will risk my own
life to stop you!
Prepare yourself then, for I
am about to take your life.
[snickers]
[music plays]
[gasps]
But Tsuruya! Don't tell
me that even you--
Please get yourself
back together!
[laughs]
I can't take you seriously
when you're dressed like that.
I'm sorry, Mikuru.
I'm being controlled
by the alien right now.
Here goes nothing...
[gasps]
[KYON] Uh... Some kind
of electromagnetic waves
coming out of the so-called
Starring Inferno wand
has turned Tsuruya and the guys
into a trio of mindless puppets.
[TANIGUCHI moaning]
[KYON]
Now she's trapped!
What are you going
to do, Mikuru?
[MIKURU whimpering]
[TANIGUCHI, MIKURU scream]
[KYON]
She couldn't do anything.
[MIKURU, TANIGUCHI
screaming, coughing]
[KOIZUMI]
What's happened?
Just grab my hand, it's okay.
[KYON]
Okay, Itsuki just showed up,
but where's he
been all this time?
I think they
accidentally got him
in the shot a few moments ago.
Oh... The water's so cold...
Would you please tell me
just what in the world you
were doing here today?
[MIKURU]
Huh? Um.. Oh, yeah.
Evil people and the
lake and uh... I don't...
[HARUHI whispers] This is
when you're supposed to faint!
[MIKURU]
Ohh...
Get ahold of yourself!
[KYON] Normally, in a
situation like this,
you'd call an ambulance
or flag down a passerby
to get some help.
But this boy decides to
carry this unconscious,
innocent, young beauty,
and is attempting to
take her away somewhere!
Damn you!
Anyway, Yuki's gang
seems to have bailed
without finishing Mikuru off,
which they totally
could've done.
With so many mysteries,
contradictions,
and plot threads left dangling,
we tilt up again as the story
finally reaches
the halfway point.
Hold on, we're only
halfway through this thing?
[music plays]
[KYON]
We're back!
And I think we're
in Itsuki's house.
What bothers me, though,
is that Mikuru, who's been
carried here by Itsuki,
looks like she's just
gotten out of the bath!
Maybe we're
supposed to think that
she was given a bath by Itsuki
while she was unconscious?!
You gotta be kidding me!
Then this would be the point
where anyone's doubt
turns into a white-hot rage,
building into a desire to kill.
But for now, I will not
give it much thought,
doing away with
all the emotions
that might be bubbling up.
We are, after all,
just watching a movie
with actors, playing characters.
This isn't reality, right?
[KYON gasps]
O-Okay, how is this
happening right now?
If your mouth gets
any closer to her,
someone standing off camera
is gonna step into frame
and kick your ass, dammit!
Hold it right there.
Itsuki Koizumi...
You should not be making
the choice of that female.
You must choose me instead,
for the true potential
of your hidden powers
will only be realized when
they mingle with my power.
Please explain exactly
what you mean by that.
[KYON] Okay, why isn't he
at least a little surprised
to see Yuki at the window?
All I can tell you at
this very moment is
that you have two choices
before you right now.
The first choice
is to be with me
and to make this universe
evolve into what it should be,
and the second
is to be with her,
but that will only
destroy the future.
[KYON]
Itsuki was worried now,
more than he ever was.
But, what Nagato-- I mean, Yuki.
What she said just now, she
was talking about him, right?
Very well!
I understand that he--
No, in this scene,
it's me, so I...
I am a kind a of key,
and a key all by itself does
not have any power whatsoever!
And a key is nothing but a tool
with which you
can open the door.
And when that door
is finally opened,
something is going to change.
And I know that what
will change is...
That's about all
I understand, Yuki.
But right now, I don't have the
right to make that decision.
In fact, I think
it's far too early
for me to come up
with a decision.
Maybe we should put all
of this deciding stuff
on hold for a while,
I really feel that
we need more time
to think this
whole thing through.
Although, if you
ever decide to tell me
the whole truth about it,
now that is a different story.
There will be time enough
for that in the near future.
I know that now is definitely
not the time for it.
We consider a lack
of information to be
more of an obstacle,
a handicap, a critical flaw.
We are unable to make
decisions based on information
that relies on what
is possible or probable.
[KYON] You could say they're
setting up a plot line,
but that dialogue
was incomprehensible!
The important thing
to note is that
the two of them have reached
some sort of understanding.
Uh, I'm standing
here in front of
Keiji Yamatsuchi's Model Shop.
He opened it last year
after quitting his
dead-end corporate job.
And models were his hobby,
so he figured why
not open a store.
Unfortunately, his sales
have been down for a while.
And compared to last year,
his first-half earnings for this
year are down about 80%. And so,
everyone should come down
here and buy lots of models!
Thank you!
[sighs]
Huh? You want me to hold it?
Y-You should never shoot this
while pointing it
at other people.
You should only shoot
empty cans with it!
Huh? You want me to shoot?
[screams]
[KYON]
I know you've probably
lost all interest in
the story by now,
but here's an
interesting development.
Mikuru and Itsuki have
started living together.
Well, now this is like
one of those cute,
young housewives' shows.
And it makes you wonder
what all those sci-fi
battle scenes were about.
Are they trying to spice up the
story by tossing out the plot
and throwing all of those
moe situations at us?
[KYON] And who the heck
is that supposed to be?
Is she Itsuki's
little sister?
And wasn't that cat
staying on Yuki's shoulder
a couple of scenes ago?
Now, Yuki tries a
different plan. And it looks
like she's transferred
into Itsuki's high school.
[KYON] Yuki attempts to ensnare
Itsuki by using her sex appeal.
And if you ask me, I guess
I'd have to say that
all's fair in love
and war, right?
[KYON] Eventually,
Mikuru also transfers
into the same high school.
[KYON]
You might be thinking,
if her job is to protect him,
why didn't she infiltrate
his school earlier/
But, you're asking
the wrong guy.
Yuki and Mikuru's
story of battling
has now turned into a
heated romantic comedy.
Or rather, nothing more
than a love triangle.
[KYON]
When they're at school,
they seem to have agreed
to a truce of some sort.
We must've missed the scene
where they do the whole
"realizing your
true nature" thing,
and the two of them are now
back to pretending to be
the battle waitress
and the alien magician
engaging in really
lame fight scenes.
As for what's
gonna happen next,
even I, the cameraman,
don't know the answer.
It's a fight to the death
that completely lacks
any sense of excitement.
[KYON] This schizophrenic
story reaches its final act,
as if it were written
by a drunk child.
I'm assuming the
director of this film
felt that they needed
to end things quickly,
and it really didn't
matter how they did it.
It's a bit late,
but that's okay.
Anyway, Yuki challenges
Mikuru to a final showdown.
I see now.
[KYON]
What exactly did she see?
Why the long face, Mikuru?
Is another creepy old
geezer stalking you?
Or did your doctor tell you
you've got athlete's foot?
The time has finally
come at last!
I must go and have
the final battle
with the evil alien witch!
That sounds amazing, Mikuru.
We're counting on you.
The Earth is in your--
Pfft! [laughs]
[KYON] I know I'm
nitpicking here,
but I don't see how Mikuru
and Tsuruya know each other.
Sure, you could
say that they met
after Mikuru transferred
to the high school,
but then how does
that explain the scene
where Tsuruya attacked
Mikuru at the lake?
That happened before Mikuru
started going to the school.
That's a huge error
in continuity and if
you don't know
what to do next,
slowly pan the camera
and shoot the sky...
[KYON] Anyway, we've reached the
climax of the film... finally.
And now, let us settle the
final score once and for all.
I am afraid that you and I
do not have very much
time left anymore.
We must resolve our conflict
before our lunch break is over.
That is something
we both agree on!
However, I'm positive
that Itsuki will say
that he's gonna choose me!
Um... Well, I just know
that he's gonna pick me!
That is unfortunate for you
because I do not intend
to acknowledge his
free will at all.
At last, his hidden
powers will all be mine.
[KYON]
If she wants him so badly,
why doesn't she
just go and get him?
Am I the only
one thinking this?
I won't let you do it!
That is the reason
why I have come here
all the way from the future!
[music plays]
[yells]
Jump!
[whimpers]
[HARUHI] Mikuru! You have
to get up and fight! Hurry!
[TEACHER] Hey!
What's going on out--
[KYON] Nevermind the
teacher that came bursting
through the door, the battle
continues on the roof.
And it looks like Mikuru's
finally been cornered.
[MIKURU whimpering]
It's really high...
The time has come for
you to give in to me.
The hour of doom is at hand.
[wand pinging]
[KYON] Yuki unleashes her death
blow upon the helpless Mikuru.
I know the special
effects here are weak,
but there's really no other way
to make this thing
more thrilling.
So please, use your
imagination to embellish.
It really looks hopeless!
What'll you do, Mikuru?
[KOIZUMI]
Are you all right?
That's enough, Yuki!
Stop this at once!
Stop talking and get on with it.
--The only thing you have
--[KYON] Hey, Shamisen, stop!
to do is take over his mind,
and then we're done here.
It's not like you haven't done
something like that before,
so just wave your little
stick at him and--
I am also a ventriloquist.
[NAGATO]
Take this, Itsuki Koizumi.
I will now proceed
to take control
of your thoughts and actions.
[wand pinging]
[KOIZUMI grunts]
--[NAGATO] Curses!
--[SHAMISEN meows]
At last, it is over,
Miss Asahina.
[MIKURU]
Uh...
[KYON] Itsuki's unexplainable
powers have awakened,
and Yuki, the alien witch,
was transported to
the far reaches
of the universe.
Peace has returned to our world.
Thank you, Mikuru Asahina.
And thank you, Itsuki Koizumi.
All is well, that ends well.
And we're tilting up again?
[music plays]
[HARUHI] This story
is a work of fiction.
All character names,
organizations, incidents,
and any other names,
phenomena, and such,
are fictional as well.
It's all made up.
Even if it
resembles someone,
it's probably
just a coincidence.
Oh! Except for
the commercials.
Shop at Ohmori Electronics
and Yamatsuchi's Model Shop
for great deals!
Stop by and buy!
Huh?! I gotta say it again?
This story is a work of fiction.
All character names,
organizations, incidents,
and any other names...
Hey, Kyon! Why do I have to
say all this stuff anyway?
[HARUHI]
It's finished!
That totally rocked!
The SOS Brigade doesn't know
the meaning of the
word "impossible!"
Isn't that right, Kyon?
[KYON] You're actually
gonna show this to people?!
It's so good the
theater will be packed
for every screening
during the arts festival!
Maybe we should charge
admission to see the film!
Oh! I should touch base
with the Film Club...
[KYON] I think I'm gonna
skip the festival today
--and take a nap somewhere.
[HARUHI]... for the sequel!
[HARUHI]
Right, Kyon?