[KYON]
Something's wrong.
That's what it felt like anyway.
The game on TV was between
schools from another town.
I had nothing to do
with either school,
but because I tend to
sympothize with underdogs,
I found myself routing
for the losing team.
And it was right about then
that I suddenly got the feeling
Haruhi was gonna call.
[phone ringing]
[KYON]
What does she want?
Your phone's ringing, Kyon.
I know, I know.
[HARUHI]
Hey, you're free, right?
Good, meet us at 2:00 in front
of the station. Don't be late!
[dial tone]
[KYON] I didn't even have
the chance to say anything.
[phone ringing]
[KYON]
What?
[HARUHI] I forgot to tell you
to bring your swim trunks.
And some money, too.
Oh, wait, and your bike.
Definitely bring your bike.
That's it! Over and out!
[phone clicks]
[KYON]
Uh. No.
That was weird.
It's like I knew what
Haruhi was gonna say
before she said it.
Yeah, no. Actually,
it felt like we'd had
the exact same
conversation before.
Like déjà vu or something.
[COMMENTATOR] There's
the wind-up. It's outta there!
Home run! What a shot!
[KYON]
Summer's almost over, isn't it?
[HARUHI]
You're late, Kyon!
Where's your motivation, huh?
[KYON] Yeah, yeah.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Oh, I just got here too.
[HARUHI] Now that we're all
present and accounted for,
we can go!
Where?
To the public pool!
Where do you think?
[KYON] Figures,
considering what I brought.
[HARUHI] We've got lots and lots
of summer vacationy things to do
during our break, but
there's only so much time,
and once it's gone,
it's gone for good.
So we're gonne do everything
we can while we can
during our one and only
summer as tenth graders.
And for starters, we're gonna
ride bikes over to the pool.
So, did everyone ride
their bikes today?
No. The only bikes
we have to take
are the ones you and I brought.
[KYON]
Huh?
All right, Kyon. Don't let
Koizumi beat you over there.
Come on, full speed ahead!
[KYON]
Boost!
Come on, guys. Hurry up
and park your bikes already.
We're trying to have fun, Kyon.
Stop acting like you're tired.
[KYON]
And whose fault is that?
[HARUHI]
Ah. Can you smell the chlorine?
That really makes
it feel like summer.
[HARUHI giggles]
Hurry up and get in!
Water's all warm. It's perfect!
[KYON] Can't she see
the no diving signs?
They're everywhere.
Doesn't that look like fun?
In a way, it makes me smile.
Such a peaceful scene, isn't it?
I mean, seeing Miss
Suzumiya enjoy the day
in a normal fashion, rather
charming, don't you think?
She called me, told me
what to bring,
and ordered me to meet her
without telling me
what was going on.
There's nothing charming
or normal about it.
Well, if you ask me,
none of what you mentioned
is anything to make
such a fuss over.
As long as Miss Suzumiya's
having a good time,
we don't have to worry about
any earth-shattering events.
[KOIZUMI chuckles]
[KYON]
I hope you're right.
[KOIZUMU]
Hm?
Something wrong?
No. It's just my imagination.
With everything that's
happened since we met,
you could say I've
become slightly paranoid.
[KYON]
Hm?
[ALL giggling]
[KYON]
Hot.... Hot. So hot.
Jeez. Now I know why they call
it a "public" swimming pool.
Seems like everyone
in town's here today.
[KYON] I wonder why
Haruhi chose this place.
[KYON]
Hm?
There's that feeling again.
It's like I've seen this
happen once before.
With Nagato looking kinda
bored like that. Alone.
[HARUHI]
Kyon!
[KYON]
Uh.
Uh-huh.
And then Haruhi's supposed
to say something like...
These two guys are
my brigade members.
And they do what I say.
So if you want somethin',
you can ask them.
It's time to have some fun!
Let's all go play water soccer!
[KYON]
Yeah, yeah.
[KYON] Oh well.
Sometimes déjà vu's happen.
[HARUHI]
Here is comes, Mikuru!
[MIKURU]
Okay!
[MIKURU yelps]
[HARUHI] I have a couple ideas
about the rest of our vacation.
Check it out!
[KYON]
Two weeks to do all of that?
Is there anything you
want to do, Mikuru?
[MIKURU] Umm... I'd like
to try goldfish scooping.
[HARUHI]
Okay. Goldfish scooping it is.
Could I see that?
Thank you.
We'll the list tomorrow.
Does anyone know if there's a
bon festival happening close by?
Or a firework show?
I can check and see
if there's anything.
[HARUHI] Don't foget
about goldfish scooping.
It's Mikuru's only request.
[KOIZUMU]
I'll get right on it.
[KYON] I always get
stuck with the bill.
[HARUHI]
Well, that's it. See ya!
[KOIZUMU]
I'm off, too.
[MIKURU]
Bye, bye.
[KYON]
Nagato!
Uhh, it's...
I guess it's nothing important.
Anyway, how've you been?
Is everything okay?
I am fine.
Well, that's good to hear.
Yes.
[grunts]
[KYON] What the heck?
Why did I wanna talk to her?
[phone ringing]
[KYON] The next morning, I was
waken from my peaceful slumber
by a call from Haruhi.
She said they'd
found a bon festival.
It was happening tonight.
At a park somewhere.
We're all gonna go buy yukatas!
[KYON] So, we went
to a clothing outlet.
Haruhi picked out yukatas
for Miss Asahina and Nagato.
Then marched them straight
into the changing room.
After making us wait
about an hour or so,
they all three finally came out.
[KYON]
Whoa.
[KOIZUMI]
You look wondering in those.
Of course we do!
I picked them out myself.
Especially Mikuru's.
Look at you, you're so cute.
I must be a genius.
Uh... Uh, yes.
[KYON]
The blushing makes her cuter!
Wow.
[KYON]
A bon festival, huh?
It figures that
it'd be so crowded.
Hm?
I haven't been to a
bon festival in a while,
but it feels like I
just went to one.
That tower.
Those vendors.
[HARUHI]
Look, Mikuru!
They've got goldfish scooping
just like you wanted!
You're gonna catch a ton!
Do you wanna go scoop some fish?
We could have a contest.
I think I'll pass.
How 'bout you, Nagato?
Wanna get some food?
[KYON]
Hm?
Don't tell me you're actually
into this kinda stuff.
I got it.
[NAGATO]
No.
That.
[VENDOR]
It's yours for 800 yen!
[KYON] I wish she would've
let me buy tht for her.
It's the least I could do
after all she's done for us.
Wow! What an unbelievable haul!
But I only kept one, 'cause
I don't have any place
to keep 'em. And I
gave one to Mikuru.
Go ahead and have one,
but only one.
Okay, thanks.
[HARUHI] Uh. Hey, Yuki.
What's up with the mask?
[NAGATO]
I bought it.
[HARUHI]
Oh, okay.
[HARUHI] Fireworks!
That's what we're gonna do next!
We'll go set up some fireworks!
[KYON]
Do you even understand
the meaning of the
word moderation?
[KYON] It was summer,
and summer vacation.
And I guess that's why I
wanted to forget about it.
But the truth was, I couldn't
ignore it any longer.
[HARUHI] Tomorrow,
we're gonna catch some bugs.
Haruhi, I don't want
to spoil your fun,
but have you finished
your homework?
[HARUHI] Are you kidding?
That stuff's totally easy.
You can finish it
in like three days.
Three days?!
[HARUHI] You have to get
rid of that junk first
so you can spend the rest
of your summer having fun
and not worrying about it.
That's the only way
to really get the most
out of your vacation.
[KYON] Why does she
have to be so smart?
[KYON] The folks upstairs
weren't terribly fair
when they were divvying
up the stats for us.
[HARUHI] Listen up! We're gonna
go bug catching tomorrow!
And whoever catches
the most bugs is gonna
get to be brigade
leader for a whole day!
[KYON]
No thanks.
That sounds like fun.
But, can we catch just any bugs?
[HARUHI]
Hm... No. Only cicadas!
That's it!
I'm calling it the SOS Brigade's
cicada catching contest!
[KYON] The next day was
beautiful, sunny and bright.
And although everyone caught
bugs the best way they knew how,
the winner of the contest ended
up being, you guessed it,
Haruhi.
[HARUHI] It's important
to follow the spirit
of catch and release
with these guys.
You never know.
If we let 'em go now,
they might return
the favor sometime.
[KYON] Now, what could a
cicada possibly do for me?
[HARUHI]
Hurry! Go back to the mountains!
[cicadas chriping]
[KYON]
For some reason,
I kinda feel like
Pandora opening her box.
[MIKURU]
W-Welcome to our store!
[KYON]
We met the next day,
eventhough we had no
idea what was going on.
Our cluelessness continued as we
were made to wear frog costumes
and hand balloons out in front
of the local supermarket.
Welcome to our part-time job.
[sighing]
[HARUHI]
Good work, you guys!
[KYON] What's with
the special treatment?
You're the best.
The manager's super grateful
for all the hard work.
Who cares how grateful
he is. What about our pay?
That's it.
[KYON]
Huh?
I've had my eye
on this for a while.
The manager gave it to us
'cause Mikuru
looked so cute in it.
[KYON] We were working, sweat
pouring down our foreheads,
for that?!
We'll keep 'em in the
club room as a souvenir.
Mikuru, you have my permission
to wear 'em whenever you want.
Isn't he the greatest?
[gasps]
Uh.
[KOIZUMI chuckles]
[KYON] Later that night,
my peaceful slumber
was interrupted by a phone call.
[phone ringing]
Damn it.
[MIKURU groaning]
[KYON gasps]
[MIKURU]
Kyon...
Miss Asahina?
[MIKURU]
Yes, it's me.
Something really bad...
I don't know...
[MIKURU crying]
Wha--?
[KOIZUMU]
Hello. It's Koizumi.
[growls]
Why are you with Miss Asahina
in the middle of the night?
[KOIZUMU]
We have a situtation here.
Do you think you could
come meet us right now?
[KYON]
Absolutely. Where?
Miss Asahina! What happened?
Oh... Oh, Kyon. I can't...
[crying]
I can't go back to the future.
[MIKURU sobbing]
I'll explain it the best I can.
Currently, we're stuck in a time
loop that seems to be infinite.
[KYON] It's hard to
believe you're serious
with that smile on your face.
Come on, Koizumi, do you
realize what you just said?
[KOIZUMU] Of course I do.
More than I want to, believe me.
Ealier, I was having a
word with Miss Asahina.
[KYON] Next time, call me
when you have a word with her!
And that was when
we both realized that
something seemed off about
our current flow of time.
Actually, Miss Asahina
discovered it.
Thanks to her, my suspicions
were confirmed.
What kind of suspicions?
[KOIZUMU] That we'd been
reliving the same period of time
over and over again.
[KYON]
You already said that.
[KOIZUMU] We've been
repeating the days
between August
17th through the 31st.
It's a never-ending,
endless summer.
The future doesn't exist
in this world anymore.
Time stops at September 1st.
That's the reason Miss Asahina
can't travel back to the future.
It's only natural.
There's nothing natural
about not having a future.
Who's gonna believe
such a thing?
Well, for starters, we were sort
of hoping you would believe it.
[MIKURU crying]
Um...
I can try to help explain it.
Here goes.
Because I have to
classified information,
I used classified information
to get in touch with the future.
The thing is,
I haven't gotten any classified
information for about a week.
And I started to think
how weird that was.
I was so surprised.
I classified information,
I really did,
but it was classified
information, too.
I don't know what to do.
[MIKURU crying]
[KYON] I don't know how to
help you, but I'm wondering,
are all the classfied
things you're talking about
stuff you can't say on TV?
What about those closed spaces
you were talking about before?
Maybe we're trapped
in one of those.
[KOIZUMU]
Mh-hm.
It's not one of those.
A specific section of
time has been torn away.
At exactly midnight on August
the 31st, everything resets,
and then time
reverts straight back
to the morning
of August the 17th.
That's the process.
What about our...?
Wait, what about the
whole world's memories?
Their memory is reset.
Everyone's memory starts
over from the beginning.
[KYON] Another problem
involving time. Perfect.
I guess that figures when
there's a time traveller around.
[KOIZUMU]
No.
Miss Asahina didn't have
anything to do with this.
[KYON]
Then what's causing it?
[KOIZUMU]
Miss Suzumiya.
[sighs]
Somewhere inside her,
there's a desire to have
summer vacation last forever.
I'm sure she
doesn't even realize it.
Oh, come on.
You mean she still
hasn't had enough fun?
That's what it looks like.
Perhaps she feels like
there's something else
that needs to happen before
our summer vacation is over.
[KYON] Man, the trouble
she gets us into
is always galactic in scale.
[KYON] All right,
what do you want me to do?
If I knew that, we'd have
this problem solved by now.
[KYON]
You're too close.
You seem like
you're enjoying this.
You wanna tell me why?
Please don't take
it the wrong way,
but this explains the
feelings of déjà vu I've had,
and the ones you've
been feeling as well.
Now that I think about it,
they were most likely the
residue of our memories
from every instance where
time had been reset.
[KYON]
Are we the only ones?
Or can other people
feel this, too?
[KOIZUMU]
I doubt that.
You and I are acceptions
to the rule, though.
The only people who can
sense this strangeness,
are the ones closest
to Miss Suzumiya.
[KYON]
What about Haruhi?
Does she even know
this stuff is happening?
[KOIZUMU]
No, I don't think so.
Besides, it would be very
bad for us if she did.
However, there is someone
who is unaffected by
the feelins of déjà vu.
As a matter of fact,
this person remembers
everything that's happened.
Oh, yeah? Who would
that person be?
[KOIZUMU]
You already know.
It's Miss Nagato.
The data integration thought
entity transcendes space
and time. So does she.
Is that true?
[NAGATO]
Yes.
Then, you remember everything?
Really?
So, how many times has
this happened to us?
[NAGATO]
This would be 15,498 times?
[gasps]
[KYON] Fifteen thousand,
four-hundred and ninety-eight?
What do you mean 15,498?
What are you saying, Nagato?
And, you're being
completely serious?
Yes.
[KYON] So, you're saying
we've done the exact same things
every time that many times?
[NAGATO]
Not necessarily.
Throughout 15,498 repitions,
we did not attend a bon
festival the 2,391st time
and the 11,054th time.
We went to the
festival but did not go
to a fish scooping
booth 437 times.
We obtained part-time
jobs 9,025 times
--and there were six different--
--[KYON] Okay. I got it.
[KYON] Fifteen-thousand,
four-hundred ninety-eight.
That's what she said. Times two
weeks. That's... 594 years.
She's the only one who remembers
everything we do
all those times.
And she's had to repeat
them over and over again.
Nagato...
I can't even begin to image
what it's been like for you.
That's gotta be the
craziest story ever.
[KYON] The next night,
we went stargazing.
We were on the balcony
of Nagato's apartment,
since her place
had the best view.
Koizumi brought the telescope.
[HARUHI]
I wonder if they're real.
What's real?
[HARUHI]
Martians.
[KYON]
I kinda hope they aren't.
[HARUHI] I can't see
anyone on the surface.
You know, I bet there is a
reserved race of beings
living underground.
They're probably friendly, too.
[KYON]
Yeah. Dream on.
[HARUHI] Whenever us
humans finally land on Mars,
I'm sure the Martians will pop
out from wherever they're hiding
and say, "Welcome
to Mars," or something.
[KYON] It'll get
mistaken for an attack.
[HARUHI] Oh. I'm bored.
I'm gonna look for UFOs now.
I wish I knew what
else she wanted to do.
Yes, what indeed.
If we knew that, we'd be on
our way to solving this problem.
Here's something.
Why don't we try this?
What if someone were to grab
Miss Suzumiya from behind
and then they whisper,
"I love you" right into her ear.
And who's going
to be doing this?
Who else could play
that role other than you?
[KYON growls]
I'm vetoing that idea!
[KOIZUMU] All right.
Shall I give it a try?
No, I'm just kidding.
That isn't a role I can play.
Besides, it would just
confuse Miss Suzumiya.
[KYON]
The next day,
we swung for the fences
at the batting cages.
[HARUHI grunts]
[KYON]
Hey, Nagato.
You knew about this
time loop we're in
way before Miss Asahina
figured it out, didn't you?
Yes.
So, how come you didn't
say anything about it?
[NAGATO]
My function is to observe.
[HARUHI grunts]
[KYON sighs]
[KYON]
Right.
We kept chugging along,
doing all kinds of
summer vacation things.
We just kept going and
going and doing stuff.
And the whole time,
all I could think was
that none of it was going
to be enough for Haruhi.
But what could I do
about it? Nothing.
So, we ended up like we
always did at August the 30th.
[HARUHI] That's it, we've done
everything on our list.
[sighs]
But now I'm wondering
if we did enough... if....
No, I guess we did.
Hey, is there anything
else you want to do?
Oh, okay.
I guess we did everything we
wanted to do over the summer,
so that's enough.
[KYON] No, it's not.
Not by a long shot.
You're still not satisfied.
Okay, we're done for today.
I set tomorrow
aside just in case,
but you can take
the day off, I guess.
I'll see you guys at the
club room on Monday.
[KYON gasping]
[KYON]
No, wait! Haruhi!
[KYON gasps]
There's that feeling again.
It's strong... Stronger
than all the others.
I can't let Haruhi leave.
If I let her walk out that door,
we'll end up reliving the past
two weeks again and again
for a thousand more times.
But... what should I do?
What should I say?
There must've been a clue
in something Haruhi said.
But what was it?
What's she been
saying all this time?
[KYON]
I don't know. I can't remember.
It's August 31st.
And I still haven't
touched my homework yet.
Whatever. Doesn't matter.
[KYON] There's no point
doing it. I mean,
we're just gonna keep reliving
the last couple of weeks.
Whatever happens next,
whether tomorrow comes or not,
a different version of me
will have to deal with it.