[music plays]
[KYON]
Surreal and incomprehensible,
cobbled together during
an all-night editing session,
the movie, spawned from
the director/producer's
whacked out mind,
was finished.
The SOS Brigade was now free
to spend a peaceful first day
at the school arts festival.
Fortunately for me,
Haruhi decided she'd handle
all the negotiating and
promoting stuff by herself.
My job was to drop off the
DVD with the Film Club,
who was screening
the movie for us.
After that, I wandered
around the campus
with a cloud-free conscience,
enjoying the festival atmosphere
despite my sleep-deprived state.
[KYON] However, there was
still one important duty
that I had to take care of.
[KYON]
Unlike my class of slackers,
whose activity was some
kind of campus survey thing,
Nagato, Koizumi,
and Miss Asahina
were working the attractions
their classes had organized.
[NAGATO] You will buy
soft-serve ice cream
five minutes and
fifteen seconds from now.
You will drop it in
five minutes and
twenty-eight seconds from now.
You will hit your head on a sign
seven minutes and
six seconds from now.
And then, you will bump into
your girlfriend and fall over.
The items in her
bag will scatter,
leading to quarrel...
[KYON]
Take it easy, Nagato.
You're telling their fortunes,
not predicting their future.
You and I both
know very well that
the law of probability
governs all of nature
and the world around us.
And yet, having witnessed
this phenomenon,
I now find it difficult to
believe in such a thing.
Perhaps we should think on this
occurence in a different way,
that we are in the midst
of something supernatural,
a far cry from anything
we have ever known.
For example, let us say
that we have six monkeys...
[KYON]
What is this?
Could you just let us know
when we're supposed to laugh?
Come on in and check
out our stuff today!
You'll be sorry if you don't!
[TANIGUCHI]
Yo!
[KYON]
You guys have any luck?
Nope. Not as much as I expected.
Table Tennis Club had
ping pong ice cream, though.
Senior year, class 3,
had some good oden.
Junior year, class 5, had
chocolate-covered bananas
that were more
bananas than chocolate.
You're kidding!
All you're doing is eating?
Yeah, we're just
sampling the food.
Now it's time to get to
the real deal, though.
The cosplay cafe!
[KUNIKIDA]
Man, that bunny girl outfit
from a while back
was unbelievable.
I wonder what she's
gonna wear today.
Yeah, well, we acted
in your movie for free.
And then I was pushed
in the water for free.
And all we got to show for it
is a coupon for 30%
off some fried noodles?
You ask me, it really
wasn't worth it.
You don't like it, don't come!
Just go home!
Yeah, right! Not before I
sneak a peek at Miss Asahina
in all her cosplay glory.
I wonder if she'll be a waitress
in a tight little miniskirt
like she was in the movie.
[KYON] Her sense of style isn't
the same as Haruhi's, buddy.
But a waitress outfit handmade
by one of her classmates?
I'm so there!
[TSURUYA]
Thank you.
Hey! It's Kyon and his buddies!
Come on over here,
Thanks for coming by.
Table for three today?
Oh, wait. What do you
think about my outfit?
Doesn't this thing look
totally awesome on me, megas?
Aren't I cute, nyoron?
Oh, absolutely.
You're packing them in!
The fish always take the bait!
I mean, it's just
bad fried noodles
made with really
cheap ingredients,
but look at all these
people standing in line!
We're raking in so much money,
I can't stop laughing!
[KYON] Yeah, and I'm
sure it's just coincidence
that all your
customers are guys.
Oh, head over there!
It's the end of the line!
Go on, get in line!
Here we are.
Please pay in advance.
Oh! And another thing,
we've only got fried
noodles and tap water.
Now, the noodles
are 300 yen each,
but the water's free,
so it's all you can drink!
So, what's this get us?
Let's see, so it's just
the three of you...
With these things,
we're talking 500 yen!
Some deal, huh?
Okay, boys, hang out
here for a sec,
and your turn'll be
coming up shortly!
Wow, she's a hyper girl.
Is she a member of
you and Suzumiya's
buncha whackos, too?
Nope.
By the way, don't forget
to split the change with us.
[KYON]
He got me.
The, uh, "shortly" that Miss
Tsuruya was talking about
was 30 minutes.
So, we stood outside and waited
until she finally let us in.
[MIKURU]
Okay. Oh! Welcome to our cafe!
[TANIGUCHI screams]
[KYON]
She's a dazzling waitressi
who'd put a million dollar view
of the city lights to shame.
She's got a different glimmer
here than back at the club.
Welcome! And thank you so much
for stopping by to see us today!
[MIKURU]
Um... Uh...
--Taniguchi!
--Kunikida!
[MIKURU giggles] Thank you
for your help on the movie.
[KYON]
I see...
If they let you take pictures,
there'd be a riot for sure.
I'd give those costumes
the award for best design.
Then you've got those two,
who could be on the cover
of a teen fashion magazine.
[KYON] Put 'em together,
and it's a magnificent sight.
Mikuru's in charge of
collecting the tickets.
She's also the one
clearing the empty plates
and refilling the water.
If I let her serve the noodles,
she'd probably trip and
spill 'em on somebody!
[KYON]
Wow, she really gets it.
In the end,
pressured by the super
fast customer turn-around,
we inhaled the fried
noodles in about five minutes,
and left the place feeling
slightly less than satisfied.
[TANIGUCHI]
Sorry!
[KUNIKIDA]
So, what do you guys wanna do?
I was thinkin' we could check
out the movie you guys made.
I kinda wanna see what I
look like on the big screen.
[TANIGUCHI]
Pass! It's prolly gonna be lame!
[KYON]
I quite agree!
However, hearing that coming
from you really irks me.
Man, those fried
noodles weren't enough.
Oh, yeah! Next up's the barbecue
hosted by the Science Club!
You're still hungry?
Before we hit the barbecue, how
'bout we score us some hotties?
Hotties?
That's right,
Mr. Kunikida, hotties.
We find a coupla
girls dressed casual,
kinda like those two. Then we
make with the chit-chat,
and it's on.
It's a tactic I developed
over years of experience.
[KYON]
What good is your experience
when your success rate is zero?
Thanks, but I'll pass.
You guys are on your own.
I think I'll pass, too.
Good luck, and if you
find a girl to hang out with,
you can introduce me
to one of her friends.
Uh, what? So you guys are
just gonna chicken out?!
[KYON]
I'm not a coward.
It's just that if a
certain someone saw me
hitting on a girl, it could be
a little bit of a problem...
Actually, a big problem.
[KYON] Look, just try to enjoy
the rest of the arts festival.
And do it normally.
[CHILD]
You dumb bear!
[KYON] Now then,
where should I go next?
You did it!
[VENDOR] Don't forget, people,
that we've got a raffle going on
for a brand new scooter today!
[KYON] The wind ensemble's
performing in the lecture hall.
Then the Rock Club's hosting a
concert with a bunch of bands.
I guess I'll head over there.
After pulling that all-nighter,
it's the perfect place to
rest my sleep-deprived body.
[band playing]
[folk singing]
[yawns]
[terrible metal playing]
You rock, North High!
We are Bandage!
Thank you and good night!
[whistling]
[KYON]
Huh?
[ANNOUNCER] Next up, we have
the Rock Club's very own, ENOZ.
[gasps]
[KYON]
Y-You're kidding!
What the hell is she doing?!
[instruments tuning]
[GIRL STUDENT A]
A girl band?
[BOY STUDENT A]
I think bunny girl's hot!
[gasps]
[music plays]
[HARUHI]
♪ Blazing on by ♪
♪ There's nothing
more that I can do ♪
♪ I'm sorry that I'll
never be with you again ♪
♪ Even though my heavy
heart is parched with pain ♪
♪ I know somehow, your sorrow's
something I won't see ♪
♪ It's my life ♪
♪ I'm moving on and
never going back there ♪
♪ But you just turn away and
leave me on the lonely rail ♪
♪ God Knows that I would follow
you if that is what you wanted ♪
♪ Take me into all of
your darkest shadows ♪
♪ and you'll see that I'm even
stronger than you could know ♪
♪ God know that I am standing
here and you could disappear ♪
♪ slipping right over
the edge of the future ♪
♪ If I had my way,
we'd be together forever ♪
♪ Eternally, God bless ♪
♪ The way you're
standing there ♪
♪ I feel as though
we're almost one again ♪
♪ and yet, we're miles
apart in time ♪
♪ Beneath the pale blue moon ♪
♪ I see your eyes are
glistening with so much love ♪
♪ It's tearing you
apart to be here ♪
♪ You know it ♪
♪ God knows that I would follow
you if that is what you wanted ♪
♪ Take me into all your
darkest shadows, ♪
♪ and you'll see that I'm even
stronger than you could know ♪
♪ God knows that I
am standing here ♪
♪ and you could disapear ♪
♪ slipping right over
the edge of the future ♪
♪ If I had my way,
we'd be together forever ♪
♪ Eternally, God bless ♪
[applause]
[HARUHI panting]
[giggles]
[KOIZUMI]
Miss Suzumiya's very good.
So is Miss Nagato.
What's up with that
outfit you're wearing?
I hurried over here
as soon as I heard.
The student council was
buzzing with this rumor
about how Miss Suzumiya was
going to be doing something
in the lecture hall today.
This would be that something.
Uh, hi.
Everyone, this is ENOZ.
The name ENOZ comes from
using the first letter
of the last name of
each of the members:
Enomoto, Nakanishi,
Okajima, and Zaizen.
Unfortunately,
something happened
and Enomoto and Nakanishi
couldn't come up here
to perform for you today.
That's Yuki over there.
Well, she and I
aren't in the band;
we're just filling in. Sorry!
Let me introduce you to the
real members of the band.
On drums, we have Mizuki!
And that's Mai, on bass.
And filling in for Miss
Nakanishi on guitar, Yuki!
And I'm filling in for Miss
Enomoto today
on guitar and vocals.
I don't know if I can
play this thing very well.
In fact, I don't know if I'm
doing so hot singing either.
What I'm saying is that
I got the sheet music
about an hour ago, so I'm
sort of winging it here.
By the way, if there's anyone
out there who wants to hear
the real song performed with
the real vocalist and guitarist,
come see us after
the show, okay?
Oh! And if you wanna
bring a mini disc,
we'll make a copy of the
songs for you for free.
Is that cool?
Mm!
So that's that.
We're gonna do one more.
I didn't have much time, so I
only got two songs down.
This'll be the last one.
Sorry if you were
expecting more,
but we're playin' our
hearts out up here for you.
You ready?
This is "Lost My Music."
♪ When I look up at the sky ♪
♪ I can't help wonder why ♪
♪ we can't be here together ♪
♪ Hey! ♪
♪ And no matter where
you are right now ♪
♪ all I want is to be by your
side ♪
♪ Every time I think of you ♪
♪ I wish I were there, too ♪
♪ instead of feeling lonely ♪
♪ Since you took
me to the cinema ♪
♪ I can't help it ♪
♪ you're always on my mind ♪
♪ 'Cause, oh boy, our love
has gone so far away ♪
♪ and it hurts so much,
I almost lost my music ♪
♪ I can't wait to wake up
from this endless dream ♪
♪ and be together every
day till we say good night ♪
♪ I still, I still, I love you ♪
♪ I'm waiting, waiting forever ♪
♪ and I just can't
make it stop ♪
[KYON]
Later, I got the whole story.
I was passing out flyers for
our movie, but I ran out,
so I headed back to the
club room to get some more.
I was walking by the shoe
lockers, and I saw the band
arguing with the Festival
Operations Committee.
I guess they weren't going
to let them on stage to play.
The lead singer, Miss Enomoto,
had to go to the
hospital the night before
because she got
a case of tonsillitis.
And on the day of the concert,
Miss Nakanishi, the guitarist,
tripped and sprained her wrist.
So, neither of
them could perform.
Miss Nakanishi's a senior,
and this was her last
North High festival.
She wanted to play
even if it killed her.
They were going
to play new songs,
but in the end, Miss Nakanishi
had to be taken away
to get her wrist looked at.
And that's when you decided to
get involved and
help the band out?
I can really understand
how they felt.
Even if my throat was wrecked
and my arm went numb,
I'd be up on that stage
playing on willpower alone.
I don't doubt it.
[HARUHI]
But when I saw Miss Nakanishi,
I figured there wasn't
anything they could do.
I mean, if you saw her,
you'd feel bad for the other
members of the band, right?
They must've practiced
so hard for that show.
So then, this is
what I told them:
"Since you guys are in a jam,
you want me to fill in for her?"
I'm kinda surprised that
the other two girls agreed
to let you do that.
I told them all I'd do is sing,
and both Miss Okajima
and Miss Zaizen said:
"Hey, with you, we
just might pull it off!"
After all, I was in the
Rock Club for a little bit,
and they probably remember
me from back then!
[KYON]
Stories about Haruhi's
eccentricity are
pretty well-known.
But she's also famous for
being a super-utility player.
She can do anything
and everything!
[HARUHI] I wanted to play
all the guitar stuff, too,
but there wasn't
enough time to learn it.
I had to go over
the sheet music.
All I could do was get
the main chords down.
That explains Nagato.
Yeah! I barged in on her
fortune-telling racket,
and when I told her
what was happening,
she decided to join me!
Did you see her play?
I never knew she was dexterous!
She took one look at the music
and then played it perfectly!
I wonder where the heck
that girl learned to
play guitar like that.
[KYON] Probably the
moment you brought it up.
[KUNIKIDA] Hey, it looks
like we have a couple guests.
They wanna see Miss Suzumiya.
[HARUHI gasps]
Well? Go talk to them.
[HARUHI]
Okay, but you're coming, too.
[KYON gasps]
[HARUHI]
Is your throat any better today?
Yeah, that's for asking.
And how's your wrist doing?
It's not 100% yet, so studying
for my exams will be a drag.
I wanted to thank you,
Miss Suzumiya.
[gasps]
You won't believe how
many we requests we got
for the original songs
after the show, it's crazy!
We can't dub our stuff
onto mini discs fast enough!
There's so many
people who want it!
[KYON gasps]
But really, it's all
thanks to you.
Because of what you did for us,
our songs didn't
have to go to waste.
And we really appreciate it.
You're something else,
Miss Suzumiya!
This festival was gonna be my
last memory with the Rock Club,
so I really wanted to play it.
But this was way better than
having us back out of it.
Yeah...
Anyway, we want to do
something for you in return.
No, it's okay, really.
They were great songs,
and I had a blast singing them.
I'd feel bad if
you guys went and
gave me something on
top of that experience.
Actually, why don't
you tell Yuki?
I want her to hear it
'cause I kinda forced her
to come along and play.
[ENOMOTO]
We already went to her class.
She just nodded once,
and then she pointed
us to this classroom.
Oh.
Hey, we're gonna play a gig
somewhere before we graduate,
so if you want, come check
us out, okay?
And you can bring...
your friend here with you, too.
[KYON] And after that, Haruhi
slipped into one of her moods.
Then when lunchtime came around,
she rushed out of the classroom.
I'm serious!
There wasn't a single
decent-looking
girl at the arts festival!
You wanna know what I think?
I think this school's
built on a bad location.
We'd get a better crowd
if it wasn't on this hill.
[KYON]
After lunch, I took a walk.
I figured it would
settle my stomach.
And no, there wasn't
any other reason.
Hey!
Yeah? What is it?
[HARUHI]
I didn't have time to practice,
so we had to make
them sound simpler.
People wanna listen to the
real thing though, don't they?
[KYON] You're talking about all
the people that want mini discs?
[HARUHI]
Yeah.
[KYON]
That was a heck of a performance
for being on the fly, though.
Don't you think it was
good publicity for them?
[HARUHI] If I just had
one more day to practice,
I could've nailed it.
Part of me's asking,
"Was it good enough?
Could it have been better?"
I don't know...
How do I explain it?
When I was up on that stage,
I felt like I was really
doing something.
This sucks. I mean, why can't
I just forget about it already?
[KYON]
How should I know?
But I do.
It's because you're
just not used to
being appreciated by others.
The things you do aren't things
that people usually
thank you for.
[HARUHI]
Hm? What is it now?
If you've got something
to say, just say it.
Spit it out already!
It's probably something
stupid anyway,
but don't just stand there
and keep it bottled up!
It's not good for you!
[KYON]
Seriously... It's nothing.
[HARUHI grunts]
[screams]
[coughs, spits]
[KYON chuckles]
Hey! Do you know how
to play any instruments?
I don't...
It doesn't matter 'cause
we got a whole year to
practice our butts off for
the next arts festival!
[KYON]
Oh, come on...
Our goal is to enter next
year's North High Arts Fest
as a real band!
I'll be the lead singer,
and Yuki can play guitar!
And we'll have Mikuru
shake the tambourine
and be a totally awesome
stage decoration!
[KYON]
Oh...
And of course, we'll have to
make a sequel to our movie, too!
Next year, we'll be super busy.
After all, our goal
each year should be
to increase the number of
goals we set for ourselves.
[KYON]
Hold on!
Come on, Kyon, let's get moving!
Where are we moving?
We're gonna get
some instruments!
[KYON gasps]
First, we'll hit the
Rock Club's room.
I know we'll find
stuff they're not using
just lying around up there.
Then, we'll ask the ENOZ chicks
to teach us to write music!
[KYON]
Huh?
[HARUHI]
Don't sweat it.
I'll write the songs,
compose the music,
and I'll do the choreography!
[KYON] But you don't
have to do it right now!
[HARUHI] Are you nuts?
A year's gonna go by like that!
[KYON] And what do you
mean by choreography?
I thought we were
gonna be a band!
[HARUHI]
We need it!
We're gonna create a new
image of what bands should be!
[KYON] But that's no
different from a pop idol!