[ASAKURA] You want me to
take you to see the nurse?
[KYON]
Hmm...?
[sighs]
Good morning.
I don't think she's
feeling too well.
Take care of her, hm!
[KYON sighs]
[KYON] So why didn't
you come by yesterday?
Thought you wanted to have a
review session or something?
[HARUHI]
Shut up.
I had a review session
by myself, okay?
[KYON]
With a little prodding,
Haruhi told me that
after school yesterday,
she'd gone back and
walked the entire course
we covered on
Saturday by herself.
[HARUHI]
It's hot and I'm tired.
When do we get to
change uniforms?
I wanna change into
my summer uniform now.
Suzumiya, I know I
said this already,
but why don't you just quit
searching for these mysteries
you're never gonna find, okay?
I mean, why don't you
go out and have fun
like a normal high school
student for a change?
What kind of fun does a normal
high school student have?
How 'bout you find a nice guy
and go walking around the city
looking for strange things?
It's a date, so you can kill
two birds with one stone.
[HARUHI]
Huh. What do I care about men?
Romantic emotions are
nothing but a passing phase.
Just a form of mental illness.
Heck, every now then,
even I get into the mood for
dumb stuff like that.
I'm a healthy young woman;
I've got needs.
Sometimes I don't know
what to do with myself.
But I'm not stupid enough to
get stuck with all of that grief
just because of some momentary
urge to get all mushy.
Besides, if I went out and
really started boy hunting,
what's gonna happen
to the SOS Brigade?
I mean, I just
created the thing.
You could just change the
Brigade into some sort of
random club that has fun
and you'll have a
ton of people in it.
No way! I made the SOS Brigade
because that stuff's
totally boring.
I mean, I gotta moe character
and a mysterious
transfer student,
so why hasn't anything
happened yet?!
Oh, why can't a couple of weird
things happen right now?
[ASAKURA] Don't go asking
for trouble like that.
But then again, it might
actually be kinda neat
if something were to come along
and turn our everyday lives
into something more fun.
[sighs]
[KYON] This is a p  never seen Haruhi this down.
Isn't her dejected
little face cute though?
I wonder if Miss Suzumiya's
in love or something?
Impossible.
[KYON] Okay, Suzumiya falling
in love and, or something weird
popping up to make her
happy are two things
that will definitely not
happen any time soon.
Wrong.
Actually, something weird
was quietly lurking
just around the corner.
[KYON] That morning
as I talked to Haruhi,
I was actually thinking
about something else.
[TEACHER] And now, without
an enemy, Umako Sagano
became tremendously arrogant.
[KYON] Didn't something
like this happen before?
Yo.
[KYON] It was pretty obvious
the handwriting wasn't Nagato's.
Besides, she's not really
the type to go around
putting messages in
a guy's shoe locker.
Could it've been Miss Asahina?
Nah, no way. She'd set
a specific time to meet,
and I doubt she'd
scribble it on paper
torn out of a memo pad.
[door opens]
--[HARUHI] Oh, it's so hot!
--[KYON] Haruhi...
[KYON] Impossible. She'd
just grab me by the collar
and drag me over
to the stairwell
just the like last time.
And Koizumi would just say,
"Hey, let's talk."
[HARUHI sighs]
We definitely need
an air conditioner.
[KYON]
Clearly it's not a love letter.
All I know is, it's
requesting my presence
at a specific location.
Wait a sec... maybe
Tanaguchi and Kunikida
are playing some kinda joke.
Yeah, that's it. That's the
most logical possibility.
Although, I'd expect more
if those two were involved.
Wait! What the heck's that?!
What? They're just pictures.
They're totally cute
shots of Mikuru!
[KYON]
Yeah, I see that!
What the hell're you
doing with these?!
I'm loading them onto the
main page of our website!
Now we'll get tons of email
about cool, weird happenings!
Our site'll get tens
of thousands of hits!
The counter will roll
so high, it'll be nuts!
Wonder if the counter
even goes that high...?
Wait!
Ah! What're you doing,
you idiot?!
I'm putting an end to this.
[KYON] If Miss Asahina found
out that the entire planet
could see pictures of her
wearing that maid outfit--
in stunning poses, I might add--
she would pass out on the spot.
Haruhi glared at me as I
feverishly tried to explain
to her why this was
such a bad thing.
In the end, I don't know if she
understood how dangerous
it was to put such personal
stuff on the internet
where any creep could access it.
[HARUHI]
Hmph. Fine, whatever!
[KYON] She reluctantly
agreed to trash them.
Now, this would've been
the time to delete
the photos once and for all,
but it would be a shame
to waste 'em...
[KYON]
There!
That's it. I'm going home.
Huh?
[MIKURU gasps]
Oh, I'm sorry!
Ah...
Uh...
Did something happen?
No, everything's a-okay.
An evil conspiracy's
just been vanquished.
[KYON] Since we had nothing
to do, I was playing Othello
with Miss Asahina when
Koizumi came in
with that smile of his.
Sorry, guys, but I gotta leave
early today to go to work.
[KYON] I wonder what
kind of job he's got?
I'm gonna change,
so don't wait for me.
[KYON] Taking advantage
of Miss Asahina's request,
I bolted from the room.
[KYON] Seeing her standing
there caught me off guard,
to say the least.
Why don't you come in?
It was you...
Yes. Are you surprised?
[KYON]
What d'you want?
I wanted to talk to
you about something.
Actually, it's a question I had.
It's about Miss Suzumiya.
What do you think of her?
[KYON] Oh brother, she's
onto Suzumiya as well.
People always say that
it's much better to regret
something you did rather than
regret something you didn't do.
What do you think about that?
Well, I'm not really sure people
always say that, but I think
it means what it means.
Well, then, let's pretend if you
knew that if you kept things
exactly the same as
they are right now,
you'd be completely broke.
And let's say you that just
didn't know how you could
possibly make things any better.
I wonder what you'd
do about that?
I don't understand.
Are you talking about
the Japanese Economy?
As a start, wouldn't you think
about trying to change
something, anything?
I mean, nothing is going
to change if you
stay the same, right?
Well, yeah, I guess if you're
gonna put it that way.
Then you agree with me!
But you know, my superiors
are extremely stubborn
and lack any vision whatsoever.
But you can't have that kind
of thinking out in the field.
If you just twiddle your thumbs,
things'll go from bad to worse.
And if that's the case, wouldn't
it be okay to force change
to happen when you know
it's all for the best?
[KYON]
What's she talking about?
Is there a hidden
camera in here?
Is Tanaguchi hiding
in the closet,
laughing at me right now?
[ASAKURA] I'm getting bored and
just fed up watching something
that doesn't seem to
be changing at all.
That's why I'm going
to kill you and see how
Miss Suzumiya reacts.
[KYON gasps]
[gasps]
[KYON]
What the hell?!
Is she serious?!
Wait, hang on.
What just happened?
Why is Asakura coming
after me with a knife?
Whoa, wait a minute,
what did she just say?
"I'm gonna kill you"?
Naze... why?
Stop kidding around! You're
gonna hurt someone with that!
Even if that's a rubber knife,
you're scaring
the hell outta me!
You think it's a... joke?
Huh...
You don't wanna die?
You don't want me to kill you?
I'm sorry, but I just don't
understand the concept of death
regarding organic lifeforms.
Okay, this isn't funny anymore!
I don't know why you're
doing this, but please,
just put the knife down!
Heh. I can't.
Because whether you
care about it or not,
I really do want you to die.
[gasps]
[ASAKURA]
It's useless.
Right now, I have the control
over the flow of the data
in this space.
Nothing can enter,
nothing can leave.
[KYON] I have no idea
what's going on here.
If anybody understands,
get the hell over here
and explain it to me!
Oh, please, won't
you just give up?
You're gonna die no matter what,
so let me kill you.
[KYON] Just what the
hell are you anyway?
[yells]
Ah-ah...
I already told you it's useless.
Everything in the classroom
is now under my control.
[KYON]
Wait, wait, wait!
What the hell's going on?!
She's gonna kill me to
see how Haruhi reacts?
Haruhi, Haruhi!
Man, she's popular!
And if that's the case,
then why am I the one
that's gotta die?!
Silly me, I shoulda done
this from the get-go.
[gasps]
[KYON] I can't move!
Wait, that's not fair!
Your death is the
perfect way to make
Haruhi Suzumiya take some
sort of action, you see?
Finally, I'll be able to observe
a huge explosion of data.
It's a once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity!
[KYON]
Tell me about it!
Now you die.
[gasps]
Ow, that hurt!
Wait...
[gasps]
[KYON]
I can move!
Nagato?!
[ASAKURA gasps]
[NAGATO]
There are flaws in your program.
Your data shut down and spatial
blockades are faulty.
It is how I detected you,
why I was allowed inside.
You stopped me?
But if I kill this human,
Haruhi Suzumiya is bound to
do something interesting.
It's the only way for us
to acquire more information.
You are supposed to
be my back-up unit.
You are not permitted
to act on your own.
You'll obey my orders.
[ASAKURA]
What if I said no?
Your data link will
be terminated.
[ASAKURA] Would you like to try?
In here, I have the upper hand.
This classroom is a space
where I control the data.
Commence request for
data link termination.
[gasps]
[ASAKURA giggles]
[KYON]
It was right about this time
that I was thinking to myself...
Oh, man, these girls
really aren't human...
[grunts]
[NAGATO]
Stay behind me.
[KYON grunts]
You cannot defeat me
while we're in this space.
[indecipherable muttering]
...hostile interface, name:
"Ryoko Asakura."
Terminating data links
to organic life form.
I'll stop your functions
before that happens.
[KYON]
Hey--!
[KYON grunts]
How long will you last
if you're protecting him
while you're fighting me?
[indecipherable muttering]
[KYON gasps]
[KYON]
Nagato!
You need to stay right
where you are.
I'm fine.
[KYON] Uh, no... you
don't look fine at all.
[ASAKURA] With that
much damage, I'm afraid
you won't be able to interfere
with any other data.
Well, I'll finish it.
Now you die.
[gasps]
It's over.
What's over?
Do you mean your life for
the last three years?
[NAGATO] No. Commence
termination of data link.
It can't be!
[NAGATO] You are an advanced
interface. That is why it took
so long to hack into
this time-space program.
But it's over now.
You modified your program with a
detonation element, didn't you?
I thought you seemed weak,
but that explains it.
That's the reason you used
all your attack data when
you started to fight.
Oh, this is a shame.
I guess I really was just
a back-up interface.
I thought this was my big
chance to get something
to finally happen around here.
[KYON gasps]
I guess I lost. Aren't you
happy you get to keep living?
But please be careful though.
The data integration thought
entity has more interfaces
that are just like me.
Someday, you might meet
another interface that also
seeks radical change.
Or perhaps the one pulling
Nagato's strings
will change his mind?
Till then, enjoy your life
with Miss Suzumiya. Goodbye.
[giggles]
[KYON]
Hey, Nagato!
Hang on! I'll get some help.
No. My physical injuries
are not critical.
This space needs to be corrected
before I do anything else.
The corrupt data must be removed
and the classroom rebuilt.
Are you sure you're really okay?
All processing power is
engaged with manipulating
and overwriting data.
This interface will be
repaired shortly after.
Repair in progress.
[NAGATO gasps]
What's wrong?
I forgot to recreate
the glasses.
[KYON] Actually, I think you
look cuter without those things.
I don't really have a
glasses fetish anyway.
[NAGATO]
What is a glasses fetish?
It's nothing! Never mind,
just forget it.
I see...
What is up?
♪ I for-for-forgot my bag. ♪
[screams]
[KYON] Mom, Dad, if you
saw how Nagato and me
are positioned in the frame,
I know you'd think
we were getting it on right now.
Okay... Take your time!
[NAGATO]
Interesting human.
[KYON chuckles]
Oh man, what're we gonna do?
[NAGATO] Leave it to me.
I'm adept at controlling data.
I'll make it so Asakura
suddenly transfers.
[KYON]
No, not that!
Okay, I need to calm down now.
As for the last 10 minutes,
I think it's safe to say
I experienced something
extraordinary.
This isn't a problem
about whether or not
I believe that crazy story
Nagato told me the other day
or any of her other delusions.
No, what happened
just now made me realize
what real danger feels like.
I was five seconds
away from dying.
There's no longer any
doubt in my mind that
Nagato is an alien, or is
at least involved with
aliens in some fashion.
[KYON]
The next day, Ryoko Asakura was
mysteriously absent from class.
[TEACHER] ...almost overnight
it seems. She transferred out.
[STUDENT]
Where did she transfer?!
--[STUDENTS gasping]
--Huh?!
Kyon! Hear that?! A mystery!
[KYON] Filled with boundless
energy, Haruhi had that glimmer
in her eye again.
What should I do?
Should I tell her the truth?
[KYON] No way. Actually,
I don't wanna tell her.
I keep hoping that everything
I saw was just a hallucination.
This is too good to be true!
First, a mysterious
student transfers in,
now, a girl mysteriously
transfers out!
We are so investigating this!
[KYON] Right now, I can't
deal with the extra work.
I have another matter;
a pending inquiry, if you will,
that I'm mulling over.
What's with you?
It's nothing.
[KYON] Today's communique
was conveniently housed
within an envelope.
I found it in my shoe locker
just like the note yesterday.
I mean, seriously, is putting
notes in people's shoe locker
some new trend? Well,
thing is, this time around,
it's different.
[crash]
[KYON] I have to be careful.
I don't wanna waltz in there
just to face another life
or death situation.
It doesn't matter, though,
'cause I'm going anyway.
I mean, Miss Asahina wanted
to see me in private.
Now, I don't have any
proof that Miss Asahina
actually sent this letter,
but I know in my gut
that she did, okay?
She's definitely the type
that would send little notes
to people, and the image I'm
seeing of her scribbling away
on super-cute stationary
fits her personality to a T.
Besides, it's the clubroom.
Nagato's gonna be there.
Well, here goes nothing.
[knocks]
[MIKURU]
Ah, come in!
Hi, Kyon.
It's been ages.
[KYON] She sure looks
like Miss Asahina,
but she definitely
is not Miss Asahina.
Um, are you Miss
Asahina's big sister?
[gasps, giggles]
But it's me, Kyon.
I'm Mikuru Asahina.
I'm the me from a future
that's a little further down
form the me you know right now.
I wanted to see you.
Hey! You don't trust me?!
Okay, this'll prove it.
See, I've got it a tiny
star-shaped mole right here.
It's not a fake mole, either.
Wanna touch it?
[KYON]
Super-size me!
[ASAKURA]
You believe me now?
[KYON] Whether I believe her
or not, I don't recall where
Miss Asahina keeps her moles.
The only time I was able to
see that much of her body
was when she was cosplaying
as a bunny girl.
And that other time when I
peeked in as she changed--
which wasn't my fault!
I never saw any moles because
I never made it a point
to go looking for them.
Oh? Well, I remember
that you were the one
who told me that I
had a mole here.
I didn't even know I had
one there until you--
[gasps]
I... just... Oh no!
This is before we--
Oh, what have I done?!
I totally screwed up just now.
I'm sorry, Kyon, just forget
everything I said, okay?
[KYON]
Easy for you to say.
It's all right, really.
I believe you, I do.
The truth is, with everything
that's going on,
I'm in the right frame of
mind to believe just about
anything today. Wait,
if you're standing here,
that means there's
two Miss Asahinas
in the same time plane, right?
Ah. Right.
The past, I mean, the me from
the past, the younger me,
right now, she's eating
lunch in my old classroom
with all her classmates.
There's something important
I had to tell you,
so I pulled some strings and
they finally let me come back
to this time plane again.
If you're wondering,
I asked Miss Nagato
to step out for a bit.
[KYON] Wait, Miss Asahina,
you know about Nagato?
[MIKURU]
Sorry, that's classified.
Wow, it's been forever
since I last said that.
[KYON] Funny, I heard you
say it a coupla days ago.
Ah...
I won't be able to stay
here much longer, so listen,
cause this is important.
Do you know the story
of Snow White?
[KYON]
Uh, yeah, sure I do.
[MIKURU] From now on, if you
ever find yourself in danger,
I want you to remember
those words.
Can you do that?
[KYON] Okay, the seven
dwarves, the wicked witch,
the poison apple,
and all that stuff?
[MIKURU] That's right.
The story about Snow White.
[KYON] Well, if you're talking
about serious danger,
I just had some
of that yesterday.
[MIKURU] That's not the one
I'm talking about. It's worse.
Let's see... I can't
give you any details,
but when the time comes, Miss
Suzumiya should be at your side.
[KYON]
Huh? You mean me and Haruhi?
What's gonna happen?
When it does happen, Miss
Suzumiya probably won't consider
the event to be all that
dangerous. But it will be.
And not just for you and
her, but for all of us,
so just keep that in mind.
Oh, come on, can't you
give me any more details?
Is that classified, too?
[MIKURU] I am sorry, but I
thought that if I at least
gave you a hint...
This is the best I can do...
So that's why you're telling
me about Snow White?
[MIKURU]
Yeah...
Okay, I'll try to remember.
[MIKURU sighs]
[giggles]
[MIKURU] I'm amazed I could
wear something like this.
It's out of the question now.
Well then, can you tell me
what other kinds of outfits
Haruhi made you wear?
That's a secret.
It's just too embarrassing.
Besides, you'll find
out soon enough.
Well, I better go...
[KYON gasps]
[MIKURU] Something else
I need to tell you...
Don't get too friendly
with me, okay...?
[gasps] Wait, I just
wanna know something!
Miss Asahina, how old
are you right now?
That's classified.
[KYON] That was a smile
that would make anyone
who saw it fall in love.
It's been ages.
[KYON] In other words, the high
school version of Miss Asahina
is gonna return to her
time in the future.
I wonder when that's
gonna happen...?
And how many years between
the one that's in school
with me and the one I just met?
From the way she looked just
now, it could be three or
even five years. Women change so
drastically when they graduate
from high school.
Better get back
to the classroom.
Man, I'm really hungry.
Hey, you didn't happen to pass
someone in the hall just now
that looked a lot like
Miss Asahina, did you?
[NAGATO] The Mikuru Asahina
from another time plane,
I met her this morning.
I never asked you before, but
can you time travel like her?
Can that data thing
time travel, too?
I am unable to.
However, time travel is not
that difficult to accomplish.
I'd like some tips
on how to do it.
[NAGATO] Language cannot
explain the concept,
nor are you able
to understand it.
Is that so?
[NAGATO]
It is so.
Then I guess it's my loss.
[NAGATO]
Your loss.
Nagato, thanks again
for yesterday.
Don't thank me. Asakura's
abnormal behavior
was my responsibility. I failed.
I really think you look
better without glasses.
[HARUHI]
Where were you?!
I'd thought you'd be back!
I was waiting, and
didn't even eat lunch!
[KYON] Could you say that again,
but like you're an old friend
who's embarrassed and
only acting angry?
[HARUHI] Stop being an idiot
and come with me right now!
I went to the teacher's
lounge and asked Okabe.
Get this: no one
knew that Asakura
was transferring
until this morning.
Apparently, someone claiming
to be her father called in
and said they were moving away!
Just like that!
You wanna know where
they're moving to? Canada!
Can you believe that?!
Something's fishy here.
[KYON]
Ya think?
[HARUHI] There's more!
I asked for their contact info
in Canada. You know
what they told me?
"Sorry, we don't have
that information."
At the very least, you tell
someone your new address!
I'm sure something
funny's going on!
[KYON]
No, there isn't.
[HARUHI]
I kept up my interrogations
until I got Asakura's
old address.
After school, I'm going
straight over there.
I'll crack this thing wide open!
[KYON] Still the same.
She never listens to anything.
And I won't stop her.
Hey, Haruhi's the one
who's wasting her time
with this, not me.
[HARUHI]
And you're coming, too.
Why me?!
[KYON grunts]
Ow!
And you call yourself a member
of the SOS Brigade?!