[KYON] It was summer.
But with finals looming,
my usually chipper mood
was out wandering around
Brazil somewhere, and
it wasn't coming back
any time soon.
Hey, Kyon, do you
know what today is?
Is it your birthday?
Guess again.
[KYON]
Miss Asahina's birthday.
Wrong!
[KYON]
Koizumi or Nagato's birthday?
I don't even know
when those are!
[KYON] Since we're on the
subject, my birthday's on--
Yeah, whatever!
You have absolutely no
idea what an important day
today is, do you?
[KYON] It's just another
hot weekday to me,
if you wanna know the truth.
[HARUHI] Okay, tell me
what today's date is.
It's the seventh of July...
Now I get it, you've been
talking about Tanabata
this whole time, haven't you?
That's what I'm talking about!
Today's Tanabata!
Come on, you're Japanese!
You have to remember
this kinda stuff.
My bad.
Every year, I make it
a point to get involved
with activities like
this. But this year,
the SOS Brigade'll make it
the biggest event ever!
[KYON]
Here we go...
[school bell chimes]
[KYON] Since the spring,
whenever Haruhi sank her teeth
into something, I'd find myself
aimlessly running around.
You could say it'd
become my daily routine.
I was getting used to it.
And I hated that.
[knocking]
[MIKURU]
Come in.
Hey, guys.
Oh, hello!
Hello!
How's your day so far?
Little crazy, just like every
day since I started high school.
[MIKURU]
Here.
Thanks, I needed that.
Why, you're very welcome.
[KOIZUMI]
Wanna try something new?
[KYON, MIKURU]
Hm?
You know, at some point, we're
gonna get bored playing Othello.
[KYON] Yeah, sorry, but I
don't know the rules.
[KOIZUMI]
Oh, that's too bad.
You-know-who's come up with
another harebrained scheme.
This is probably our
last chance to relax.
[door clicks]
Uh--
Hey-ho!
I know, I know,
I'm sorry I'm so late!
What's with the weird
greeting and that thing?
I found it in the forest!
Then it's considered private
property, you bamboo thief.
Look, I also made tanzaku,
so everyone has to
write their wishes on 'em.
Tanzaku?
That's right, today is
Tanabata, isn't it?
But first, there are conditions!
What conditions? I don't recall
anyone agreeing to anything yet.
Hey, Kyon, I bet you don't know
who makes everybody's wishes
come true during Tanabata.
Orihime and Hikoboshi?
Lucky guess. That's ten points.
But do you know which stars
represent Orihime and Hikoboshi?
I don't.
It's Vega and Altair.
Correct, sir! That's why you
hang your tanzaku to face them!
Eighty-five points!
Mind telling us where
the other 15 points went?
A-hem!
First of all, according to
the theory of relativity,
it's not possible to travel
faster than the speed of light.
The distance from the Earth
to Vega is 25 lightyears,
and to Altair it's 16.
That means, any information
that leaves Earth
is going to take at least that
much time to reach those stars!
I can't believe you actually
researched this stuff.
That's why, when you make a
wish, it takes such a long time
for the gods to
make it come true.
For example, if you wanna have
a boyfriend by this Christmas,
he won't show up
for you in time.
If it takes that long
for a wish to go one way,
wouldn't it take 50 or 32
years to make it back?
Yeah, but they're gods,
so I'm sure they have a way
to get around it. Like a
half-price summer bargain.
[KYON] So what happened to
the theory of relativity?
[HARUHI] There's a tanzaku
for Vega and one for Altair.
So the trick is to make wishes
you'd want to come true
25 or 16 years from now!
[KYON] How can we know
what we'll be doing
25 or even 16 years from now?
What the heck are we
supposed to wish for?
She's always coming up with
these irrational activities
for us to do. I keep wondering:
which part of the universe
does she get her idea
of "normal" from?
Don't be so quick to judge.
Despite her actions,
Miss Suzumiya has a firm
grasp of what normal is.
How can you be
so sure about that?
Well, for one thing, she wants
the world to be a bit more
exciting and unusual,
and she has the power
to reshape the world
according to her whims.
Also, the world hasn't lost
its rationality yet, has it?
That's how I can be so sure.
Hey, cut out the whispering!
[KYON growls]
[KYON] I dunno if she's
got the hang of this thing.
I'm afraid mine are
a little ordinary.
Yeah, that's pathetic.
Shut it.
That settles it, mine
are better than yours.
It's apples and oranges.
Make sure you guys remember
the wishes you made today.
It's only 16 years till
the first batch comes true.
And then we're gonna see who's
wish Hikoboshi grants first!
[sighs]
[HARUHI] Sixteen years is
a long time, though...
[KYON]
Hm?
[KYON] After that,
Haruhi was strangely quiet,
and dare I say,
a bit melancholy.
In a way, the fact
she was so calm
was a little... unnerving.
And the quieter she was,
the more worried I became.
Would you like me to
pour you another cup?
Ah. Oh, sure, I'd love one.
Huh?
Shh.
[KYON]
So cute.
Now.
[KYON]
You know I will!
I'm going home...
The last one out
should lock the door.
[KOIZUMI]
I'll be going, too.
[KYON]
Lucky me, lucky me.
Uh. Hey...
[KOIZUMI]
Well, see ya later.
Okay.
[door clicks]
Thank goodness, I thought
they'd never leave us alone.
[KYON] Why? Is it something you
don't want the others to hear?
Um, yes...
There's a... a place I
sort of wanna take you to.
[KYON]
Sure, where do you wanna go?
Well, uh...
It's three years ago...
[KYON]
Three--
I'm sorry! I know it sounds
really strange, but...
Well, will you go?
So, we'd be time
travelling, then?
Yes, that's right.
I don't have a problem
going with you or anything,
but why me?
What for?
I can't say now,
but when we get there...
Maybe...
[KYON groans]
[MIKURU] Please don't
ask me anything else!
Just say you'll go with me!
Because if you
don't go, then I'll...
[squeaks]
...get in trouble...
[KYON]
So cute.
Well, uh... Okay, sure, I'll go.
Really?!
Thank you!
[KYON]
So cute...
[sighs]
Thank goodness.
[KYON] Come to think of it,
my knowledge of Miss Asahina's
time travelling was based
solely upon her word.
And the only proof
I had was that
I'd met the adult
version of her.
This was my chance to confirm
whether she was a girl
from the future... or not.
Okay, show me the way
to your time machine.
[MIKURU]
We'll leave from here.
From here?
[MIKURU]
Kyon? Sorry.
Uh?
[KYON groans softly]
[MIKURU]
Oh, you're awake!
Ah... I was sort of
you'd be waking up soon,
because my legs
are getting numb.
[gasps]
Uh, why was I
sleeping in your lap?
Sorry about that.
But I can't let you see how
time travel happens
because it's classified.
So, uh, are you mad?
No, not at all. I mean, if
Haruhi tried to do that to me,
I'd probably smack her, but
since it's you, it's no biggie.
Thank goodness.
Are you sure that right now
is really three years ago?
July the seventh
three years ago.
It's about 9 pm.
You sure about that?
Really sure.
Yeah...
Hm.
[KYON]
I know this park...
It's where Nagato told me
to meet her that one time.
Is this a mecca for
weirdos or something?
Miss Asahina?
Um...
[KYON] Okay, calm down.
Should I...? Should I not...?
Hello, Kyon. It's me.
[KYON]
Miss Asahina!
So this was how I looked
all asleep and everything.
[giggles]
All she had to do was get you
to come to this point in time.
It's going to be my job now to
guide you along from here on.
Okay, but you put her
to sleep. How come?
When I was here, I didn't
meet the adult version of me.
That's why I couldn't
let her see me here.
In this time plane, anyway.
Huh.
If you just follow the railroad
tracks, you'll come to a school.
You're going to have to help the
person you find at the gates.
And, you'll also have to
carry that version of me
along with you.
This feels like going
on a quest in a game.
After I'm done, do I get
something, like a reward?
A reward, huh?
Let's see...
I'm actually not supposed
to give you anything.
Although, if you really want to,
you can give that
version of me a kiss.
But only while
she's sleeping, okay?
That's, uh... A little...
[KYON]
Under the circumstances,
this goes completely
against my principles
Yeah, well, sort of.
That's it. It's time
for me to go now.
You're going to have to keep me
a secret from her, too, okay?
Promise me.
Let's pinky swear.
Uh...
[MIKURU]
Now it's official.
I'll see you later then, Kyon.
Bye-bye.
[KYON] I wonder how
much time had passed
for the adult Miss Asahina
since the last time I saw her.
I couldn't really tell if she'd
changed that much, if at all.
So now I'm starting to wonder,
is this really three years ago?
I need to confirm this somehow.
Maybe I should call
information or something.
East Junior High...
Uh... Hm.
[KYON]
Hey.
What? Who're you?
[KYON] Okay, now I'm sure
I've gone back three years.
That's Haruhi Suzumiya,
the seventh grade version.
Are you gonna tell me
who you are or what?
Pervert? Kidnapper?
What do you think
you're doing over there?
[HARUHI] Isn't it obvious?
Breaking and entering.
[KYON] She's committing a
crime, and announcing it.
How am I supposed to react?
I don't know who you are,
and I really don't care,
just gimme a hand.
'Cause if you don't,
I'll call the cops.
[KYON]
Yup, that's Haruhi, no mistake.
This way.
[KYON] Good thing it's dark out.
She won't be able to get
a good look at me
or Miss Asahina.
Since this Haruhi
from three years ago
doesn't remember us, I sort of
feel I need to keep it that way.
I got this from the storage room
after school and hid it.
Pretty smart, huh?
I can handle that thing.
You go grab the line marker.
Huh?
Hm.
[KYON]
Hm?
Well, whatcha gonna
do with this thing?
[HARUHI] You're gonna draw
lines where I tell you.
Who, me?
Yeah, that's right, you.
I am the supervisor
of this project.
[KYON sighs]
[HARUHI] Hey, that line's all
crooked! What're you doing?!
[KYON] Ordering around a
high schooler she just met
without any hesitation
is so very Haruhi.
Now, if I had met this girl
back when I was going to
junior high, I guarantee
I would've thought she
was 100% nuts. No joke.
So, I ran around and drew
white lines on the ground
wherever Haruhi
told me to draw them.
I remember Taniguchi telling me
about a mysterious message.
Never dreamed I'd be
the one who drew it.
[HARUHI]
Yeah, I guess it'll do.
[KYON]
Whatever.
So do you think aliens
are real, or not?
That's sorta random.
Just answer the question.
I guess they are.
And time travelers?
I wouldn't doubt those, either.
How about ESPers?
I'm sure they're lurking
around every corner.
What about Sliders?
I haven't met any
of those guys yet.
[HARUHI]
Hm...
Is that a North High uniform?
[KYON]
Uh-huh.
[HARUHI]
What's your name anyway?
It's John Smith.
[growls] You're such a dork.
[KYON] Let's just say
I wanna remain anonymous.
[HARUHI] Who's the girl
you were carrying?
[KYON]
She's my big sister
and she has these
sudden fits of narcolepsy.
She just falls asleep wherever,
so I have to carry
her sometimes.
[HARUHI]
Hmph!
[KYON] Anyway, what's that
thing supposed to be?
[HARUHI] What do ya think
it looks like? It's a message.
[KYON] A message for Orihime
or Hikoboshi, right?
Okay, how'd you know that?
Well, it is Tanabata. And I
remembered someone I know
doing something similar once.
Oh, yeah? I'd love to
meet someone like that.
Does that person go
to North High, too?
Sort of.
[HARUHI]
Hm... North High...
I'm done. I'm goin' home now.
See ya!
[KYON] She didn't even thank me
for helping her. Typical.
[KYON]
Miss Asahina?
Yes... class...
[gasps]
Wh-Wh-Wh-Where am I?!
What happened,
and when is it right now?!
--Well, uh--
--[screams]
I don't have my TPDD anymore!
Huh?
I don't have it!
[wails]
What's wrong?
What's a TPDD, anyway?
[MIKURU]
It's classified, but,
it's sort of like a
time machine... [sobs]
Where do you think
it could've gone?
[MIKURU] I don't know! I should
have it, but I-I lost it!
Is there anybody who
could come pick us up?
[MIKURU]
There isn't!
Okay, so what's gonna
happen to us then?
We're stuck. We're stuck
in this time plane
three years in the past
with no way of getting home,
and we can't get
back to our time!
That sounds pretty serious.
Super serious... [wails]
[KYON]
For some reason,
I wasn't too concerned
about our situation.
That TPDD thing was probably
taken by the adult Miss Asahina.
In fact, that's probably
why she was here.
To make sure this version of her
actually lost the
TPDD thingamajig--
[gasps]
Everything's gonna be okay.
Huh...?
[ringing]
Does a Miss Yuki
Nagato live here?
Uh... I'm not really
sure how to say
what I'm about
to say, but...
What if I told you that I'm an
acquaintance of Haruhi Suzumiya?
[doorbell rings]
Howdy.
Is it okay if we come in?
[KYON]
That's pretty much it.
Now you know who we are
and why we're here.
Oh, and the you from three years
in the future gave me this.
Understood.
As for as everything goes, this
is the first time you've met
the two of us, right?
Yes, I have accessed the memory
of the unit in the
other time plane,
and I have downloaded the
data from the opposite side
of the linked-time boundary.
The unit that exists
three years from now and I
are the same being.
As such, we have access
to each other's memories.
Our memories are shared.
Really? How?
We synched.
Wait, I don't understand.
[gasps]
Why are you wearing
a North High uniform?
Have you enrolled already?
[NAGATO] Not yet. I am
currently in standby mode.
[KYON]
What?
So you're gonna be in standby
mode for three years?
[NAGATO]
Yes.
That's a really long time
to be in standby mode.
It is my role.
There is more than one way
to travel through time.
The TPDD is not the only
device that can do it.
It is imperfect.
But, um... How is it imperfect?
When an organic lifeform
uses the TPDD,
the movement created by
the event causes noise.
We believe it is
imperfect and primitive.
By "we", you mean that
thought entity-thing.
So, Miss Nagato, when you
travel through time,
you can do it perfectly?
Perfection does not matter.
As long as data can
travel unobstructed.
[gasps]
D-Do you want us
to sleep in here?
Us? Together?
Yes.
Me and Miss Asahina...
[NAGATO]
Yes.
Lie down.
Just like that?!
Just sleep.
[KYON] I wouldn't have it
any other way, however...
I guess we don't have
any other choice, do we?
Nuh-uh...
[MIKURU squeaks]
[gasps]
Huh?
[KYON]
Huh...?
[MIKURU gasps]
No way!
[KYON] Are you okay?
What's that? The TPDD?
No, it's not. It's just
my radio wave watch.
We're back in our
time, thank goodness.
It's just after 9:30, July
the seventh, the day we left.
[sighs]
How did you do it?
I suspended the flow of data
inside this time-space.
Then I released it at
a pre-determined point
in the time-space continuum.
You mean you actually
stopped time?!
[KYON]
Huh?
Miss Nagato's saying
she stopped time
in this room for
the past 3 years.
And when today came around,
she started time up again.
That right?
[NAGATO]
Yes.
I can't believe it.
If that's true,
then that means...
On the night when I came over,
and you told me
you were an alien
and stuff, Miss Asahina and
I were asleep in this room
together the whole time?!
[NAGATO]
Yes.
[gasps]
I was always impressed at
how amazing you could be,
but I didn't know
you are omnipotent.
I am not. This was a
special case. Emergency mode.
Seldom activated
unless necessary.
[KYON]
Thank you.
You're welcome.
[KYON]
Hm?
Before we go, could you
tell me what this says?
"I am right here,"
is what is says.
Hold on a second, are you
telling me that this thing
is written in a language
used by aliens or something?
[KYON]
Nagato didn't answer me.
[MIKURU]
I'm sorry, it's just that...
I-I don't really know too much.
I'm just an assistant.
No, an intern.
Wait, no, I mean I'm
kind of like a trainee.
But even so, you get to
stay pretty close to Haruhi.
That's because
Miss Suzumiya caught me.
I never expected something
like that to happen.
[MIKURU] I'm just following the
orders given by my superiors.
Or, what's another term?
The people in charge?
I just follow orders, that's why
sometimes I don't understand
the things I'm supposed to do.
[KYON] I wonder if the
grown up Miss Asahina
is one of her superiors.
If that's the case, then the
adult Miss Asahina knows
how things'll turn out for us.
But for some reason, she
didn't tell this Miss Asahina
anything about it.
Oh well, I guess people from
the future have their own way
of doing things.
Maybe when stuff starts
falling into place,
someone will explain
everything to her.
[KYON] Of course, the next
day was July the 8th.
And even though I knew
it was the next day.
In reality, it had been
three years and one day
since I'd been back to school.
[KYON]
Hm?
What's wrong? You eat a
poisonous mushroom or something?
[HARUHI] No, just thinkin'
about some stuff.
I remembered something about
Tanabata from a while ago.
Really?
[KYON]
Hey, Nagato,
Miss Asahina's really
from the future, right?
Yes.
Yeah, well, something about
the process of time travel
and how the past and
future are linked
seems a little off to me.
What d'you mean?
[KYON] Miss Asahina told me once
that there's no connection
between the past and the future.
So, I go back three years,
bump into Haruhi,
and tell her some stuff that
I didn't think was important.
But there's a chance
that what I told her
is the reason she decided
on coming to North High
and why she began
looking for people...
...who weren't normal.
So there has to be a link
between the past and
the future, right?
Even though it contradicts
what Miss Asahina said.
A theory that is contradictory
in itself cannot begin
to explain the contradictions
inherent within it.
If that was supposed to be an
explanation, I didn't understand
a word of it.
One day, you will.
[KOIZUMI]
This is what she means.
Using our game as an example,
notice that my King is in check
by your Rook.
"This is terrible!
Oh, I think I'll run away."
See that? Can you tell me
what was contradictory
about what I just did?
Of course, as far as our
little group is concerned,
the King isn't so important.
To everyone here, the only
thing that really matters
is the Queen.
Yeah, whatever. I don't
know what's gonna happen
to us next, but whatever it is,
I want it to be something
that doesn't require
as much thinking.
[KOIZUMI] I'd love it if
things stayed nice and quiet.
But you would prefer it
if something happened?
[growls]
[KYON]
Jerk.