[KYON] Something's wrong...
That's what it felt like anyway.
[KYON] I didn't care about
the baseball game on TV,
but I ended up
watching it anyway.
And right about then,
I suddenly got the feeling
Haruhi was gonna call.
Hm?
[COMMENTATOR]
The bleachers behind third
are going nuts out there.
[phone rings, buzzes]
Hey Kyon, your cell
phone's ringing.
Yeah I know; you don't
have to tell me.
[HARUHI] Hey, Kyon!
You're free today, right?
[KYON grunts]
[HARUHI] Good. Meet us at 2:00
in front of the station.
And don't be late!
[dial tone]
[KYON] I didn't even have
a chance to say anything.
--[phone rings]
--[KYON gasps]
[sighs]
Now what?
[HARUHI]
I forgot to tell you something.
Make sure and bring your swim
trunks and some money, too.
Oh, and don't forget to bring--
Don't forget to
bring my bike, I know.
[HARUHI]
Uh... Right! Yeah, bring it.
And if you're late,
you're buying lunch!
[dial tone]
[KYON]
Huh?
How did I know about
the bike just now?
--[metal clink]
--[KYON gasps]
[COMMENTATOR] What a shot!
It's a big, fat hit!
[KYON'S SISTER] Look! I think
that one's gonna make it over!
[KYON'S SISTER]
I knew it!
[KYON] I wonder where
I put my swim trunks.
Summer's almost over.
[HARUHI]
You're late, Kyon!
[KYON]
Yeah, yeah.
I'm sorry if I kept
you guys waiting.
No worries. I just
got here, too.
You have absolutely no
motivation whatsoever.
Now that we're all present
and accounted for, we can go!
Where are we going today?
To the public swimming pool!
Where do you think?
[KYON] That figures...
considering the stuff I brought.
But, we've only got
so much time because
once it's gone,
it's gone for good!
So we're going to
do everything we can
during our only summer
as tenth graders.
Hey, Kyon? Are you listening?
Uh... Yeah.
For starters, we're gonna ride
the bikes over to the pool!
Okay. Did everyone
ride their bikes today?
Well, actually...
The only bikes we have are
the ones you and I brought.
Huh?
[KYON]
In other words, you mean...
You gotta be kidding!
All right, Kyon, you can't
let Koizumi beat you!
Come on! Full speed ahead!
[KYON]
You demon! You fiend!
[KYON panting]
What are you doing?
We're trying to have fun,
so stop acting tired!
[KYON]
And whose fault is that?!
[HARUHI]
Wow! Look at all the people!
And can you smell the chlorine?
That really makes
it feel like summer!
Come on, guys, it's perfect!
Let's find a place to dump
our stuff and go swimming!
[KYON]
Okay.
[HARUHI laughs]
Hey! Wait a se...cond...
Can't she see the "no diving"
signs? They're everywhere.
[HARUHI laughs]
Come on! The water's
warm! It's perfect!
Mikuru! Yuki!
Don't just stand there!
Guess you better go have fun.
We're never gonna hear
the end of it, if you don't.
Oh! Okay!
Miss Suzumiya!
Wait up, we're coming!
[HARUHI]
Slow poke!
In... you... go!
[MIKURU screams]
[laughs] It's such a
peaceful scene, isn't it?
What?
I was talkin' about
Miss Suzumiya.
She's enjoying herself
in a normal way.
It's rather charming,
don't you think?
She called me and
told me what to bring.
And then, she ordered
me to meet her
without telling me
what was going on.
--That's not charming or normal.
--[KOIZUMI chuckles]
[KOIZUMI] If you ask me,
none of what you mentioned
is anything to make a fuss over.
As long as Miss Suzumiya's
having a good time,
we don't have to worry about
any earth-shattering events.
[KYON]
I hope you're right.
[KOIZUMI]
Hmm?
[KYON]
Hm? Something wrong?
Nothing...
I guess it's just
my imagination.
With everything that's
happened since we met,
you could say I've
become slightly paranoid.
[KYON]
Him too? Weird.
[HARUHI, CHILDREN laughing]
[KYON] Now I know why they call
it a "public" swimming pool.
Seems like everyone
in town's here today.
Hm?
She's been over
there this whole time?
Why's she sitting
over there by herself?
What the...?
That's so weird!
It's like... I've seen
this happen before.
Nagato... all alone...
[HARUHI]
Kyon!
[KYON gasps]
[KYON]
Haruhi...
Yeah... That's right...
She shows up and says...
"These two guys are my brigade
members. They do what I say.
So if you want something..."
[HARUHI]
...you can ask them!
[KYON gasps]
It's time for some water soccer.
I need everyone in the pool!
Yuki!
[KYON] Have I become like
a psychic or something?
[HARUHI]
Heads up, Kyon!
[KYON]
Ugh!
...or not.
[KYON] Oh, well. I guess
déjà vu's happen sometimes.
That's all it was.
I've been thinking of
some fun things to do!
What's that for?
I came up with this schedule of
how we're gonna spend the
rest of our summer vacation!
We've only got two weeks...
[KYON]
Two weeks to do all that?!
[HARUHI] Is there anything
you wanna do, Mikuru?
[MIKURU]
Um... Maybe goldfish scooping?
[HARUHI]
Okay! Goldfish scooping, it is.
[writing]
Um... Could I see
that for a moment?
Hm.
[chuckles]
[KOIZUMI]
Thank you.
[HARUHI]
We'll start the list tomorrow!
Does anyone know if there's a
bon festival happening close by?
Or a firework show?
[KOIZUMI]
I can check around for them.
I'll give you a call
if I find anything.
[HARUHI] Don't forget
about the goldfish scooping.
After all, it's Mikuru's
only request.
[KYON]
I got stuck with the bill again.
[HARUHI] Yeah, well, that's
what happens when you're late!
That's it for today, guys!
Okay? I'll see you tomorrow!
Well, I'm off, too.
I'll see you later!
Okay!
[KYON gasps]
[KYON]
Nagato!
I... I was... It's nothing
important or anything...
[KYON]
So, uh... How have you been?
Is everything going
okay with you?
[NAGATO]
It is.
[KYON] Okay, then.
I guess that's a good thing.
[NAGATO]
Yes.
[gasps]
Ah! Well, uh, that's all
I was wondering.
So yeah, I'm, uh...
sorry to keep you.
[KYON]
What the heck?
What was that?
Why'd I talk to her?
[KYON] The next morning,
I got another call from Haruhi.
They found a bon festival.
It was happening
at a park tonight.
[footsteps]
[HARUHI]
Sorry, guys!
[KYON]
Well, it's about time--
[KYON stutters]
[KOIZUMI] The three of
you look wonderful in those!
Well, of course we do!
I picked 'em out myself, y'know.
Especially Mikuru's!
You're so cute! I'm a genius!
[KYON]
Oh, Miss Asahina! Yes! Yes!
[chattering]
[MIKURU]
Oh!
There's a lot goin on here,
but I wonder where all the
things we wanna do are.
[KYON]
What the...?!
It feels like I was just here!
That tower... Those vendors...
I remember them.
[HARUHI]
Look! Mikuru!
[gasps]
[HARUHI] See? They have goldfish
scooping, just like you wanted!
We're gonna catch a whole bunch!
[MIKURU whimpering] Miss
Suzumiya, don't pull so hard!
Do you wanna go
scoop some fish, too?
Nah, I think I'll pass.
So how 'bout you, Nagato?
You wanna go grab
some food or somethin'?
Huh?
[KYON]
Hm?
Are you actually
into that stuff?
Okay! I got it!
No.
But--
That one.
[VENDOR]
It's yours for 800 yen!
[KYON] I wish she would've
let me buy that for her...
It's the least I could do
after all she's done for us.
[HARUHI]
I caught thirteen!
But, I don't have enough
room for all of 'em.
That's way too many fish.
So I kept one, and gave
one to Mikuru!
Here! Go ahead and have one!
But only one, okay?
Okay. Thanks.
Woah! Hey, Yuki? What's the
deal with the mask?
I bought it.
Oh! Okay...
Let's shoot off
some fireworks next.
It'll be a great
way to end the day!
[KYON grunts]
[KYON] It was summer,
and summer vacation.
I guess that's why I
wanted to forget about it.
Truth was, I couldn't
ignore it any longer.
[HARUHI] Tomorrow,
we're gonna catch bugs!
Hey, Haruhi?
Yeah? What?
I don't wanna spoil your fun,
but have you finished
your homework?
Finish my homework?
Aw, that stuff's easy. You can
finish it in like three days.
[gasps]
You have to get rid of it first,
so you can spend your summer
having fun and not
worrying about it!
That, is how you get the
most out of your vacation!
[KYON grunts]
The gods can be so cruel...
So tomorrow, we're all
gonna go bug catching!
But only cicadas.
I'm calling it the SOS Brigade's
cicada catching contest!
[KYON]
The next day was
unbelievably beautiful,
sunny, and bright.
Perfect for the SOS Brigade's
cicada catching contest,
which was currently underway.
And although everyone caught
bugs the best way they knew how,
the winner of the
contest ended up being...
Surprise! Haruhi...
[HARUHI] It's important
to follow the spirit of
catch and release
with these guys.
I mean, if we let 'em go now,
they might return
the favor some time.
[KYON] Now, what could a
cicada possibly do for me?
[cicada's chirping]
[KYON] I sorta feel like
Pandora, opening her box.
[KYON]
We met the next day,
even though we had no
idea what was going on.
Then, we had to
wear frog costumes
and hand balloons out
in front of the supermarket.
This was our part-time job.
[GROUP sighs]
[MIKURU whimpers]
I feel like the Gundam Virtue
after it pops its armor.
[door opens]
[HARUHI]
Good work, you guys!
[KYON] What's with
the special treatment?
You're the best!
The manager's super
grateful for all the hard work.
Who cares how grateful he is?
Where's our pay?
That's it!
Huh?
[HARUHI] I've had my
eye on him for a while now.
The manager said we
could have it 'cause
Mikuru looks so cute in it!
[MIKURU laughs nervously]
[KYON]
We were working,
sweat pouring down
our foreheads...
...for that?!
[HARUHI] We'll keep him in
the club room as a souvenir.
Mikuru, you have my permission
to wear him whenever you want.
Isn't he the greatest?!
--[KYON gasps]
--[MIKURU] Uh... Okay...
Um... Thank you, I guess...?
--[phone rings]
--[KYON] Later that night,
my peaceful slumber was
interrupted by a phone call.
[KYON grumbles]
Shut up...
[phone beeps]
[KYON sighs]
[phone rings]
[KYON]
Shut up!
Ugh, dammit...
Hello?
[MIKURU whimpering]
Kyon...
Miss Asahina?
[MIKURU]
Yes... It's me...
[sobbing]
Something... really bad...
I don't know...
At this rate... I--I...
What's wrong?
[KOIZUMI]
Hello, it's Koizumi.
[KYON growls]
What are you doing
with Miss Asahina
in the middle of the night?
[KOIZUMI]
We have a situation here.
Is it possible for
you to come meet us?
[KYON]
Oh, absolutely!
[bike rattles]
[KYON]
Miss Asahina!
--What happened? Are you okay?
--[MIKURU sobbing]
Oh, Kyon! I can't... Future...
[KYON]
Future? W-What?
I can't go back to the future!
[KYON]
Huh?
[KOIZUMI]
I'll explain it the best I can.
We're currently stuck in a time
loop that seems to have no end.
[KYON] It's hard to
believe you're serious
with that smile on your face.
Come on, Koizumi. Do you have
any idea what you just said?
[KOIZUMI]
Of course, I do.
Much more than
I want to, believe me.
Anyway, I was having a chat
with Miss Asahina earlier.
[KYON] Next time, call me
when you have a chat with her!
[KOIZUMI]
And that's when the two of us
realized that something
seemed a little off about
the current flow of time.
Actually, Miss Asahina
discovered it.
Thanks to her,
my suspicions were confirmed.
What kind of suspicions?
[KOIZUMI]
That we've been re-living
the same period of time,
over and over again.
Yeah, you already said that.
[KOIZUMI] We've been
repeating every day between
August the 17th
through the 31st.
We've become stuck
in the middle of
what seems to be an
endless summer vacation.
[KYON] Well, at least
it's summer vacation...
[KOIZUMI] A never-ending,
endless summer vacation.
The future doesn't exist
in this world anymore.
Time stops at September the 1st.
That's the reason Miss Asahina
can't travel to the future.
It's only natural.
There's nothing natural
about not having a future.
Who's gonna
believe such a thing?
[MIKURU sobs]
Well, for starters, I guess
we were sort of hoping that
you would believe it.
Maybe it's one of
those closed spaces
you were talking about before.
Could we be trapped in
one of those things?
That's not it.
This time, it's different.
A specific section of
time has been torn away.
At exactly midnight
on August the 31st,
everything resets.
Time reverts to the
morning of August the 17th.
That's the process.
Perfect, another
problem involving time.
But I guess I
shouldn't be surprised,
considering there's a time
traveler hanging out with us.
[KOIZUMI]
No...
[KYON]
Hm?
[KOIZUMI] Miss Asahina didn't
have anything to do with this.
Okay... Then what's causing it?
[KOIZUMI]
Miss Suzumiya.
[sighs]
[KOIZUMI] Somewhere
inside her, there's a desire
to have summer
vacation last forever.
I'm sure she
doesn't even realize it.
[KYON] You mean she still
hasn't had enough fun?
[KOIZUMI]
That's what I think anyway.
Perhaps she feels
there's something else
that needs to happen before our
summer vacation can truly end.
[KYON growls]
All right, what do you
want me to do about it?
If I knew that, we'd have
this problem solved by now.
[KOIZUMI chuckles]
You seem like
you're enjoying this.
[KOIZUMI chuckles]
Please don't take
that the wrong way,
but this explains
the feelings of déjà vu
we've both been having.
[KYON]
Are... we the only ones?
Or can other people feel
this happening, too?
[KOIZUMI]
It doesn't seem like it.
But then, you and I are
exceptions to the rule.
The only people who can sense
these strange feelings happening
are the ones who are
closest to Miss Suzumiya.
But, what about Haruhi?
Doesn't she get that
weird feeling, too?
[KOIZUMI]
No, I don't think she does.
Besides, it would be
very bad for us if she did.
[KOIZUMI]
But...
...there is someone else.
Someone who isn't
affected by the time loop,
or the feelings of
déjà vu we've had.
She remembers it all.
I can't imagine what that
would be like for someone.
Okay then, who is it?
You already know. Don't you?
[KYON]
Hmm.
[KOIZUMI] The thought entity
transcends time and space,
and so does she.
Nagato, is that true?
It is.
So, then you can
remember everything?
I can.
Okay then, how many times did we
re-live the last two
weeks up till now?
This would be 15, 513 times.
[gasps]
[KYON] Fifteen thousand
five-hundred thirteen times?
What do you mean 15,513 times?
Nagato, do you know
what you just said?
[KYON] And... you're being
completely serious?
[NAGATO]
Yes.
[KYON] So, you're saying that
we've done the exact same things
every single time,
that many times?
[NAGATO]
Not necessarily.
[KYON]
Huh?
What do you mean?
[NAGATO] Throughout 15,513
repetitions, we did not attend
a bon festival the 2,391st
time and the 11,054th time.
[KYON]
Uh--
[NAGATO] We went to a
bon festival but did not
go to a goldfish
scooping booth 437 times.
We obtained part-time
jobs 9,031 times
--and worked six different jobs.
--[MIKURU whimpers]
In addition to handing
out balloons,
we worked as movers, cashiers--
[KYON]
Got it. I got it.
[KYON] Fifteen thousand
five-hundred thirteen times...
That's what she said.
Times two weeks...
That's, uh...
about... 594 years.
She's the only one of us who
remembers everything we did.
And she's had to repeat them
over and over and over again.
[KYON]
Nagato...
What's it like to re-live the
same things that many times?
[chuckles]
[HARUHI]
I wonder if they're real.
[KYON]
Who?
[HARUHI]
Martians.
[KYON]
I kind of hope they aren't.
[HARUHI] I bet they're
a noble race of beings
who have to live underground.
They're probably friendly, too.
[KYON]
Yeah, dream on.
[HARUHI]
This is boring... I know!
I'm gonna look for UFOs now.
[KYON] You know, I wish I knew
what else she wanted to do.
[KOIZUMI]
Yes, what indeed.
If we knew that, we'd be on our
way to solving this problem.
[KOIZUMI] I know!
Why don't we try this out?
[KYON]
What?
What if someone were to grab
Miss Suzumiya from behind?
And then they whisper, "I love
you," right into her ear?
And who's gonna be
doing the whispering?
Can you think of anyone
better suited to play
that role than you?
I'm exercising my right to veto!
I won't do it.
If that's how you feel...
All right, then I'll
give it a shot.
[KOIZUMI grunts]
Just kidding.
That role requires a certain
something which I lack.
Besides, it would just
confuse Miss Suzumiya,
and we wouldn't want that.
[KYON sighs]
[HARUHI grunts]
Hey, Nagato.
You knew about this time
loop thing we're stuck in
way before Miss Asahina
figured it out, didn't you?
Yes.
So, how come you didn't
say anything about it?
My function is to observe.
--Understood.
--[HARUHI grunts]
[HARUHI]
All right!
[KYON]
Hm?
I did it! Look! I got
a home run! Yay!
[KYON]
We were always doing something,
always on the move.
We went to a real firework show,
and we even signed up for
a goby fishing tournament.
We did the test of courage,
went to the beach, went bowling,
did some karaoke,
and went to the movies.
And the whole time,
all I could think was that
none of it was going to
be enough for Haruhi.
But, what could I do about it?
Nothing.
So, I just bit my
lip and watched
as the last days of our
summer vacation went by.
And then, before I
knew it, it was August the 30th.
[HARUHI] That's it. We've done
everything on our list.
[sighs]
But, now I wonder
if we did enough.
Hmm, oh well... Yeah...
I guess we did a lot.
Unless... does anyone else
have anything they wanna do?
Oh, okay then.
We pretty much did everything
we set out to do this summer,
so I guess that's good enough.
[KYON]
No, it's not.
You're still not satisfied.
Okay, then.
We're done for today!
[MIKURU gasps]
I set tomorrow
aside just in case,
but I guess you can
all take the day off now.
I'll see you guys at the
club room on Monday, okay?
[KYON]
Wait.
Haruhi, wait.
Don't go.
Wait, come back.
If I let her walk out that door,
we're gonna have to re-live
the past two weeks
over and over again,
maybe for a thousand more times.
[KYON]
But... what should I do?
What should I say?
There must have been a clue in
something Haruhi said, but...
...what was it?
What's she been
saying all this time?
[KYON]
I... I don't know.
Wait...
Stop...
Haruhi...
[gasps]
[SERVER]
Thank you! Come again!
[KYON]
It's August the 31st.
I haven't touched my homework.
[sighs] Whatever...
It doesn't matter anymore.
There isn't any
point in doing it.
We're just gonna keep re-living
the last couple weeks anyway.
[KYON] Whatever happens next,
whether tomorrow comes or not,
a different version of me
will have to deal with it.
[KYON sighs]
[click]