We're movin' on
to the next scene!
In this one, Yuki,
I want you to use your magic
to zap the heck outta Mikuru!
[KYON]
Your answer should be, "No!
There's absolutely
no way I'd let you
hurt Miss Asahina
with your powers!"
Look at her...
[KYON]
She's so terrified,
she's turning blue
and shaking like crazy!
Oh, well...
I guess we'll have to use
CG effects in this scene.
Hey, Kyon, don't forget to
make a couple of beams come out
of Yuki's wand, okay?
[KYON]
How am I supposed to know
how to make a
visual effect like that?
[HARUHI] Okay, Mikuru!
I want you to scream,
and then fall down
like you're in pain!
[MIKURU]
Ahhhh...
Ahh...
[HARUHI]
Hmm...
We need a scene with pigeons.
[KYON]
What?
There's a shrine nearby.
We're going there next.
I wanna shoot Mikuru
walking heroically
as pigeons fly all around her.
[HARUHI] It would be so awesome
if the pigeons were all white.
But I guess it doesn't matter
what color they are.
[KYON]
Can't you read Japanese?!
[whimpers]
[KYON] What am I
supposed to be shooting?
[HARUHI]
Hwah!
[yelps]
Kyon! That's the shot!
Hurry up, roll the camera!
Don't just sit there,
look heroic!
[PRIEST] Hey!
Whaddya think you're doing?!
[GROUP screams]
Yah!
[KYON]
Uh-oh!
[MONK grunting]
[HARUHI]
Retreat!
--[KYON panting]
--[MIKURU whimpering]
[sobs]
[HARUHI]
Oh, Mikuru...
You don't eat much, do you?
You'll never get any bigger
if you don't eat more.
If your boobs are
the only things growing,
you'll only appeal
to a small fanbase.
You need to get taller.
[KYON]
She'll grow up, all right.
I dunno how many years it'll
take, but Miss Asahina is
gonna grow up to have
a face and body so fine,
she could be a contender
for the Miss Universe pageant.
But I doubt she knows that yet.
[KYON] Hey, Haruhi.
What are you gonna do
if that priest decides to file
a complaint with our school?
Koizumi's wearing
his uniform today,
and that's pretty much
a dead giveaway.
Aw, don't worry.
It's gonna be okay.
Besides, jackets
like that are common.
If the priest says something,
we'll just play dumb.
[KYON] Once we show
this movie to everyone,
our cover's gonna be blown.
I mean, I seriously doubt
there are that many waitresses
coming out to the shrine
just so they can run around
with the pigeons.
Anyway, what next?
Where are we shooting?
I'm thinkin' we go back to
the park and shoot some more.
I just realized that we
didn't get enough footage
for the fight scene.
I wanna get Mikuru running for
her life through the forest,
with Yuki chasing her!
Then, we could have Mikuru
fall off a cliff!
But Koizumi just happens
to be walking by
and saves her
at the last minute!
[KYON] What a slap-dash way
to come up with a story.
Wait, what if she really does
make Miss Asahina
fall off a cliff?
You should fall off instead!
Why don't you wear her costume
and be her stunt double?
You're not as busty
as Miss Asahina, but still.
Hey, what are you
thinking about?
If you think I'm gonna
put on her waitress outfit,
you've got another think comin'!
[KYON]
She's a mind reader?
Is anyone else going
to be in the movie,
or just the three of us?
[KYON]
Don't ask stupid questions!
You've got a point.
Three characters
might not be enough.
Thanks for the
head's up, Koizumi!
I almost missed that one!
You just got more screen time!
Oh, wow! Thank you!
[KYON]
Serves you right.
You go stirring up a hornets'
nest, you get what you deserve.
Notice I didn't say anything.
Before the boss can be defeated,
the good guys have to beat up
a buncha minions first.
Are minions gonna work, though?
[KYON]
Minions are good.
I know, right?
[KYON]
Taniguchi and Kunikida,
the perfect
supporting characters.
Ultimate minions.
[HARUHI]
A lot of bad stuff
has to happen to Mikuru
in this movie.
After all, the theme
of the story
depends on how hard she suffers.
She has to overcome
horrible odds
before she can have
a happy ending.
And the more we can make
Mikuru suffer in the movie,
the bigger the pay off
is gonna be in the end!
[MIKURU sobbing]
[KYON] What's with that
look she just gave me?
Does she really think I'm
gonna let this happen to her?
[KYON] Later, we returned to the
park and the woods for more fun.
We're not gonna use the
guns in the next scene.
I was hoping for something
cooler and flashier,
but ours don't
shoot smoke or flames.
They're just not
realistic enough.
Mikuru, you stand here.
Yuki, you're over here.
[MIKURU whimpers]
[HARUHI]
Don't move from your marks.
I wanna shoot you guys staring
each other down, okay?
[HARUHI] Grab the reflector
board, Koizumi.
And, action!
[KYON]
What the--?!
[MIKURU whimpers]
[KYON]
Action?
All you did was
tell them to stand there.
What kind of action were you
expecting out of them anyway?
[MIKURU]
Hah!
Uh...
[HARUHI]
Oh, come on!
You call this a battle scene?!
[KYON]
What do you expect?
They're just standing there.
[MIKURU]
Huh?
[yelps]
What is your problem?
Just because you're cute
doesn't mean you have the
right to slack off, you know!
There are lots of other
girls who are just as cute
who'd kill for your spot!
If you don't get
with the program,
you're gonna be left in the dust
by someone even
younger and cuter!
[KYON]
What's she talking about?
Do something, Mikuru!
At least try shooting
a beam out of your eye!
Huh?
I can't do that!
That's the whole point
of your left eye
being a different color!
I didn't just make it
blue for no reason!
There's incredible power
hidden inside that eye.
That's what the
beam's all about!
It's the Mikuru Beam,
so start firing it!
I can't!
Get into it! Fire it!
--[MIKURU] You're hurting--
--[KYON] You idiot!
Hey! Cut it out!
[HARUHI]
What are you doing?!
[KYON]
I said, cut it out!
--[HARUHI] Let go!
--[KYON] Stop! Calm down!
[BOTH grunting]
[KYON]
What, are you crazy?!
People can't fire beams
from their eyes!
[HARUHI]
Hmph. I know that.
All I was trying to do
was get her to act like
she could really shoot a beam.
It's hard to believe
she's the hero
when she's
not that into it.
You never get it
when I'm joking around.
[KYON] That's because your jokes
never turn out to be jokes!
What if Miss Asahina
actually does shoot a beam
out of her eye?
What happens then, huh?!
You... can't, can you?
Huh?
If I might make a suggestion,
maybe after we shoot the scene,
we could figure out the CG part.
Thank you.
[KYON]
And who's gonna do that?
[HARUHI] That's what
I was gonna do anyway.
[HARUHI]
I didn't like that last take.
So we're gonna do it again.
When you strike this pose,
you're gonna shout,
"Mikuru Beam!"
Uh... Is this right?
No, it's like this.
And you gotta shut
your right eye, like this.
[HARUHI]
Okay, Mikuru, go for it!
[MIKURU]
Mi-Mikuru Beam!
[HARUHI] Ugh, you gotta
do it louder than that!
[MIKURU]
Mikuru Beam!
[HARUHI]
Don't be shy! Louder!
[MIKURU]
Uh... Mi-Mi-Mikuru Beam!
[HARUHI]
Project from the diaphragm!
[KYON] The stares from
the families watching us
are starting to hurt.
[HARUHI] Okay, good!
Let's do this for real!
[MIKURU whimpers]
Unleash the beam!
Mi-Mi-Mikuru Beam!
[KYON]
Wha--?!
[gasps]
Huh?
What's up, Yuki?
How'd you end up back there?
You're off your mark.
[gasps]
[MIKURU whimpering]
[HARUHI]
Wait! Stop! Cut!
[MIKURU]
Miss Nagato!
[HARUHI]
What are you doing, Yuki?! Stop!
Nagato! What are you doing?!
Come on, get off her!
[MIKURU sobbing]
[KYON]
Are you all right?
Huh?
Ugh, what do you guys
think you're doing?
If it's not in the script,
then knock it off.
Huh?
Mikuru, what happened
to the contact lens?
Huh? It's not there?
[KYON] At times like this,
you ask the person
who looks like they
know what's going on.
Nagato, do you know what
happened to the contact
Miss Asahina was wearing?
I do not.
[KYON]
Liar.
[HARUHI] Maybe it fell out when
you two were struggling.
Oh, it's gotta be
around here somewhere.
[KYON]
You could at least help us look.
It's so light, it could've
been blown away by the wind.
That's what I think.
[HARUHI]
What happened?
Did it break?
That's weird.
It must have been cheap.
Huh. Oh, well. It's the photo
club's equipment, so go figure.
Just tape up the back, Koizumi.
That should fix it for now.
[KOIZUMI]
You got it.
If you don't have
the contact lens,
then the shots aren't
going to match up.
What'll we do now?
I've got an idea!
We could have her
eye color change
right after
she transforms!
Tr-Transform?
[HARUHI]
Of course!
It's not realistic if you're
always in the same costume!
You need an alter ego!
[KYON]
There's something unreal about
people who want realism
in their fiction.
I think that's a wonderful idea!
I'd really like to wear some
normal clothes for a change!
That's what we'll do!
When you're in normal mode,
you'll wear the
bunny girl outfit!
[MIKURU]
What?! Wh-Wh-Why?!
Well, because that's the only
other outfit I brought along.
Besides, if you wore
your normal clothes,
it wouldn't look as cool
on the big screen.
Wait! Hold that thought!
I just got another idea!
Mikuru's alter ego
is a bunny girl
who's got
a job at the mall,
getting customers to come in
and shop at the stores.
And she only transforms
when she senses danger.
That's when she changes
into a battling waitress!
What do you think?
Pretty cool, huh?
[KYON] What about the realism
you were talking about before?
[HARUHI]
Come on, let's go!
[MIKURU whimpering]
[KYON]
Your efforts... are appreciated.
Okay, you wanna explain the deal
with all the ad-libbing?
[NAGATO]
Here.
[KYON]
So you were the one who took it.
A laser.
[KYON]
Huh?
Hey, Nagato,
your explanations
tend to be a bit short.
D'you think you could try
maybe talking for at least,
oh I don't know, ten seconds?
It's a narrow, spatially
coherent beam of light
invisible to the eye.
[KYON]
Got it.
A narrow, spatially
coherent beam-y thingy...
Sorry, I'm even
more confused now.
A laser?
[NAGATO]
Yes.
Well, that's unexpected.
May I?
There's nothing unsual
about this contact lens.
[KYON]
What are you looking for?
Would you please show me
the palm of your right hand?
[KYON]
Huh?
Sorry, I didn't mean you.
I meant Miss Nagato.
[NAGATO]
It broke through my shield.
[KYON]
You act like it's no big deal!
Just looking at it hurts!
[NAGATO] It was strong;
I had to act fast.
Did the laser beam
that damaged your hand
come from Miss Asahina's
left eye?
[NAGATO]
Yes.
[KYON]
"Yes?" That's it?!
[NAGATO]
It will repair itself.
[KYON gasps]
You gotta be kidding!
Miss Asahina was just shooting
particle beams out of her eye!
It wasn't a particle beam.
Cohesive beam.
[KYON] Laser, mazer,
marker-like fop?! Whatever!
They're all the same
to us normals.
[KYON] The thing I'm having
trouble with is that
she has the ability
to fire heat rays.
It's not a heat ray.
Photon laser.
[KYON] Again, we don't need to
get all scientific about it!
Do you think Miss Asahina's
always had the power
to do something like this?
[NAGATO] No. Currently, Mikuru
Asahina is a normal human being.
She is no different
from anyone else.
Could there be some sort
of tiny mechanism inside?
[NAGATO] It is a simple
cosmetic accessory.
This is amazing.
[KYON] If Nagato hadn't
stepped up when she did
and blocked the laser beam
Miss Asahina shot at us,
it would've gone right
through the camera lens.
Then... it would've
gone through my eye,
cook some stuff and then
come out the back of my head!
Not a pretty picture.
[KOIZUMI] Miss Suzumiya
was the one who caused it.
She wanted to have a
Mikuru Beam in her movie,
so reality changed
and provided one for her.
Very interesting.
Wait a second!
Nobody cast a magic spell
on that contact lens!
So even if Haruhi wished for it,
how can a killer beam
come out of it?
That's easy.
Miss Suzumiya doesn't need magic
spells or strange technology.
All she has to do is believe
something exists, and it will.
Yeah, but she wouldn't
really expect a beam
to come shooting out of her eye!
Yes, that's true.
Miss Suzumiya has enough common
sense to know fact from fiction.
However, it's also true that
the common sense of this world
doesn't really apply to her.
Today's incident is
most likely the result
of a phenomenon of some sort.
I think tha--Uh-oh,
she's on her way back now.
We'll have to continue this
discussion a little later.
[HARUHI] Would you stop
complaining?! Geez!
Act like an actress!
To get on the fast track
to a Blue Ribbon award,
you can't be so shy
about stripping!
Sorry to keep you guys waiting.
[KYON panting]
[KYON]
Zoom... in!
Confirmation obtained.
It's the real Miss Asahina.
What're you doing?!
Hmph.
You're not supposed
to be shooting anything
unless I tell you!
[KYON]
Yeah, I know...
I didn't press
the record button,
I was just...
focusing the camera.
Okay, okay, everyone!
Listen up now!
Let's make this happen!
[KYON] I shot footage
that was supposed to be
"day in the life of
Mikuru Asahina" stuff,
but I'm still not sure
what kind of life
she's supposed to have.
And after making Poor Miss
Asahina run this way and that...
[HARUHI]
Hmm...
I'm not feelin' the whole
mountain-in-the-background
thing.
We're gonna go into town!
[KYON]
Oh, geez!
So...
Miss Asahina wore her bunny girl
outfit until the sun went down.
[KYON] In fact, all
she ever did that day was
walk around in that costume.
Not that I'm complaining.
[KYON]
Asking for permission to film
was a foreign concept to Haruhi.
In her mind,
she was free to shoot
wherever and whatever
she wanted.
But then, her notion of
what "free" actually was
was similar to the
domination of the papacy
during the age of
Pope Innocent III or something.
[KYON] She doesn't get
what "free" means.
[HARUHI]
Hmm...
Yeah! That's good for today.
[GROUP sighs]
[KYON]
That was a long day.
But tomorrow's Sunday,
so I get to chill out.
Okay! See ya tomorrow!
You know the drill--
Same place, same time,
same everything!
[KYON]
She said, like it's no big deal.
I hope she gives us time
to change our clothes.
What was that?
We're on a tight schedule.
We can't take it easy
for even a second!
You're gonna have plenty
of time to kick back
once the arts festival is over.
Consider your calendars booked
until we get
this thing finished!
Here.
We're gonna do our best
to make this movie awesome!
Actually, since I'm
the one directing it,
this movie's awesomeness
is practically guaranteed!
Everthing else depends
on how hard you guys work!
Make sure you're
on time tomorrow.
If anyone shows up late,
I'm gonna bust some heads!
[HARUHI humming]
Don't worry, I'll take care
of telling Miss Asahina, okay?
Now what are you talking about?
[KOIZUMI]
The laser, of course!
Beams won't shoot out her eye
if she doesn't change the color.
On second thought,
perhaps we should take
further precautions against it.
I'm sure she'll
cooperate with us.
[chuckles] After all,
beams are dangerous things.
[KYON sighs]
Oh, man...
Nagato keeps jumping
in and saving my life.
You totally lied!
What's the deal, Kyon?!
Where's Miss Asahina, huh?!
The only reason I came is 'cause
you said she was gonna be here!
I don't see her, do you?!
I want my eye candy, bro!
Where is she?!
Thirty percent of
this picture's success
is riding on you
and that bunny tail!
[TANIGUCHI] Yeah, all I'm
seeing is Suzumiya's angry face.
It's a scam, man!
What the hell?!
[KYON]
Then stare at Nagato.
Just die already.
I kinda think that costume looks
pretty cool on Miss Nagato.
Hey, Kyon!
So what's up with Mikuru?
[KYON] It looks like Miss
Tsuruya's been tricked
into being an extra, too.
What are we supposed
to be doing today, huh?
I was told to show up
if I wasn't doing anything!
Hey, so what's it say on
Miss Suzumiya's arm band?
Ooh! What's the
video camera for?
Hey, what's up with
Yuki's crazy outfit?
Koizumi's looking
super hot today! Whoa!
[KYON]
What a spaz.
What did you just say?!
Your stomach hurts?!
Idiot! Seriously, what are you,
still in junior high school
or something?!
You've got 30 seconds
to get over here!
[KYON] Miss Asahina
appears to be suffering
from a sudden bout
of shut-in syndrome.
[HARUHI growls]
I'm gonna have to go get her.
Where is that bag?
[tires screeching]
I think I can understand
Miss Asahina's apprehension.
It looks like she
might actually become
a real-life version of the
transforming heroine she plays.
The laser beam shooting out of
her eye is a bit much, though.
Anyway, not to worry.
It's safe to say
we won't have to
deal with any
strange beams again.
And why is that?
[KOIZUMI] Miss Nagato
gave us a hand with it.
What did you guys do
to Miss Asahina?
She neutralized the laser beam.
I'm not sure how, though.
Unlike some of the other
TFEI terminals out there,
Miss Nagato isn't
very talkative.
Okay... What's a TFEI?
Just an acronym my
organization assigned to them.
Its meaning isn't
anything important, though.
But as far as
Miss Nagato's concerned,
I have to admit,
she's most unusual.
Compared to the other TFEIs,
that is.
--[KYON grunts]
--[KOIZUMI chuckles]
[TANIGUCHI] Anyway, it was
pretty dark that night.
I was on the way home
from the store,
and I passed this taxi
parked by the curb.
[KUNIKIDA]
Oh yeah?
[TANIGUCHI]
So, I'm lookin' at it,
and you know that
light that tells you
if it's available or not?
I coulda sworn it said "love."
You don't see that every day.
Before I could take a
closer look at the thing,
it drove away.
So I'm standing there, right?
And then, I realized
the sign didn't say "love."
Love's what's missing
from my life!
Well, you never know. Maybe the
sign really did say "love."
Maybe it was a private taxi.
[KYON] I never thought we'd have
to rely on these two Einsteins.
Unbelievable.
[GROUP]
Huh?
[HARUHI]
Pretending to be sick!
You outta be
ashamed of yourself!
You're shooting today, period!
[TSURUYA]
Hiya, Mikuru!
Wow, you're looking
super sexy in that dress!
I'm sorry I'm so late!
[KYON]
Oh, that's okay. I don't mind.
[TSURUYA]
Hiya, Miss Suzumiya!
Sorry about yesterday.
I don't know what happened;
I just started firing lasers
all over the place.
Oh, don't worry,
it didn't hit me or anything.
Hm?
I was bitten.
[KYON]
Really? By what?
Miss Nagato.
She injected some
nanomachines into me.
And now, nothing's gonna
come out of my eye anymore.
Thank goodness.
[KYON]
What did she inject you with?
Nanomachines!
Last night, her and
Koizumi came over--
[TSURUYA]
Whatcha whisperin' about, huh?!
Ooh, you're so cute, Mikuru!
I wanna keep you as my pet!
[KYON] Don't stare.
You'll wither her cuteness.
[HARUHI]
I've got our location for today.
There's a big lake
by Koizumi's house
that's perfect
for the next scene!
Come on, everyone! There's a
ton of movie left to shoot.
[giggles, hums]