[HARUHI laughing]
[TANIGUCHI]
Huh?
[KYON sighs]
[HARUHI]
Well, here we are!
[KYON] Doesn't that mean
we shouldn't be going in?
Even little kids would avoid
shooting in a spot like this.
Except for the stupid ones,
that is.
[HARUHI]
Don't just stand there.
Hurry up and climb over already!
[KYON] Oops, forgot.
She's really stupid.
Come on, Mikuru. Hurry up!
[gasps]
Mm-mm...
[laughs]
The fence is rather high;
it might be too difficult
for everyone to climb over.
Would you have
a solution for us?
[KYON]
Hm?
[gasps]
Wow, that gate's
gotta be really old...
[TANIGUCHI] Am I gonna have to
play a sea monster or somethin'?
[TSURUYA] The lake didn't always
have this fence around it.
You know, people used
to fall in a lot.
[KYON] Thank god,
they're all so clueless.
[HARUHI]
There. That'll do the trick.
So this is the scene
where Mikuru gets cornered
by the baddie.
She can't use her beam
'cause Yuki neutralized it.
Well, the cue cards are done.
Here, hang onto this
for me, kid.
Huh?!
[HARUHI]
Mikuru, are you ready?
[whimpers] Yes.
[HARUHI]
Come on, louder!
Yes!
[KYON]
I feel your pain.
[HARUHI]
Okay! Here we go!
And... action!
[yelps]
[MIKURU]
E-E-Even in times like this,
I won't ever run away!
Y-You're an evil bad alien...
And... now, you better
leave this planet at once!
[HARUHI]
Cut!
[NAGATO] For he is very
valuable to us, you see.
And while we're seizing him
and his hidden powers,
we will also invade the Earth.
[HARUHI]
Cut!
I-I won't let you
get away with that!
I will risk my own life
to stop you!
[HARUHI]
Cut!
See? You're startin'
to get the hang of it!
Good job!
Okay, c'mere a sec.
I gotta talk to you
about the next shot.
[MIKURU]
Okay...
[KYON]
I hope we get out of here soon,
before anybody in the
neighborhood notices we're here.
So that's your
video camera, huh?
[laughs] I betcha got a lotta
goofy shots of Mikuru on there.
[laughing]
[KYON]
I don't see what's so funny.
There's a lot of
damaging stuff in there.
What if Miss Asahina stops
coming to school because of it?
[HARUHI]
We're back!
And we're gonna be
kickin' things up a notch!
Check it out!
Cool, huh?
[KYON]
Oh god, no!
It's gonna be a repeat of
what happened yesterday!
This is bad!
Go ahead, Mikuru.
I don't care what comes
outta that miracle Mikuru IR.
Whatever it is, make sure
it's destructive!
[yelps]
[MIKURU screams]
[HARUHI]
Oh, come on, Yuki!
You're supposed to be
an evil witch!
Stop whipping out
the wrestling moves!
Well, I guess this works, too.
Whatever gets more viewers.
Hey, Kyon!
Why aren't you rolling?
This is Yuki's concept!
Don't waste it!
[KYON]
It's not a concept.
This is racy stuff...
I shouldn't be
shooting this, but...
Put the target in
the center and hit record.
No, I mustn't, I mustn't.
[crash]
[GROUP]
Huh?
You better leave
this planet at once!
[HARUHI] Oh, geez! I can't
believe we lost another contact!
My mistake.
I disabled the laser function
she had access to.
However, a high-frequency
molecular cutter was activated.
[BOTH gasp]
That looks like damage
from a monofilament attack.
Oh, no!
I'm really sorry about that.
But, um... what did you
inject me with this time?
I altered the phase of
your dimensional cycles,
and generated a force
field around your body,
which alters
gravitational waves.
I understand.
For the time being, it looks
like it's been taken care of.
[KYON]
Yep, still don't get it.
As for what happened
to the fence,
the others seem to think
it was old and falling apart.
And thankfully, it was the only
thing that got damaged.
Yeah, but what are we gonna do?
I mean, if we keep
shooting this thing,
I'm scared that something
really bad's gonna happen.
Regardless, we can't interfere
with the completion of the film.
Can you imagine what
Miss Suzumiya would do
if we tried to force her
to stop shooting it?
[KYON sighs]
I don't care.
I guarantee,
she wouldn't be happy at all.
A closed space would be
torn apart by the Shinjin.
You have to understand,
Miss Suzumiya's
having so much fun,
she just can't help herself.
And in a way, this is a
chance for her to play god.
The process of putting
the movie together
is Miss Suzumiya's way
of creating a world
that functions
according to her will.
[KYON]
Selfish as ever, I see.
Of course, Miss Suzumiya doesn't
realize any of this
is happening.
She thinks she's creating
a fictional world
for the story of her movie.
However, I believe
that subconsciously,
she's so passionate about it,
she's actually starting
to change the reality
of this world.
[KYON]
Fiction, he says.
Either way you slice it,
we get a bad ending.
If we have to choose between
stopping the shoot or
seeing it through to the end,
I would strongly recommend
we finish it.
Even if Miss Asahina turns
into some kind of super woman?
Compared to having
the Shinjin appear,
it's a small price to pay.
Think about it.
Wouldn't it be easier
to deal with
abnormal phenomena
one at a time, as opposed to
having the world rebuilt from
scratch right under your feet?
[KYON s
If you ask me, it's all pretty
much the same thing, isn't it?
Here's another option
for us to consider:
We could knock Haruhi out cold
and wake her up
after the festival's over.
That's a frightening
thought to consider.
But if you're prepared to take
responsibility for the outcome,
I wouldn't get in your way.
[grunts]
[growls]
I don't think my shoulders can
handle the weight of the world.
[MIKURU]
Um...
I don't want you
to worry about me.
I'll be okay and find a way
to get through this.
[gasps]
[KYON]
I am in awe of her selflessness!
[HARUHI] These are the
characters you guys play.
Here's the deal,
since Mikuru's the hero,
she doesn't believe
in hurting innocent people.
Yuki takes advantage of this
and uses her magic to
get you guys to attack her.
Since Mikuru wouldn't
hurt you guys,
she gets beaten up!
[GROUP gasps]
Mikuru's gonna get beaten up!
Here's what you do!
The three of you are gonna throw
Mikuru right into the lake!
[BOTH gasp]
Wait a second,
you wanna throw her in there?
The water might be warm
but it's cold out!
Besides, that water's
pretty filthy!
B-But Miss Suzumiya,
couldn't we do this at a pool?
No one said this shoot
was gonna be easy.
So suck it up already!
You have to make
these kinds of sacrifices,
especially if they're gonna help
us get the realism we're after!
You can't let something
like this stand in your way!
You have to overcome it!
This is a big step up
for you as an actress!
See what I'm saying?
Good! Get ready!
Hang on!
[KOIZUMI]
Mm-mm.
I-I'll... Okay! I'll do it!
Thatta girl!
Yes!
That's why I picked you
to be a brigade member!
[MIKURU whimpers]
[KYON]
Miss Asahina...
One, two, three!
[MIKURU screams]
[KYON]
Heaven protect her.
[KOIZUMI] What's happening?
Just grab my hand. It's okay.
[coughs]
[KYON]
Good grief!
We've got enough crap here
to open up a pawn shop,
but we don't
have a towel for her?
What's up with that?
[HARUHI]
Hm...
This could work for the
scene where they meet.
You can feel the awkwardness
between Itsuki and Mikuru.
[KYON]
Really?
Looked like Koizumi was just
acting like he always does.
We're moving on
to the next setup!
It's the scene right
after Itsuki saves Mikuru,
where he picks her up and
carries her back to his house.
[gasps]
Hang on!
That makes absolutely
no sense at all!
What happened to Nagato,
Taniguchi, and the others?!
The audience is
gonna get totally lost
if they just disappear
from the story!
Oh, be quiet!
The audience is gonna be
so wrapped up in the story,
they'll be fine with it!
[KYON]
No they won't!
You just wanna see Miss Asahina
get tossed in the lake!
My house isn't
too far from here,
and Mikuru looks
like she's freezing.
Is it cool if
she changes clothes?
'Cause she might end up
catching a cold!
That's a great idea!
Can we use your house
for our next location?
It's the perfect place
to shoot the scene
where they get all
friendly with each other!
Yep! Go ahead,
knock yourself out!
Uh, what do you want us to do?
You can go home.
I'm done with you.
[BOTH]
Huh?!
[KYON] Congratulations,
you guys have been sacked.
It looks like you're about
as important to Haruhi
as a bunch of spent BBs.
Which isn't such a bad thing,
if you wanna know the truth.
[TSURUYA]
Ta-da! Here it is!
[KYON]
Ginormous!
What sorts of evil things
do I have to do
to live in a place like this?
So anyway, this is my room!
You guys can wait here till
Mikuru's done with her bath.
[KYON] Whoa, this place
makes my bedroom
look like a cat condo.
[HARUHI]
Great room!
This is a perfect location!
Oh, yeah!
Hey, Tsuru, I wanted
to ask you something.
When you get the...
[whispering continues]
[laughs]
[KYON]
Huh?
[TSURUYA]
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Here you go.
Thank you!
Thanks for waiting.
Sorry I took so long.
[TSURUYA]
Here you go!
[KYON gasps]
[KYON] Am I being
tested here or something?!
Miss Asahina, that outfit
is absolutely criminal!
Here you go! Drink up!
[KYON]
Thanks.
Thank you.
[KYON]
Watching her take a sip
is another direct hit
to my libido!
Okay, let's knock this one out!
[KYON] And with that,
we started shooting.
In the shot, Koizumi carried the
pretending-to-be-unconscious
Miss Asahina into the room.
For some unknown
and convenient reason,
there was a futon
spread out on the floor.
Go, Mikuru, start waking up.
[whimpers]
[KOIZUMI]
Are you awake now?
Yes...
But, um...
I don't know where I am.
[KOIZUMI]
You're in my room now.
Thank you for taking care of me.
[KYON]
She seems a little too sexy.
Is that acting?
[HARUHI] Bring your faces
closer together.
Yeah!
Now, Mikuru, close your eyes.
Koizumi, put your
arm around her!
All right, now push
her down and kiss her!
[grunts]
[growls]
Hold it!
This is going too far!
Why is this scene
happening anyway?!
What is this?!
It's a love scene, of course.
We have to have one to
pat out the picture's runtime.
You're crazy!
Are we shooting a movie
for late-night TV or what?!
And why are you suddenly
getting into it, Koizumi?!
If this thing ever screens
at the school festival,
I guarantee you're gonna
get a ton of hate mail
crammed in your shoe
locker the next day!
I'll even write some myself!
[TSURUYA laughs]
Mikuru, you're so weird!
[KYON]
Normally, I'd disagree,
but she is acting
a little strange.
Her eyes are all glazed over,
and her cheeks are flushed.
She looks like she'd let
Koizumi do whatever he wants!
This isn't funny anymore!
Hey... Koizumi, I feel hot...
and my head's all heavy...
[KYON] Geez, it's like somebody
drugged her or something.
[gasps]
Sorry, I sorta spiked her juice
with a little bit of sake.
I was told it would help her
loosen up and act better.
[HARUHI]
Hmph.
It's not right to get
people loaded like that!
Just look at her, she's sexier
now than ever before!
Don't listen to him,
kiss her! Go ahead!
Kiss her right on the mouth!
[growls]
Don't do it, Koizumi.
Madam Director...
I hate to say it, but I'm
feeling a little overwhelmed.
Besides, it looks like
Miss Asahina's
reached her limit, too.
Nah... I feel fine...
Let's keep shouting...
Aw, geez! This won't do...
[MIKURU]
Huh?
Man, I can't believe
you'd get so plastered
from just a little sake.
[KYON] I can't believe
you made her drink it!
Come on, snap out of it!
[yelps]
You call that a reaction?
Whenever I tap you on
the head with this thing,
you have to straighten
out your back.
That's the rule!
Let's try it again, okay?
Now focus!
[yelps]
[KYON]
Cut it out!
How is that supposed to help?!
And how is any of this
gonna fit in the movie?!
Huh?! What's your problem?
I don't have to tell you
how I'm gonna use this,
that's my business!
You can't tell me
because you have no idea!
Stop making excuses!
Oh, yeah!
Like you know anything!
You don't even know
what this movie's about!
How dare you make
selfish demands?!
You're the one who's
being selfish here!
You're just hitting Miss
Asahina because you want to!
How dare you
treat her like that?!
Don't you talk to me like that!
Who do you think you are?!
This is called "story" and
it's important for my movie!
Get it now?!
It's not important!
Know what?! This sucks!
Miss Asahina is not your toy!
Shut up! It's important to me!
And I can treat her
like a toy if I want to!
[growls]
[BOTH gasp]
[HARUHI]
Wha-What is it?!
What is your problem
anyway, huh?!
You just have to do
what I tell you!
I'm the brigade leader!
I'm the director!
Whatever!
Do what I say or get out!
[KYON]
Let go, Koizumi!
I don't care if it's
a person or an animal,
if they won't listen,
they deserved to be smacked!
If she doesn't learn
her lesson now,
she's gonna grow up to be
some kind of lonely freak!
[MIKURU]
Stop it! Don't!
Stop fighting... Stop it!
Or else... Nevermind,
it's classified anyway...
[TSURUYA]
I'm sorry, Kyon.
I got a little carried away.
You don't have
to worry about Mikuru.
I'll take her home
or have her stay the night.
I always thought of you
as being more rational
than you were back there.
[KYON]
Yeah, so did I.
The good news is that
closed space hasn't appeared.
It looks like Miss
Suzumiya's subconscious
was able to control
itself this time.
[KYON]
Awesome. Less work for you.
[KOIZUMI]
By the way, if you're free,
there's a place
I'd like to take you to.
And what if I said no?
I don't think this
should take too long.
[KOIZUMI] Do you remember what
Miss Suzumiya said yesterday?
How am I supposed to remember
all the crazy stuff she says?
When you see this, I'm sure
it'll come back to you.
I think they've been like that
ever since this morning.
Did someone come out here and
paint 'em all or something?
No, that's the natural coloring
of their feathers.
There's no mistaking it.
Well, maybe all
the gunfire yesterday
scared the heck out of 'em.
Even if that were
really the case,
do you think this is
what would happen?
[KYON]
Yeah, I know.
[HARUHI] It would be so awesome
if the pigeons were all white,
but I guess it doesn't matter
what color they are.
[KYON]
Apparently, it did.
Here's my perspective
on the situation.
Miss Suzumiya's special.
However, at one point,
she was given her godlike powers
by someone or something else.
Ultimately, she's just an
ordinary human being,
as opposed to a divine being.
Her presence in this world
is proof of that.
Well, that's a
new spin on things.
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but didn't you say
something before
about how Haruhi
was a god?
Really? Did I say that?
[KYON]
Don't mess with me.
Of course I'm only kidding.
Miss Suzumiya is the one who
can create the world around us.
And at the same time,
she can destroy it.
Perhaps the reality
we're currently in
isn't working as
efficiently as it should.
And perhaps the only person
who has the power to fix
this failed world of ours
is the one we've come
to know as Miss Suzumiya.
[KYON]
Yeah, sure.
[KOIZUMI]
Consider this:
If she's creating all this
strange phenomena
to fix whatever's wrong
with the world,
then our attempts
at covering it up
might be preventing that
change from taking place.
[KYON]
Hmph. So what?
[KOIZUMI] It means we
could be in a lot of trouble,
that's what.
When Miss Suzumiya
changes this world
to a version that's
functioning properly,
do you think there would
still be a need for us
and our special abilities?
Or, will we be considered
the bugs in the program
and exterminated?
[KYON]
Who knows?
Honestly, with all its faults,
I like the world the way it is.
It's been built piece by piece
by so many different people,
from ancient times
to the present.
If I had my way, I wouldn't
change a single thing about it.
That's why I do what
I can about Miss Suzumiya
and the situations
she puts us in.
I wonder if this world
is really worth
all the trouble
you're going through.
Oh?
I thought you of
all people felt it was.
Otherwise, you
wouldn't have come back
from closed space that one time.
Or am I mistaken?
Well, who knows? I don't.
It's out of character for me
to be so presumptuous.
And for a second there,
I might've sounded
like I was inferring
that we were the
protectors of this world.
Please forgive me.
[KOIZUMI]
Rather than being angry today,
it seems Miss Suzumiya
is too busy feeling sad.
[KYON]
Really? Why's that?
[KOIZUMI] I thought you
of all people would know why.
I don't mind
explaining it, though.
Miss Suzumiya always thought
that no matter what happened,
you'd be right there,
by her side,
even though you'd
sometimes complain.
You alone would forgive her.
[KYON] Yeah, well, the only one
who could forgive her now
would be a martyred saint.
[KOIZUMI] Do you think
you could say something
to Miss Suzumiya
to cheer her up?
If you don't, she might
continue to get depressed.
And then something much worse
than closed space could appear.
I don't even want to think about
what would happen
to the world if...
...well, if she were to sink
into a deep depression.
[KYON] So, you're telling me
to go cheer her up.
[KOIZUMI] You just need to get
back together with her again.
[KYON] Yeah, see,
that's where you're wrong.
I was never "with her"
to begin with.
[KOIZUMI]
Oh, well...
I thought that you would've
cooled off a bit more by now.
I guess I was wrong.
[KYON] The reason
I got so angry yesterday
was because I couldn't
stand watching
Miss Asahina getting abused
and degraded like that.
But that's not the only reason.
I could've been suffering
from calcium deficiency.
So, before bed last night,
I downed a liter of milk.
And it seemed to
calm me down a little bit.
It... could've been
a placebo effect, though.
[TANIGUCHI]
Yeah, movie, what a joke.
[KUNIKIDA]
Don't listen to him.
He's just upset
'cause he wanted to
hang out with you guys
and Miss Suzumiya some more.
He even cancelled
his plans on that day.
Don't tell him that, you jerk!
So anyway, you can
just forget about
me helping out on any more
of your stupid projects.
Movie... yeah, right.
Nobody's gonna watch that trash!
For real.
[KYON growls]
You're the last person
I wanna hear that from.
[TANIGUCHI]
Hm?
[KYON] It's not like I
can't imagine it, though.
But hearing a guy like him
say it really pisses me off.
At least Haruhi's
doing something
for the school festival.
She's trying to get involved.
Can you say the same
about yourself?
Who cares if it's stupid?!
At least she's trying
to make something.
Look at you!
You're just sitting
there complaining!
Man... That really
pisses me off!
Why am I so angry
about it though?
I wonder...
Is it because I've
suddenly found a passion
for making movies or something?
Is there something wrong, Kyon?
Miss Suzumiya looked upset, too.
Did something happen?
[TANIGUCHI]
Lovers' spat, whatever.
[KYON]
Hmph.
I get it now.
I do what Haruhi tells me to do,
and then I go out
and complain about it.
There's no difference
between me and Taniguchi.
I mean, I got so mad at the
stuff he was saying just now,
but how's it any different
from what I've said before?!
Dammit! Taniguchi, you bastard!
Thanks to you,
I've realized something
and I'm not happy about it!
And now, I'm gonna go do
something I know I'll regret!
Dammit... Dammit! Dammit!
[HARUHI gasps]
Hey, Haruhi.
What do you want?
We're gonna finish this movie,
and it's gonna be awesome.
[HARUHI gasps]
[chuckles]
Well of course, it will!
I am the director, after all.
Everyone knows it's
gonna be awesome.
I certainly don't need
you to tell me that.
[KYON]
Man, talk about a mood swing.
Oh, well. Things get weird
when Haruhi's grumpy,
so I guess this
really is for the best.
Here we go!
You could've at least
tried to pick a better way
to say it to her.
Sorry.
Not only is she back
to her old self,
now she's even more
powerful than ever!
Sorry.
We won't be able to cover things
up for much longer.
Can you believe
how perfect this is?!
I was just thinking about a
scene with cherry blossoms!
This weird weather came along
right at the nick of time!
Let me see your victory pose!
[MIKURU]
Huh?
[whimpers]
I know!
We need to find ourselves a cat!
A cat?
Yeah. Every witch
needs a familiar, right?
And nothing says
familiar like a cat!
I wonder if there's
a black cat around here.
Wasn't Nagato supposed to be
playing an evil alien
in this thing?
You and your details.
I need a cat for this movie,
so let's find one!
How 'bout it, Yuki?
Do you know any
place around here
where we can find
a buncha stray cats?