I brought some tea.
Here you go.
Oh, thanks a lot.
[KYON slurps]
Huh?
Uh...
Wow, it's really good.
[MIKURU]
Mm-hm!
Here you go.
Why, thank you very
much, Miss Asahina.
[KYON] The SOS Brigade
was officially created
by Haruhi in May.
It's already June now.
During that time, I was involved
in an incident that's, well...
It was like the world got a
sudden case of leg cramps.
All that aside, today's episode
goes a little
something like this:
[HARUHI]
Hey, you guys!
We're gonna enter ourselves
in a baseball tournament!
[KYON] Since the day
of that "incident,"
nothing really out of
the ordinary's happened.
We were enjoying our brief
moment of peace and boredom
as best we could. And boy,
was it a brief moment.
You might be wondering why.
[KYON] Because when she
turns on that smile of hers,
somehow I'm the one who always
ends up completely exhausted.
What did you say we're gonna do?
[HARUHI]
We're gonna do this!
"Announcing the ninth all city
amateur baseball tournament."
And, who's gonna be entering
this little sandlot
baseball game?
You've gotta be kidding!
Us, of course!
So when you're saying "us,"
you're talking
about everyone here
--including me?
--[HARUHI] Somehow,
we need to find at least
four more people.
[KYON] As usual, if somebody's
opinion's inconvenient,
she doesn't even hear it.
Hey, do you even know
the rules for baseball?
Of course I know the rules.
When I tried out for
the baseball team,
they gave me the rundown
of all of the basics.
But I wasn't having any fun,
so I hurried up and went home.
[KYON] Well, if you think
baseball's so boring,
why do you wanna enter
the tournament so badly?
Because it's our chance
to show the entire world
just who we are! If we win
this baseball tournament,
the SOS Brigade will take
on a life of its own
and be known all over the world!
It's a great opportunity!
Right, Mikuru? Isn't
that a great idea?!
Huh? B-But I wo--
Don't you think
baseball is great?!
In fact, we're gonna
shoot for the championship!
We can't afford to
lose a single game
because you know
how I hate losing!
[screams]
You got that?
Well, I think it
would be all right.
Don't smile like that
and give into her demands.
Why don't you try
disagreeing with her
every once in a while?
Actually, I think this
is much more sensible
than walking around the city
looking for aliens and UMAs.
[groans] All right, when's this
tournament supposed to happen?
It's this Sunday!
[KYON] Day after tomorrow?
Are you kidding?!
Don't you think
that's way too soon?
But I already turned
in the application.
Oh, don't worry
about it. It's all set.
I put "SOS Brigade"
as our team name.
That's one thing I made sure of!
And as for the other
four players we need,
you got any ideas on
where to find them?
If I come across anybody
walkin' around lookin' bored,
I'll just grab 'em.
[KYON] Scary thing is:
she really means that.
All right, Haruhi,
just hang on a second.
I think that
Taniguchi and Kunikida
might have some free
time on their hands.
[HARUHI]
They'll do.
[KYON] It's true: Haruhi thinks
of her classmates as objects.
Okay then... Let's see,
we need two more.
Uhm... If you don't mind,
I think I might have a friend.
[HARUHI]
Perfect!
[KYON]
Apparently anyone will do.
Hey, wait, Miss
Asahina's friend?
Okay, that's interesting.
Friend from where?
And what time period?
It's okay, she's
from this time-- Uh!
I mean, she's just a friend
I met in one of my classes.
I know someone. It's an
acquaintance who's been curious
about our group for some
time now and I think--
[KYON]
I'll handle it, thanks.
Now that that's settled,
it's time for some
intensive training!
Intensive training?
You mean, right now?
Yeah!
Yeah, but where?
Over there!
[BASEBALL PLAYERS yelling]
[KYON]
So, all of us got roped into
entering a baseball tournament
just like that. Why, you ask?
The reason's very simple:
It was because...
Well, Haruhi was... bored.
[giggles]
[HARUHI] Hey, you guys!
Can we use the field now?
And we also wanna
borrow your equipment.
Huh? What the heck
are you talkin' about?
We need to have
baseball practice,
and we're also
kind of in a hurry,
so would ya get lost?
Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
[HARUHI] It'll only be for
a little while, right, Mikuru?
[squeals]
[gasping]
[KYON]
Adolescence is so predictable.
For starters, we're
gonna practice catching
1,000 grounders!
Huh?
Wah! [screams]
Oh, come on, the future
of the SOS Brigade
is riding on that ball,
so get ready!
[KYON] This is the first time
that I've heard that our future
was riding on such a tiny ball.
[HARUHI] Okay, Mikuru,
here comes some more.
That hurts! No! Stop!
[gasps]
Miss Asahina, are you
all right? Can you stand?
If you're too nice to me,
it'll happen again.
Please don't.
[MIKURU whimpers]
Dammit, you guys! Get back
to your positions right now!
She's injured, okay?
[growls] Fine, then!
Next up, the baseball team!
Why do we have to do it?!
[HARUHI grunting]
All right, you guys!
That's it for today!
[BASEBALL PLAYERS groan]
[sighs]
Well now, that's surprising.
Miss Suzumiya batted
exactly 1,000 hits.
Frankly, I'm more surprised
by the fact that you counted
every single one of them.
Hm? Oh, hey, Nagato.
On the day of the
tournament, I was wondering
if it was possible
to make it rain.
You know, a big one
that'd cancel the game
with a rain delay.
It is possible, but I
would advise against it.
Yeah, why's that?
Any alteration of the regional
climate could possibly
have devastating after-effects
on the eco-system of the planet.
And about when would these
after-effects happen?
Several hundred to 10,000 years.
[KYON sighs]
Then I guess we'd better
try not to do that, right?
Right.
[HARUHI growls, grunts]
[KYON] The day of the baseball
tournament has finally arrived.
[GIRL laughs]
So, you're Kyon?
I hear an awful lot
about you from Mikuru.
Hm... Ah...
Oh, this is Miss Tsuruya,
that friend I was talk--
I'm Taniguchi. It's very
nice to meet you.
And I'm Kunakida.
Yeah, see, when he asked me,
I just couldn't turn down
my good buddy, Kyon.
--[TSURUYA] So you're...
--[KYON] Oh, brother...
[HARUHI]
Kyon!
Come over here for a minute.
Okay, what were you
thinking? Seriously?
You gonna make something
like her play baseball?!
[KYON] Hey, don't go calling
my little sister a "something."
She's a person!
[HARUHI] Yeah, well,
she introduced herself
as a ten year-old fifth grader!
I mean, she's so sweet! I can
hardly believe she's related
to someone like you.
This baseball tournament's
open to the general public,
it's not some crummy
little league game!
You are aware of that?
[KYON]
Yes, Miss Haruhi.
All the more reason to bring
my little sister today.
We really don't have
a chance of winning,
but since this is Haruhi
we're talking about,
watch us win the
championship by accident.
That would be a pain.
But, if we have a fifth
grader in the lineup,
then we're sure to lose.
Huh. Fine, whatever.
Guess it'll be a handicap.
I'd feel bad if we won
this thing too easily.
[KYON] She still thinks
we can win this thing.
[yelling]
By the way, has it occurred
to you that you need to decide
the batting order and our
positions on the field?
Oh, I thought
about that already.
Here, take a look
at this: two types!
One for batting order,
the other for field position.
Oh, and I'm the pitcher,
and I'll be batting first.
So you're saying all
you've figured out was
how we're gonna
decide those things.
Yeah, and? You gotta
problem with that?
This is the democratic method.
In ancient Greece, they
picked numbers out of a hat
to elect their leaders.
[KYON] Don't compare picking
the batting order for a sandlot
ball game in modern Japan to how
the Greeks picked their leaders.
Besides, you get to
do whatever you want.
How's that democratic?
Whatever. All the more
reason to go home early.
I mean, from what I hear,
our first opponent is a team
of college students,
the Kamigahara Pirates.
Apparently, they're the
favorites to win the tournament,
and the game is called when
one team gets a ten-run lead.
So it's not too early to start
packing up to go home right now.
Play ball!
[gasping]
Hah! You kidding?
You call that a pitch?!
Come on, everybody,
follow my lead!
[PITCHER]
Hm.
[CATCHER]
I'll try to do my best toda--
--[UMPIRE] Stike!
--[yelps]
[gasps]
[KYON] Why's he throwing
so hard at Miss Asahina?!
If he hits her, I'm gonna charge
the mound and deck that guy!
[UMPIRE]
Strike!
--[HARUHI] Mikuru!
--Huh...?
Like this! You
swing it and bang!
[UMPIRE]
You're out!
Damn you! Why didn't you
even swing the bat?!
[UMPIRE]
Strike!
You're out!
Yuki, if you don't swing,
you'll never hit the ball!
Kyon, you're batting cleanup!
You'd better hit the ball!
[KYON] What do you expect
from a cleanup hitter
picked by a lottery?
Strike!
[KYON] Haruhi hit that thing
into the outfield...?
Strike two!
[PITCHER]
Hmph!
Strike three, you're out!
--[HARUHI] You idiot!
--[KYON] I have dishonored
my family...
Let's take 'em out!
[ALL]
Yeah!
Play ball!
[UMPIRE]
Strike!
Huh...?
[UMPIRE]
Strike!
Strike three! You're out!
[KOIZUMI]
Nice pitching.
Piece of cake, no sweat, guys!
[UMPIRE]
Foul!
[BATTER]
Hm.
[HARUHI gasps]
[HARUHI growls]
[KYON] She can only
throw straight pitches
through the strike zone.
When they figured it out,
it was only a matter of time.
On top of that, our
defense has more holes
than an anthill in the Savanna.
We're so toast.
[KYON] The fact that they only
scored two runs off of us
must be because
the opposing teams'
goddess of victory's
running late.
I guess everyone wants
to relax on a Sunday.
Well, the top of
the second inning
went by really quickly,
and in the bottom of the inning,
we gave up a few more runs.
Looks like we'll be
heading home next inning.
[UMPIRE]
Out!
Phew, that was hard!
It's all I can do to just
hit the ball with the bat.
Looks like I'm gonna be
needing it after all.
Time out, ump!
[MIKURU]
W-Wait a minute! Miss Suzumiya!
[HARUHI]
Come on, hurry up!
[MIKURU]
N-N-No!
[HARUHI] Get out of those
right now and put this on!
[HARUHI giggles]
You look good in that!
Can I get a picture of
you guys with my phone?!
I wonder if up in a ponytail
would be better...?
[growls] Fine! Cheer on!
I'm not really sure
how to do this!
You do it like this,
and yell as loud as you can!
Yo!
Everyone, pl-please hit
the ball! I'm begging you:
Do your best out there!
Yeah, I'll knock
this sucker out!
Strike out!
Hah, the sun was in my eyes...
Don't sweat it, I wasn't
counting on you anyway.
[whimpers]
Uh...
[gasps]
Safe!
[HARUHI] Mikuru! Just make sure
to hit the ball this time!
--[TSURUYA] Go for it, Mikuru!
--[KUNIKIDA] Miss Asahina!
[gasps]
Strike!
[HARUHI]
Mikuru! Like this! Like this!
[KYON]
What is she doing...?
Looks like she's trying
to reduce the magic points
of the other team's
pitcher or something.
Well, it seems to me that she's
trying to signal for something.
[KYON]
Did we ever decide on signals?
[KOIZUMI] No. But I think
that she's signaling
for a squeeze-play right now.
[KYON] She's signaling
for a three bunt squeeze
with two outs?
Even the most senile
coach in the league
would make better
decisions than that.
[KOIZUMI]
The chances of Miss Asahina
actually hitting the ball
are close to none. However,
if we can catch the Pirates
off-guard by going for a
squeeze-play that normal people
wouldn't think of, there's a
possibility that one of their
infielders might make an error.
Or, maybe she's thinkin'
that somehow, Miss Asahina
might even hit the ball
with the bat for once.
[KYON] Well, it looks like
they figured it out now.
--Huh...?
--[UMPIRE] Strike!
And you're out of there!
Mikuru, get your butt over here
and get ready for
some pain, girl!
Huh?!
Take your punishment!
Let everyone have a good, long
look at that funny little face.
Please stop, it hurts!
[KYON]
Hey, numbskull.
It's all your fault for
giving confusing signals.
Maybe you should've tried
to steal home
yourself or something.
[growls]
[phone rings]
[gasps]
[KOIZUMI] Things aren't
looking so good anymore.
[KYON] I don't wanna
hear it, but go ahead.
[KOIZUMI] A closed space larger
than anything we've seen before
is starting to form.
And it's spreading
at an alarming rate.
[KOIZUMI]
It will continue growing,
and the you-know-what's will
keep tearing things apart till
Miss Suzumiya's mood improves.
And that's happening just
because we're losing?
Oh, man, you've
gotta be kidding me.
You're still talking as if it
has nothing to do with you.
Believe me, you're involved with
what's happening now, Kyon.
Do you remember how we
all had to pick numbers
to determine the batting
order for the day?
As a result, you're
batting cleanup.
I'm not all that happy
about it, you know.
[KOIZUMI] That's not the point.
Miss Suzumiya wished for you
to bat cleanup and you are.
That is not a coincidence.
Because you're not performing
like one would expect
from a cleanup batter, she's
feeling a little disappointed.
Well, excuse me.
[KOIZUMI]
In any case,
we should all try to
play the best we can
so that they don't and
call the game this inning.
Because if the game
ends here, you can say
it's the equivalent of this
world coming to its end.
[HARUHI] Let's go, dammit!
Take your positions!
This inning, we need to hold
them to two runs no matter what.
[KYON] Two outs,
man on first and second,
and we're down by nine.
If they score another run,
this game will be over.
[grunts]
[MIKURU whimpers]
[MIKURU]
It's coming this way!
[KYON]
Gotta catch it...
Gotta catch it!
Wow! Amazing!
[sighs]
--Nice catch!
--[laughing]
[sighs]
Getting back to what we were
talking about earlier...
Little close there. What's up?
The other day when you and
Miss Suzumiya were stuck
in that other world, I was
wondering how you managed
to get yourselves out of it.
Do you have to
remind me of that?
It's just that if you
use that trick again,
maybe everything here
will start getting better.
Forget it.
That's exactly what
I thought you'd say.
Very well, let's just go
and win this game instead.
After all, she shares
the same concerns we do.
[MIKURU]
Miss Nagato is finally...
What, are you saying there's
something the matter with her?
It looks like she's
casting a spell...
A spell? Wait, what're
you talking about?
Let's see... That's classified.
A spell, huh?
[cheering]
Take it. I changed the
elemental boost information.
Elemental what?
Homing mode.
[gasps]
[KYON]
Wow! It's flying!
I see. Homing mode, huh?
Oh man, there's gotta
be a limit to this.
[KYON]
Hm?
[KYON] This is great,
but if we keep doing this,
things are gonna get ugly...
in all kinds of ways.
Well, that should be enough.
I see.
Strike! Strike! Strike!
[KYON] I had forgotten
about it, but the first round
has a 90-minute limit.
That means this
is the last inning.
If we can keep them
from scoring, we win!
Is it all right for us to win?
It is necessary for us to win.
Thanks to all of our efforts,
the expansion of the closed
space looks like it's stopped,
at least for the time being.
But if they suddenly
make a comeback,
then that'll be the
game right there.
[KYON] It's a waste of time to
think about how Haruhi's mood
will turn if that happens.
[KOIZUMI]
I've got a plan.
Huh?
Are you serious?
Yes, I am dead serious.
It's the only option we have
if we're to get through
this inning without
givin' up too many runs.
[KYON]
Oh, brother...
Foul!
Damn you! Be serious about this!
If you lose, you're buyin'
everyone lunch after the game!
[KYON] I know that. After all,
the fate of the entire world
is resting on my pitching.
I guess the world's
not worth very much...
[KYON]
Thanks to my Mysterious Ball--
I named it myself--it looks like
the world will be spared
from certain annihilation.
St-Strike two!
You're out!
[KYON] In just three pitches,
yet another batter struck out.
And now it seems the last
batter's at the plate
--with two strikes on him.
--Strike two?
Kyon, wrap it up with
the next pitch, okay?!
[KYON] There was no doubt
about that happening.
Sorry about this,
Kamigahara Pirates...
[BATTER]
Yeah!
Pick up the ball, Nagato!
Pick up the ball and throw it!
Hurry! Hurry!
--[HARUHI] Over here!
--[KYON] Second base!
What the--?!
I'm terribly sorry, but you
see, we're not the typical
team of athletes you're
used to playing.
[UMPIRE]
That's game!
[cheering]
[KYON] Thanks to Nagato's
magical cheating,
we were able to win the game.
[KOIZUMI] What're we going
to do about the game
in the next round?
[KYON] I'm gonna feel bad
for the Kamigahara Pirates
if we beat them in the second
round like we just did.
I'm really sorry about this,
but I'm afraid I'll need to go
and help my colleagues
out in a little while.
[KYON] So we're gonna be
short a player then.
How 'bout we forfeit?
Sounds like a good
plan. After today,
it looks as if it's a bad thing
when Miss Suzumiya's bored.
We should probably keep
that in mind during
any future activities.
[KYON]
Had enough fun for today?
Koizumi had to bail on us
because he had something
pop up suddenly, and to
tell you the truth,
my arms and legs are
killing me right now.
I guess if you're all right
with it, then, oh well.
Anyway, I'm hungry. How 'bout
we all go and get some lunch?
[KYON]
You got it.
Thank you, thank you!
I can't thank you enough!
[KYON] No, it's nothing!
See you around!
Wait, you know, that bat...
I never thought about
it, but yeah, man...
I heard so much
about you from...
Eat up, everyone!
Kyon's treating us today!
What a game, huh, guys?!
[KYON]
Oh, well.
Thanks to the Pirates, I gained
a little extra cash today.
Kamigahara Pirates,
I wish you luck.
[yelling]
[HARUHI]
Sorry I'm so late!
So, which one do you
think we should try next?!
Soccer or American Football?!
How many do we
need to play each?!
Is the number of people
we had last time enough?!
[KYON] As I looked over at
Haruhi's brilliant smile,
I was trying to think
about which sport
would require less people.
[KYON] American Football?!
No way! How 'bout bowling?!