[KYON] Well, it's been about a
month since we started school,
and I've been enjoying
my early morning hikes
about as much as I could.
Although, I sort of
feel like Sisyphus,
cursed to forever roll
that boulder up the hill,
tryin' to make it to the top.
And then something hit me.
Something that felt
like an 8.0 earthquake,
which brought my normal
life to a grinding halt.
[KYON]
No, that's not quite right.
Actually, something
was starting to happen.
[HARUHI] If it doesn't exist,
I should just make it myself!
Make a club!
And you're gonna
help me with it!
I've just figured out what
we're gonna call ourselves!
The SOS Brigade!
[KYON] And so begins
my never-ending hell,
thanks to the eccentric
Haruhi Suzumiya.
[ASAKURA]
Good morning!
Uh... Oh, morning.
[ASAKURA] I forgot I had
class duties today.
I have to get the class log
from the teacher's lounge.
I have to hurry!
I'll see you in class!
[KYON] Hard to believe
a girl like that's
in my class along with...
Hmm?
[HARUHI] Hey, Kyon! Can you
think of anything else
we're gonna need right now?
What do you mean?
I wanna get my hands on a
mysterious transfer student.
What d'you think of that?
I beg you, please start the
conversation by making
the context clear.
It's exactly what
the SOS Brigade needs.
We need something like a
mysterious transfer student.
Okay, before you
kidnap anyone else,
what do you mean
by "mysterious"?
Check it out: school started
less than two months ago, right?
So I'm thinking that
anybody who transfers
into our school right now has
to be mysterious! Am I right?
Maybe the kid's dad got
relocated because of work.
[HARUHI] Oh, work with me here.
It's not normal!
I'd sorta like to know what
you consider normal,
but I'm almost afraid to ask.
[HARUHI] Hmm... I wonder if
we'll get anyone like that.
A mysterious transfer student...
[sighs] I guess in other words,
you don't really give a damn
about anything I say at all.
Whatever...
[KYON] Apparently there's a
rumor floating around school
that Haruhi and I
are up to something.
Level with me. What are
you and Suzumiya up to?
You guys wouldn't happen to be
dating or anything, would you?
Ugh, no, we're not dating.
And trust me, I'd also
like to know what we're
supposedly up to.
I don't have any idea
what I'm doing anymore.
Just don't overdo it. You're
not in junior high anymore.
You guys mess up the
school or anything,
you'll get suspended
at the very least.
[KYON] At least I can keep Yuki
Nagato and Mikuru Asahina
from getting involved in
anything too crazy.
[KYON] Since the
SOS Brigade was founded,
the once empty room of
the former literary club
now has lots of things in it.
Maybe she's planning on
living here or something.
You know what? It'd be great
to have a computer in here!
We're living in
the information age
and we don't even have a
computer. I can't forgive them.
[KYON] And who is it
you can't forgive?
What d'ya say? Let's go get one!
Do you have any idea
how we're gonna get one?
You're not gonna rob
a computer store, are you?
No way! We're gonna
hit someplace closer.
Hi, everyone!
I've come for a computer
and all the accessories
that go with it!
Who in here's the president?
I guess that'd be me?
There's only one reason
why I would schlep
all the way over here
to the computer club.
I'm here for a computer!
I only need one.
Excuse me?
You crazy or somethin'?
We only need one, and you guys
got a whole bunch in here.
Hang on a sec,
who the heck are you anyway?
We are the SOS Brigade, and I'm
Haruhi Suzumiya, the leader!
And these are my henchmen
Number 1 and Number 2!
[sighs]
Don't give me any crap.
Just hand over a computer
and no one gets hurt.
Why the hell should I?!
I'm not givin'
you guys anything!
[HARUHI]
Hmm...
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT]
Hmm?
Okay. Here's how this is
gonna go down, boys,
so try to pay attention.
[hums]
[whimpers]
[gasps]
[screams]
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT]
What're you doing?!
[grunts]
And! One more shot!
[screams]
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT]
What're you doing?!
[HARUHI]
Ah-ah-ah!
I have photographic evidence
of blatant sexual harassment.
If you don't want any
of these pics to show up
all over campus, hand over a
computer and be quick about it.
This is ludicrous! You forced
me to touched her breasts!
I'm innocent I tell ya!
Wonder how many people
are gonna listen to
your side of the story,
you sexual harasser.
What?! Hang on! All the club
members here are witnesses!
That's right!
[MEMBER B]
Yeah, it wasn't his fault!
Then I'll tell everyone at
school that all you geeks
ganged up on her and ----ed her!
[gasping]
You out of her mind
or something?!
Well, chief?
You gonna hand it over or not?
M-Miss Suzumiya...
That's--!
[growls]
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT]
Take whichever one you want.
[HARUHI]
Hmm.
Get up, man!
[MEMBER B]
Get a hold of yourself.
It's gonna be okay.
[MEMBER C]
We'll figure this out, sir.
[MEMBER B]
Don't cry.
[KYON] It's... like a bad
comedy skit or something.
Which one's the latest model?
Give me one good reason
why I should tell you that!
[HARUHI]
Hmm!
[whimpers]
[sighs]
[HARUHI]
That one...
[gasping]
I almost forgot....
I got a list from the list
from the computer
store yesterday.
It's got all the
newest models on it.
[gasping]
And, it looks like this
computer's not listed.
Uh...
[HARUHI]
Hm...
[gasping]
Think I'll take that one!
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT]
Wait, that's the machine
we just bought!
You can't do this!
[gasps]
Take it, you thief...
[KYON]
Yeah, you got that right...
She is a thief.
[HARUHI]
Hey, Kyon!
[KYON]
Hmm?
Could you get this?
[KYON] And, just like that,
Haruhi procured
a state-of-the-art computer.
It was only then she learned
that the literary club
wasn't wired for internet use.
So she called the Computer Club
over to run a LAN cable
between our rooms.
She also had them set us up
so that we could connect
using the school's domain.
Can you say "Extortion"?
Good.
Come on, what d'ya say we
go back to the others?
[MIKURU whimpers]
Miss Asahina, I was
thinking maybe it's best
you don't get involved
with this brigade thing.
I mean, who knows what she'll
end up doing to you if you stay?
No, it's all right I guess.
But you'll stay too, won't you?
Uh...
I guess the probability
of this happening
on this particular time
plane's is unavoidable.
Huh...?
And I'm worried about why
Miss Nagato's here, too...
What'd you say?
Huh?
Oh, nothing.
I was just babbling.
I might be a little
inexperienced, but I know
I'm gonna get along
with everyone here.
By the way, you don't have to be
so formal.
Please just call me Mikuru
if you don't mind.
[KYON]
Okay...
So what's next...?
[KYON] So, about this website,
who're you gonna get to make it?
That'd be you.
Beats sitting around
being bored all the time.
I have to go out and find
some more members now.
Oh, and make sure
you finish the site
in the next couple of days.
The club's dead in the water
until we have our
site up and running.
[sighs]
I'm building a website, huh?
[KYON] Despite my griping,
I kinda enjoyed making it.
The guys from the
Computer Club installed
all the software for me, so it
wasn't too hard to figure out.
Not a bad way to spend
an otherwise boring lunch.
Okay. What am I supposed
to put on it?
I mean, I still had absolutely
no idea what the SOS Brigade
was actually going to do.
Hey, Nagato, was there anything
you wanted me to
put on this site?
No, there's not.
[KYON] Not that I should
get involved, but...
...does this girl
even go to class?
[birds chirping]
[school bell chimes]
[KYON snores]
Uh. Oh crap!
I gotta go to class!
[KYON]
Huh...?
Take it...
I'll lend this to you...
Uh...
[door closes]
[KYON] Okay, I'm still not sold
on this whole "Brigade" thing.
So why do I find myself eagerly
commuting to the club room?
Why? Is it simply
what you call "habit"?
[KYON]
Hey!
[KYON] These two can't
be that bored, can they?
Can't say I'm not
bored either, but...
Where's Miss Suzumiya?
Dunno. By the time I managed
to get to our 6th period class,
she wasn't there.
How much you wanna bet
she's out there right now
extorting more gear
from somebody?
Will I be forced to do
something like yesterday?
You'll be fine, trust me.
I'm not gonna let anything like
that happen to you ever again.
You mean you'll protect me?!
Oh, thank you so much!
Guess I'll be counting
on you, then!
It's an honor to be counted on.
[HARUHI]
Ya-hoo!
[KYON]
Ya... hoo?
[grunts]
[BOTH gasp]
First, take a look at this!
"SOS Brigade... an explanation
of our general policies..."
And now, for this:
Ta-da-da-da, da-da!
We're gonna pass out
flyers wearing these.
[KYON]
Where at?
The main gate.
There's a bunch of students
still hanging out on campus.
[KYON]
And what exactly are we wearing?
You're not the one wearing it.
I got this outfit for Mikuru.
Ah! What?
A bunny girl costume.
But... how... how am
I supposed to...?
[HARUHI]
Come on! Put it on! Get dressed!
[MIKURU]
But I don't want to!
[HARUHI] Shut up and strip!
Come on, girl!
[MIKURU]
Nooo!
Hey, Suzumiya! Stop it!
Please, no! No, don't look!
[gasps]
[HARUHI]
Quit struggling!
[MIKURU]
But I don't wanna put it on!
[HARUHI] Move your arm!
Let's go, Mikuru, take it off!
Take it off!
[screaming]
[sighs]
[MIKURU]
Noo... don't...
[GIRLS]
Let's go! Let's go!
[MIKURU]
Let me take it off myself!
No! Noo!
[HARUHI]
You can come in now!
[KYON]
She's like an evil overlord.
Well? Think we'll get some
attention now or what?
[KYON] Don't think
that'll be a problem.
Nagato wasn't into it?
[HARUHI] Nah, I could
only afford two of 'em.
I got the deluxe set,
so they were expensive.
[KYON]
Where'd you buy these things...?
[HARUHI]
I got 'em online.
[KYON]
I see.
[HARUHI]
Well, we'll be going now.
Come on, Mikuru, let's head out.
No, I don't wanna...
Nooo!
[HARUHI]
Let's go! Yeah!
[whimpers]
[KYON]
Sorry...
Honestly though, that outfit's
killing me right now.
My passion's going
through the roof here...
[KYON]
Hmm?
[gasps]
[sighs]
[KYON]
Oh brother...
It's still warm from
their body heat...
[KYON]
"The SOS Brigade:
An explanation of our
general policies.
We, the SOS Brigade, are
committed to seeking out
mysteries in this universe.
[HARUHI] To anyone who has
experienced strange phenomena
in the past, anyone who has a
mysterious experience recently,
or anyone who plans on having
a weird experience
in the future.
If any of the above applies
to you, come see us!
We'll help you find the answers
you need, fast!
However, if your mystery is
ordinary, we can't help you.
We only accept phenomena and/or
mysteries that freak us out!
Please keep that in mind."
[KYON] I think I'm starting
to understand the reason
for this brigade's existence.
They piss me off so much!
I mean, what's with
those stupid teachers?!
They're always butting in!
So what happened out there?
Did you guys get into trouble?
Unbelievable! We passed
out half our flyers
and teachers came out of
nowhere telling us to stop!
Who do they think they are?!
[KYON] If two girls
in bunny suits
are passing out flyers
in front of the school,
everybody'd come running
to check that out.
[HARUHI] Mikuru starts sobbing,
I get yanked into detention,
and Okabe, that handball
freak, comes over-- Augh!
[KYON]
I'm sure they didn't know
what to keep their
eyes focused on.
Well, I guess that's
it for today.
Dismissed!
[gasps]
[HARUHI]
How long you gonna cry anyway?!
Let's go! Take it off, come on!
Um, say, Kyon...
If I find I'm unable to get
married after all this,
would you be willing
to marry me...?
[KYON]
What should I say?
Miss Asahina, you look
like you just found out
you didn't get accepted
into college.
Or, like someone
who's just lost her job
the day after buying
her dream house.
Wait... Oh man, now you're
calling me Kyon, too...
By the next day, the name Haruhi
Suzumiya had become infamous.
Now everyone at school
was talking about her.
Hey there, Kyon,
hate to say it,
but it looks like you've
gone and done it.
You've become one of Suzumiya's
gang of weirdos, huh?
Oh, shut up.
[KYON] The sucky thing about
being part of all this
is that my name and
Miss Asahina's are now
floating around the campus, too.
I couldn't believe what
I was seeing yesterday.
A couple of bunny girls hanging
out by the school's main gate.
I mean, the girl in red was
Mikuru Asahina, wasn't it?
Now everybody in school's
talking about you guys, Kyon.
Everybody.
[ASAKURA] What exactly
is this SOS Brigade?
You're gonna have
to ask Suzumiya.
I really don't know.
I don't even wanna know.
Well, it definitely
looks like you guys
are having a lot of fun.
But you know, yesterday's stunt
was a little overboard.
[KYON] That day Miss Asahina
didn't show up to school.
Unbelievable. Not a single email
after all that publicity!
[KYON] After publicity like
that, I don't think anyone's
gonna want anything
to do with us.
Have to admit though, that stunt
caught everyone's attention.
Hang on... Where's Mikuru?
Didn't she come to school?
[KYON]
She might never show up again.
Hope she wasn't too
traumatized by all this...
And I even got a new outfit
for her to wear today, too.
Why don't you wear
it yourself then?
[HARUHI] Oh, don't worry,
I'm gonna wear it.
It's just not any fun
if Mikuru isn't here...
[KYON] Why don't you
have Nagato wear it?
I doubt she'd have
any complaints.
In fact, I don't think I'd
mind seeing her wear it.
Agh!
I got the SOS Brigade
up and running,
and now we're just
sitting around.
What is it, everybody holding
out on me or something?
Keeping their mysteries
to themselves...
[KYON] Okay, Haruhi.
Look, ask anybody in this room
and they'd say, "Sure,
mysteries? Why not?"
But an ordinary high school like
ours isn't gonna have a bunch
of weirdness just stacked in the
corner somewhere for you.
You know that, right?
I mean, you do realize
that, don't you?
You don't have any place
to channel all that
adolescent frustration
boiling inside you.
Isn't that what's really fueling
all this impulsive behavior?
Snap out of it and go find
yourself a good-looking guy
and let him walk you
home from school.
Heck, go see a movie with him
on Sunday or something.
Or, why don't you try sports?
Get on one of the teams and give
'em hell out on the field.
I'm sure you'll make the
starting line up on any
varsity team you pick.
[HARUHI]
I'm going home.
[KYON sighs]
[KYON]
Well, guess I'll head out, too.
[YUKI]
Did you read it...?
[KYON]
What?
Book...
Oh, no I haven't yet.
Do you want me to
give it back to you?
That will not be necessary...
[KYON] When Yuki does talk,
she has a tendency to avoid
the pitfalls of idle
conversation.
Please read it today...
[KYON]
Hmm?
As soon as you get home...
All right, I will.
[KYON'S SISTER] Huh!
Where're you going now, Kyon?
[KYON] I'm meeting with
someone at the station,
and don't talk with
your mouth full.
I'm sorry... Was today the day?
You weren't waiting for me here
last night as well, were you?
Well, why'd you pick
this place to meet up?
Follow me...
So, uh... Where're your folks?
They're not here...
Uh... Yeah, I know they're
not here right now, but,
did they go somewhere?
Actually, I am the only
one who is ever here...
You live by yourself?
Yes...
So what is it you wanted
to see me about?
Drink it...
[KYON slurps]
Is it good?
Yeah, thanks.
[KYON slurps]
[groans]
[KYON gulps]
[KYON sighs]
I'm gonna explode...
Okay... You think it's about
time you got around to tell
why you wanted me to come
all the way out here?
Were you uncomfortable
talking to me at school
about it or something?
It's about Haruhi Suzumiya.
And, in addition,
it is about myself...
That is what I would
like to talk about.
Okay... You and Suzumiya.
So what's up?
It is difficult to find
the words...
There might be discrepancies
in the transmission of data.
However, please listen...
Haruhi Suzumiya and I are
not ordinary human beings...
Yeah, I already sorta figured
out that you two
weren't exactly normal.
That's not what I mean...
I am not referring to the
absence of universally accepted
personality traits.
What I mean is literal, in that
she and I are not the same
as ordinary human beings.
Human beings such as yourself.
I have been created by the data
integration thought entity
that supervises this galaxy.
I am a humanoid interface
designed to make contact with
organic lifeforms like you.
Do you understand?
Huh...?
To use a common term that is
applicable to this situation,
I believe I would be
classified as an alien.
[KYON]
An... alien.