[COMMENTATOR] At the time
of the seventh, the score's 7-0.
Next batter up is Yamada.
[KYON] Something's wrong...
That's what it felt like anyway.
[KYON] I didn't care about
the baseball game on TV;
it was between schools
from another town.
But because I tend to
symphatize with underdogs,
I ended up rooting
for the losing team.
And it was right about then,
that I suddenly got the
feeling Haruhi was gonna call.
--[phone rings]
--[gasps]
What the heck does she want?
[KYON'S SISTER]
Hey, your phone's ringing, Kyon.
Yeah, I know that.
You don't have to tell me.
[phone ringing]
[COMMENTATOR]
The bleachers behind third
are going nuts out there.
[HARUHI]
Hey, you're free, right? Good.
[HARUHI] Meet us at 2:00
in front of the station.
And don't be late!
[dial tone]
[KYON sighs]
[KYON] I didn't even have
a chance to say anything.
[phone rings]
--[KYON] Yeah, what?
--[HARUHI] I forgot to tell you,
make sure and bring your swim
trunks and some money, too.
Oh, and your bike.
Definitely bring your bike.
That's it. Over and out!
--[dial tone]
--[KYON] Ugh.
Weird... It was like I knew
what Haruhi was gonna
say before she said it.
Yeah... No...
Actually, it felt like we'd had
the exact same conversation
once before. Kinda like
déjà vu or something.
[metal clink]
[COMMENTATOR]
Oh, what a shot!
It's a big, fat hit heading
straight for left field!
And it's over the fence!
And it's gone!
[KYON]
Summer's almost over...
You are late, Kyon!
Where's your motivation?
[KYON]
Yeah, yeah.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Now that we're all present
and accounted for, we can go!
[KYON]
Where?
To the public swimming pool!
Where do ya think?
[KYON] That figures...
considering the stuff I brought.
[HARUHI] We've got lots of
summer vacation-y things
to do during our break!
But we've only so
much time because
once it's gone,
it's gone for good!
We'll do everything
we can, while we can
during our only summer
as tenth graders!
And for starters, we're gonna
ride the bikes to the pool!
[KYON] Did... everyone
ride bikes today?
No, the only bikes
we have to take
are the ones you and
I brought with us.
[KYON]
Huh?
[HARUHI] Kyon, you better
not let Koizumi beat you!
Come on! Full speed ahead!
[HARUHI] Well, here we are.
Hurry up and park the bikes!
We're trying to have fun,
Kyon, so stop acting tired!
[KYON]
And whose fault is that, huh?!
[HARUHI]
Aah, can you smell the chlorine?
That really makes
it feel like summer!
[KYON]
Crowded...
Here's the plan, you go
dump our stuff somewhere,
and then meet us in the pool.
We're gonna have a little race.
Come on, Mikuru, you and me!
[MIKURU screams]
[HARUHI gasps]
Hurry up and get in, guys!
The water's warm! It's perfect!
[KYON] Can't she see
the "no diving" signs?
They're everywhere!
[KOIZUMI chuckles]
Doesn't that look like fun?
It's such a peaceful
looking scene, isn't it?
And in a way, it makes me smile.
I mean, seeing Miss
Suzumiya enjoy the day
in a normal fashion.
It's a rather charming sight,
don't you think?
She called me,
told me what to bring,
and then ordered me to meet
her without telling me anything
about what was going on.
That isn't charming or normal.
Well, if you ask me,
none of that
is anything to make
such a fuss over.
And as long as Miss Suzumiya's
laughing and having a good time,
we don't have to worry about
any earth-shattering events
happening any time soon.
[KYON]
I hope you're right.
All right!
[gasps]
What?
Nothing. It's just
my imagination.
With everything that's
happened since we met,
you could say I've become
a little bit paranoid.
Here you go!
Oh, thanks for making the tea.
Oh, it's delicious!
[HARUHI] Come on,
let's go swim some more!
[MIKURU whimpers]
[KYON]
Geez...
Now I know why they call
it a "public" swimming pool.
Seems like everyone
in town's here today.
I wonder why Haruhi
chose this place.
Hm?
[KYON]
Huh?
There's that feeling again...
It's like I've seen
this happen before,
with Nagato sitting there
like that, looking bored.
[HARUHI]
Kyon!
[KYON] Yeah... And then
Haruhi shows up, and says...
These guys are my
brigade members.
They do what I say.
So if you want
something, ask them!
Time for some fun!
Let's play water soccer!
[KYON]
Uh. Yeah, sure...
[KYON] Oh, well.
Sometimes déjà vu's happen.
Get ready, Mikuru, surf's up!
[MIKURU yelps]
[gasps]
[MIKURU whimpering]
[HARUHI]
I've been thinking about
some fun things we could do.
[KYON]
What's that thing?
I came up with this
schedule of how we're gonna
spend the rest of
our summer vacation!
I realized something...
We've only got two more weeks
of summer vacation left to go!
That fact totally blew me away.
I know we've done a lot
of cool things so far,
but we've only so much time,
and there's a bajillion
more things left for us to do!
So, we're gonna
pick up the pace!
[KYON]
Two weeks to do all that?!
Mikuru, is there anything
else you wanna do?
[MIKURU]
Huh?
Uh... I'd like to try
goldfish scooping.
Okay!
Goldfish scooping, it is...
Could I see that for a moment?
[KOIZUMI chuckles]
Thank you.
Does anyone know if there's a
bon festival happening close by?
[KOIZUMI] Oh, I could
check around for one.
That'd be awesome.
Okay, tomorrow,
we start the list.
And I guess that's it for today.
[bike rattling]
[KYON]
Nagato!
Hey, it's nothing important
or anything, but...
I was just wondering...
Is everything okay with you?
It is.
Uh... Great,
that's good to hear.
Yes.
[KYON]
What the heck?
Why'd I want to talk to her?
I guess that's it.
[KYON] The next morning, I was
wakened from my peaceful slumber
by a call from Haruhi.
She said they'd
found a bon festival.
We're all gonna go buy yukatas.
I guess Yuki doesn't have one,
and neither does Mikuru.
And I don't have one either,
but I know a place that sells
them in sets for really cheap.
[KYON] So, we went
to a clothing outlet,
and Haruhi picked out yukatas
for Miss Asahina and Nagato.
Then, she marched them straight
into the changing rooms.
After about an hour...
--...they emerged.
--[HARUHI] Ta-da!
[KYON]
Whoa! Blinding!
The three of you look
absolutely wonderful in them.
Well, of course we do!
I picked them out myself,
especially Mikuru's!
Look at you, you're so cute!
I'm a genius!
Oh? Uh, yeah!
[KYON]
Miss Asahina... Aah!
[MIKURU]
Wow!
[HARUHI giggles]
They've got goldfish scooping,
just like you wanted!
I bet you're gonna catch a ton!
[KYON]
A bon festival, huh?
It figures that
it'd be so crowded...
Huh?
[KYON] I haven't been to
a bon festival in a while,
but it feels like I
just went to one.
That tower... Those vendors...
[KOIZUMI]
Do you wanna go scoop some fish?
[KYON]
Hm?
We could have a little contest.
Leave it to the expert!
[KYON]
Mm, I'll pass.
How 'bout you, Nagato?
Do you wanna go get some food?
[KYON]
Hm?
Don't tell me you're
actually into this stuff.
I got it.
[NAGATO]
No.
That one.
[VENDOR]
It's yours for 800 yen!
[KYON] I wish she would've
let me buy that for her.
It's the least I could do
after all she's done for us.
[HARUHI]
What an unbelievable haul!
I caught thirteen!
But, I only kept one
'cause I don't have any
place to put all those fish.
I gave another one to Mikuru!
[HARUHI] Go ahead and
have one, but only one!
[KYON]
Okay, thanks.
Hey, Yuki, what's up with
the mask you got there?
I bought it.
Oh... Okay.
Anyway, let's go
shoot up fireworks!
We'll end the day
with a firework show!
[KYON]
Do you even understand
the meaning of the
word "moderation"?!
[KYON] It was summer,
and summer vacation.
And I guess that's why I
wanted to forget about it.
But the truth was, I couldn't
ignore it any longer.
[HARUHI]
Tomorrow, we're catchin' bugs.
Hey, Haruhi, I don't
want to spoil your fun,
but have you finished
your homework?
Are you kidding?
That stuff's easy.
You can finish it
in like three days.
Three days?!
[HARUHI] You have to get
rid of that junk first,
so you can spend the
rest of your summer
having fun and not
worrying about it!
It's the only way to get the
most out of your vacation!
[KYON] Why does she
have to be so smart?
The folks upstairs
weren't terribly fair
when they were divvying
up the stats for us.
Kay, listen up! We're gonna
go bug-catching tomorrow!
And whoever catches the
most bugs is gonna get...
Lemme see... I know!
They'll get to be brigade
leader for a whole day!
[KYON]
No thanks!
That sounds like a lot of fun!
But, can we catch
just any random bug?
Um... No, wait... Only cicadas!
That's it, I'm calling it
the SOS Brigade's
cicada catching contest!
[KYON] The next day was
beautiful, sunny, and bright.
In fact, it was the
perfect day for us
to have our SOS Brigade's
cicada catching contest.
And even though everyone caught
bugs the best way they knew how,
the winner of the
contest ended up being...
You guessed it, Haruhi.
It's important to
follow the spirit of
catch and release
with these guys.
I mean, if we let
'em go this time,
they might come back
and return the favor!
--[cicada's chirping]
--[GROUP gasps]
[KYON] What could
a cicada do for me,
even if it did come back?
I sorta feel like Pandora,
when she opened her box.
[MIKURU]
W-Welcome to our store!
[KYON]
We met the next day,
even though we had absolutely
no idea what was going on.
Our confusion continued
as we stood outside
the local supermarket,
wearing frog costumes
and handing out balloons.
Hey, it's a living.
[MIKURU whimpers]
[KYON] I feel like I just
escaped the Adzam's leader beam.
You guys did an awesome job!
[KYON] What's with
the special treatment?
You guys are the best!
The manager's super grateful
for all the hard work.
Who cares how grateful he is?
What about our pay?
That's it!
[KYON]
Huh?
I've had my eye on this little
guy for a long time now.
The manager gave it to us
'cause Mikuru looks
so darn cute in it!
[KYON]
We worked in the sun,
sweat pouring down
our foreheads...
...for that?!
We'll keep him in the
club room as a souvenir.
And Mikuru, you can wear
him whenever you want.
Help yourself!
You have my permission, 'kay?
[KYON]
Hm?
[sighs]
[KYON]
Later that night...
My peaceful slumber was
interrupted by a phone call.
[MIKURU whimpers]
[gasps]
[MIKURU whimpering]
Kyon...
Miss Asahina?
[MIKURU sobbing]
Yes... It's me...
Something... really bad...
What's wrong?
[KOIZUMI]
Hello, it's Koizumi.
What are you doing with
Miss Asahina at this hour?!
[KOIZUMI]
We have a situation here.
Is it possible for you to
come meet us right now?
[KYON] Miss Asahina! What
happened? Are you okay?
[MIKURU sobbing]
It's terrible... I can't...
I can't go back to
the future anymore!
[MIKURU sobbing]
I'll try to explain
it the best I can.
We're stuck in a time loop that,
as far as I can tell,
seems to have no end.
[sighs]
It's hard to believe
that you're serious
with you standing there,
smiling like that.
Come on.
Koizumi, do you have any
idea what you just said?
Of course, I do. Much more
than I want to, believe me.
In fact, I was having a word
with Miss Asahina earlier.
[KYON] Call me when
you have a word with her!
It's like this, we came
to the conclusion that
something seemed a little off
about the current flow of time.
Well, actually, it was Miss
Asahina who discovered it.
And thanks to her,
my suspicions were confirmed.
What suspicions?
That we've become
stuck in a time loop.
We're re-living the same period
of time, over and over again.
I know; you already said that.
We're being forced to
repeat every day between
August the 17th
through the 31st.
In other words, we're in the
middle of what seems to be
an endless summer vacation.
Well, at least it's
summer vacation, right?
It's a never-ending,
endless summer vacation.
In the world we're in now, the
future doesn't exist anymore.
All time stops at
September the 1st.
That's the reason Miss Asahina
can't travel to the future.
It's only natural.
Look, there's nothing natural
about not having a future.
And who's gonna
believe such a thing?
Well, for starters, we were sort
of hoping you would believe it.
[KYON sighs]
For what it's worth, I can
try to explain it, too.
Here goes...
Because I have to
classified information,
I have to use
classified information
to contact the future.
The thing is, for a week now,
I haven't gotten any...
...classified information.
That's kind of weird.
I was so surprised that I...
classified information.
I did, but it was
And now, I don't know...
what to do...
[sobbing continues]
[KYON] I don't know how to
help you, but I'm wondering...
Are all the classified
information things
you're talking about stuff
you can't say on TV?
What about those closed spaces
you were talking about before?
Do you think it could
be one of those?
No, it isn't one of those.
What happened is that
a specific section of time
has been torn away.
At exactly midnight
on August the 31st,
everything as we
know it, is reset.
Then time loops back on itself,
back to the morning
of August the 17th.
That's the process.
[grunts]
Then what about our--
Wait, what about the
whole world's memories?
[KOIZUMI]
Those get reset as well.
Everyone's memory starts
over from the beginning.
Perfect, another
problem involving time.
But I guess that's
to be expected
when there's a time
traveler around, huh?
Oh, no, Miss Asahina didn't
have anything to do with this.
Okay then, what's causing it?
It's Miss Suzumiya.
[sighs]
I'm sure she doesn't
even realize it though.
But I do think that deep
down inside herself,
she'd prefer it if summer
vacation would last forever.
You're kidding me!
You mean she still
hasn't had enough fun?
That's what I think.
Perhaps she feels there's
something else that
has to happen before our
summer vacation can end.
[sighs]
[KYON] Oh, man...
The trouble she gets us into
is always galactic in scale.
Right, what do you
want me to do about it?
If I knew that, we would have
this problem solved by now.
You sure seem like you're
enjoying this an awful lot,
what's up?
Please don't take
that the wrong way.
But, this explains the feelings
of déjà vu I've been having.
And the ones you've
been having as well.
And now that I think about it,
those feelings were probably
the residue of our memories
from all the instances
where time was reset.
Are we the only ones?
Or can other people feel
this happening, too?
It doesn't seem that way.
But then again, you and I
are exceptions to the rule.
The only people who can sense
this strange thing happening
are the ones who are
closest to Miss Suzumiya.
But what about Haruhi?
Do you think she has any
idea what's been going on?
No, I don't think
she knows about it.
Besides, it would be
very bad for us if she did.
Although...
There is someone else who isn't
affected by feelings of déjà vu.
As a matter of fact, this person
remembers everything
that's happened since
this whole thing started.
Stop holding out
on me. Who is it?
You already know who it is.
It's Miss Nagato.
The thought entity
transcends space and time,
and so does she.
Is that really true?
[NAGATO]
It is.
Then you can
remember everything.
[NAGATO]
I can.
So then, do you know
how many times
this has happened
to us up till now?
This would be
15, 524 times so far.
[KYON gasps]
[KYON] Fifteen thousand
five-hundred twenty-four?
What do you mean 15,524?
Nagato... What are you saying?
You're completely
serious about that?
I am.
[MIKURU whimpers]
[KYON] So what you're
telling me is that
we've done the
exact same things,
every time, that many times?
[NAGATO]
Not necessarily.
Throughout 15,524 repetitions,
we did not attend
a bon festival the 2,391st
time and the 11,054th time.
We went to a bon festival
but did not go to
a goldfish scooping
booth 437 times.
--We obtained part-time jobs...
--[KYON] Okay! I got it...
[KYON] Fifteen thousand
five-hundred twenty-fourtimes...
That's what she said.
Times two weeks... That's,
uh... about... 595 years!
And she's the only
one who remembers
everything we
did all those times.
She's been repeating them,
over and over.
Nagato...
What's it like to re-live the
same things that many times?
That, has gotta be
the craziest story ever.
[KYON] The next night,
we went stargazing.
We were on the balcony
of Nagato's apartment.
And Koizumi brought
the telescope.
[HARUHI]
Oh... I'm bored.
I'm gonna look for UFOs now.
Hmm...
[KYON]
Hm.
[KYON] I wish I knew
what else she wants to do.
Well, that's
the question, isn't it?
I think I just might
have an idea though.
What if someone were to grab
Miss Suzumiya from behind,
and then whispered, "I love
you," right into her ear?
[KYON gasps]
And who's gonna be doing this?!
Who else could play
that role, other than you?
Yeah, I knew you
were gonna say that.
Like hell.
All right, how 'bout
if I give it a try?
[chuckles] Of course,
I'm only kidding.
[KOIZUMI laughs]
[KYON growls]
[metal clink]
[KYON] Anyway, the next day,
we went to the batting cages.
[HARUHI grunts]
[MIKURU yelps]
[KYON]
Hey, Nagato...
You knew about
this time loop thing
before Miss Asahina, didn't you?
[NAGATO]
Yes.
So how come you didn't
say anything about it?
My function is to observe only.
All right!
[HARUHI giggles]
I win again, losers!
[MIKURU screams]
[HARUHI laughs]
[movie screaming]
[HARUHI]
Yay!
More time!
I guess that's it. We've done
everything on our list.
Hmm... But now I'm
wondering if we did enough.
Hmm... Oh, well. That's good.
Unless there's something
else you guys wanna do?
[MIKURU whimpers]
[KYON grunts]
[HARUHI]
Hm?
Oh, okay then.
We did everything we set
out to do this summer,
so I guess that's good enough.
[KYON]
No, it's not.
You're still not satisfied.
Okay, guys,
we're done for today.
I set tomorrow
aside just in case,
but I guess you can
take the day off now.
I'll see you all at the
club room on Monday!
[KYON]
Wait, Haruhi.
There's that feeling again...
It's strong, stronger than
all the others.
I can't let Haruhi leave.
If I let her walk out that door,
we'll end up re-living
the past two weeks
again and again for a
thousand more times!
But, what should I do?
What should I say?
What's she been
saying all this time?
I don't know...
I can't... remember...
[KYON]
It's August the 31st,
and I still haven't touched
my homework yet.
Whatever... It doesn't
matter anymore.
There's no point in doing it.
I mean, we're just gonna keep
re-living the last couple
of weeks, right?
Whatever happens next,
whether tomorrow comes or not,
a different version of me
will just have to deal with it.