[gasping]
I don't think you
should move him.
[ARAKAWA]
The master's dead.
It's a fruit knife.
[KYON]
This is definitely not good.
[door creaks]
[KOIZUMI]
Hm.
The knife went all the way
through the notebook.
At least one
thing's for certain:
whoever did this
must be really strong.
[KYON] If that's the case,
then another thing's certain.
The culprit has to be a man.
And since we haven't seen
Mr. Yutaka Tamaru around today,
well...
What do you wanna do
about your little sister?
I don't want her to know
anything about this.
It looks as if we have a real
mystery on our hands here.
In fact, what we have
is a closed circle.
First impressions are
that this is a murder.
We have a room where
the door and windows
are locked from the inside.
Now then, if the room was
locked when we got to it,
how did the killer enter
the room, commit the crime,
and then leave the scene?
Uh. Kyon, did
something bad happen?
[KYON]
I told you already.
Mr. Keiichi got sick and
he's resting in his room.
So we have to stay here, okay?
So, is Mikuru sick?
[whimpering]
[HARUHI]
Kyon, can we talk?
Yuki, lock the door.
And don't open it for anyone,
no matter what. Got that?
I understand.
[HARUHI]
Do you think he was murdered?
[KYON]
That's what it looks like.
[HARUHI]
Oh, this is nuts.
I never thought something like
this would ever really happen.
[KYON]
But all you keep saying
is how badly you wanted
something mysterious to happen.
[HARUHI]
Well, yeah,
because I never really
thought it would happen!
[KYON] A murder happens
in a locked room
on a deserted island in
the middle of a typhoon.
What're the chances we'd stumble
onto something like that
while on vacation?
Then again,
maybe this is happening because
Haruhi wished for it to happen.
We're in some really
big trouble, aren't we?
[KYON] Right now, she looks
like a mischievous little boy,
worried about how an April Fools
joke went from bad to worse.
I hate to say this, but as far
as prime suspects go,
Mr. Yutaka is front and center.
No one knows where he is. It's
like he just up and vanished.
[HARUHI]
Hey, wait a minute.
Yesterday, Mikuru
told me something.
[KYON'S SISTER giggling]
[HARUHI]
Don't let it hit the water!
Nice! Here comes another one!
[KYON]
She saw them arguing?
[HARUHI] That's what
it looked like anyway.
And last night,
I overheard something.
Remember? I went to the
bathroom during the game.
I was standing
in this same spot.
[YUTAKA]
Yeah, I'm in a hurry.
Get my passport and
traveler's checks ready, okay?
[HARUHI]
Now I know what that was about.
I'll bet you anything
that he was arranging
his escape overseas.
[KYON]
But what about the sealed room?
He wasn't trying to fake
Mr. Keiichi's suicice,
so what's the point in locking
up the room like that?
[HARUHI]
Hm.
I can't just stand here and
not do anything. Come on.
We're gonna go take a closer
look in Mr. Keiichi's room.
I'm sorry. I called
the police already,
and they insisted that no one
is allowed inside the room
until they arrive on the island.
Did they say when
they would get here?
I checked the forecast,
and right now,
it looks like the weather
will start clearing up
by tomorrow afternoon.
It's safe to assume that the
police will arrive around then.
[HARUHI] Was his door
locked all night long?
[ARAKAWA]
I have no idea.
When I saw that the door
was closed, I knocked.
[HARUHI]
And that's it?
[ARAKAWA] Mr. Keiichi keeps
important work related documents
in there, and it was
forbidden to open the door
if he didn't answer it.
He was very adamant about that.
So Mr. Keiichi and Mr. Yutaka
didn't get alone
with each other?
I really wouldn't know
anything about that.
There are many things
regarding those two
with which I am not familiar.
You see, Ms. Mori and myself
have been employed here at
the mansion for only one week.
[HARUHI, KYON]
Only a week?
Ms. Mori and myself
are working part time
as Mr. Keiichi's
temporary maid and butler.
Our contract with him was brief.
It was to last a mere
two weeks out of the summer.
So, you two were just
hired to work here
and you never worked
for him before this?
Precisely.
As for the relationship
between the two brothers,
all I know is that
Mr. Yutaka was an employee
in Mr. Keiichi's company.
[KYON]
Something's not right.
[KYON] I've suddenly got a
strange feeling about this.
[HARUHI]
Mm. Uh.
Koizumi! What're you doing?
[KOIZUMI] I was just having
a look around the mansion.
I can't find Mr. Yutaka
anywhere. How 'bout you?
[HARUHI] I'm going outside to
see if the boat's still there.
[MORI] I don't think
you'll find the boat.
What do you mean?
Well, late last night,
I noticed that Mr. Yutaka seemed
as if he were in an awful hurry.
I saw him heading for
the front entrance.
[KOIZUMI] Then, are you implying
that Mr. Yutaka took the boat
and left the island?
[MORI] I'm not positive
that's what happened, no.
But that was the last
time I saw Mr. Yutaka.
About what time?
I believe it was around
one o'clock in the morning.
[KYON] One wrong step and
we'll both fall off the cliff.
Oh well, even if we
fall, when I'm with her,
I feel like my chances for
survival are pretty good.
Kyon, do you see that?
[KYON]
The boat's gone.
So Mr. Yutaka did it after all.
[KYON]
Grey skies and black seas,
it reminds me of being
inside a closed space.
There's no way
I'd ever get used to
a monochromatic world like this.
[HARUHI]
Kyon!
Someone's there! See!
Just past the rocks!
I wonder if somebody else
is out there looking.
Or maybe that's the--
the-- the murderer!
[KYON]
Haruhi! Wait!
Hey. Are you sure you saw
him come down this way?
[HARUHI] He had to.
This is the only path.
[HARUHI yelping]
[KYON]
Haruhi!
Kyon.
Kyon! Kyon!
Are you all right?
Are you alive?
Yeah, I guess I'm okay.
[HARUHI] Looks like
we're in a tough spot.
[KYON]
Yeah.
I don't think we can
make it back to the path.
[HARUHI]
Hey, over there.
[KYON] Forunately, it was
warm inside the cave.
Was it just the Earth's heat?
Or was there an underground
hot spring near by?
I know I saw a
shadow back there.
[KYON]
You sure it was even a person?
I mean, maybe it
was something else.
[HARUHI]
No way. I saw what I saw.
Although, I was thinking...
Hey, Kyon.
Do you really think
Mr. Yutaka killed Mr. Keiichi?
[KYON]
What're you getting at?
Well, I've just been
thinking about everything.
According to what Ms. Mori
said a little while ago,
Mr. Yutaka left the island
around one in the morning.
When we found Mr. Keiichi's
body, I touched him.
He was still warm. You see
what I'm getting at?
His body was still warm. That
means Mr. Keiichi was killed
right before we found his body.
So what does that mean?
Mr. Yutaka left
the mansion at night
in the middle of a typhoon,
hid till morning,
then stabbed Mr. Keiichi
before splitting the island?
[HARUHI] But I don't think
that's how it happened.
Look, even if
Mr. Keiichi was killed
an hour before we found him,
that means someone should've
seen or heard something.
Remember, we were all awake and
wandering around the place.
Someone should've
heard something.
A sound. A scream.
[KYON]
Don't you think that's strange?
I mean, you really think
that Mr. Keiichi stayed
alive for hours on end
and managed to lock himself in
his room after beind stabbed?
Think about it.
If Mr. Yutaka
wasn't the murderer,
then why'd he run--?
Wait! I got it!
Now I've got it. I know
what happened in there.
[KYON sighs]
Are you even listening to me?
[KYON] Yeah. Come on
then, let's hear it.
I'm sure Mr. Yutaka's the
one who stabbed Mr. Keiichi.
Like you said, why else
would he run away
unless he was
the guy that did it.
[KYON]
Yeah, that's true.
[HARUHI] So Mr. Yutaka stabbed
Mr. Keiichi, we know that,
but how did it happen?
I'm pretty sure
it was an accident.
They were arguing.
Mr. Yutaka lost his temper,
picked up the fruit knife,
started waving it around,
and bam!
But the knife didn't
go all the way through
to Mr. Keiichi's heart.
[HARUHI]
The notebook stopped the knife.
It was stuck in him,
but it wasn't fatal.
Here's where it
gets complicated.
Mr. Keiichi went into shocked
and passed out right
there on the spot.
When that happened,
Mr. Yutaka though he'd killed
his brother and ran.
Now comes the tricky part.
Mr. Keiichi, who wasn't dead,
stayed unconscious
throughout the night
and came to the next morning.
When he woke up,
Mr. Keiichi was in a daze.
He stood up, but his legs
were a little wobbly.
He remembered how his
brother tried to kill him,
so he staggered over to
the door to lock himself in.
This part's the
most tragic of all.
Mr. Keiichi, still dazed,
trippped over his own feet
and fell face down on the floor.
The weight of his body pushed
the knife up into his heart,
and that's what caused
Mr. Keiichi's death.
That's how it happened.
Wait a minute.
You honeslty think it all
went down that smoothly?
What're gonna do?
That's the way it happened.
Unless you've got a better idea.
I'm sure Mr. Yutaka would know
if he really killed
his brother or not.
Besides, when we got to him,
Mr. Keiichi was lying face up.
If everything happened
the way that you said,
we would've found Mr. Keiichi
lying face down, not face up.
[HARUHI]
Well, that's true, but...
No... No wait!
If that's how it
really happened, then--!
[KYON]
Hey, what's wrong?
[HARUHI]
Uh. Oh, nothing.
I guess I wasn't thinking
straight there for a second.
[KYON]
Hm?
[KOIZUMI]
Hey! Can you hear me?
You guys okay?
[KYON] It looks like
Haruhi's deduction
has completely crumbled.
But if that's the case,
what really happened?
Mr. Yutaka wasn't on the
island when Mr. Keiichi died,
which means that somebody
else is the murderer here.
[plates clattering]
[KYON]
Hm?
[KYON'S SISTER]
Which one should I eat?
--[KYON] Hey.
--[KYON'S SISTER squeals]
[KYON'S SISTER]
Kyon, you scared me! Stop it!
Stealing food, eh?
[KYON'S SISTER grunts]
I was hungry. You're mean.
I'm sorry about that.
I'll bring something up
to your room right away.
[KYON'S SISTER]
Hey, no fair.
Someone got to eat their
food before anyone else.
[MORI]
Yes, it was Mr. Arakawa.
He hasn't had a thing to
eat since this morning,
so I delivered his meal
ahead of everyone else.
You always find a way to
embarrass me, don't you?
[KYON'S SISTER whines]
[KYON]
Huh?
[KYON'S SISTER]
Is somethin' wrong?
[HARUHI]
Yuki, it's me. Open the door.
[NAGATO] I was told to not
open the door for anyone.
But it's okay now. Open up!
[NAGATO] Then I would be
opening the door for someone.
I was told not to
open it for anyone.
I take it Ms. Asahina's
still unconscious in there.
I'd assume she is,
otherwise, we'd hear her.
[HARUHI]
Yuki, when I said anyone,
I meant anyone who isn't
a member of the SOS brigade.
I mean, we're all
members, right?
[NAGATO]
That is not what I was told.
I was given an order
to lock this door
and under no circumstances
was I to open it for anyone.
But, Yuki, you
didn't say anything
when I left the room
a little while ago.
[NAGATO] My orders did not
specify the door being opened
from inside this room.
[KYON]
Hey, Nagato.
As of right now, Haruhi's
order has been retracted.
If you want, I'll just
give you a new order.
Look, my sister's out here.
Please open the door.
[HARUHI] Jeez, you don't have
to be so literal all the time.
[KYON] Maybe that was Nagato's
way of playing a joke on us.
Come on, Nagato.
No expression. Not even a blush?
Your face never changes.
You can't be serious
all the time, can you?
[KYON'S SISTER]
Thanks, Yuki!
What do you think
we should do now?
Do you wanna keep trying to find
the answers to this mystery?
Not anymore.
I guess I'm not the great
detective I thought I was.
Oh, well. We'll let the
police handle this one.
[door clicks]
I see. So that's what you were
talkin' about in the cave.
But something's strange.
If she really wanted to
play the detective so much,
why did she just suddenly drop
the whole thing like that?
I think I can understand that.
Or at least, where
she's comin' from.
Would you like to hear
my theory about it?
Yeah. I'm all ears.
Up to a certain point,
Ms. Suzumiya's
deductions are correct,
but the last part of the mystery
is where she got it wrong.
Mr. Keiichi was
stabbed by Mr. Yutaka.
However, he didn't
die right away.
Mr. Yutaka thought he
killed him, so he fled.
That's all correct.
But Mr. Keiichi came to because
of our knocking and shouts.
And just before we
tried opening the door,
he staggered over,
dazed, and locked it.
And then...
[bang]
[gasps]
That was the moment the knife
was pushed through the notebook
and into Mr. Keiichi's body.
In other words,
he was really killed...
...by the people who
rammed the door in.
Basically, it was
me and it was you
and it was also Mr. Arakawa.
I'm positive Ms. Suzumiya
figured all that out,
and that's why she
didn't say anything.
She was protecting us.
That's why she decided to keep
the truth of this
case to herself.
[KYON] Your theory does
make a lot of sense.
But it's unfortunate you had
to figure out the truth.
All I have to do is
keep you quiet,
and this whole thing goes away.
No one will ever know.
Isn't that right?
Someone help me!
Help me! Help me!
It's Koizumi.
I don't know who, but
somebody stabbed him
in the chest with
a knife, and he's dead!
What did you say?
Impossible!
[KYON'S SISTER]
Come on! Follow me!
Hurry! Hurry!
[HARUHI] I never thought
you'd be such a badass.
[KYON] Yeah. Well, just
keep your mouth shut,
and I won't have
to kill you, too.
Here's how it goes.
Mr. Yutaka snuck back
here and killed Koizumi.
Only a killer knows
their motive, right?
So we say that we thought
he seemed a little... off.
Yeah, he was acting weird.
That'll be the story.
[HARUHI] You think the police
would actually buy that?
[KYON]
Yeah, but first,
we're gonna have to stab
the corpse a few more times.
It'll make Mr. Yutaka
seem like a total psycho.
Here goes!
Wait!
Uh...
Well, it looks like
we've been found out.
The game's over and we lost.
It's true, you beat
us fair and square.
I'm sorry. I did it
'cause Kyon told me to.
Right. Now, Madame Haruhi,
supernatural genius
and number one sleuth,
will reveal the results
of her amazing detectiving.
[KYON] Why don'tcha pat yourself
on the back a little bit harder.
By now, it should be evident
that the murder mystery
was, in fact, an elaborate hoax
designed and orchestrated by
Koizumi, the Tamaru brothers,
Mr. Arakawa, and Ms. Mori.
It was an impressive plot,
especially with that
red herring at the end.
Nice observation.
It was all in fun, though.
A surprise party with
a twist, if you will.
[KYON] I'm sure she knew what
was up right from the start.
I hate to admit it,
but in the beginning,
you guys had me going.
Until I got your fake solution
where Mr. Keiichi was killed
by Kyon and the boys
busted through the door.
But I realized something.
If he really did collide
with the door hard enough
to push the knife
through to his heart,
then the door should've had
blood or scratches on it.
But there wasn't anything like
that on the inside of the door.
[KYON]
I noticed that, thank you.
Okay, but you're talkin' about
a really sturdy door there.
I mean, I don't think that
gives you very much evidence
to suspect anything.
There were other
fishy things, as well.
Like the day when Koizumi
first met Mr. Arakawa.
He said, "I haven't
seen you in so long."
But Mr. Arakawa said he only
started working here a week ago,
so it would've been
the first time they met.
You are 100% correct.
[KYON]
I figured that one out, too.
There was also that time
when we all ran up to
Mr. Keiichi's room.
You headed right down the hall
to his door, right, Koizumi?
So how could you have
known which room was his?
You told us this
was the first time
you'd ever been here, remember?
I can't believe it.
Not just one, but two mistakes?
But that's not so strange.
He could've found out
which room was mine
while the rest of you were
off doing something else.
That is correct.
However, the final clue
was the empty plate
Kyon saw in the kitchen.
I'll let Kyon take this one,
'cause I didn't
actually see the plate.
I noticed that Mr. Keiichi is
the only one on this island
who eats with a fork and knife
instead of chopsticks.
Of course, there's
the possibility
that Mr. Arakawa eats
with a fork and knife, too.
But, you see, the carrots
remained on the plate untouched.
That's when I realized that it
was actually Mr. Keiichi's meal.
If you add it all up, there's
only one conclusion to come to
and that is...
...there was never a
murder to begin with!
Mr. Keiichi was, is,
and always has been alive!
Wow!
[KYON]
I'm sure that, in her mind,
Haruhi's probably
hearing applause
that's 100 times
bigger than that.
So, we decided to
turn the tables
and put on a little
show of our own.
Then the fight I saw
on the balcony that day
was part of the act as well.
[KEIICHI]
That's right.
[YUTAKA] And that late night
phone call was a fake, too.
I was planning on lettin'
the cat out of the bag
at some point.
I'm still amazed you solved
the mystery so quickly.
Well, all of your sleuthing
caused their whole dasterdly
scheme to unravel,
that was some nice
detective work there.
Of course!
It's elementary, my dear Watson!
Elementary!
So all of this was something
your organization cooked up?
Yes. The Tamaru brothers,
Mr. Arakawa, and Ms. Mori
are all collegues of mine.
I told ya we'd have a blast!
[KOIZUMI] We believed it would
be best if Ms. Suzumiya
had a mystery to keep her mind
free of any strange thoughts,
if you know what I mean.
Well, you do.
Although, bringing your
sister along was not
a part of the plan.
I asked you at the beginning
of this trip and you told me
that the organization didn't
have anything to do with it.
Naturally!
I couldn't tell you the truth
about their involvement
right then.
If you don't mind me asking,
when did you catch
on to our scheme?
To tell you the truth,
I knew about it right
from the beginning.
[KOIZUMI]
Indeed.
An incident like this
could never happen.
Because there's no way that
Haruhi would ever really wish
for someone to be murdered.
That's just how she is.
[KOIZUMI] Then you really
trust Ms. Suzumiya, don't you?
And there's one more
thing that I wanna know.
Haruhi said she saw a shadow.
You had something to
do with that, right?
I don't know
anything about that.
I'm tellin' the truth!
The mystery solved, so there's
no reason for me to keep acting.
Well, she saw something.
What do you think it was?
Can't be...
Apparently, Ms. Suzumiya
wished for a murderer
that wasn't one of us, and that
was probably the shadow.
But if it was something Haruhi
wished for that came to life,
then...
Uh!
That means... there's some
kind of horrible... something
lurking on that
island right now.
Naw, it was probably
just the storm
that was making
Haruhi see things.
So, where do you wanna go next?
How about the Bermuda Triangle?
[KYON'S SISTER]
Is Bermuda really a triangle?