I know of one.
[KYON]
And with that,
Nagato took us to a spot
behind her apartment building.
[HARUHI laughs]
[cats meowing]
[HARUHI] Oh, look.
They're not afraid of us.
Let's see, where's a black cat?
[sighs]
Oh, well, then.
This guy's just as good.
[KYON]
She changed the concept again!
He's not exactly a black cat,
but he's better than nothin'!
Okay, Yuki. This is your
brand new familiar.
I know you'll be good friends.
[cat meowing]
[KYON]
We started shooting again.
Looks like it doesn't matter
where we shoot anymore.
Attack Mikuru with
your weird powers!
Accept your fate.
[screams]
Cut it! That's nice!
Wouldn't it be cool
if the cat could talk?
I mean, he is a
witch's cat, after all.
He should make some
snide remarks or somethin'.
[KYON]
That's absurd!
[HARUHI] I think I'm gonna
call you Shamisen.
Come on, Shamisen,
say something!
[KYON]
He's not gonna talk...
Oh, please, cat! Don't talk!
Wait, "Shamisen"?
We got some good stuff today.
Kyon, you're gonna be
responsible for that cat.
Take him home tonight,
and teach him a
coupla tricks by tomorrow.
Something simple like, I dunno,
like jumping through
a ring of fire!
[sighs]
Well, that's a wrap
for today, everyone!
We're gonna be shootin'
the big climax tomorrow!
The footage looks great,
and everybody's doin'
an awesome job!
Get some rest and we'll
hit it hard tomorrow!
[hums]
[GROUP sighs]
[KYON chuckles]
Good work today.
I'll go buy you
some cat food later.
Or maybe some dried sardines.
Either one's okay with me.
[MIKURU]
Huh?
Hey, Nagato,
was that you just now?
I was actually
talking to the cat.
Well, you asked me
a question, didn't cha?
That's why I answered.
Did I say something wrong?
Or were ya speakin'
to someone else?
Japanese Bobtail...
Quite the surprise, isn't it?
That's probably the last thing
you should be surprised by.
[MIKURU]
That's amazing!
I never thought
I'd see a talking cat.
[SHAMISEN]
I don't understand why
everyone here is so
surprised that I'm talking.
[KYON] He's a mutant cat...
No, a cat monster!
But looking at it
from your perspective,
I can see how
the sounds I'm making
might seem like
human speech to you people.
And if that's the case,
how can you be sure that
the sounds coming out of me
mean the same as the words
you think I'm saying?
It might be gibberish, you know?
But the fact that you're
answering my questions
is proof you understand
what I'm saying.
Look, it's possible
that these sounds
only happpen to seem like
answers to your questions.
Just because I reply to you
doesn't mean I know
what I'm talkin' about.
So basically what
you're saying is that
even if two people are talking,
it doesn't mean they're
actually having a conversation.
You know, that's true.
Even if two people
are in a conversation
and believe they
understand each other,
there's no guarantee they're
truly expressing the ideas
behind the words they're using.
He's right.
People can say one thing
and mean another.
[KYON]
Oh, shut up.
The cat does bring up a good
point though, doesn't he?
[KYON]
I'm sorry,
but do you think you
could stop talking, too?
As it stands right now,
the situation is pretty bad.
It seems we've underestimated
Miss Suzumiya's
abilities yet again.
Sorry, I don't
think I understand.
There's a chance
the reality of the movie
might very well become
the new day-to-day
reality of this world.
If Miss Suzumiya
says to herself,
"I'd like to shoot a scene
where a giant meteor crashes,"
it might actually happen.
[MIKURU]
What are we gonna do?
We have to keep her
from using her imagination
from destroying our world.
As it is right now,
she's unconsciously
confusing what's real
with what's not real.
It's hard to stop her
when she's on a roll.
Miss Suzumiya's
strange powers...
...are being filtered and
given life through the world
of the movie she's making.
If we want to prevent
anything bad from happening,
we have to figure out how to
make her accept
that it's all fiction.
Then, we have to help her
turn the story around
into something more reasonable.
That's great, but how
are we gonna explain
a talking cat to her?
I really don't think we should
explain anything to her.
If we did that, we'd find
ourselves in a new reality
where every single cat would
suddenly be able to talk.
But you see, something like that
isn't possible in our world.
What about the fact
that you guys are here?
True.
The three of us wouldn't
be sitting here with you
if it weren't for Miss Suzumiya
and her abilities.
The same goes for
the talking cat.
[KYON] Can't we do
something about this?
[KOIZUMI]
If this were a fantasy world,
you wouldn't need explanations
for all the phenomena around us.
But if we tell her that talking
cats and Mikuru Beams exist,
then the reality of
this world will change.
Do you understand
what that means?
The reality of our current world
would suddenly change.
It would turn into a place where
supernatural phenomena exist
and are the norm.
So what are we gonna do?
We just have to find a suitable
ending to the movie--
One that Miss Suzumiya
will accept, of course.
Sure, if one exists.
Well, actually,
there is one type of ending
that can take
any nonsensical plot
and turn it into something
that makes perfect sense
to an audience.
Well? What is it?
"It was a dream."
No joke, that was the ending
I was talking about.
Do you honestly think
Haruhi's gonna believe that?
I didn't say it
was gonna be easy.
But if she believes it's the
best way to end the movie,
our problems will be solved.
The trick is to pitch
the concept to her,
so that she accepts an ending
where everything is explained
as a dream, a lie, or a mistake.
[KYON] You might think
that's the best solution.
And even I might be inclined
to agree with you on that.
But what's Haruhi gonna say?
[grunts]
[KYON]
Here's the deal:
No talking in the house.
You're a cat, and you're
gonna act like a cat, got it?
[SHAMISEN] Not quite sure
what "act like a cat" means,
but if that's what you want,
I'll do my best.
[KYON]
Don't talk!
If you wanna say something,
say "meow."
[SHAMISEN]
Meow.
[giggles]
Kitty, kitty,
kitty, kitty, kitty.
[SHAMISEN]
"Meow."
[KYON]
There we go.
Okay, I guess
I'll see you later then.
Yeah, you got it.
[KYON] It was just a few days
before the festival,
and an atmosphere of utter chaos
was slowly spreading
through the school,
as if it were somehow connected
to Haruhi's excitement.
[SOLDIER-STYLED MAN]
Hurry!
We've got to find the legendary
crystal, crescent orb!
[DWARF MAN]
Yeah, yeah, yeah! [laughs]
[KYON]
And, if a couple of people
from another world
decided to show up,
I doubt they'd feel
out of place here.
[TSURUYA]
Hey, Kyon!
Mikuru wants to
tell you something.
Go ahead, Mikuru,
give it to him!
[MIKURU]
Okay...
Um, this is for our...
Here!
It's a coupon for
the yakisoba cafe
our class is doing
for the festival.
Thank you, I'll definitely come.
And if you wanna bring
some friends along,
you can invite them, too.
Guess we'll be seeing you later!
[giggles]
[KYON]
Oh?
Can we talk?
Is everything okay?
It's just... if I say
what I'm about to say,
it might sound like
I don't trust Koizumi.
But, um...
I have to say it anyway.
Uh-huh?
It's just that... Um...
I don't think the same as him.
How do I say it?
I've got... a different opinion
about things than Koizumi.
Are you talking about his theory
that Haruhi's a god
or something?
[exhales]
[MIKURU] There's no doubt
that Miss Suzumiya
has the power to alter
the reality of the present.
But I don't think she can change
the actual structure
of this world.
The world has always
been this way.
[KYON]
So what you're saying is that
you believe
the complete opposite
of what Koizumi told me.
[MIKURU]
I'm pretty sure Miss Nagato
has a different opinion, too.
Um... I know this might give you
a bad impression
of Koizumi as a person.
I'm really sorry, but...
It's just that...
You shouldn't believe
what he says.
Wait! No! I didn't
mean it that way!
Um... I'm sorry!
I'm no good at
explaining things,
and I'm not allowed to say much.
Oh... But still, I--
I think I understand.
You don't think there's any way
Haruhi could be a god.
Your explanation is way easier
to understand than Koizumi's,
that's for sure.
Thank you.
Still, I hope
you understand that
I don't have anything
against Koizumi as a person.
I just wanna be clear
about that, okay?
[BOTH chuckle]
This is what Mikuru Asahina
believes to be true:
Haruhi Suzumiya
did not create the world.
The world as it currently exists
has always been this way.
Psychic powers and time travel,
extraterrestrial life forms
and supernatural beings,
are all tangible
elements within reality.
Haruhi Suzumiya's purpose is
to unconsciously discover them.
Her ability to do so activated
approximately three years ago.
She is able to
detect the unusual,
but she can never
recognize their existence.
That is because there
are elements in place
which prevent her from
discovering the truth.
That would be us.
[KYON]
Hm?
Haruhi never notices the weird
things going on around her.
Do Miss Asahina and Koizumi
have different reasons
for keeping her
in the dark like that?
[NAGATO]
Yes.
Miss Asahina was sent by her
superiors to this time plane
to protect the time
plane where she is from.
[KYON] I think she just
said something important,
but she's so casual about it.
[NAGATO] Itsuki Koizumi and
Mikuru Asahina will never agree
on their respective
interpretations.
To them, any theory which
diverges from their own
disrupts the logic
of their theory
and negates their existence.
Hold on!
I remember Koizumi telling me
he didn't get his ESPer powers
until three years ago,
is that true?!
There is no evidence that
what Itsuki Koizumi says
is actually the truth.
[KYON]
She's right. There's no proof.
Koizumi's theory is just
a convenient explanation
for all the weird stuff
that's happened to me.
So who knows
if that's the truth.
The same goes for
Miss Asahina's theory.
There's no guarantee
her version of things
is the right one either.
[KYON]
What's your opinion about it?
Who's telling the truth?
And what about the stuff
you were telling me before,
you know, about auto-evolution?
Regardless of which theory
I present you with,
there is no way for you
to determine its truth.
Why not?!
[NAGATO]
There is no guarantee that
what I have been saying
is the truth either.
[NAGATO]
Not for you, anyway.
[door clicks]
[KYON]
I don't get it.
But who would?!
Koizumi and Nagato
need to figure out
how to explain this to me,
so I can understand.
The only person who thought
the shoot was going well
was Haruhi.
Of course, this made the gloom
on the faces of Koizumi,
Miss Asahina, and myself
that much gloomier.
[MIKURU whimpers]
[KYON]
At some point during the day,
the toy guns started
firing water bullets
instead of BBs.
Haruhi brought different colored
contacts for Miss Asahina,
which made her shoot even
more dangerous things at me.
And each time she did,
Nagato bit her.
A couple of days after the
cheery trees started to blossom,
the petals fell off.
The white pigeons at the shrine
had turned into
passenger pigeons,
which had been extinct
for a while now.
And even the seasons seemed
to be completely out of whack.
[TV ANNOUNCER] The current
high for Nikkei Features
has risen to 9,360 yen...
[KYON'S SISTER]
Hey, Kyon!
Your friend's here!
[KYON]
Hm?
Hm.
Hi.
It's clear that
Miss Suzumiya doesn't care
about certain details
like plot or foreshadowing.
And I doubt that
she's even come up with
a proper ending
for the film yet.
Who knows, the movie
might end unfinished.
That could be a big problem,
couldn't it?
Only if the reality
of this world
suddenly becomes
a fictional one.
You know, I've been meaning
to tell you something.
The organization I belong to and
the group Miss Asahina's with
aren't the only ones
with theories
centered around
Miss Suzumiya and her powers.
There are many others.
I'd love to tell you all about
the conflicts and bloody battles
going on behind the scenes.
Or at least give you
the condensed version.
There's alliance and betrayal,
sabotage and sneak attacks,
destruction and slaughter.
Each group locked in a fight
to the death, trying to survive.
Of course, none of it
has anything to do with you
or Miss Suzumiya.
Don't you worry about that.
And I'd prefer it if
Miss Suzumiya
never found out about it either.
I wouldn't wanna do anything
that would cause her any pain.
If I held her up
to my standards,
I'd say Miss Suzumiya
has a lovable character.
Oh, and so do you, of course.
Is there some reason that you're
telling me all this stuff?
There isn't any reason at all;
just making an observation.
It's not important anyway,
and not much fun to discuss.
You're right about that.
I'm definitely not having fun.
There's something else
you should hear
that won't be fun either.
Have you ever wondered
why Miss Asahina's a part
of our little group?
I mean, the real reason
why she's with us?
Her role in all this is to
entice you over to her side.
The only person I know
who can get Miss Suzumiya to
listen to them is you, isn't it?
You see, that's why
it's so important
to get a hold over you.
With her good looks,
her childish behavior,
and the way she
constantly allows herself
to be subjected to Miss
Suzumiya's unreasonable demands,
it's all just
an elaborate scheme
to get your attention, you know?
[KYON sighs]
Getting tired of your jokes now.
[KOIZUMI chuckles]
Oh, I'm sorry.
I guess I don't have the
talent to keep a joke going,
even if I started it.
I was kidding, of course.
Had you going, though.
The pressure of my class play,
along with
Miss Suzumiya's movie,
are starting to get to me.
At least,
that's my interpretation.
And, if closed space were
to appear on top of all that,
I think I'd probably pass out.
In fact, that's the reason for
the request I'm about to make.
Please help.
You have to try to put an end
to all the strange phenomena
that's being caused by
Miss Suzumiya's movie.
Let me get this straight:
You want me to make sure
Haruhi thinks that everything
she's been putting in her movie
is a product of her imagination,
is that right?
Yes, exactly.
It'll only work
if she believes it.
And it has to happen before
we finish shooting the movie.
[KOIZUMI]
All of us are counting on you.
[KYON sighs]
What the heck's with that guy?
He just made me
responsible for everything!
Yeah, but still...
[sighs]
I guess I can't just ignore it.
God, this is so annoying!
A movie's a movie,
and reality's reality.
They're two totally
different things.
It's pretty obvious.
So why is it up to me
to convince her of it?
Koizumi said the movie
has to be a dream,
but there's gotta
be another way.
Huh?
[KYON]
The next day, I cornered Haruhi
and pitched the concept
I had in mind.
Then after discussing it,
she agreed.
[HARUHI]
Okay! Cut!
Great job, guys!
We're only a couple shots
away from finishing this thing.
Everyone's been great,
I mean it!
Let's meet in the club room
first thing tomorrow morning
for a sneak preview!
[MIKURU cries]
[HARUHI]
Oh, Mikuru! Why are you crying?!
Save those tears of yours for
when you get the Palme d'Or
and the Oscar!
We should all be happy
we made this together!
[nervous laugh]
[KYON] The final battle
between Mikuru and Yuki
awakens Itsuki Koizumi's powers.
And this deus ex machina power
that no one understands
knocks Yuki out into space!
With that, the curtain
lowers on our story.
The end!
[KOIZUMI]
Looks like it's finally over.
[laughs]
But now that we're done,
it feels like it ended
rather quickly, doesn't it?
You know that old saying,
"Time flies when
you're having fun"?
Although in our case,
I wonder who was having fun.
Beats me.
[chuckles]
I hope it won't be
too much trouble
if I leave the rest
for you to handle.
I can't stop thinkin'
about that play I'm in.
Unlike a movie, if I'm up on
stage and I mess up a line,
there are no second takes.
Oh, there's one more thing.
My organization's very grateful.
They thank you.
And I thank you, too.
[HARUHI]
Okay! Shout it loud!
Our movie's gonna be
a Hollywood blockbuster!
We'll win the Golden Bear
and a Gold Lion at Cannes!
[HARUHI]
That was great!
Now, point to the future!
Oh, brother...
[MIKURU]
Okay...
[KYON] To tell you the truth,
up until the very end,
I didn't have a pixel of an
idea what kind of movie
Haruhi was actually
trying to make.
And I bet you already knew this,
but there wasn't enough time
to finish the visual effects.
Not that I was capable of
doing stuff like that
in the first place.
[KYON]
And Haruhi didn't like that.
We can't show this picture
until all the effects are done,
so it's up to you!
Now figure it out!
But the festival's tomorrow.
I'm running on fumes here!
You can make the deadline
if you work through the night.
Pull an all-nighter
if you have to.
I'm gonna stay too
and help you out.
[KYON]
When all was said and done,
Haruhi wasn't much help at all.
[sighs]
[gasps]
[KYON]
Huh?
[growls]
[KYON]
To be perfectly fair though,
I sorta fell asleep, too.
[HARUHI]
Kyon.
Kyon! Come on! Wake up!
[KYON yells]
[groans]
So? How did it turn out?
[KYON] There wasn't any point
staying overnight.
The thing still isn't finished.
[MIKURU]
...from the future!
[music playing]
Wow!
[KYON]
Huh?
[MIKURU yells]
[HARUHI]
I'm surprised.
Considering you did all
the effects last minute,
it's pretty good!
[KYON]
It wasn't me.
Someone else must've done it.
Odds are, Nagato.
Next, Koizumi.
Miss Asahina? Doubt it.
Or, it could've been someone
who hasn't shown up yet.
There's a scary thought.
Good morning.
How'd it turn out?
I hope you didn't
stay up too late.
Good morning, everyone.
[HARUHI]
Good morning, guys!
Guess what we have to show you?
Made with blood,
sweat, and tears,
it's a full-blown spectacle!
[MIKURU]
Wow! You finished it!
That's wonderful, really!
[HARUHI chuckles]
Now, it's time for us
to watch it together!
Aw, Mikuru! You were so awesome!
I bet you're gonna have
a lotta fans from this!
They're gonna eat you up!
[KYON]
The arts festival had begun.
And there was
nothing more for me to do.
All the fears we had
of our reality changing
have disappeared.
I knew that for a fact because
Shamisen stopped talking.
[KYON]
Oh, yeah... That reminds me.
It had been a while since
I'd seen all those guys
who were dressed kinda strange.
I don't think they were
in any of the plays
the other classes
were putting on.
Who the heck were they, anyway?
[KYON] The movie ended with
a bit of narration by Haruhi.
I convinced her it would be cool
if she gave a speech about
how the story wasn't real,
that it was all
supposed to be fun.
Those were the magic words
that cancelled out
everything that happened.
[HARUHI] ...are fictional
as well. It's all made up.
Even if it resembles someone,
it's probably
just a coincidence.
Oh! Except for the commercials.
Shop at Ohmori Electronics
and Yamatsuchi's Model Shop
for great deals!
Stop by and buy!
Huh? I gotta say it again?
This story is a work of fiction.
All character names,
organizations, incidents,
and any other names--
Hey, Kyon! Why do I have
to say all this stuff anyway?
I mean, it's totally obvious!
[KYON]
It might not seem like
anything ever gets
under Haruhi's skin,
but the truth is,
there's one thing
that bothers her--
The world's too normal.
Now, you're probably wondering
what a person like her
would consider "not normal."
The answer is: the supernatural.
For example, she'd say,
"Why haven't I seen a ghost yet?
What's up with that?"
It's something I'm sure
is always on her mind.
I've got something really
important to tell you.
Okay.
A while ago, you said you
wanted to hang out with
aliens, time travelers,
and ESPers.
Are you still into those things?
Yeah, I am.
But why are you
bringing that up?
Because I know for a fact
that aliens, time travelers,
and ESPers are real,
and they're even closer
than you think.
[HARUHI]
Hm?
Really? Closer than I think?
Well, the only people
I can think of
who'd fit that description would
be Yuki, Mikuru, and Koizumi.
I mean, could there be anyone
closer to me than those guys?
Actually...
That's pretty much exactly
what I was gonna tell you.
What?! Are you crazy
or something?
Do you honestly think
I'd believe something
as convenient as that?
[KYON] Well, normally,
that would be true...
[HARUHI]
Okay then, fine.
Who's who?
[KYON]
You're gonna love this.
Yuki Nagato is an alien.
She's with the Data Integration
Entity or... something.
Anyway, she's like an agent
for this entity thing.
Uh--Oh yeah!
Humanoid interface,
that's what
she said she was.
[HARUHI scoffs]
Really? How 'bout Mikuru?
[KYON] Miss Asahina's
a little easier to explain.
Here goes:
She's a time traveler.
She's from the future
and travels through time,
a time traveler.
[HARUHI]
What time is she from?
[KYON] I don't know, she won't
tell me, says it's "classified."
[chuckles]
Uh-huh. I think I got it.
So, you believe me then.
Next, you're probably
gonna tell me
Koizumi's the ESPer
in the group.
Am I right or am I right?
Yeah! That's exactly what
I was gonna say to you next!
[HARUHI]
Mm-hmm.
[KYON]
[HARUHI]
Hm.
[KYON]
[HARUHI]
Hm...
[KYON sighs]
[HARUHI]
Hm...
[KYON]
Hm...?
Don't mess with me!
Hmph.
[KYON]
What a nut!
She picks the weirdest things
to get all rational about.
[KYON] Everything would
be so much easier if,
for once, she would
just believe me!
[SERVER]
Hey, thanks! Come again!
[KYON]
But, it's probably for the best.
If Haruhi ever found out about
all the strange phenomena
happening around her,
we'd all be in big trouble.
Oh, brother...