[BISHAMON sobbing]
It's happened again.
How many members of
my family are dead?
I don't know if I can bear this!
I don't get it.
Yato hasn't killed
anybody tonight.
So who did kill them?
The mastermind of
this little scheme.
[YUKINE]
Huh?
[YATO] A Regalia who conspired
against his own master.
We know you're there.
No reason to keep
lurking in the shadows.
[bell jingles]
[footsteps]
[KUGAHA]
Aww, poor things!
They're barely clinging to life.
You should put them
out of their misery.
Eh? Go on, Lord Yato.
Doctor... Kuga...?
Kuga, huh? So that's your name.
Thought I'd be seeing you again.
Quite an elaborate
plan you cooked up.
[KUGAHA] This would've
happened eventually,
one way or the other.
Bishamon hounding
you all the time
has to have gotten old by now.
Here's your chance
to be free of her.
I don't understand why
you would hesitate.
Haven't you already massacred
a clan of Regalia?
What's one more?
It was you? Why?
You're still a little
out of it, aren't you?
Maybe I should explain
what's happening.
The fact of the matter is
you caused this. You.
By needlessly granting names
to Regalia after Regalia.
You're a failure as
both master and god.
Knowing that,
do you truly believe
you can continue as you are?
The name Bishamon is supposed
to belong to the
noblest, fiercest,
and mightiest god of war.
A model of godhood who uses
only the finest Regalia
to expel evil from the world.
But instead, we have you.
A god who strokes her own
ego by granting names
to worthless, broken souls
and is then forced
to drug herself so that
she can endure their pain.
A god obsessed with
a personal grudge,
dragged her Regalia into it,
and then shamefully,
disgracefully, was corrupted.
Takamagahara has been desecrated
by your defilement.
You've become detestable.
Evil.
Look at what
you've done tonight.
You destroyed your
own Blessed Vessel.
No one will ever willingly
follow you again.
I can see your tears,
but tell me this,
Lady Bishamon:
for whom do you weep?
Do you weep for yourself?
If so, you're
utterly despicable.
However, if it is for the sake
of your Regalia that
you shed those tears,
then I don't need to tell
you what must be done.
You already know.
[KURAHA]
You filthy, traitorous snake.
You're actually asking
our master to die?
To end her own life?
Of course I am.
I'm hurt that you would
call me a traitor, though.
Through it all, I have
only ever had Bishamon's
best interest in mind.
Our master deserves the
chance to be born anew.
And the proper guidance
that I will provide.
Yeah?
[YATO] You know what I think
you're really saying?
"Look at me. Pay more
attention to me, Mommy!"
That's what I'm hearing.
What?
[YATO] If you want
your master's approval,
then do your job well. If you
wanna oppose your master,
then take it up
with your exemplar.
People distinguish
between right and wrong,
but those concepts
don't apply to gods.
And do you know why that is?
Because every action that
a god takes is the right one.
[KUGAHA grunts]
You know what it's like,
you forcing her reincarnation?
It's like a spoiled kid
trying to kill his parents.
You are something
less than human.
You'll pay for what
you've done, Kugaha.
I promise that.
[KUGAHA]
Come forth, Goki!
A mask? What is this?
[roars]
I brought you here to help me.
If you're not going to kill
her, then I will kill you.
I'll end your very existence.
[SKELETON PHANTOM 2A growls]
[MINEHA]
We should get out of here.
What are you waiting for?
If we can get to the
master's purifying spring,
I think we'll be safe.
[FUMIHA]
Why bother?
You saw what happened.
All my friends are dead.
Our master's gonna die, too.
I don't wanna live anymore,
either. What's the point?
What do you mean,
"What's the point?"
Our master saved us.
We owe it to her to
survive if we can.
She gave us names.
She carried our pain.
She made this place
a home for us.
[FUMIHA] It won't ever
feel like home here again.
[MINEHA] You're saying that
because you can't see
past your grief right now.
You're sad because so
many people are dead.
I know. I feel the same.
But us dying too
won't help, Fumiha.
That's the name our
master gave you, isn't it?
Let's go, Fumiha. Let's try.
[SKELETON PHANTOM 2A]
Let's go. Let's go, Fumiha.
Let's die.
[roars]
[SKELETON PHANTOM 2A]
Die.
Now or never! Are you with me?
Yeah!
[SKELETON PHANTOM 2A]
Die!
Get back, Hiyori.
You didn't get what you want,
so now you're throwin'
a tantrum, huh?
[KUGAHA]
Shut up!
You wouldn't
understand my reasons.
Not a nobody like you, Yato god!
[SKELETON PHANTOM 6A grunts]
[YATO grunts]
Are you okay?
[KUGAHA] Ha, ha! Look at you,
bested by a measly Phantom.
You are a poor, pitiful
excuse for a god.
Blinded to your duty by
your devotion to people.
You're a useless fool!
Just who the hell
do you think you are?
It's over!
I thought you would
be a useful tool,
but obviously, I was wrong.
You're finished now,
lowly god of calamity!
[grunting]
[roars]
A lowly god, am I? Right.
You know, I used to
hear that all the time.
Yukine, now!
I'm ready!
[roars]
O' masked one who
seeks to scourge.
Your desecrations
shall not be allowed!
Hear me. I am the god, Yato.
I now lay thee waste
with the Sekki,
and expel thy vast
defilement. I cleanse thee!
[roars]
Rend!
[grunting]
[YATO] Yes, you were
very wrong about me.
I'm nobody's puppet.
Certainly not yours.
[YATO]
What are you doing, Bishamon?
[BISHAMON]
I won't let you touch him, Yato.
He is family. Just as
all my Regalia are.
[gasps]
You're serious.
Tell me, Kugaha.
Do you remember
the day I named you?
I do. Quite well.
[BISHAMON]
It was cold. Snowing.
I found you along the wharf.
You had nowhere to go.
You soon proved your skill
at concocting remedies.
and you were happy to share
your knowledge with others.
You became a close
adviser to Kazuma.
And in your capacity
as our curer,
you competently looked
after my health.
[sneezes]
[BISHAMON] Your ministrations
often helped me
to forget my pain.
But that was wrong of me.
I shouldn't have forgotten it.
The root of my pain
was your own.
How could I lose sight of that?
I am truly sorry.
What? I don't want your apology!
This is disgraceful! Bishamon.
I swear on your name.
I've never once
tainted you. Not ever!
He's really trying
to play innocent,
after all he's done?
Except he isn't lying.
She would have been
stung if he was.
[BISHAMON] You seem to be
telling the truth.
You truly believed that,
by forcing me to reincarnate,
you would be doing
the just thing.
In which case, you've
acted righteously.
[KUGAHA]
Yes! Exactly!
I've done nothing wrong!
My actions were just!
[AKIHA] Lady Bishamon!
Please, we need you inside!
A masked Phantom is
attacking everybody!
[gasps]
You know who brought it here.
Him. "Just actions?" He called
a freakin' Phantom here
and you're gonna let him live?
[BISHAMON]
Truly?
[BISHAMON gasps]
I feel an ache in my heart.
Is this your pain, Kugaha?
Enough. Out of my way!
[BISHAMON]
What you asked before.
If I could really
continue on like this.
To be honest, I'm not sure.
But for now at least,
I will do what
must be done. Rokki!
I'd forgotten.
You're a balance scale.
Please don't!
I apologize for putting
you to so little use.
Wait! No! Don't do this!
It was for you! Everything I
have done has been for you!
It's over now.
Rokki! I release you!
Stop! No!
Lady Bishamon!
[YATO]
After all that, you let him go.
[BISHAMON]
It was my decision.
Now go. Do as you wish.
Akiha. Look after the others.
I will.
[YATO]
You're just gonna run away?
I am not.
Please, Yato. Let's leave.
Not yet.
There's still a Masked One
here to deal with.
Let her go.
She needs to do it herself.
[sighs]
[YUKINE]
Hiyori! Are you okay?
[HIYORI]
Yeah.
Damn, Kazuma. He
must've told Hiyori.
[YATO]
Hey! Bishamon!
You shouldn't feel
bad about this, okay?
Not at all. Listen to me.
No matter what anyone might say,
what you're going
in there to do...
...is right!
--[REGALIA whimpering]
--[SOHA] Everyone stay calm.
The monster shouldn't
be able to reach us here.
--[rumbling]
--[REGALIA gasp]
[REGALIA scream]
[SKELETON PHANTOM 2A]
Die.
Die. Die. Die. Die. Die.
[roars]
You see, it's all right.
We'll be safe here.
[SOHA]
Impossible!
It shouldn't be able to walk
through the water
in this spring.
[roars]
Come, Ruki!
[SKELETON PHANTOM 2A groans]
I hoped you'd come!
I'm sorry I'm late.
I hate to ask this of you.
I know it isn't a pleasant task.
[RIHA]
Please!
If a rusted swordstick
like me can be of use,
I'm happy to help any
way I can, my lady.
Those who the monster has
eaten are gone forever.
I would never forgive myself if
I let these youngsters suffer
the same fate as them.
[BISHAMON]
Thank you.
[PHANTOM REGALIA 6A]
Help, my lady!
[PHANTOM REGALIA 6B]
It hurts!
[PHANTOM REGALIA 6C]
My lady!
[PHANTOM REGALIA 6D]
Please help us!
[BISHAMON]
I hurt with you.
The root of my pain is your own.
I make you this promise:
[growls]
[BISHAMON grunts]
I will end your suffering!
[KAZUMA]
My comrades. I'm sorry.
Once again, I've lost my way.
My mistake has hurt you all.
I failed as your exemplar.
I failed to protect her,
just like before.
--[KAZUMA gasps]
--[CLERIC 4A] Who was it?
Who tainted her?
For all we know, it was you!
Excuse me?
[REGALIA screaming]
--[REGALIA 4O grunts]
--[CLERIC 4A yelps]
[REGALIA grunting, yelling]
[panting]
[BISHAMON] Go, Kazuma.
Stay away. It will spread.
[KAZUMA] This is our fault.
We've betrayed you, Master.
What can we do?
How can we ever atone for this?
[BISHAMON]
Promise me.
If this is the end for me...
If I die, will you be my
Regalia again when I am reborn?
I won't let you die.
[KAZUMA] I will protect you.
No matter what it takes!
No matter what I must become.
Whatever happens,
I will keep you safe.
I swear it! I swear it!
[GIANT PHANTOM 4A growls]
[REGALIA screaming]
[gasping]
[KAZUMA]
It is we who make mistakes.
That is a human failing.
Veena. Whatever you do,
it is always right.
[yells]
[SKELETON PHANTOM 2A growls]
[BISHAMON yells]
[PHANTOM REGALIA 6A]
Please... my... lady!
[BISHAMON]
I'm sorry.
[SKELETON PHANTOM 2A groans]
I'm sorry, but I will
do what must be done!
Now, it's over!
[SKELETON PHANTOM 2A roars]
Goodbye, my children.
[BISHAMON]
I'm so sorry.
You're awake.
How long has it been?
It seems like your health
is greatly improved, Master.
You haven't called me "Master"
in a long time. Were you
dreaming of the old days?
You're right, though.
I am feeling better.
[AIHA screaming]
[BISHAMON] Aiha successfully
underwent an ablution
to remove the blight.
The other Regalia
have labored untiringly.
It is true that we've
lost many of our kin.
But many are still alive,
and they are thriving.
[BISHAMON]
They're working hard.
Starting over from
scratch together.
It makes me happy to see.
[KAZUMA]
Master.
[BISHAMON]
Mm?
I must ask you to release me.
I've disgraced you twice now.
I don't deserve
to be your Regalia.
Like the old woman said
when I transformed.
[KAZUMA]
I only end up hurting you.
[BISHAMON]
Yes, but I don't mind.
[KAZUMA gasps]
Any of you could hurt
me, sooner or later.
It's part of being master.
[BISHAMON]
You are all so kind.
When you hurt me,
you feel hurt in turn.
That's why I've always
tried to hide my pain.
I worried that
complaining about it
would only increase the
guilt you already felt.
I need to change
that, but honestly,
I don't know where to start.
This is how I've
always done things.
I need you. Be my
guide, Kazuma.
I'll lose my way
again. I know I will.
You're allowed to make mistakes.
Can't you accept that?
My lady...
[knocking]
[TSUGUHA] We brought it,
my lady. Sorry it took so long.
[KINUHA] Oh! Kazuma's
awake! That's wonderful.
I should let everyone know.
[TSUGUHA] He looks so different
without his glasses, doesn't he?
[AIHA] Oh, yeah! Ten years
younger at least.
[MINEHA]
What if he wore pink glasses?
[AIHA giggles]
I don't think so!
[TSUGUHA] Hey, we started
an exchange diary
that we take turns writing
notes in. Here, see?
I think you should write
something in it, too.
[BISHAMON]
Eh-hem. Don't laugh, all right?
It's just an idea I had.
To get to know you all better.
[AIHA]
Tsuguha! Why'd you write that?
What's wrong with
my romance stories?
[TSUGUHA] Like I said in
the diary, they're obnoxious.
I just tell it like it is.
[AIHA]
They're not obnoxious!
[TSUGUHA]
You know what's worse?
The awful pun someone attempted.
That's not an appropriate
response, Master.
What? Really? It isn't?
[KAZUMA laughs]
[ALL but KAZUMA]
Huh?
[laughs] No, it most
definitely is not.
[chuckles] There, you see?
I'm simply lost
without my guide.
Kazuma. I hereby
lift your exile.
Come back. Say you'll
be my exemplar again.
[KAZUMA]
I will.
[NORA] Kugaha turned
out to be a failure.
What a shame.
All he could manage
was a jingle.
Never any real music.
[gasps]
[bell jingles]
I'm to bring Yato here?
Yes. I'll do that, Father.
[KAZUMA]
An exchange diary, huh?
I wonder what I should write.
Let's see, "Dearest Veena"...
No, I can't say that!
[TSUGUHA]
On the next Noragami Aragoto:
"How to Worship a God."
[KAZUMA] Tsuguha! How
long've you been there?
[TSUGUHA]
The whole time.