[banging]
[gasps] Where are we?
I wish I knew.
We were knocked out.
I didn't see how we got
here. And we're trapped.
The door's been scourged
from the outside.
This sounds like
a classic kidnapping!
[KAZUMA]
Uh, yes.
I've been trying to free us,
but nothing's worked.
[HIYORI chuckles]
[gasps]
[HIYORI] The kidnappers
made one serious oversight.
Those fools.
They should have known
better than to kidnap me!
Huh?
[HIYORI]
Let's go! Jungle Savate!
[screams]
[KAZUMA]
Are... you okay?
And I've got my
advancement exam tomorrow!
I'm sorry.
You should never have
been dragged into this.
It's okay... Really.
I hope Yato's all right, though.
He was in pretty bad shape.
Knowing him, he'll go
and push himself too hard.
[KAZUMA]
At this point, you should really
be more concerned
about yourself.
[HIYORI]
Hm?
This is serious.
We're both sealed off
from the outside.
You can't remain this
way for too long...
...or you'll die.
[gasps]
[HIYORI'S MOM] What happened?
Did she faint again?
[HIYORI'S DAD]
Try to stay calm, dear.
She isn't hurt anywhere.
She's just asleep.
[HIYORI'S MOM]
But look at her!
[HIYORI'S DAD] She's probably
worn out from studying.
Why don't you
stay here with her?
She's breathing shallower
than I'd like.
To be safe, let's prep
an oxygen ventilator.
God, I beg you, let her be okay.
Let her come back to us.
[HIYORI] I'm really going
to die here? No. I can't.
It's my fault. I should
have prevented this.
But still. What happened there?
Kugaha clearly had his
sights set on you. But, why?
Plus, my invocation
had no effect on him.
I shackled him with the
"Kuga" name, and yet...
Shackled him with a name?
[KAZUMA]
Yes.
For Regalia, a name is
a bestowment and a scourge
from the god we call master.
Both things at once, in simpler
terms, it's a gift and a curse.
Even for you? Your
name... is a curse?
[KAZUMA]
Yes.
Names dwell within those
to whom they refer.
Invocations are
based on that fact.
Yet, when I invoked his name,
Kugaha remained unaffected.
Could it be? Is he...?
[HIYORI]
Eh?
[KAZUMA]
No. I can't know that.
All that's certain is
that he's betrayed Veena.
Using their names
to employ Phantoms
and scourged weapons,
Kugaha and Aiha have defiled
their god-given gifts!
[KAZUMA]
How could they?
Names are so precious to us!
Kazu-ma.
Why are you the only one
whose name ends differently?
Kugaha, Aiha, Suzuha...
Their names all end in "ha."
Why does yours end in "ma"?
[KAZUMA] It's something
a lot of the gods do.
They'll add a common character
to all their Regalia's names.
For some, it's like
a brand of sorts.
For others, it is a way
to foster a familial bond.
Veena currently
unifies her Regalia
under the "Ha" Clan name.
[HIYORI]
"Currently"?
[KAZUMA] Yes. The previous
clan shared the "Ma" name.
I'm the sole survivor
of that clan.
The "ma" in Kazuma is a relic.
What? What happened
to all the rest?
They were annihilated.
Yato slaughtered
the entire clan.
[BISHAMON] Yato. If you want
Kazuma, you can have him.
Go ahead and make him a Nora.
May he betray you as he did me.
When next we meet,
I will eradicate your name.
Not even a shred of a
memory will remain of you.
[YUKINE]
What? Bishamon took Hiyori?
But, why? That's crazy! What
would Bishamon want with her?
How could you let
this happen, Yato?
[gasps]
[YUKINE]
It's my fault.
Never mind that.
Let's go kick some ass.
Yeah!
Wha-- Hey!
Hold on! You're not
planning to assault
Bishamon's headquarters
by yourselves, are you?
That's crazy!
You've been smart enough
to stay away from her.
Don't change that now!
You know what happens to anyone
who messes with that chick!
How do you even plan to
get to Takamagahara, huh?
Do you hear me?
[KAZUMA]
Yato was very thorough.
The destruction was total.
We lost our family.
Only Veena and I
survived the massacre.
She wept for their loss,
and fell gravely ill
for a long time. Eventually,
her sorrow changed into hatred
for Yato and she
obtained a new Regalia.
Then another and another.
She gave them the "Ha" name.
They're her family now.
So great is her guilt
for the "Ma" Clan's death,
she now makes any spirit she
comes across into a Regalia.
Among all the gods in existence,
only a very few are capable
of shouldering so many of us.
It takes immense
strength and determination
to endure the pain of
bearing even one Regalia.
That is what makes her
the mightiest god of war.
And probably the one with
the kindest heart, as well.
I do like that about her,
but it also makes me worry.
I can't help but fear that,
someday, her kindness
might be her undoing.
We can't allow a
repeat of that tragedy.
But she's now beset
by poor health
and her Regalia's betrayal.
It's almost like before!
If nothing changes,
then soon, Veena will--
[gasps]
[KAZUMA] Wait. Is that what
Kugaha is after? Succession?
[AIHA]
I don't understand!
Did the plan change
at some point?
I thought we were just
capturing the girl.
Why'd we take Kazuma, too?
[KUGAHA] Because, he is
a traitor to his kin.
Besides, he might
be able to tell us
Lady Bishamon's weaknesses.
And that could be very helpful.
[AIHA] What?! You're
not making any sense!
There, do you see?
Using that staff made
a bunch more grow!
I can't go anywhere like this!
People will see them!
[KUGAHA chuckles]
You know, you're as gullible
as you are pretty.
You're my creature now.
If you want this to stay
secret, you'll do as I say.
Now, you could have
an ablution done.
Of course, if you did
that, there's no doubt
you would be exiled for good.
[laughs]
Lady Bishamon will be
replaced soon enough.
Until then, just take
some more of these.
[KUGAHA]
Todays' dose.
What? Something's going
to happen to our master?
[KUGAHA]
You catch on quickly.
Yes, a successor is
going to take her place.
But first, she's
going to have to die.
[KAZUMA]
Gods are born from wishes.
Because of that, gods with a
name are immortal, in a sense.
A god's death won't
change people's faith.
The name of
Bishamon will remain.
And if people still pray to it,
a new god will be born.
[KAZUMA]
There will be a new Bishamon.
[KUGAHA] The time is ripe
for a successor.
And when our new master arrives,
I'll be standing by
to take Kazuma's place
as exemplar with the absolute
power of a mighty war god
at my fingertips.
That's horrible.
But Bishamon's so powerful,
how can he possibly kill her?
If you don't return,
Yato will think
Veena abducted you.
He'll come to your rescue,
and he'll be very angry.
[HIYORI]
Huh?
[KAZUMA]
Yes. Kugaha can't do it himself.
He plans to have Yato kill her.
[AIHA] No! That's absolutely
unforgivable! I won't--
Stop talking.
Unless becoming a monster
is what you actually want.
[DAIKOKU]
Damn it!
Where is Kazuma, now that
we actually need him?
You'll have to use me to
stop Yato. C'mon, let's go!
[DAIKOKU]
Kofuku!
If we did that,
the Storm we'd cause
would be huge. Do you know
how many people would die?
But what should we do?
Those two may well
kill each other.
Bishamon would be
reborn right away,
but Yato's got no name,
and there's Yukine!
[KOFUKU]
Let's make a bet!
The odds against Yatty
winning are ten to one.
So I'll bet on Bisha!
Gambling? Now isn't
the time for--
That's right. Think
about it for a second!
I'm the god of poverty.
If I bet money on Bisha,
then she should lose.
Which means Yatty
should win, right?
Certainly not!
You know that I
don't have a shrine.
Without one, I can't get
to Takamagahara on my own.
Please, Tenjin.
Just take us up there.
For Hiyori.
[sighs] This sort of thing
is exactly the reason
you shouldn't be keeping
her tied to the Far Shore.
I'll agree to help you
on two conditions.
First, no one is to know
I was involved in any way.
As for the second...
I assume you know.
Yeah.
[TENJIN]
Yato. Yukine.
It seems strange.
Bishamon has always been
such a noble god.
Not the sort who would
stoop to kidnapping a girl.
[TENJIN]
What is it? Are you worried?
Well, a little.
He is obstinate, though.
Once he gets going,
not much can stop him.
They'll be just fine. I'm sure.
Still, this is going
to be one stormy night.
It certainly will be.
And the plum blossoms
are in full bloom.
I do hope they survive
the disturbance.
Let's go, Sekki!
[REGALIA screaming]
[REGALIA 4A]
What's that?
[REGALIA 4B]
Intruder at the front gate!
[REGALIA 4C]
Run!
[REGALIA 4D]
All non-weapons, get inside!
[REGALIA 4E]
Who goes there?
[REGALIA 4F]
Alert the master!
[BISHAMON] I never expected
you to come to me.
I've been wanting
to see you, Yato.
It looks like you got your wish.
Not yet, but soon enough.
Gaiki! Suki!
I want you at maximum firepower!
Feel that?
Those two Regalia
seem extra powerful!
They're way beyond
normal handguns.
[YATO]
With Kazuma gone, there's nobody
to keep this crazy
woman in check!
But that doesn't matter
if she can't hit us!
[YATO yells]
[KAZUMA]
I'm her exemplar!
I should have seen this coming.
He's set two gods
against each other.
It's unthinkable!
Don't do it, Veena!
You can't face Yato!
You're playing into
Kugaha's hands!
[KUGAHA]
I'm glad you came, Yato god.
I've sickened Bishamon for you.
I think you'll find her much
weaker than you expected.
Considering how graciously
I've prepared everything,
I think it's only fair
you do your part
and kill Bishamon!
This is awful!
[TSUGUHA]
There you are!
[AIHA gasps]
Oh, awesome!
I'm glad you're
already standing by!
This is a big one!
We're up against Lord Yato.
You're more experienced,
so we're holding you in reserve.
If I go down, it'll
all be up to you.
Milady, I'm coming!
Come! Kinki! Shoki!
Jinki! Shuki!
[KURAHA roars]
[YATO grunts]
[YATO]
What the hell?
Why'd you go dull
all of a sudden?
Sorry, I can't help it.
Her whip, her lion,
her outfit...
They're all Regalia like me.
How can I kill them?
They don't share your
reservations, you know.
They're trying to kill us.
Yeah, I know that, but still.
Maybe if I put it another way.
Protect me!
[gasps]
We came here to get Hiyori back!
[heartbeat]
[YUKINE]
All right.
[YATO]
Let's go!
Suki! Gaiki!
[grunting]
[BOTH gasp]
[BISHAMON]
Don't flinch!
Blast him and his
Regalia to bits for me!
[yells]
[KARUHA yelps]
[gasps]
Karuha!
Tell me where Hiyori is!
What? How should I know?
[YATO] That's one tough Garment
for how little it covers.
Don't play dumb, coward!
You dragged an innocent
person into this!
You act so righteous.
You, who slaughtered
my entire family!
Tell me! Why did you
kill them, Yato?
What I'm wondering is why
I just didn't kill you, too!
[HIYORI] Why would he do
something like that?
[KAZUMA]
Because of me.
Huh?
[KAZUMA]
Because I asked him to do it.
I asked Yato to murder my clan.
[KAZUMA]
As is natural for a war god,
Veena has always
kept many Regalia.
Now. Come, Choki.
Uh. Yes, Lady.
[KAZUMA] As a fledgling Regalia,
I was just a simple nail.
I wonder what that portends,
his impaling our master's body.
This isn't an ill omen
of things to come, I hope.
[BISHAMON]
Don't judge too swiftly.
It could be a sign that he
will always serve me soundly.
Let's go easy on him.
We have all the time
in the world, after all.
I will serve you soundly.
I'll make you proud.
[KAZUMA] She won me over
easily with her kindness.
I was determined to live
up to her expectations.
Borderline! Borderline!
Pathetic!
Keep going like that,
and you'll never
be any use to the master.
Borderline!
[KAZUMA]
And then, one day.
[groaning]
[CLERIC 4A] This is terrible!
Our master has been befouled!
Who is responsible?
You'll pay dearly for
this when I find out!
[REGALIA 4G]
How can this be happening?
[REGALIA 4H] There must
be something we can do!
What will happen
to us if she dies?
[REGALIA 4I]
Nothing good.
I'm sure our clan will be
banished after her succession.
[REGALIA 4J]
Are there any other gods willing
to accept Regalia such as us?
Step forward this instant!
Or I shall have a god of
calamity strike you down!
God of calamity.
[KAZUMA]
I'd heard rumors of him.
Of a god who
reveled in atrocities,
wielded a Nora, and
slaughtered all he saw.
If the guilty one
will not confess,
we will have to hold
an ablution for you all!
[KAZUMA]
But we could never determine
who was responsible.
[KAZUMA] The ablution
rituals changed nothing.
Veena's condition worsened.
[REGALIA 4L]
Whoever it is should confess!
[REGALIA 4K]
Shut up. I bet it's you.
[REGALIA 4M]
It's not me. It's her!
[REGALIA 4N]
How dare you!
[KAZUMA]
Suspicion and distrust built
among the ranks of the Regalia.
--Until...
--I will find the person--
[REGALIA grunting, screaming]
[KAZUMA]
Powerless to do anything,
I had no choice but
to seek outside help.
[KAZUMA] I hoped this
god of calamity would
grant the most taboo of wishes.
[KAZUMA] The Ma Clan,
Regalia of Bishamon,
have become corrupted.
They cannot be saved!
I beg you to kill them!
[YATO, BISHAMON grunt]
[KUGAHA] I've made sure
she's well drugged.
And Aiha's transgressions
must be affecting her.
After everything I've done,
she can still fight?
[grunts]
[YATO groans]
[KUGAHA] Behold and tremble,
for the war god,
Bishamon, is among us.
[YATO grunts]
[BISHAMON] You stubborn
louse. Aki, Koora, Kinu.
Keep your eyes on Yato!
[REGALIA 4S]
Why did she revert her weapons?
[REGALIA 4T]
Is that a good idea, my lady?
[YATO laughs]
Can't handle that much weight?
Somebody's corrupted you
again, haven't they? Aww.
My Regalia are loyal.
There are no traitors!
[NORA] Now this is betrayal
on a grand scale.
Did you hear him, Yato?
This boy is begging us
to kill his comrades.
What payment can you offer?
I... I don't have anything.
[NORA] You have your name.
Do you want to be a Nora?
[BISHAMON]
Kazuma!
[KAZUMA] My name was given
to me by my master.
It belongs to her.
I have come here ready to die.
We have disgraced our lady.
The "Ma" name will be forsaken,
never to be called again.
But I don't care!
I will give my name back to her.
If it will save her,
I'll do it gladly!
[YATO]
Take me there.
You can repay me later.
[GIANT PHANTOM 4A growls]
[NORA giggles] The Regalia
have become a giant Phantom.
That's the end for Bishamon.
[NORA] She'll die now and be
replaced. It's for the best.
[KAZUMA]
No! There she is! In its mouth.
She hasn't been absorbed yet.
I beg you. Please save her!
Hiki.
[REGALIA screaming]
[REGALIA 4U]
My lady.
[REGALIA 4V]
Please help me!
[BISHAMON]
Stop! Please! Don't kill them!
Have mercy! O' fierce
deity. Take pity!
Don't kill my
little ones, please!
They're innocents.
Gentle children, all of them.
I beg you! Don't kill them!
My lady! Help!
Please, my lady!
[REGALIA]
Lady Bishamon!
[gasps]
[BISHAMON]
How dare you? How dare you?
Somehow, Veena
survived that day.
However, her hatred
for Yato endured.
I'm sorry for burdening
you with all this.
That's what you meant before.
You told me once... that you
owed him a great deal.
There's a way to stop them.
There must be, right?
If they keep fighting like this,
there'll be no
undoing what happens.
[yelps]
[yells]
Tch! Nice try! Sekki!
Now!
[KINUHA, KURAHA, AKIHA]
Confine!
[gasps]
[BISHAMON]
You're finished.
Come, Saiki!
[yells]
[YATO]
No--
Yukine!
[HIYORI]
What was Yato like
back when you met him, Kazuma?
[KAZUMA]
He was cool.
[HIYORI]
"Cool"?
The guy with the tracksuit
and "fluffy-fluff" scarf?
[KAZUMA]
On the next Noragami Aragoto:
"Divine Acclamation,
Imprecation."
Cool in a scary sort of way.
[HIYORI]
He was cool. Wow.