[KUGAHA] Hm. Yes. This one
absorbs water the best.
Hope you don't mind, tree.
Your sap is what I need.
For making pills,
there's none better.
[gasps]
[NORA]
So. We meet again, Kugaha.
[KUGAHA]
Ah. Hello, Norry.
[NORA] Don't call me by
that name. I don't like it.
Really? What should I
call you instead, then?
There are plenty of options.
[KUGAHA]
You have quite a sense of humor.
By the way, that Yato fellow.
I paid him a visit.
And? Your conclusion?
I think he'll be useful.
What's going on?
Those two usually
don't act so serious.
Yato, I need to talk to you.
Oh, yeah? About what?
Oh, no! Are they breaking up?
Has Yukki finally
had it with Yatty?
Try not to cry for him.
Yato deserves this.
I have no doubt he
brought it on himself.
I...
Go on.
[YUKINE]
I...
I think...
I think I made a new friend!
Aw! How sweet!
[DAIKOKU groans]
Oh? Good for him.
That's wonderful!
Is this his first
friend as a Regalia?
Are they about the same age?
[YATO] I don't know how
thrilled I am about this.
The kid is just too
easily distracted.
[TENJIN] I'm relieved to see
that Yukine is thriving,
even with a subpar master.
[gasps]
[MAYU] Maybe he looks
to Yato as an example
of what not to do.
[yelps]
Well, good for Yukine.
Who does this friend
of his serve?
Oh. Good question.
[MAYU]
As on the ball as ever, I see.
Do you always have
to insult me, Tomone?
You know it's Mayu now!
And I'm not insulting you,
just stating the truth.
Anyhow. What an
excellent development.
Yukine had a rough
time of it at first.
He seemed like a rather
troubled young man.
No kidding. He's got
father issues of his own.
His own issues?
[OCTOPUS PHANTOM 2A growls]
[YATO]
Rend!
[OCTOPUS PHANTOM 2A roars]
Great job! It only took one hit!
[YATO]
Revert, Yuki.
She's right, that
was a good job.
I can tell you're really--
Hey! Listen to me
when I'm praising you!
[YUKINE]
Sorry! I'll listen later!
[YATO]
Where are you going?
To see my friend!
Don't forget about
your homework, Yukine.
[YUKINE]
I'll do that later, too.
That punk. Ditching his master.
Aw, just let him go.
You finished your subcontract
work for Lord Tenjin.
Don't call it that, okay?
We helped him. Helped him.
[HIYORI]
Sure, sure!
Just look at him.
He's so happy lately.
[YUKINE]
Suzuha!
Hey! How are you?
[YUKINE panting]
Sorry I'm so late.
Don't worry about it.
You're the one helping me out.
How 'bout I get you
my master's autograph
as a thank you?
[YUKINE]
Nah! That's okay!
[SUZUHA] What's your master's
name again? Lord Yato?
I'll have her make it out:
"To Yato and Yukine, with love!"
[YUKINE]
Uh, no, seriously!
--I'm good.
--[SUZUHA] Aw!
--Don't be like that!
[SUZUHA laughing]
[YUKINE]
If he'd ever heard of Yato,
he wouldn't be suggesting that.
[YUKINE] Wow. Your master
gave you all of this?
Sure. All the fertilizer
and seedlings I want.
[YUKINE] Man! You've really
got it good, you know that?
My stupid master
never gives me stuff.
He actually stole
money from me once!
A real jerk move,
but I got back at 'im!
[SUZUHA chuckles]
You guys are close, huh?
How d'you figure that?
My master is totally amazing,
but she's got lots of us.
Including her
super-talented go-to team.
Kuraha, the divine beast!
Akiha, the knife.
Karuha and Kazuha, the handguns!
Yugiha, the great sword!
Kinuha, the whip!
And Tsuguha, in
charge of defense.
Jeez, that's a lot.
Of course, there's also
the Blessed Vessel
and exemplar. Kazuma holds
them all together!
Blessed Vessel, huh?
They're all elite
soldiers ready to rush
into battle at
a moment's notice.
Together, they're the
ultimate team of Regalia
for the ultimate
god of war, Bishamon!
They're the top, but the master
is still really nice
to all the rest of us.
Even with so many,
she treats us like family.
That's the sort of god
she is. Powerful and kind.
Sounds like a great master.
I can tell you
really respect her.
[SUZUHA]
Of course I do!
But, considering how
many Regalia she has,
I haven't been
called up in years.
[YUKINE]
Oh.
[SUZUHA] Hey, I know!
You wanna see something cool?
[YUKINE]
It's huge!
[SUZUHA] This cherry tree was
uprooted during a typhoon,
and it got sick. I've
been taking care of it.
The hollow's finally
growing roots again. See?
That is cool!
You did this yourself?
I did have a little
advice from an expert.
This is a pretty big tree,
too. It must've been tough.
I guess. A friend and
I made a promise, though.
That we'd see its
blossoms together.
[YUKINE]
Oh. Another Regalia?
[SUZUHA]
No, actually.
She was a living person,
but she could see me.
[YUKINE]
How long ago was this?
It's been about 30 years now.
[YUKINE gasps]
[TOMOKO] The flowers around
here are so big and pretty!
Are you the one who takes
care of them, mister?
[SUZUHA]
Hm?
[TOMOKO]
These are sunflowers.
And those are morning glories.
Not bad! You know
your flowers, kid.
[TOMOKO]
Don't call me kid! I'm Tomoko!
[chuckles] Okay, Tomoko.
What's this red one here?
[TOMOKO]
A doodle-doo!
I don't think so.
I'm pretty sure these flowers
are called hollyhocks.
Cock-a-doodle-doo!
[TOMOKO] The flower garden
here is always so pretty!
Are you the one who
looks after them, mister?
Hello, Tomoko!
Huh?
How do you know my name--
have I met you before?
[TOMOKO] These flowers are
so beautiful every year!
So, is this your garden?
[SUZUHA] Tomoko's
grandmother lived nearby.
So she came to visit
every summer vacation.
[TOMAKO]
...a butterbur cup...
...and a thistle basket!
[SUZUHA] You're really good
at remembering flower names.
Is there anything
else you remember?
[TOMOKO]
Doodle-doo!
[laughs]
[SUZUHA]
But she could never remember me.
She only ever came to
visit during the summer.
But one time,
she said she wanted to see
the cherry blossoms with me.
So we carved a promise
into the tree.
I haven't seen her since.
[SUZUHA]
That's how it goes.
The living forget us so quickly.
But, I'm hoping, at least,
she remembers this cherry tree.
That would be enough for me.
[YUKINE yelps]
What are you doing coming in
through the window?
[YATO] Well, if I came
in through the door,
Daikoku would make me do chores.
[YUKINE] Then do some!
Don't you owe them that much?
Forget that for now.
Did anything happen
with you today?
I've had a pain here for hours.
[YUKINE]
It's none of your business.
Please don't give me
that. Just talk to me.
I don't think either
of us want a repeat
of what happened last time.
[YUKINE]
Fine. It's about Hiyori.
[YATO]
Hm?
[YUKINE]
She's a living person.
When she gets older,
will she forget us?
You falling for her?
[YUKINE]
Shut up! It's not like that.
I didn't think much
about her at first.
She was just someone who
seemed handy to have around.
But...
What are you waiting for?
Then I can't be friends
with you anymore!
I'm so relieved! I'm so
glad you're both okay!
[YUKINE]
She's more than that.
She always tries
so hard to help us.
But, it seems like
a waste of her time.
What do I matter?
I'm already dead.
I might as well never existed.
Why do so much to
help somebody like me?
I mean, really. Why bother?
What's the point, anyway?
She's gonna keep getting
older, isn't she?
She'll go off to
school, get a job.
Someday, she'll get married.
She'll keep changing,
and I'll always be the same.
That's fine, really.
I knew it would be like that.
I was hoping that we
would stay friends.
But... But what if...
...she forgets us,
and doesn't even
remember who we are?
[YUKINE sobbing]
[YUKINE]
Sorry. Does it hurt?
Eh, don't worry. It's
better not to hold it all in.
You just cry all you need to.
Seems like being around her
might be hard for you.
You gonna quit studying?
[YUKINE] No, I'm not.
I don't want to quit.
Even though this might
be my cherry tree.
Your cherry tree?
[YUKINE]
It's hard to explain.
By the way, Suzuha's having
a blossom viewing party soon,
and he invited me to go to it.
[YATO]
Suzuha? That's your friend?
[YUKINE] Uh-huh. He's one
of Bishamon's Regalia.
[YATO gasps]
[KUGAHA]
It's taken root beautifully.
Hi, Doctor.
[KUGAHA] It's going to
bloom just fine this year.
Thanks to all your hard work.
Well, thank you.
But, I just did what
you told me to do.
[KUGAHA] So, all sad and
alone again this year?
[SUZUHA]
Wha--?
[KUGAHA] How long are you
going to keep this up?
For decades? For centuries?
I mean, surely it's
obvious by now.
She forgot you a long time ago.
[gasps]
[KUGAHA] And she isn't
the only one, is she?
How long has it been
since Lady Bishamon
called your name?
Years now, right?
Even your master
has forgotten you.
That must be pretty depressing.
You're totally alone
in the world.
There's nothing for
you here. Why stay?
[WOLF PHANTOMS panting]
[gasps]
[panting]
[BISHAMON]
A name has disappeared.
That would only happen
if one of my Regalia died.
But how?
It's unwrapped.
I wonder what Suzuha
was thinking.
You can't just leave it exposed.
He knows better than that.
Jeez.
Hold on a sec. I'll help you.
[YUKINE]
I hope he shows up.
You even made food for us.
I wonder why he's not here yet.
Suzuha...
So he's one of Lady
Bishamon's Regalia, right?
And that's not a problem?
It's really no big deal.
He's actually never
even heard of Yato.
And I was told I should just
"run along now and play nice."
Like I'm a five-year-old
or something.
[HIYORI]
Now I get it.
He's a lot more worried about
Yukine than he lets on.
Which explains all these texts.
[YUKINE] We're gonna have
a blossom-viewing party
in the spring when it blooms.
You can come if you want.
Really? I'd like to.
You might forget. It's not
for a little while.
Don't say that. I won't forget.
Yato still hasn't fixed my body.
And I've got a ton of
stuff left to teach you.
Keep studying with me, okay?
[chuckles]
[phone rings]
[YUKINE]
You hungry? Should we eat now?
That sounds good. Just
give me a minute, okay?
[YUKINE]
Hm?
"If you have some
leftovers, don't be greedy.
Remember gods gotta
eat, too." And send!
[HIYORI]
Quit being a dirty sneak!
You wanna say something?
Say it to my face!
Was that a tracksuit I saw?
[HIYORI]
Hmph.
Did he follow us
here or something?
Oh, who knows?
Never mind that idiot, Yukine.
I'm hungry. Let's eat our lunch.
[YUKINE] Suzuha told me
he's been taking care
of that cherry tree
all this time.
Wow.
It means a lot to him.
That's why I don't get it.
He should be here now.
[BISHAMON]
The flowers. Was it Suzuha?
[FUMIHA whimpering] This is bad.
Suzuha hasn't come back.
Don't cry about it.
You know crying
makes the master hurt.
[REGALIA 2B]
Do you think a Phantom got him?
Can you help me?
[REGALIA gasp]
Of course, my lady.
The three of you
spend a lot of time
with Suzuha, don't you?
Do you know where he might be?
No, I'm sorry.
[ALL]
Everything's just fine, my lady.
There's nothing to worry about.
Okay, thanks.
Tsuguha? What happened
to your hair?
Nothing, my lady.
Please, you seem shaken.
Has something happened?
No, of course not!
I'm just being silly.
Getting upset over
a bad haircut!
I hope it didn't affect
your health at all.
Well, I'm all better.
I should get going.
[PHANTOM 2A whines]
[gasps]
[KAZUMA]
She's taking more medication.
She seems so melancholy
and run down lately.
[KAZUMA]
Veena.
[KAZUMA gasps]
[REGALIA murmuring]
Why are we gathering
so late at night?
It looks as though every
Regalia's been summoned.
Ah. What's going on here?
Is this what I think it is?
We are holding
an ablution tonight.
[gasps]
[KAZUMA] Know that I do
this on my own authority,
as your exemplar. Our master
has no knowledge of it.
The Lady Bishamon
has been blighted.
[REGALIA gasp]
[KAZUMA] Which means one
of us has been corrupted,
and thus, brought her harm.
A Phantom must have manifested
on the body of the one
responsible for the blight.
I ask you to show yourself.
[sighs] All right.
Then we'll have
to inspect everyone.
Please cooperate.
For our lady's sake.
Dr. Kuga, if you will?
[KUGAHA]
All clear. Next.
All clear.
[KUGAHA]
You're clear, Aiha.
You're clear, too.
Well, I examined everyone.
Not a Regalia among us
seems to be tainted.
Are you satisfied,
then? Are we done?
Actually. There's
still one left.
You haven't been checked.
Ah. Of course. You're right.
Well, that's easy
enough to remedy.
[TSUGUHA]
Uh...
[REGALIA scream]
[KUGAHA]
There!
--Feast your eyes!
--[KURAHA] Dr. Kugaha!
--Pristine, isn't it?
--There are ladies present!
Kinuha! Stop staring!
Cover your eyes!
But then who has blighted her?
I don't know.
But I can't believe
you suspected us.
I'll agree that she has
seemed exhausted lately,
and no one can blame you
for being concerned.
But don't forget
your responsibilities
as our master's
exemplar, Kazuma.
We can't afford to have you
distracted or suspicious of us.
When we see your
confidence begin to waver,
it shakes us all.
[BISHAMON]
What's going on here?
My Lady Bishamon!
Oh, err, we were just...
The blight is gone. But how?
[BISHAMON]
Mm?
[REGALIA 2F] Wait. So he had
it wrong the whole time?
[REGALIA 2G]
I'm glad Lady Bishamon is okay,
but I can't believe Kazuma
had so little trust in us.
[YATO]
I knew it.
It's not much,
but it's stormy here.
So, what happened?
If it's what I suspect...
[YATO] You really reek
of dog. Did you kill him?
[KUGAHA] It isn't good
to be so suspicious
and mistrustful all the time.
Such traits can prove fatal.
Especially for denizens of
the Far Shore, like us.
Wouldn't you agree?
[YATO]
Who are you?
[KUGAHA]
Oh, nobody special.
Just someone who wanted to
meet the great Yato in person.
[YATO]
Not gonna give me a name?
What for? I'm just
an ordinary Regalia.
Do you really need my name?
[YATO]
I'll ask a different question.
Why don't you tell me
whose pet you are.
There's some real fire
in you, isn't there?
That said, Lord Yato.
It doesn't matter how many petty
wishes you grant.
You're a nobody.
No one will ever remember you.
I bet you must live
in constant fear.
Without a Regalia, what are you?
Just a pathetic
excuse for a god!
[KUGAHA grunts]
Did your master
teach you to greet
an unarmed person
with a Borderline?
That's really horrible
manners, you know.
[laughs] You don't have
a single shrine,
but you're that powerful?
You must have a particularly
strong tie to the Near Shore.
[KUGAHA] Bonds with the
Near Shore can be fleeting.
Also remarkably fragile,
as I'm sure you're aware.
Ephemeral. I think perhaps
that's the best way
to describe it, don't you?
I hope we'll meet again
sometime, Lord Yato.
And please, until we do,
try not to fade away, all right?
That's no problem!
I'm not gonna disappear!
Not as long as there's
someone out there who still--
[YATO]
...remembers who I am.
[NORA] Well, it looks like
somebody taught you a lesson.
[chuckles] Oh, yes.
I think Yato's exactly what
I've been looking for.
Everything is falling
into place perfectly.
The Regalias' bonds
are already unraveling
and growing hollow.
Many are ready to fall
with only the
slightest of nudges.
Bishamon is known for
being a violent god of war.
Unfortunately, she is
no longer living up
to her reputation.
Like it or not, you're going
to help me, Yato god.
Oh, really? It's happening?
[KUGAHA] It is. The end
is near for Bishamon.
Very near, indeed.
[HIYORI]
Can you tell me how to solve
this equation, Mayu?
[MAYU]
Of course I can!
I do serve the god
of learning, you know!
[HIYORI]
Great, thank you!
I think I'll call you
Lady Mayu from now on!
[MAYU] On the next Noragami
Aragoto: "False Bond."
[YATO] You've never once
called me Lord Yato!