[music plays]
[BOY] Excuse me, Mr. Yato,
the light is green.
[BOY]
Will we be there soon?
[gasps]
Hey, it looks like your
shoelace is untied.
I've tried very hard,
but it's difficult
for me to tie them.
[LADY 9A]
Welcome! Come in, have a seat!
Anything in here sound
good to you, Ebisu?
Well, Yato made
it back. Finally.
Yeah.
It was nice of Lady
Bishamon to give him
a room to recover in.
Though I'm kind of surprised.
Yeah.
And Kofuku gave him
all those snacks.
He'll be well fed while
he heals, at least.
Yeah.
I just hope he'll
be okay. You know?
Me, too.
But, I wish I
could help somehow.
[HIYORI sighs]
Huh?
[KAZUMA]
Yukine!
[YUKINE]
What is it? Is something wrong?
[KAZUMA]
Have you seen Yato recently?
--[HIYORI] Hm?
--[YUKINE] Uh...
Ebisu came to visit Yato,
but now they're gone.
The room is empty, and we
have no sign of them.
And, my room had been ransacked.
[BOTH gasp]
That was them!
[silverware clinking]
So this is the Olive Tavern?
Feel free to order
whatever you want.
I mean it, go nuts.
It's Kazuma's treat today.
Well, dear, what
can I get for you?
Looks like they
have a kids' meal.
How's that sound?
Even comes with a toy.
[EBISU]
No, thank you.
I'd like a simmered
Hamburg steak.
Well, what do ya know?
I had a feeling that's
what you'd ask for.
You look just like
another gentleman
who gets that all the time!
He must be your daddy!
Like father, like son, eh?
[yelling]
Rend!
[GODS screaming]
[TAKEMIKAZUCHI]
He cut through it? Impossible!
[YATO grunting]
[grunts, coughs] That was
incredible! Yato god!
He truly is fearless.
And so is his Blessed Vessel.
Damn monkey suit.
How does Kazuma
stand this thing?
Feels like I'm suffocating.
If you don't mind
me asking, sir,
is there a particular
reason you brought me here?
[YATO]
Because it was Ebisu's wish.
You mean my last self?
Were you friends with
my previous incarnation?
[YATO]
Your last self, huh?
Veena, look!
No! Run, Ebisu!
[cackles]
[YATO]
You really did reincarnate.
Yes.
From what I've been told,
plenty of gods reincarnate,
though none do it
as frequently as I do.
The previous Ebisus--
[YATO] I don't care
about previous Ebisus.
Far as I'm concerned,
there's only one,
and he's gone for good now.
[LADY 9A]
Well, all righty! Here we are!
[YATO]
Good choice! That looks tasty.
[EBISU]
Thank you for this food.
It's really yummy!
Oh, yeah? How yummy?
Does it bring back memories?
Hey! I'm talking
to you, kid. Well?
Geez.
This really is incredible.
I have never tasted
anything so delicious before!
That's not exactly true.
From what you had told me,
it sounded like you seriously
liked the food here.
Well, this me likes it, too.
Reincarnation doesn't
change everything, huh?
You're still as clumsy
as ever, that's for sure.
[YATO] So, kid. You really
don't remember anything?
[EBISU]
Nothing.
Not the fight we had
in the underworld?
Or our mad dash
to escape Izanami?
No, but did I really
fight you, Mr. Yato?
[sighs] I guess memories aren't
passed down at all, huh?
I don't know.
I was just suddenly here.
From the shrine I could
see the beautiful sea
and a quiet, peaceful
town full of people
who were hard at work.
I fell in love with this
incredible world at first sight.
I knew right away
that I wanted to make
the people here happy.
A strong desire to
make everybody happy.
That must be the natural
instinct of the Ebisu god.
[EBISU] What do you mean?
Aren't all gods like that?
Wow, good question.
So you're a war god,
aren't you Mr. Yato?
What's that like?
I bet you must be a
really good fighter.
[YATO] Yeah, I am.
Seems to be all I'm good at.
[EBISU] That's so cool!
I'm really clumsy.
I bet I'd be bad at fighting.
Did I at least do okay
in the underworld?
Remember?
You said that you
and I fought one time.
Fighting a war god,
I can't believe it!
And what about my Regalia?
Was I good friends with them?
Was I the kind of god
that made people happy?
I hope so! But maybe I wasn't.
Everyone says the
heavens executed me.
[gasps]
So, I guess...
I must've been a pretty
bad guy if that happened.
That isn't true!
[gasps]
[YATO]
You were a righteous man!
You were willing to
sacrifice your life
for the sakes of others!
And your strength--
It was unbelievable. I don't
even begin to compare to you!
But still, you...
[EBISU]
Revert, Kuni!
[KUNIMI grunts]
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[groaning]
[GODS cheer]
Ebisu!
[YATO]
Hang in there. Okay?
Come on! Ebisu!
[TAKEMIKAZUCHI]
Farewell, Conjurer Ebisu.
Hopefully your new
overseer will ensure
that you behave with more
discretion in your next life.
May you now decease
without worry.
[YATO]
Don't you die! Ya hear?
Don't you dare die on me, Ebisu!
[seagulls cawing]
[REGALIA 10A]
It's all right.
You are very famous, Lord Ebisu.
[REGALIA 10B] A god like you
will always be reborn.
[REGALIA 10C] See? There's
no reason to be scared.
[REGALIA]
Don't worry. It's okay to die.
[YATO] Ebisu! Come on,
stay strong, man!
[sputtering]
[YATO]
What about you as an individual
[EBISU gasps]
[YATO] Is dying here
really what you want?
What this you wants?
[whimpers]
[EBISU]
Ya-Yato god.
I consider myself
lucky to have met you.
[gasps]
[YATO]
Ebisu. I'm the lucky one.
No, please! I don't want to die!
[gasps]
[YATO] But you did. And I
couldn't stop it. I'm sorry!
Uh, but, Mr. Yato,
what happened wasn't your fault.
[YATO]
Please.
Let me apologize.
As you may know,
the heavens issued
an official sanction.
Along with my reincarnation,
my exemplar Iwami was expelled.
In exchange, they were
willing to leave
the rest of the
Mi Clan unpunished.
So I thought about it.
And have I decided to make
Kunimi my new overseer.
I don't want anything
bad to happen to Iwami.
He's been with me
for a long time.
Thanks to all your help,
the heavens haven't been
able to find him yet.
I would like to keep it
that way, if possible.
In order to do so,
I think it would be best
for him to remain here.
If that's acceptable to you.
[BISHAMON]
It is.
Thank you so much,
Ms. Crazy Chick!
[KAZUMA, TENJIN,
OKUNINUSHI gasp]
That name. Where did
you hear it, Ebisu?
Oh, is it wrong?
I learned it from Mr. Yato.
I thought it was weird, but he
said it was your real name.
Did he?
[KUNIMI]
You must be curious.
Allow me to recount
the facts for you.
The young master
entered Izanami's realm
in order to find an
underworld Locution Brush.
What does such a thing do?
[KUNIMI]
It gives one the ability to name
and employ Phantoms.
[KUNIMI]
Over many incarnations,
he studied methods
of controlling them.
He was very thorough and
dedicated to his work.
[KUNIMI]
But he was never able to achieve
satisfactory results.
So that's why he was gettin'
so sick all the time.
And this Locution Brush.
Does he have it now?
[KUNIMI]
Actually, it's gone missing.
I am certain he brought
it back with him, though.
To be honest, if I had my way,
it would stay missing.
I hope he never touches
that damn thing again.
Look, what I don't get,
is why he was so obsessed
with using Phantoms
in the first place.
[KUNIMI] As you are all
aware, the young master
is a god of commerce.
But inevitably, his
incarnations realize
that wealth alone is not enough
to bring people happiness,
and so he eventually becomes
obsessed with conjurers
and the power to
control Phantoms.
He convinces himself
that he can curb disaster
and use Phantoms for
the benefit of humanity.
[OKUNINUSHI]
This is news to us.
All this time, and we had
no idea what he was up to.
He only wanted to help people.
Could we have
prevented his death?
Things could have turned
out quite differently
had we known more.
Yeah, maybe.
[KUNIMI] I'm sure the
desire to help humanity
will be passed on to the
newest young master as well.
[laughing]
[DAIKOKU] Yato's at it again,
sponging off us and actin'
like he owns the place. Tch.
He just sits around
all damn day.
We're not running
a charity here.
Would it kill him to wash dishes
or fold laundry sometime?
If he did some chores,
it might help him
work up an appetite.
We make him all that food
and it just goes to waste
while he pines away.
[KOFUKU giggles]
These complaints,
coming from you?
The man who swept the
attic every day Yatty
was gone so it would be ready
for him when he came back?
[DAIKOKU grunts]
[KOFUKU] Admit it, you big
softy. You missed him. Right?
[DAIKOKU grumbles]
[KOFUKU] I understand.
I want him to get better, too.
He'll have help. He's
got Yukine and Hiyori.
You're right, he does.
I'm sure the three
of them will be fine.
Yukine. Come with me.
[HIYORI inhales]
I recognize that smell.
Well, out with it. If you've
gotta talk, then talk.
Okay then.
From the time I was little,
I used Nora to kill
people. So many people.
That's in the past.
[YATO]
No, I kill people.
It's what I've always done
whenever I was told to.
Even just recently.
[gasps]
[YATO]
Disgusting, huh? But...
I really want it to stop.
I don't want that
to be me anymore.
You have the determination
that marks a good god.
The kind of god that
can make people happy.
[YATO] I keep asking
myself: "What can I do?
How can I be like Ebisu?"
[gasps]
[splashing]
Nora.
[NORA] You're terrible, Yato.
Leaving me behind like that.
But I suppose I can forgive you.
You completed your
task, after all.
You rescued Ebisu
from the underworld
like you were told to.
[YATO]
Tell me something.
Was it a set-up?
Was Ebisu killed in
place of my old man?
[NORA giggles] Are you only
now figuring that out?
The heavens were
relentlessly investigating
their conjurer. Someone
needed to take the fall.
Ebisu happened to
share an interest
in controlling Phantoms,
so he was the perfect choice.
All it took was one tiny
little nudge from Father,
and the heavens
sprang into action.
They got their conjurer,
and he got to live.
A happy ending for all!
[giggles] Now, come.
Let's go home, Yato.
Father will be so proud of you.
Like hell he's going with you!
Are you still here?
I don't see why.
This doesn't concern
weaklings like you.
[YUKINE gasps]
Say. Do you know the
sounds a human body
makes as it dies?
[gasps]
Do you know the color blood
turns when it dries?
The smell of flesh as it
grows colder and harder?
The feel of bones as they're
crunched beneath a blade?
Don't you see?
You don't have what it takes
to carry Yato's burden.
[YATO]
Y'know something?
This is how you've always been.
You never change.
[YATO]
You always smile just like that.
No matter who weeps or who dies.
But I've changed.
I can't smile with you anymore.
Hiki.
I have a new purpose now.
Thanks for everything, Hiiro.
You can't be serious.
We've always been together.
We belong together.
Yaboku!
Not anymore. I am Yato now.
We're done, Hiki. I hereby...
...release you!
[gasps]
[splash]
[YUKINE]
A new purpose? What is it?
Yukine.
I meant it. I wanna change.
I wanna be a different god,
one who makes people happy.
But killing is the only
thing I'm any good at.
Tell me, what can
I do? Be my guide!
I need you!
Well, I don't think you need
to do anything
different, really.
[gasps]
[YUKINE]
If all you can do is kill,
slay disaster before it strikes.
I'm here for you.
I am your exemplar.
I won't let you
become a murderer again.
[clapping]
[YATO, YUKINE gasp]
[YATO]
It's Hiyori.
I wish for Yato to succeed.
May he become what
he wants to be.
[gasps]
[HIYORI]
Yato, you chose Yukine.
And, Yukine, you chose Yato.
So I'm sure my wish
will come true.
And if you're not... I have
enough faith for all of us!
[YUKINE]
Yato!
That Storm's huge!
Come, Sekki!
[gasps]
[YUKINE] By killing Phantoms,
you can save the people
who would become their victims.
And you can keep others
from going astray.
I'm certain of it.
So, Yato, your job is to
find disaster and slay it!
[YATO] This is the land
of the Rising Sun.
Your desecrations
shall not be allowed.
Hear me. I am the god, Yato.
I now lay thee waste
with the Sekki,
and expel thy vast defilement!
I cleanse thee!
[YATO]
Rend!
I never knew you had such
a way with words, kid.
Oh, shut up. Just do
your job right, okay?
Sure thing, O' Wise Exemplar!
[YUKINE]
I don't need your attitude!
[NORA]
I'm back, Father.
So, that weakling actually
released you, Mizuchi.
[chuckles] Looks like he's
hit his rebellious stage.
Well, isn't that just adorable?
[SEKI]
Fujisaki, you ready?
Yeah!
What was so interesting?
[FUJISAKI]
Hm?
[panting]
[FUJISAKI]
Nothing, really.