[EBISU] It seems that
Regalia are limited
in their use of Masked Ones.
They do not have the power
to turn Phantoms into puppets.
Only a name-bestowing god
is able to do that.
[door clicks]
Have you captured a Phantom?
[IWAMI]
Yes.
Good. Then let's begin at once.
[growling]
[EBISU]
My Earthly name is Ebisu.
Bearing a posthumous name,
I don this mask,
and proclaim myself
a spirit vessel!
Ye names that assemble
cannot defy me.
You are bound and beholden
to my every order!
Submit yourself to me,
and obey the mask!
Yield now, Ryoki!
What're you doin'?
Who the hell do
you think you are?
The guys who're gonna
take you down, that's who!
Ah, kiss my ass!
Like hell I will!
[PUNKS]
We're gonna kill you!
[YATO]
All right, that's enough!
This is the land
of the Rising Sun.
Your desecrations
shall not be allowed.
Hear me. I am the god, Yato.
I now lay thee waste
with the Sekki,
and expel thy vast defilement!
I cleanse thee!
Rend!
[PUNKS]
Uh...?
And thus, it's done, boys.
May our fates intertwine.
[YATO] Make way!
Hiyori is coming through!
Yeah, that's right,
I'm talkin' to you, shorty!
Outta the way!
Look out, there's some
gum there, watch your step.
Dandelion fuzz incoming!
Quick, cover your ears!
[yelps]
Enough! Can't I walk
to school in peace?
[YUKINE]
Sorry about that, Hiyori.
He's been a little
overexcited lately.
[YATO] 'Course I have!
See! Get a load of this, yo!
[HIYORI]
Resident registration card?
That's right!
Takamagahara has
officially recognized
this lil' beauty as my shrine!
Seriously? They actually
approved that thing?
Well, of course they did!
[YATO] Come on, guys,
please! Have a heart!
I visited the office
every day right before
closing time until
they finally caved!
[YUKINE]
Man, talk about lax!
[HIYORI]
I guess government officials
are the same everywhere.
[YUKINE] Does this new
status come with any perks?
[YATO]
It sure does.
I can attend things
called Colloquies now.
I'm licensed to sell
official merchandise.
And I even have my very
own holy book and song.
Which you wrote yourself!
It doesn't seem much
different than before to me.
Oh, but wait! I saved
the best perk for last!
Tad-ah! My own plot of
land in Takamagahara!
[YUKINE]
It's tiny!
You know what this
means, don't you?
We'll always have
somewhere to sleep.
Yeah, I think I'll stick
with Kofuku's place.
And now that we've got a shrine,
we can visit the Heavenly
Realm whenever we want to!
Not bad!
That is pretty cool!
And all of it's thanks to you.
Really. I'm glad you
didn't give up on me.
Sure. You're welcome.
[YATO] Hello there!
Nice to meet you, I'm Yato!
I just moved into
the neighborhood.
[NEIGHBOR GOD 8A]
I have some young Regalia,
and they need their sleep.
I hope you boys don't make
too much noise after dark.
Nope! Quiet as mice,
don't you worry.
[REGALIA 8D] You didn't hear
it from me, but apparently...
Oh, my! Positively
appalling! Really!
[AMI]
Guess what, guess what!
Yama's got a crush on someone!
[YAMA]
Say it a little louder.
I don't think the whole
school heard you!
--Geez, Ami!
--[HIYORI] Tell me more!
--What's he like?
I don't really know
much about him except
that he's in a
higher grade than us.
Oh-ho! An older man, huh?
What else? What else?
[YAMA]
He transferred here last spring.
And his voice!
He sounds just like the
Hundred Archfiends' singer!
[MANABU]
Hey, Iki!
[HIYORI] Hi, Manabu!
How've you been doing?
Getting along any better with
your classmates these days?
A little bit.
At least, I'm not
getting bullied anymore.
But still, I'm basically
invisible to everybody.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
School can be rough, huh?
Nah, it's no big deal.
When I do get down though,
I remember what you said:
"Find one special person
and you're set," right?
[gasps] Did I say that?
[MANABU]
Yeah.
You gave me a lot
of really good advice.
Use this, sweetie.
but remember, if you're
gonna fight rough,
then your opponent
should be armed, too.
Wha--? I never said
anything like that!
No way!
You mean Yato.
It was him who gave you advice.
[MANABU]
Yato?
Yeah, you know, the
guy in the tracksuit.
He and Yukine were
in the girls' bathroom,
so I beat them up, remember?
No idea. Sorry.
[gasps]
Well, a-anyway.
you were really there
for me when I needed it.
And... there's something
I've been wanting
to tell you since then.
I don't know how to say this.
The thing is, I--
I... Like... Like...
I like your shoes!
They're really nice!
Bye!
[HIYORI]
Why doesn't he remember Yato?
[door clicks]
[HINAHA] Excuse me, my lady.
You have a visitor.
[KAZUMA]
Yukine?
Hello, Lady Bishamon.
I'm sorry to bother you.
[BISHAMON]
What do you want? Are you alone?
[YUKINE]
Um, yes.
I've come to say hello
for my loser of a master.
We've just been granted land
in Takamagahara, you see.
[BISHAMON]
Here? The Yato god?
[YUKINE]
Yes...?
A-Actually. That's not all.
I have a personal
request. For Kazuma.
[KAZUMA]
Uh--
[YUKINE] Could you teach me
how to use invocations?
Say yes. I'm Yato's exemplar.
I wanna keep getting stronger.
Please help me do that!
Well, I...
[sighs]
Yes. I would be happy to.
[YUKINE] All right! I'll
work really hard, I swear!
[BISHAMON] Please don't
let them live nearby.
[KOFUKU]
You're awfully quiet.
Whatcha lookin' at, Yori?
[HIYORI sighs] Yato's been
acting really weird lately.
If we're not together,
he sends me a text
like every five minutes.
Look at this!
Whoa! There're hundreds!
And this isn't even
the half of it.
Looks like a good
parade. We should go.
They've got a
couple's room here.
What do you think, huh?
A gondola ride, ooh!
I was just callin' to say hi!
[HIYORI groans]
[KOFUKU giggles] That kind of
behavior's only natural.
You are Yatty's first.
[DAIKOKU] That may not be the
best way to put it, Kofuku.
There aren't many
people out there
who even know Yatty exists.
And nobody was ever so
determined to stick with him
before you came along.
Honestly, I'm relieved.
This means he can lead
another long life.
What?
[KOFUKU]
Yatty has always had a hard time
attracting long-term believers
and dedicated Regalia.
He's had to survive
within people's broken,
scattered memories.
I can only imagine how
difficult that must have been.
Famous gods like me
and the Seven Gods
of Fortune are lucky.
We don't have to worry
about that stuff.
It's totally different for
unknown gods like Yatty.
Once they've been forgotten,
they vanish from existence.
[HIYORI gasps]
Like forever?
[KOFUKU]
Yeah.
A god is born from the
wishes people make, you know.
When those wishes stop coming,
he loses his purpose.
He vanishes for good.
No reincarnation or anything.
That's why this is so great.
'Cause Yatty has someone
to remember him.
A believer he can
really count on.
I get his reaction now.
[HIYORI]
Wait! What if I do forget him?
Will he vanish?
No, no.
I wouldn't worry
about it too much.
After all, he's survived
this long, hasn't he?
I'm guessing he's got some
other believers out there.
[DAIKOKU] I've always
wondered that about Yato.
How could such an unknown god
endure for centuries?
He should've vanished long ago.
[DAIKOKU]
Bit of a mystery, really.
Now, in order for
an invocation to work,
it needs to be tied to a name.
Which leads us to
Rule Number One:
know the name of your target.
But your name's
right on your hand
where anyone can see it.
Isn't that sorta risky?
Yes. Rule Number Two:
invocations won't work on
those of greater status.
To use an invocation
is to impose submission.
It's actually a terrible act.
As such, it could even
harm your own master.
So think carefully
before using one.
Right.
When you act, do so
with confidence.
You're a Blessed Vessel.
Make sure your
opponent knows that.
[YUKINE]
What do you mean?
How should I put it?
Always treat your opponent
with... contempt, I guess.
Uh...
And Rule Three:
there is no such
thing as practice.
--Border--
--[KAZUMA] Restraint!
Too slow!
You need to draw more quickly.
Till you're called or it
wears off, you're stuck.
Uh-- Huh?
Just keeping score.
Now, let's go again. Yukine.
Dammit!
--Restraint!
--[YUKINE] Bor--
[KAZUMA]
Too slow! Again!
--[YUKINE] Again?
--Restraint!
--Borderline!
[YATO, KOFUKU, HIYORI,
DAIKOKU laughing]
[KOFUKU]
That's hilarious!
Kazuma needs to find a
new way of keeping score.
I don't like this one!
Ah! Don't take pictures!
You did your best.
That's what matters.
[YUKINE whimpers]
Oh, come on. Don't cry.
How 'bout I take
you to Capypa Land?
Hell no, you freak!
Aww! But I wanna
go to Capypa Land!
I wanna! I wanna!
[YUKINE] You don't need
to drag me along with you.
Just go by yourself!
No way! I can't go on
all the rides all alone!
[YUKINE]
Shut up!
[YATO]
Please! I wanna see the Capypas!
It'll be fun, I swear!
But seriously, I think
the three of us should go.
You, me, and Hiyori.
We all gotta go to Capypa Land
and get our picture together!
I don't think
I've ever seen you
look so happy before.
You are unusually chipper.
Well, whaddya expect?
My centuries-long dream
has finally come true.
I have a shrine of my own.
I was told I didn't need one.
I almost gave up hope
entirely after that.
If only my kid self
could see me now.
He'd be so happy.
[YUKINE] Hold on, you were
actually a kid once?
I don't buy it!
[KOFUKU]
Aw!
[HIYORI]
Yato as a kid...
Who would have said
something like that to him?
[DAIKOKU]
Hey!
[YATO sighs]
Easy, there. He must
be real drunk.
He never talks about his past.
[HIYORI]
All right. I should get going.
[YUKINE]
Hold on. I'll walk you.
[KOFUKU]
Have a good night, Yori!
[YATO] I'm happy!
--So very happy...
--[DAIKOKU] Yeah, yeah.
I'm on my own two feet now,
and it's all thanks to Hiyori.
On your own two feet?
Not if you're relying on
a schoolgirl all the time,
you're not.
[YATO]
I've decided.
I'm gonna make Hiyori the
happiest girl in the world.
You just watch me!
[DAIKOKU coughs]
[DAIKOKU]
I don't know if you meant that
the way it sounded.
[KOFUKU] It's totally different
for unknown gods like Yatty.
Once forgotten, they
vanish from existence.
If only my kid self
could see me now.
He'd be so happy
Yato... I wonder.
What kind of life
have you lived?
[phone rings]
[YATO gasps]
I wasn't sure you would
actually come, but you did.
[YATO] I came because
we need to talk, Hiiro.
[NORA] Do you know how nice
it is to hear you say my name?
I've decided I want
to end things with you.
And why's that?
Because I've got
my own shrine now.
And there's Yukine.
He's become a solid Regalia.
I don't want to
betray those things.
[NORA] And that's why you've
decided to release me?
[YATO]
Is that so bad?
You have plenty
of other masters.
You don't need me anymore.
Tell me, who made
me a Nora, Yato?
[gasps]
[NORA] You're horrible. We've
been together all this time.
And now you're just
going to abandon me
without a second thought?
[gasps]
Come! Hiki!
[YATO]
A mask!
[gasps]
Not you again...
[WOLF PHANTOM 2A]
Come. You should join us.
[grunting, groaning]
I think that will do for now.
[YATO groaning]
You know you won't
be able to fight off
so many Phantoms
without a Regalia.
Aw, so weak and sad.
Poor little Yato.
You can't exist
without a lifeline.
Now be a good boy
and do what Father says.
Things will be easier that way.
[HIYORI]
Hey, sorry to bother you.
But has Yato come back yet?
Sure hasn't.
[HIYORI] He's been gone
for an entire week now.
Something must have
happened to him!
You know what he's like.
There's no way he could
stay silent this long
unless there was a reason!
See, that's where you're wrong.
[KOFUKU]
It's not really that unusual.
Yatty goes into
hiding sometimes.
His Regalia used to show up
here a lot, looking for him.
[YUKINE] Still not back?
That's my master for ya.
Well, anyway, see ya, I'm
gonna go meet up with Kazuma.
Training's a good way
to start the morning.
[HIYORI] You're working so
hard to improve your skills.
In the meantime,
what's Yato doing?
[YUKINE]
How should I know?
He's probably with Nora.
He seems upset.
I'm afraid Yato
hasn't been by here.
[HIYORI]
Oh, okay.
[TENJIN]
Just a moment.
Uh?
It's fine for you to be
concerned about Yato, Hiyori.
Understandable, even.
But please try to keep your
devotion in check, won't you?
Are you attending school?
You aren't spending more
time with gods and Regalia
than with your friends
and family, are you?
Uh... No, not at all.
[TENJIN] Really? And what
about your hobbies?
Are you engaged in
ordinary teenage pursuits?
Do you even have a
boyfriend, young lady?
Lord, that's quite rude.
[TENJIN] Go forth and
enjoy your adolescence!
Um, okay.
[HIYORI]
I can't believe Yato!
He hasn't even told
Yukine what he's up to!
Well, he better not blame me
if everyone forgets him!
Not that that's likely to...
[gasps]
[HIYORI] Manabu forgot.
Could that happen to me, too?
No! I won't forget!
There's no way!
[YATO] I hope that doesn't
turn out to be a lie.
[yelps]
Whoa! Are you okay?
That's dangerous.
Better watch your step.
[HIYORI]
Hey! Thanks for catching me!
[MOTHER 8A sobbing]
[MOTHER 8A]
My daughter was murdered.
But they won't seek
capital punishment
because it was the
killer's first crime.
I saw him in the courtroom.
He was smiling.
Please! My sweet
daughter deserves justice!
Will you avenge her?
I've heard that you do that
sort of thing. Say yes!
Please!
[YATO]
Keep it.
[MOTHER 8A]
For what I'm asking...
[YATO]
This will be plenty.
[snoring]
[NORA] So what's the plan?
Cut him up on the inside?
[CRIMINAL 8A grunts]
Huh?
[giggles]
[screams]
[YATO]
Come, Hiki.
[CRIMINAL 8A]
Who-- Who are you? Stop!
[groans]
[sirens]
[MOTHER 8A] I just received a
call from the prison officials.
He died from
"undetermined causes."
Now my daughter
can rest in peace.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you so much!
[NORA] See? People
appreciate this type of job
a lot more than
cleaning bathrooms.
The Yato god could never
perform such great deeds
with Yukine as his Regalia.
You didn't actually
think you could stand
on your own two feet?
I don't know what that
girl may have told you,
but it was nonsense.
Nothing's changed,
can't you see that?
It's been this way forever.
Everyone has always
abandoned you.
You're a god of calamity.
Hiyori and Yukine will
never really accept
that aspect of you.
We do.
You see, we understand
what you are.
We'll never betray you.
Or stray from you.
Because we love you, Yato.
Well, what happened this time?
I've never known a god whose
health was so fragile.
Easy.
[IWAMI] Lord Okuninushi,
Lady Bishamoan.
We are most honored.
We're the two pillars
of the Gods of Fortune,
so it'd be nice if you would
quit slackin' off, Ebisu!
A little quieter, please.
Shut up. I'm tired of
visiting your sick ass.
Get better and come
to my Hawaiian shrine
so we can catch some waves.
[EBISU]
I'd rather go fishing.
[OKUNINUSHI]
No problem, I've got a boat.
We'll go catch some
mahi-mahi or somethin'.
What happened?
Were you blighted?
Did you hold an ablution?
I'm tired now.
[BOTH gasp]
[IWAMI] Pardon me, Lord
Okuninushi, Lady Bishamon.
I truly hate to ask
this, but perhaps...
[OKUNINUSHI]
Yeah, all right, we get it.
We'll come back later.
Don't let him die.
[OKUNINUSHI] I don't trust
those fools any further
than I can throw 'em.
How many more times
are his Regalia gonna
pull this kinda crap?
Ebisu does reincarnate
with disturbing frequency.
I know!
Do those bastards even care
about their master at all?
[OKUNINUSHI] Why does he
bother to keep them around?
[WOLF PHANTOM 8A growling]
[grunts]
[IWAMI]
Lord Ebisu.
Where have they gone?
[IWAMI] Your visitors
have left, my lord.
Turn away anybody else
who comes by as well.
I need to be alone for
a while, thank you.
[IWAMI]
No one shall disturb you.
What a shame.
It seems I'm not very
compatible with Ryoki.
All the Phantoms I turn into
puppets eventually taint me.
I must rectify that.
Yes, who's there?
I asked that I be undisturbed.
Ah, so it's you.
Really?
You've found the
Locution Brushes?
[crashing]
[CRIMINAL 8B] Uh! Wait! Stop!
I'll turn myself in!
[CRIMINAL 8B yelps]
[CRIMINAL 8C panting]
[CRIMINAL 8C screams]
[CRIMINAL 8D panting]
[screams]
[NORA]
Look at the irises blooming!
It's that time of year already?
[YATO]
Tell me, Hiiro.
[NORA]
Hm?
[YATO] How much longer are
you gonna make me do this?
I've had enough.
[YATO gasps] How long
have I been here?
Has it been a month now?
Hiyori! Has it been too long?
Has she forgotten me?
[YATO gasps]
What is it?
[YATO]
I need to go back right now.
Back to Hiyori!
[YATO]
Damn it!
[gasps]
[YATO]
Stay back!
[WOLF PHANTOM 2A]
Lord Yato.
Please try to calm yourself.
[YATO]
Let me out!
Let me go! I want
outta here, now!
Stay the hell out of my way!
[gasps]
There you are, Father.
Yato's saying that
he wants to leave.
I don't understand.
He's never said that before.
Really? Are you sure, Father?
Yato. We have a job for you.
He says you're free to do
as you wish once it's done.
We need to travel
to the underworld
and rescue a conjurer there.
[YATO]
The underworld?
[YAMA]
The Hundred Archfiends rock!
[AMI]
No! Zenny's is way cooler!
[YAMA] Tie-breaker. We'll
text Hiyori and ask her!
[AMI]
On the next Noragami Aragoto:
"The Sound of a
Thread Snapping." Well?
[YAMA] She says "victory
is decided with fists."
[AMI]
Ugh! Martial arts fans!