He's here!
You may be one step
closer to your goal
but I won't allow you
to make it a reality.
I will stop you.
[Music]
It's magnificent!
It is the master.
Our god.
Did your eyes feast on
the glorious triumph
you helped ensure,
Tempest Hoof, Fecor?
I can only hope.
It's time.
Prepare to bear witness.
As our god declares
his Grand Order!
Look to me!
You gaze upon divinity
in its purest form!
Rejoice in your
good fortune.
Set aside your fears.
My loyal servants,
the moment of
truth is upon us.
My heart and my power
have been restored to
their former glory.
You shall be rewarded
for your service.
I now declare the
Grand Order's final stage!
The end of a task
which began eons ago!
It is thus...
...in the rift between worlds,
I will create...
A paradise called Xanadu!
Xanadu?
This world will be the sum of
your desires made manifest.
Its sole purpose
will be to welcome and
provide for all Denizens
who reside in its embrace.
Some of you were
there millennia ago
when I first
attempted this feat.
I nearly succeeded
in its creation
but the Ancient Flame Haze
that I had invited in amity
decided to seal me
inside the Abyss.
After eons of aimless wandering,
I came to an epiphany.
I now know where this
utopia is destined to be born!
That fated place
is the very prison to
which I was banished!
What's more, as I
reshaped the Grand Order
the true form of our
paradise became clear.
It must not be hidden in a
small pocket of this world
for my Denizens
deserve better.
Instead, I will duplicate
the whole of creation!
That's my gift.
A complete world
that is only for you!
Everything you know
will be part of it,
and new life will spring
from its fertile womb!
That is Xanadu!
A sanctuary where
Power of Existence
flows inexorably and eternally!
It's within your grasp,
my loyal servants.
Nothing will keep me from making
the Grand Order a reality!
Finally, I will have
answered your prayers
and fulfilled my role
as God of Creation!
Uh. Hey, Balar, you
care to summarize?
The Snake of the Festival
plans to replicate this world
within the rift.
Thereby creating a proverbial
paradise for Denizens.
That would be an abomination!
Focus now.
This is bad.
Look at all the Denizens!
The declaration sent
them into a frenzy.
We lost this battle
when we failed to prevent the
God of Creation's revival.
Attempting to
salvage this fight,
would only result in a
needless loss of life.
Supreme Commander!
We're getting slaughtered!
What do you want us to do?
I don't know if those
were Yuji's words
or the Snake of
the Festival's.
We can't be certain.
Either way, our current
predicament is the same.
Caution, it seems, has
become our greatest ally.
Well, we can't do much
to help from up here,
so what's the plan?
Perhaps we should withdraw?
Ah.
We need a clear view
of the situation.
I suggest we head back
and consult with Supreme
Commander Sawallisch
in order to form
an exit strategy.
We've managed to gather
all remaining troops
to this location,
save the ones fighting
on the plains.
I assume you're well aware
of our forces' current status?
Indeed.
To say that we're
at a disadvantage
would be a grave
understatement at this point.
Yes, it certainly was quite
an embarrassing outcome,
but retreating is the last
option available to us.
If it's our last,
then it is our best;
regardless of how
humiliating it may be.
Pride is irrelevant now.
So then.
You've settled on withdrawing
from the battlefield.
But do you
completely understand
the gravity of
that decision?
Safely pulling out
such a small force
will not be an easy task.
Perhaps you have
a plan, then?
Centerhill, the Beckoner
of Brightened Dew,
has finally offered
his opinion.
Is it possible
this is a sign
that we can
expect assistance
from the Four Gods
of the Earth?
No.
He's yet to make a choice.
Yes, we understand
and we've prepared
a contingency plan
in case matters turn dire.
This operation has
been designated "Ebb".
Our main objective
will be this waypoint.
To the east, where
Heaven's Road Palace is hidden.
The best case scenario
would be for all forces
to rendezvous there.
It would serve as a mobile
shelter and ensure our escape.
It's a decent plan,
but it's flawed.
The objective isn't
exactly nearby.
In addition to that,
we'll have to make it there
while engaging enemy
forces in a running battle.
Then somebody's gonna
have to stay behind.
We'll need a unit dedicated
to making life hell
for the Denizens that try
to pursue us from the west.
Leave that to me.
My squad is already
in prime position
for covering a retreat.
You can start making your
way to Heaven's Road Palace,
while we make the idea of
chasing you akin to suicide.
A losing battle.
Huh.
That's easy.
We just keep fighting
until we're all in the dirt.
There are plenty of
foolhardy Denizens
to create a
mountain of corpses.
We mustn't let
them go to waste.
In order for this
operation to be successful,
it must be executed
swiftly and precisely.
Once we're outside the
castle, Khamsin, Rebecca,
you will act as
the rear guard.
And as for you two...
Our purpose is quite clear.
We'll go and provide backup for
the Guardian of Steady Passage,
and cover any stragglers.
Very well, as of this moment,
Operation Ebb is
officially underway.
Wilhelmina, Shana,
a moment, please.
Do you have additional
orders for us?
Not at all.
I just wanted to address a more
personal matter with Shana.
Unless you're comfortable
going into battle as you are,
you might want to
change your clothes.
I think it would adversely
affect our troop's morale
if their reinforcements showed
up looking shabby and beaten.
Please, forgive
the oversight.
There is no hope for you!
We will ensure our
master's triumph!
Destroy all who would
oppose his Grand Order!
For Xanadu!
Die!
You first!
I feel bad jumpin'
into my buddies fights
and stealin' their
thunder, ya know?
Well I wouldn't
feel too bad
because it looks like they
still got the finishing blow!
Good to hear!
I don't think our timing
could be any better;
their reinforcements
ain't here yet.
You're good to go;
we've got this in the bag!
Understood.
All troops, it's time
to start the withdrawal.
Now, head to the east!
My body.
It has yet to recover
from the debilitating
effects of the rift.
How infuriating.
Only the long-departed
can recall
who first wished
for our god.
It has been
thousands of years
since he was drawn
to this place
by the prayers
of the Denizens.
Hey, Professor,
there's something that's
been bothering me lately.
Who exactly is that
Rofocale character?
He acts as though he's
the Trinity's equal!
I don't understand why he walked
the Path of Pilgrimage with us!
Jeez.
When will the data
I collected
with the Excellent 252546
Logical Pilgrim's box
finish its transfer?
The anticipation is
splitting my brain cells!
You weren't even
listening to me, were you?
You'll have to wait a
while longer, Professor.
We collected a ridiculous
amount of data from the rift!
Well, to answer
your question,
he is a disciple of
the God of Creation.
No way!
He's a disciple, too?
So, he really
is their equal?
I wouldn't say that;
the Trinity works
as a perfect system
that can strategize, defend,
and carry out the God's will.
It'd be pointless to
consider someone
who couldn't fulfill those
roles as their equal.
Then why did you go
with them to the Path...
Drop it, Domino!
He asked the Denizens
what they desired.
They said, "For our
bellies to be full".
Thus their wish
was decided
and the god's
ceremony began.
I must admit,
I'm impressed by the amount
of damage the enemy dealt us.
But, our losses
are nothing
compared to what
we've gained.
Then again, Bal Masque
was founded
to achieve this very goal.
So, they can't be
thought of as 'losses'.
The greatest of
hunters gathered
in the hopes of
stopping the god.
They bravely
sacrificed themselves
to forever seal
him in the Abyss.
We lost our god and
our hopes in that war.
But, from that defeat,
we learned how we
would rise again.
Strength in numbers.
A consortium of Denizens,
driven as one toward
a single goal.
Time passed,
flowed onward.
And now, three
thousand years later.
He has returned
once again
to grant the wish
of the masses.
Our god.
The Snake of the Festival.
The legendary
God of Creation.
There's another wave
comin' in fast, sir!
Our retreating forces
are depending on us
to hold the line!
Do not let a single
Denizen make it through!
Emblaze!
I'm the contractor of the
Flame of Heaven, Alastor,
the God of Atonement!
The Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter.
Shana!
And I'm the contractor
of Tiamat,
the Tiara of Dreams
and Illusions.
Wilhelmina Carmel.
The Specialist
of Everything!
Thank you both.
You are just in time!
This fortress is vital to
our operation's success.
There's no need
for thanks.
Your troops can't
do this alone.
So we'll help
lighten the load!
We've caught two more
birds in our trap
without even trying.
Attack squads,
fall back at once!
We're moving forward
with our plan.
They're withdrawing!
But why?
They had us cornered!
All forces, be on guard!
Rinne artillery spotted
to the west of us,
in the center of the plains!
We fell right
into their trap!
If all of those were to
hit at the same time...
We won't let them
get the best of us.
Concentrate your power!
Get ready!
Barricade.
Prevent passage.
And terminate.
Thy name is disgrace.
Zikmund's Gate!
This is the Unrestricted
Spell of the Guardian
of Steady Passage,
Samuel Demantius.
Stay on your guard!
He collects Power of
Existence from his comrades
to reinforce the
structures he creates.
A powerful Unrestricted
Spell, indeed.
An impressive talent.
Awesome, we've put some
distance between them!
Ah. It seems they
have no intention
of making things
easy for us.
Especially since the
forces responsible
for that surprise attack are
finally entering the fray.
More bodies means we've
got more to explode!
Let's go!
Supreme Commander, the enemy's
launched a full-scale attack!
Godspeed, comrades.
I've never seen
anything like it.
The flames of battle burn
bodies and souls alike.
There is not a
remnant left behind.
It's ironic.
In order to prevent
future carnage,
I must instigate it now.
To protect them.
To protect her.
At this very moment,
an innocent human's soul
is being devoured.
Nobody will even
realize they're gone.
There will be no
one to mourn them,
no memories to cherish.
Why would anyone want to
protect such a horrible world?
If I truly have the power
to change it, then I will!
No, I must!
If I don't, the Flame Haze
will be forced to
keep fighting forever.
Please! Do not
stand in my way.
I beg of you!
Hear me, Flame Haze!
The Lords who would
slay their brethren
and the humans they
use as weapons!
You have no cause
to resist me!
It was never my intention
to fill your hearts
with unbridled terror.
You have allowed your ancestors'
admonitions of disaster
to weigh upon you
for far too long.
I assure you,
the execution of
the Grand Order
will bring everlasting
peace to all of creation!
I realize that you have
concerns about our paradise,
Xanadu, being shaped within
the rift between worlds.
Perhaps I will set
your minds at ease
when I tell you with
absolute certainty,
despite what you have
been told for millennia,
No, he's lying.
You mustn't listen
to what he says!
I have spent thousands
of years in the rift
perfecting the
process of creation,
thereby eliminating any
chance of such a catastrophe.
In other words,
the disaster that
frightened your ancestors
enough to trap me in the
Abyss is now an impossibility!
Furthermore, I plan to gather
all of the Crimson Denizens
in this world
and take them to
Xanadu with me!
You have my word,
once Xanadu is complete we
will leave and never return.
We will leave a world in which
humans no longer disappear
and their souls
are not devoured.
Lay down your arms
and let us leave.
In doing so,
you will bring peace to the
humans once and for all.
Yuji!
You needn't
fight any more.
If you'll allow it,
we will free you from your
struggle, Flame Haze.
The battle you have fought for
millennia has now concluded.
It is over.
You must try to
calm down, Francois!
But I can't!
Because if his plan
is successful,
if that happens,
then there'll be no reason for
us to exist in this world.
We've lost,
Supreme Commander,
so what's the point
of trying to...
How can you say that?
We're still in the
midst of battle!
Sorry Grogach,
I won't give up.
It's pointless.
I mean, why
should we fight?
I guess, we're
no longer needed.
Do not give up!
Please everyone,
just calm down!
This is exactly what
the enemy wants!
We mustn't allow ourselves
to succumb to panic and chaos!
Please!
What a display of power.
All the God of Creation had to
do was utter a few words,
suddenly he's
won the battle
and the Flame Haze have lost
their sense of purpose.
Ah, it's done.
Dammit, this
ain't happening!
There's no way we can
regroup our forces now!
This is pure chaos.
I cannot believe our army
has fallen into disarray.
Our very existence as
Flame Haze is meaningless, now.
It's understandable.
Regardless, we
cannot sit idly by
and wait for annihilation!
I agree with you!
We mustn't waste our energy
worrying about our purpose
or whether we'll
win this battle!
Instead, we'll take
what we've learned
and use it to our
advantage in the next one.
But first...
We save as many
Flame Haze as possible,
and find the Supreme Commander!
I never imagined I would
secure a flawless victory
for Bal Masque
against you, Sirotci.
But now that I have,
doubtful our paths
will ever cross again.
Therefore, in tribute,
I shall leave you with
this cannon salute.
May you rest in peace.
Fire.
All forces are now
ordered to withdraw!
Just keep running!
Go east as fast
as you can!
We'll cover you, just run!
I couldn't do anything.
Not at all.
I've failed in every way.
Because I haven't
faced Yuji.
I still feel something.
Burning within me.
I may not understand it.
But my purpose is clear.
After their morale
is destroyed,
the Flame Haze Army falls
into utter disarray.
The rain begins to fall
and with it comes
a glimmer of hope.
Have their prayers
finally been answered?
Next time, on
Shakugan no Shana Final:
"Rout in the Rain."