I'll show you and
the rest of the world...
my desire for change!
Yes...
That is my heart's desire...
And it will
soon be reality.
My Unrestricted Spells
still aren't strong enough
to get me out of this...
There's only one
thing I can do...
All military forces are
now ordered to advance!
[Music]
Ah, sorry to make you
get up at this hour.
But it would
be best for us
to get an early start
on our journey.
I wish Sato was here to
say goodbye to you guys.
Jeez, it's not like
they're leavin' forever!
They'll see him when they
make it back to town.
Eita Tanaka...
I hope you understand...
how grateful I am to
you and Keisaku...
Thank you... for all that you've
done to help us thus far...
Please follow
the instructions
I've left for
Margery's care...
Hopefully, it won't
be too long...
'til we meet again.
Take care of yourself.
Yeah, you too...
Hope ya make it out ali...
I'm sorry, that slipped out...
Uh... You're gonna be fine;
I don't know what I'm sayin'.
We'll catch up with ya whenever
sleeping beauty wakes up.
Don't hog all the fun
before we get there.
Indeed, we'll be
looking out for you.
Anticipated reunion.
I really don't want
to get involved...
but now that I know the world's
fate is riding on this war...
I don't think I'll
have any choice
but to get involved
at some point.
Good luck out there...
Our world is counting on you.
It's been several days
since Bal Masque's army left
the Palace of the Stars.
I can't help but wonder
whether the fighting's
already started...
Surely, I would know...
A war between Flame Haze
and Denizens
would quickly spread
all over the world.
If so, Bal Masque is fighting
without the Trinity...
Thousand Changes, Sydonay...
The Judge of Paradoxes,
Bel-Peol...
And the Supreme
Throne, Hecate.
The Flame Haze army should
attack while they're away
and their army is weak...
Hopefully...
Sophie Sawallisch has
come up with a strategy.
For now, all I can do is have
faith and wait patiently...
until it's my turn
to join the battle.
We're finished, my lady.
I wonder if Wilhelmina...
is out there
fighting somewhere.
You must move quickly.
Indeed, I will.
Aw, c'mon...!
I don't understand what the
heck's takin' her so long?!
She's only been gone
for half an hour.
Do ya think she could
be stuck on somethin'?
Maybe we should
go check on her?
She'll be fine...
She lived there
for a long time
so she's probably
just reminiscing.
She requested to go
down there alone...
and we should
respect her wishes.
Patience is a virtue.
Fine...
I'll show you
patience, buddy!
Come on!
Please, grant me your power.
Heaven's Road Palace...
Surface!
Oh wow!
I suspect their objective
in the Eastern
Theater is Japan.
It would appear
they are attempting to
push our defensive lines
back to America.
Uh... Commander...?
Let me guess,
they've attacked Tokyo?
Yes how very
perceptive of you.
If so... why haven't we
received emergency reports?
Well?! Answer the man!
It seems we've
lost all contact
with our Tokyo Headquarters...
They've surrounded
it with a Seal...
The war has begun.
Second barrage...
Fire!
Attention
artillery squads...
you may fire at will!
Disregard the Rinne.
Attack squads follow me!
Charge!
Heavy damage to
Central Park!
Enemy forces have been
reported in the shrine garden,
heading towards the
Nishi-Sandoguchi intersection!
The Choja Bashi Defense
Force is en route.
Northern forces are
falling back to the
Shimizu-Bashi intersection.
Damn Ribesal...
It seems he's just as
good a Commander as ever.
Are we okay here?
You don't think he'll come
looking for us, do you?
Sir...! One of our
northern squadrons...
has launched an assault!
What?!
That'll show 'em...
Never underestimate
a Flame Haze!
Let's break through
their lines!
What the hell?!
No! Don't breathe
in the mist!
It's the Unrestricted
Spell Daimon!
Damn, I tried
to warn them.
Betcha we can snap
'em out of it...
if we just punch
'em hard enough.
That was too easy.
Our northern lines have
fallen into disarray!
It's a rout, sir!
They should have listened.
Um, do you think maybe
it's time for us
to go somewhere
safer Flieder?
Yes, Brigid...
I'd have to agree.
Everyone, it's come
to my attention
that our safety has
been jeopardized here...
Therefore... we must move to
the emergency command room!
Yes, sir!
Withdraw...! Who'll send a
message to the front lines?!
I'll take care of that.
If I don't make it back,
you're going to
have to take command.
Yes, sir.
But don't you worry!
I'm sure we'll make
it back safely!
This could be dangerous...
Will you join me?
Yes, of course!
I'll take it from here...
Hurry and get
her to safety!
Well, well, well.
I haven't seen you in seventy
or eighty years, Ernest...
Oh, excuse me...
You go by Flieder
now, don't you?
Ribesal...
I would think a high-ranking
commander, like yourself,
would know better than to
fight on the front lines.
I imagine Pirsoyn
finds it exhausting.
Shut up!
You can't fool me!
There's the real one!
We've got you now!
We've received a
status report...
It's from a messenger who was
able to get outside the Seal.
They confirm the presence
of enemy commander,
Dashing Earthly
Fiend Ribesal.
They go on to report that
our forces confronted him
in Shinjuku as planned.
We correctly identified
their location...
Has there been any change
on the Western Front?
No, I've been keeping
an eye on it, sir...
I haven't noticed
any major changes.
As far as I can tell,
their attacks seem
to be intensifying.
An attempt to
distract us, no doubt.
In the Western Theater,
Burning Agitation Haborym
and his forces
have besieged our headquarters
in Romania, Andrei Fortress.
Distraction or not, their
attacks have been relentless.
We've no choice but to
match their efforts.
It is imperative that we
defend the Outlaw posts,
otherwise we risk
compromising our future plans.
So far, so good.
Several posts have
sustained serious damage,
but thankfully none
of them have fallen.
They've launched a
coordinated attack
to both the East and West...
The fronts in
this war are larger
than any other in
recorded history.
And to think, it's all to
divert our attention away
from the Trinity.
Their Strategist,
the Judge of Paradoxes
is convinced one of
our fronts will fall.
She knows if that
were to happen,
we would be too busy
rebuilding our lines
to adequately
protect ourselves.
It appears...
the enemy has deployed the
majority of their forces
to fight in the
two fronts...
so, we can assume that
only a handful of troops
were left behind to guard
the Palace of the Stars.
In other words, this would
be the perfect time
to launch a surprise attack.
While it is a
risky strategy...
I wholeheartedly
trust your judgment
and therefore agree that
this is exactly how
we should proceed.
We've been watching for
Thousand Changes Sydonay
but he's yet to make an
appearance on the battlefield.
I believe his absence confirms
what we already suspected...
The Trinity is
up to something.
Yes, indeed...
and it doesn't
surprise me...
What is it, ma'am?
One of the Four Gods...
The Beckoner of
Brightened Dew...
Centerhill?
I don't understand...
As long as it is not too
much of an imposition,
we would like to temporarily
join your ranks.
Does this mean we can
expect assistance
from the Four Gods of the
Earth in this battle?
No... the other three gods have
asked that I observe you...
and then report
my findings.
We have yet to decide
whose side we will take.
Bal Masque is
endangering the Earth
by attempting to revive
the God of Creation.
Knowing that,
how could you
still be uncertain
of your stance
on the matter?
As you know, we four
priests received our powers
from those Crimson Lords
revered as gods...
And we have
devoted our lives
to destroying the evil
spirits known as Denizens.
After much deliberation
on the subject,
we've come to
this conclusion...
It makes no
difference whether...
they act as gods or prowl
the Earth as evil spirits...
Since time immemorial,
Crimson Denizens have
been an integral part
of the natural
order of this world.
As it is our duty to
uphold that order,
we cannot simply act
without first determining
the true intentions of
the one who calls himself
the God of Creation.
Therefore, until we
have that information...
we must remain neutral.
However...
once you have ascertained
Bal Masque's true intentions,
you will clarify
your position?
Yes.
Then there's
still a possibility
that you will
agree to help us?
In that case...
I would be more
than honored
to grant you a
place at our table.
We've positioned
saboteur teams
at radar stations
across Europe.
According to our reports,
initial transports
have already departed.
The second and third
waves are set to depart
on schedule as well.
Everything's going
exactly as planned.
How were you able to
gather all that data
on such short notice?
Well... you see...
We've worked for Outlaw...
for several hundred
years now, sir.
I'm so sorry I made a mess
of things, Supreme Commander!
You must calm yourself,
Adjutant Francois Auric.
You mustn't get flustered...
for the fate of the world
is now dependent
upon your judgment.
Sir!
The path to life is found
only beyond death's horizon...
young man.
The real fight has
only just begun.
The storm is rolling in.
Excellent! Isn't this exciting?!
Have you ever seen
anything so wondrous?!
I can't believe the
Abyss is so colorful!
It's even more spectacular
than I'd imagined!
This is Path of Pilgrimage...
How were you
capable of building
such a massive
structure in the rift
between the two worlds?
He's a god...
He's capable of anything!
That's correct...
my power allowed
me to create it...
This intricate...
Meandering...
pathway...
leading to myself.
Which we... now walk.
It's not as though we have
any choice, Priestess.
We've no other option.
I don't think
you realize...
how lucky you are to
have this experience.
The Path of Pilgrimage
was constructed by
the master himself.
He used his powers as a
god to craft deprivation,
suffering and despair
into a physical path.
Because of its
transient nature,
we must travel in the
company of the Priestess.
She is the only one capable
of picking up the signal
emitted by the Insignia,
which is linked to
the master's body.
Without her unique ability
we would lose our
way, or worse...
Ain't that the truth?!
If my calculations
are correct,
only fifty-four percent
of the Path of Pilgrimage
has materialized.
There are areas where the
percentage can drop to
as low as thirty-four!
So watch your step!
There's no need
for you to worry!
We'll be fine as
long as we continue
to follow the Priestess!
There isn't even a
microscopic chance
that we could get lost!
Hurry...
It's a long walk.
I seek the path but all
that returns to me...
is the sound of
wind and sand.
Decarabia reporting.
Do you read me,
Fortress Commander?
Yes, indeed...
I read you loud and clear,
Supreme Commander.
I hope all is well with
our offensive forces.
Any news to report?
All troops have
been deployed
to their various
stations as planned...
However...
What is it?
It concerns me that
there has been no sign
of The Braider of Trembling
Might, Sophie Sawallisch.
Do you suppose she
could be lying in wait
for General Sydonay...?
I'm sure she finds his
absence suspicious.
It is a possibility,
but an obvious one...
too obvious.
Fortress Commander Fecor,
I request permission to
prepare the forces charged
with protecting the Palace
of the Stars for battle.
The forces here?
You do realize the enemy
can not find the Palace,
let alone attack it,
while it's concealed by the
Crypta Unrestricted Spell.
If you have any
evidence otherwise,
please fill me in.
I have no evidence...
And I am well aware
that although the Palace
is centuries old,
its presence has never
been detected by an enemy.
Then why...?
Call it intuition.
Everything is
going too smoothly.
The Flame Haze have
been oddly quiet
which leads me to believe they
must be plotting something.
Then permission is granted...
Supreme Commander...
do whatever you must...
to protect the
Palace of the Stars
until the master can return.
Very well...
I will make the
order at once.
I don't understand...
Why didn't my Unrestricted
Spell work against Yuji?
Is it because I haven't
mastered it yet...?
Or is he so powerful now that
it's too weak to affect him?
I don't know...
When he left, it was almost
too easy to say goodbye.
But now...
I wanna see him.
I wanna see Yuji!
He's the leader of my
enemy, Bal Masque...
and I'm the Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter...
If we came face-to-face
we would have to fight.
I know that but
I don't care...
I just wanna see him again.
That's the only way
I'll know for sure...
You've got to stop
fooling yourself, child.
The time has come to
unite you with yourself.
The Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter and Shana
must become one
and the same...
Otherwise I'll never be
able to confront him
and show him the new
power I've found.
The strongest
Unrestricted Spell...
This love I feel for him.
The problem is...
I can't do anything
as long as he's
holding me captive.
If I tried to confront him
while I'm helpless like this,
he'd easily defeat me.
I need to break free of
this restrictive chain
and recover my
Flame Haze powers.
To do that, something's
gotta happen...
Something that'll give
me the opening I need.
This is ridiculous!
The biggest war in history
is being fought as we speak
and we get stuck down
here on watchman duty?!
Why do we have to miss
out on all the fun?!
Would you quit
your whining?
Supreme Commander
Decarabia ordered us
to protect the
Palace of the Stars.
Protect it from what?
Give me a break!
It's not like the
enemy's gonna come here.
What's wrong?
Who is that?
Man this sucks...!
I mean the freakin'
war of the century
is goin' on out there...
Why did we agree to hang out
in this musty, old Palace?
Yo!
You seem cool
but... ya gotta go.
Okay...
Ready to get started...
old man?
Yeah, I'm ready
if you are...
but we should probably get
outside the Palace walls first.
Ceremonial...
Equipment.
Deploy Qadesh's
Blood Seal.
Activate.
Constructing
Unrestricted Spell:
Qadesh's Blood Pulse.
Deploying!
Synchronizing to
Unrestricted Spell:
Qadesh's Blood Pulse.
That is so cool!
We'd better get a move on!
Gotcha!
Yahoo!
Wanna help the big guy
tear the place down, Balar?
You know it!
There's nothing I enjoy more
than wreaking destruction!
This is it...!
The distraction I
need to break free!
What's going on?
Ya ready, Gramps?!
Let's go!
Rebecca and Khamsin's attack
on the Palace of the Stars
causes it to
descend into chaos.
Amidst the confusion,
Shana waits for
the perfect moment
to make a break
for her freedom.
Next time, on Shakugan
no Shana Final:
"To the Palace of the Stars."