You're no longer... needed.
[Music]
Outstanding work, Priestess.
Thanks to you,
the Palace has reached
the exact coordinates.
What makes this
spot special?
If you're trying to
collect intelligence...
you should really try being more
discreet about it, you know?
Indeed...
but we've nothing
to hide from him...
this is where I will
create a gate to the Abyss.
Futile...!
Your spirit may
have found refuge
but your body is
lost for eternity!
Accept it!
No one is capable of escaping
banishment to the Abyss!
Not even you,
God of Creation.
So... naive.
You should not
take me lightly...
nor the resolve of
those who follow me.
My loyal servants and
I have gathered here
in the hopes of reshaping
this world for the better...
To do so,
we will enact a plan
set in motion millennia ago.
As I was swallowed
by the Abyss,
the Strategist sent
me the Insignia,
a piece of her existence
that would be my salvation.
Well, if I'm not needed,
then just let me go!
Sydonay finds your
presence to be amusing,.
but nonetheless essential to
Bal Masque's overall objective.
For now, Bel-Peol appears
to be of the same
school of thought...
And even though
she is aware
of our master's
fascination with you...
she is bound and determined
to keep it from
affecting our operation.
She's attacking without
casting a Seal...
My opinion, however...
is that you are
wholly unnecessary...
Especially in regard to
the master's Grand Order!
In fact... I feel you are a
threat to its very existence!
No way...
she's here of her
own accord...?
Now... be gone!
I communicated with the
Priestess through the Insignia.
After years of
meticulous work,
she ultimately succeeded in
creating an Unrestricted Spell
that would be capable
of enforcing my will.
Yes, it's the spell you
know as the Taimei Shihen
The Psalm of the
Grand Order...
My servant's set upon the
task of creating a vessel...
while I forged a path
through the Abyss...
Eventually, the vessel would
wield my power in this world,
and create a gateway
leading back to that path.
Despite thousands of years
and countless setbacks,
the Snake remained
patient in his prison...
until a suitable vessel
was finally found.
So once you form this gate,
you intend to
travel the path,
and reclaim your
original body?
Precisely, so.
Divine Gate...
I command you to...
open!
We've come here...
because these coordinates
are the closest to my
body's resting place...
Once the gate has
materialized...
I will finally be able
to reclaim what is mine.
It is done.
Now that the gate
has been opened...
the Grand Order will
soon come to fruition.
Your flame shall extinguish...
by my hand!
You!
You've surprised me.
Sorry...
Master.
But I did so for you...!
Her mere presence is toxic...
and is a threat to
the Grand Order!
This girl is the avatar
of the god slayer,
the dark God of Atonement...
For your sake;
for the order's sake...
I implore you, Master,
destroy this Flame Haze!
Her disdain for you
is nearly palpable...
isn't it, Flame of Heaven?
My loyal Priestess...
I applaud you for
your forward thinking.
However... you've
clearly underestimated
the worth of this Flame Haze.
Did you ever stop to
consider my motives
for capturing the Flaming-
Haired Blazing-Eyed Hunter?
While the feelings
of Yuji Sakai...
may well have played
a trivial role...
they alone did
not sway me.
Let's say I was to
do as you suggest
and kill her right here....
What would happen?
It's possible that,
in a fit of rage...
the Flame of Heaven would
launch a last ditch attack...
and attempt to reduce
me to smoldering ash
in the few seconds
available to him.
But he won't...
such an act is far too brash
for a Lord of his standards...
All of that power,
yet he remains willingly bound
to his rules and principles...
regardless of the cost.
If Shana's life were to end,
he would return to
the Crimson World
to forge another contract.
Then, at the worst
possible moment,
he would appear with
his new Flame Haze
and perform the Tenpa Jousai.
Can you see, now,
why the presence
of this contractor
is such a blessing,
Priestess...?
It would be an utter waste of
good fortune to kill her...
As long as we continue
to have her restricted...
we've, effectively,
put a leash on the God
of Atonement as well.
Oh my...
it appears that you've made
quite a mess of things, Hecate.
So, this is how it feels
to realize ones' destiny!
All I had to do was ask
and then the work
was done for me...!
How exhilarating!
A little more time,
and my wish will no longer
be out of arm's reach.
I can't believe Margery had
to go overseas on business!
That's a bummer.
I was hoping we could
have another study fest,
but I guess that's
totally shot.
Have any idea where Tanaka and
Sato have been hiding lately...?
You'd think they'd
at least call me.
Uh-uh.
Well, it's all good...
it'll be a nonstop party when
the gang gets back together.
I sure hope so!
Will the gang
hang out again?
I appreciate all that Shana has
done to protect this place...
and, I know that somewhere,
Sakai is trying
to do the same...
But... why've I
been left behind?
There must be
something I can do...
Fascinating, the base concept
is really quite simple.
Dantalion...
If it's not too imposing,
I'd like to tamper
with the material here.
No, tamper away...!
I have a backup
in the Conloquim,
so as far as I'm concerned,
you can fiddle with it
to your heart's content.
Go ahead buddy!
Thank you for your
enthusiastic generosity.
This is a first, you seem
thoroughly unsettled.
I hate to be the
bearer of bad news...
but it seems
there's discord
among the collective magics.
If what I'm
sensing is correct,
the "Absorption" spell has been
active for quite some time;
even before unification.
What?!
The only being who
would've required
such an Unrestricted Spell
was the second Tyrant...
to gather emotional fragments
to form its personality...
Unless you can
think of another?
Brilliant deduction!
However, you mustn't forget
the two Tyrants function
as a single unit!
For compatibility's sake,
the same spells that
gave life to the second,
are embedded in the first,
which Sabrac put inside
the Midnight Lost Child.
Well that's funny...
I made sure to deactivate
the "Absorption" function
and yet... it impatiently
decided to power up
all by itself!
I don't suppose you
have any theories
on what may have caused
this grievous error?
I'm not certain...
but I would speculate
this distortion
was caused by
exposure to the Keeper
that was placed on the
Midnight Lost Child.
I'll take the time
to look into this
while I'm investigating
your other concerns,
regarding the instability
of the Treasure Tool.
I can't remember the last time
you came drinking with us...
How long's it been?
Couldn't tell ya...
been a helluva long time,
that's for sure.
Long enough to forget
how bad the drinks are!
Their excitement's
infectious...
And so is their anxiety...
S'pose it's to be expected
before going to war.
Can't blame 'em.
Sorry fellas...
When you go into battle,
I won't be there to
fight alongside you.
Forgiveness isn't needed...
if the General is absent,
the battlefield shall
shake in his honor!
As you journey to
that forsaken place,
rest assured your men will
fight to the bitter end.
We commend your bravery
for accompanying the
master into the Abyss...
If only you could bring
along your army...
we would gladly
follow you.
The sword should not be
concerned with the shield...
for they have both
been forged by fate
and are guided with resolution
towards their common goal...
Should the shield fall...
It will fall with honor
and drag the enemy,
screaming, down with it.
Yes, General Sydonay...?
No one can predict what might
happen in times of war...
The tides can change
at any moment,
so stay vigilant.
You've not told me anything
I don't already know...
As long as I'm in command,
I foresee no problems.
Take care of my men
and there won't be.
The strategy is simple,
offensive on the front and
defensive in reserve...
Both your soldiers and the
Palace shall be well protected.
I'll hold you to that...
you better not let
me down, Decarabia.
Ah... I've been informed of
what happened after we
last saw each other...
You have my condolences.
If it would comfort you...
we could deliver a message to
the Specialist of Everything
when we rendezvous with her.
No, that's okay...
thank you though.
Well, if you're
sure about it.
Perhaps it was
rude of me to ask?
You realize that, in order
to defeat their leader,
Yuji Sakai has to
fall as well...
Doesn't that bother you?
I must admit,
I expected you would implore
us to save the Mystes.
I don't have any right
to request that...
So many Flame Haze are
about to risk their lives
to protect this world...
and defeating Sakai is the
quickest way to do that.
So...
it would be selfish to put
my feelings before that.
Also... back at the
Crystal Altar...
when he said
goodbye to me...
I think it was him ...
No, I'm sure of it!
It was Sakai...
not Snake, talking to me...
I know he's still in
there somewhere...
He may even be
there willingly,
and if that happens
to be the case...
He doesn't need me...
And the most arrogant
thing I could do
would be to interfere.
Ah... Very well said.
Forgive us, we did
not mean to pry.
I can't help feeling
we underestimated her.
It would seem so...
Humans are certainly full
of surprises, aren't they?
Khamsin?
Behemoth?
I could really
use your help...
If you have a
moment to spare.
Ah...
How can we help you?
I have a question about
this Treasure Tool.
May I come in...
Shana?
Have you recovered
from earlier?
Yes... I'm fine.
Beautiful.
Shana...
Come with me, please.
Where are we going?
Up the stairs,
for starters.
I want you by my side
to witness the start
of this great journey.
Journey to where?
Towards destiny...
The time has come to retrieve
the God of Creation's body
from the Abyss.
What's going to happen once
he's accomplished that goal...
and he has no use for you?
Don't worry...
It's true Yuji Sakai
is the bearer of the
Midnight Lost Child...
But, understand...
if his worth ended there I
would not have chosen him...
to be the vessel
of my true will.
I've no intention
of discarding him...
You needn't be concerned
for his well-being.
Oh, and Shana...
I have no intention
of sacrificing myself
for the world...
so don't worry.
I'm following this path so
I can protect everyone...
and so that we
can be together.
Those... are my
heart's... desires.
I don't understand why
Pheles gave this to me.
It seems so selfish
of a Flame Haze
to ask a human to
bear this burden.
Shana did
everything she could
to help Pheles rescue Johann
from the Midnight Lost Child.
And I was supposed
to use this
if it ever came
into jeopardy...
However...
If I did use it, it'd
deplete my Power of Existence
and I'd lose all hope
of being with Sakai.
On the other hand,
if it turned out that Sakai was
in love with someone else...
The sorrow would wash
away the feelings
I'd need to even utilize it.
Pheles knew this...
and yet, she gave
it to me anyway.
Ah... I understand.
You wish to know why the
Caprice of Beauty entrusted you
with an item meant to
safeguard the Eternal Lover.
Especially if the risk
of you being unable
to use it was so high.
Yes... I'm so confused...
I don't know...
what was behind
her reasoning.
With the way things
are right now...
I doubt I'd ever be able
to make this work...
And it's not...
because I'm afraid of
disappearing or anything...
Though the thought isn't
really a pleasant one.
It's because I know...
that Sakai's path
to happiness...
has turned so far
away from mine,
they will never
come together again.
All I wanted was to
share joy with him...
and even though I know
that can't happen...
I suggest you go
home, Yoshida.
There's no way I
can turn back now!
Whether I like
it or not...
the reason that
I am here...
is because of the
choices that I've made,
and no one else can take
responsibility for them!
Especially not Sakai!
I want to help,
but to do that,
I need you to
help me understand
why Pheles gave this
Treasure Tool to me.
Human beings truly are
beautiful and mysterious
creatures aren't they, Behemoth?
Indeed, Khamsin Nbh'w...
And that is
just one reason
our constant struggle
has so much meaning.
Alright... I'll do
what I can to help you...
But, I'll warn you...
this story won't
be easy to hear.
A long time ago...
in a kingdom
of burning sands,
there was a Prince who
possessed unnatural talent.
One day, a monster who
fed on Power of Existence
came to his country.
In order to defend
his beloved King,
the Prince
challenged the beast.
He used every ounce
of skill and power
he had in the fight...
Though he knew full well
the King he fought
for despised him.
Unfortunately,
the Prince lost...
And as he lay there, about
to be consumed by the monster,
a strange voice called
out from the heavens.
"If you will abandon
your human existence
and become my vessel,"
it said...
"I will grant you
unimaginable power."
The Prince accepted
the offer,
and drove the monster away.
But, the power he had
received came at a cost.
After risking his
life for the King
and the people
of his country,
not one of them could
even remember him.
That was what it meant to
abandon one's existence;
everything he'd
ever loved was lost.
With nothing left
to call his own,
the Prince set out in
search of the monster.
Hundreds of years passed
until the Prince finally
tracked down the beast.
It was such a cruel
irony that he hunted
the only being who
remembered who he was.
The Prince hated
the monster;
he blamed it for
everything he'd lost.
But after chasing
it for so long,
he'd come to love the beast
for giving him a purpose
and the creature
loved him in return
for granting it the same.
I don't understand...
The Prince slew the beast
as it lay in his arms.
It in turn,
inflicted a deep,
but not quite fatal,
wound on him.
Both regretted
their actions,
but knew it was
their destiny.
In the end, the pair
was heartbroken.
The same fate that had once
guided the hunter to his prey
now forced them to be torn
away from one another.
So, in defiance
of that fate...
They united in death.
Though tragic,
that was love...
And, while lovers may
come to curse, hate,
or even kill each other,
their bond is eternal
and never fades away.
An affection that
grows too strong...
may make those
outcomes inevitable.
Love is never as simple...
as sharing the same path.
Good evening, Master...
Your faithful subjects
await your word.
Very well.
So many Denizens...!
Are your hearts
ablaze with pride?!
Are your bodies
trembling with glory?!
Then you are destined to
walk this path with me!
Due to your diligence...
and courage...
I have returned to
fulfill the Grand Order.
Through this Divine Gate...
my body is bound
in chaos...
I plan to shatter
it's chains,
and finally reclaim what
rightfully belongs to me,
the God of Creation...
the Snake of the Festival!
While you remain here,
I task you!
Guard the Palace
of the Stars...
until I can return
here with the Trinity!
Let your gleaming
blades and claws
be as sharp as your wits!
Let that burning pride
scorch your foes,
and may the bellowing howls
be heralds of your wrath
as you call to them...
"No more!"...
Give no quarter, for you
will be shown no mercy!
Prove to the enemy
that you exist...!
Remember... you fight...
for the future!
From your courage...
I will be able to reach
the final stage...
of our glorious
Grand Order!
And then, I will
change the world...
I swear it!
Don't worry...
I'll return.
And when I do,
I'll show you...
As well as the
entire world...
My desire for change!
[Music]
In an attempt to
rescue Shana,
Wilhelmina raises
Heaven's Road Palace
from its watery grave.
Meanwhile, Supreme Commander
Sophie Sawallisch,
sets her own plan
into motion.
Next time on Shakugan
no Shana: Final;
"The War Begins."