Hold your lines!
The situation is
worse than we thought.
You should consider withdrawing
while you still can.
It would be irresponsible
for us to leave now.
We've yet to see anything
that would sway our stance.
How can that be?
Is there something wrong?
No, ma'am.
I feel a strange energy
emanating from the gate.
But what is it?
There is a strong presence
on the other side.
Who could it be?
You don't think this means
the Snake of the Festival's
returned, do you?
That would be my guess.
I hate to damage such
beautiful artwork.
It's nothing but a
god's ephemeral dream
of the living world.
You shouldn't feel
guilty for destroying it.
Ah, that was too
close for comfort.
So much as a scratch from
his blade could prove deadly.
We must proceed
with caution.
Yeah, to put it lightly.
Just as we planned.
Ceremonial Equipment.
Deploy Qadesh's
Blood Seal.
Activate.
Constructing
Unrestricted Spell:
Qadesh's Blood Pulse.
Deploying.
Synchronizing to
Unrestricted Spell:
Qadesh's Blood Pulse.
Impossible!
Ah, it worked.
It did, indeed.
Your attacks weren't
aimed at me;
their sole purpose was
to produce rubble.
You may be sharp but
you can't outwit me.
Ah.
He's found our weakness.
He's ripping
apart the debris
we worked so
hard to collect.
Battle breeds destruction.
We have no choice but
to accept it as fact,
for that is the
way of the world.
You may find this
hard to believe,
but you and I aren't really all
that different from one another.
We both lead
clandestine lives,
carrying out our missions,
and killing as we are told.
And, like you, I often
find myself victorious
not because of an
innate talent or gift...
...but because of the vast
power that I command.
Come on.
Destroy!
Khamsin Nbh'w!
Awaken!
I don't understand.
What point is there
in obsessing over
something this futile.
Shana. If you'll agree
to lay down your sword,
I'll allow you to
return to my side,
and we will forget
this ever happened.
I'd be more than happy
to lay down my sword
if you'll agree to stop working
for the enemy and help me!
Why would you
ask that of me?
No. I can't, Shana.
I'm sorry.
In all sincerity,
I've not withheld any
information from him.
Yuji Sakai made the decision
to walk alongside me,
knowing full well
what would happen
if the Grand Order
were to be achieved.
He wants to free you,
the Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter,
from your fate
as a Flame Haze.
He wants to protect
those close to him;
his family and friends.
That is why he
made the choice.
To join me and my
servants, Bal Masque!
The boy has chosen
to align with us;
your mindless prattling
will not sway his resolve.
Tell me, Bel-Peol,
is my return having the
effect we predicted?
Professor, can you synchronize
with the Conloquium from here?
Of course I can, anything
for you, my three-eyed beauty!
This invention can detect any
change in the outside world
and report it to
me here, in the Abyss!
It's all thanks to me
and, of course, the
miracle that is science!
May I present the 252546
Logical Pilgrim's Box!
It should be noted
that while the Professor worked
diligently on this invention
it has yet to be test...
Now, here we go!
Press!
One press of the button
and the helmet falls
right on your head!
A turn of the dial.
And I can see it all!
Your return has had a
huge effect, Master!
You are on fire, professor!
The Abyss is being torn
apart by massive quakes,
more powerful than any
ever felt on Earth!
The collapse of
its giant structures
is causing a contraction in
the rift between the worlds!
This contraction
has materialized
in the form of a
natural disaster
unlike any other we've
seen in recorded history!
Here and now,
I proclaim this destructive
force be named the Mistquake!
It is true.
The God of Creation
has returned.
The Mistquake.
Yes.
A relentless tremor that
will shake the Earth
to its very core.
Only those who control
Power of Existence feel it.
Now that it's begun,
I'm one step closer to my goal,
the Grand Order.
Whoa. What's goin' on here?
I couldn't tell ya,
but one thing's for sure,
whatever it is, it's not
likely to help our situation.
Yeah. Guess it's time to go.
Where's Chiara?
What's happening
down there?
The ground is shaking but
it's not an earthquake.
Think it's an enemy
Unrestricted Spell?
No way.
It can't be.
The Denizens
look uneasy, too.
Mammon!
This is it!
The natural disaster the
Strategist told us about.
This is precisely the
distraction we need right now!
Attention troops!
This quake is the
work of our master,
the Snake of the Festival!
We must use it to our advantage
and charge the enemy base!
All forces, move out!
Ah.
Our attacks are having
no effect on him.
What do you think
we should do?
All we can do is defend
ourselves for now,
and hope that our situation
will soon change for the better.
Well, it looks like we're
stuck walkin' the tightrope
until that happens, huh?
I don't understand
why you insist on
continuing this
pointless battle.
What could you
possibly stand to gain?
Why won't you
just give up?
You'll "conquer" me
and force me to obey?
Alastor.
Your contractor is attempting
to use your power
to threaten me.
Don't you have anything
to say on the matter?
Before she agreed to
forge the contract
which would make her
the Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter,
Shana said this to me:
I've been told that Flame
Haze are bound by duty
to fight Crimson Denizens
in order to maintain
the world's balance.
But I will determine
whether or not
I should fight on a
case by case basis.
In other words, it doesn't
matter how much you love me,
nor does it matter how
much I love all of you.
If I don't think it's
the right thing to do,
I won't do it.
My iron-willed
contractor refuses
to blindly follow your
path towards the Grand Order.
She insists on attempting
to create her own instead.
Who am I to
stand in her way?
As you know, she possesses
greatness unlike any other.
There is no one more
worthy of being my contractor.
She courageously goes
where others fear to tread,
and she does so with
her head held high.
While it is true that
Atonement protects the world
from disruption,
it also stands to become
the world's final judgment!
Therefore, I will walk
alongside this great one,
as she charts a path that
will benefit everyone.
Very well then.
It is unfortunate that our
paths must diverge this way.
But I will return to make my
declaration of the Grand Order
and you can't stop me.
Oh no. It's the God of Creation!
Holy crap!
The guy's an actual snake?
The Snake of the
Festival has returned!
Our master.
A true Crimson God!
Activate!
Deploy Qadesh's Blood Pulse!
Synchronize!
Release Qadesh's
Blood Pulse!
This time we got ya, bozo!
The sheer enormity.
It's amazing!
Could this be the end?
Well, well, looks like
someone got their butt kicked.
You'll have stay shackled until
we can make it out of here.
I would rather die.
What was that?
You heard me.
Sabrac?
I want to stay,
and watch it a
little while longer.
It's massive,
an overwhelming power
that's far too
strong to resist.
What is this
horrible feeling
that's suddenly
washed over me?
Is this how I made you feel?
Is this the reason
you left me, Mare?
Although I know it's wrong,
I can't help but be
jealous of your power.
Mine is inferior
in every way.
It's so weak and frail.
I had no idea this was
how I made you feel.
I'm sorry.
Now I understand
why you couldn't bear to
stay with me any longer.
This magnificent
presence has taught me
that there are beings far
more powerful than myself.
From its perspective,
there is no difference
between you and me.
We are equally frail.
Perhaps that will bring
a smile to your face,
my beautiful butterfly.
We've lost our ally, Sabrac,
the Destructive Blade.
That's a shame.
We managed to make
it out alive somehow.
Yeah, but we've got
a long way to go.
Indeed, we must stay diligent
and keep our guard up.
We must fight onward!
Ah. You've got a point.
Since we're already
face-to-face.
We might as
well fight them.
Let me go after them.
May I, sir?
That which falls to rubble.
That which departs.
For now, I set
aside my sorrow.
To follow my path.
The one I have chosen.
Begone!
Shana!
Yuji!
If we're going to
go through with it,
we don't have a moment
to spare, Takemikazuchi.
I wholeheartedly agree,
Sophie Sawallisch.
Seriously?
You're actually
going to try it?
Yes. It's a last ditch effort
but I'm going to attempt to
destroy the Divine Gate.
Is it even possible?
We have to at least try!
Now that we know that
the Snake of the Festival
has been revived,
I'm afraid the odds are grim
that the four Flame Haze,
who followed him through
the gate, are safe.
Heavenly Father, I submit
myself to your authority
and claim your power.
I pray that you grant me
the strength and confidence
to lead my followers to victory.
Protect us and lead
us in thy grace.
Thy will be done.
Yuji, I'm going
to defeat you,
and if the God of Creation
tries to stand in my way,
I'll fight him, too.
Then you'll be free,
and we can start
creating a path
that we can
walk together.
Shana, if you still
think that's possible
after you've heard my
declaration of the Grand Order,
feel free to
challenge me again.
But I'm done for today.
Time's up.
Chigusa once told me
that when you
kiss another person
it's similar to a vow.
Shana.
I know it won't
happen today,
but that kiss is my
vow to conquer you.
There's no way
you can defeat me.
It's not whether I can,
it's that I will do it.
That's what makes it a vow!
[Music]
The moment of truth is here.
My resurrection is complete!
[Music]
You may be one step
closer to your goal
but I won't allow you
to make it a reality.
I'll stop you.
After his successful
resurrection,
the Snake of the
Festival declares
he is ready to begin the final
stage of the Grand Order.
This leaves the Flame Haze
shaken and forced to retreat.
Next time on Shakugan
no Shana Final:
"Declaration of
the Grand Order."