Like so many before you,
your existence was lost
in a futile battle...
It seems that is
the way of this world.
You were such
a helpless fool,
worthy of little
more than pity.
You coveted vast power.
You gave your life for it.
However...
I still don't understand.
What is this mysterious
power you desired...?
And why did you choose to take
flight to go in search of it?
Perhaps avenging your death...
Will reveal the
answer to me...
Mare, the Keeper
of Jestful Slumber.
[Music]
You should go on
ahead, Nietono;
we can handle this loser!
Agreed... Good luck.
Will you be okay?
Synchronization.
Let's go!
She's safe!
The Destructive Blade, Sabrac,
is a terrifying foe indeed.
I thought we were rid of him
after our last battle
in Misaki City.
He was drawing strength
from Power of Existence
emanating from the city.
When we cut his supply,
it indeed weakened him,
allowing us to defeat him.
Or so we thought...
His survival is a threat.
The Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter
escaped my grasp...
She somehow broke
free from captivity,
reunited with her comrades
and warned them of our plans.
Since they were
expecting me,
my well-thought-out plan
resulted in little
more than a scratch.
As I've said before,
nothing ever works
out the way you plan.
We have arrived,
my servants...
This is the shrine
that holds my body!
It appears everything's
already been set in motion.
Because the General's
in a hurry,
though I don't know why...
You haven't forgotten
about the war
that's ragin' outside,
have you?
I'd like to wrap this up
so I can join my men in battle.
What...?! You've got...
to be... kidding?!
I don't understand
why anyone would rush such
a titillating experience!
I mean, just look at the
magnificence surrounding us!
It's amazing!
Ah...
Now we won't have to waste
any more of our time talking.
Sabrac's speeches are
unexpectedly verbose for someone
so sparse with his words.
You underestimate me,
Aged Tuner...
but I guess that's to
be expected seeing
as we've never faced one
another on the battlefield.
I look forward to
witnessing the power
of your Ceremonial
Equipment firsthand.
Jeez, I'm seriously
havin' a hard time
keepin' up with
you old timers...
Way to blow my confidence!
Don't worry you'll get a
chance to redeem yourself.
I realize this may not be the
best time to bring this up
but... my Ceremonial Equipment
seems to be useless here.
Well, we don't need it...
Wait, yeah we do!
How can you be sure?
Request demonstration.
Considering it took
all my strength
just to break off that
small piece of rock,
and propel it
towards Sabrac...
I doubt I'd have enough power
to construct the
Ceremonial Equipment.
The Destructive Blade
must have diffused his
power through this area
to weaken our attacks.
So beatin' this guy
ain't gonna be easy, huh?
Your wound concerns
me, Specialist...
It's worsening because of his
Unrestricted Spell, Stigma.
What? But I thought that's why
we were using the bandages...
to keep this
from happening?!
Indeed, but it seems
Sabrac has altered Stigma
since I last faced him...
thereby rendering the spell
placed on these
bandages obsolete.
I am currently
analyzing my catalog
of Unrestricted Spells
to determine whether any
will have an effect.
Thankfully, the
bandages have indeed
kept the wound
from spreading.
However, we must
be cautious
not to incur any
further injuries.
Avoid at all costs.
I get what you're sayin'
but it's not like we
can just keep dodging
that monster's attacks,
we've gotta fight back, too!
She's right...
The question is whether we
can carry out our original plan
without using the
Ceremonial Equipment.
We should deploy Qadesh's
Blood Seal regardless.
He found us...
Spread out!
A dream?
As I walked the path,
I often wondered whether
everything before me
would disappear
should I wake.
I would ask myself
if this was reality
or nothing more than
an ephemeral illusion,
dreamt over my
millennia of slumber.
But now, as I stand
before this shrine...
I have no doubt that
this is reality!
I promised I would return...
and, you waited
patiently for me...
Now... your wait's over
Please awaken my body
from its slumber.
Yes sir!
Return the Insignia to me.
I'm sorry, Supreme Commander!
I never expected the
enemy's reinforcements
to get here so
quickly, ma'am!
There is no need for you
to apologize, Francois.
You are not at fault.
Not even a
seasoned general
could have predicted
this outcome.
That's true; we had
no way of knowing
their western forces
would get here so soon.
Unfortunately, war never
goes as one might expect.
In the hopes of avoiding
such an attack,
I ordered our pursuit forces
to keep the enemy at bay...
However, it seems they
were unable to do so,
despite their best efforts.
I thought the deployment
of Sale and Chiara alone
would be enough
to stop them...
But apparently
Bal Masque's Denizen Army
has a few tricks
up its sleeve
All we have left
are the troops
sent to delay their
forces to the East
and they're holed up
on Mount Tanigawa.
If the enemy breaks
through those lines,
I'm afraid we'll
have nowhere to run.
What are our
chances of victory
if we're already worrying
about our escape route...?
We cannot give up.
Damn it! What now?!
We can't afford to be
stuck in this blizzard
while the war rages on!
We would have no problem
breaking through their lines
if we weren't dealing with
that madman, Mikalojus!
I bet that's exactly why
they've stationed him here.
If only this blizzard
would let up a little,
I could probably take 'em
out with my Daimon spell.
I remember the Strategist
mentioning something
about creating a
natural disaster.
She said we should "be
cautious but hopeful".
If it happened now,
it might be enough
to distract them.
I am the Supreme Throne Hecate,
a loyal servant
of our master...
With my great staff, Trigon,
I will break the bonds
that have held him
captive for so long.
Let them be broken.
Let them be broken!
I commend you my loyal
servants, the Trinity!
My pride and joy!
God of Creation,
my comrade and
fellow deity...
now that you have been
reunited with your body...
I shall return to the hands
of my contractor Shana,
the Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter.
Yuji Sakai...
I sincerely hope this
isn't our last meeting.
I can assure you...
that isn't the
case, Alastor...
We will meet again.
It won't be long, until our
separate paths become one.
Now join Shana at the
Palace of the Stars.
We've accomplished
our goal...
Our work here is done.
Let us return
to the Palace!
Alastor, you're back?!
This is where
I'm meant to be.
You've made it farther
than I thought you would!
Are you ready?
You know it!
As usual, nothing ever works
out the way I've planned...
Perhaps it's a sign...
It's time to
switch strategies.
Got ya!
Ya better run, chump!
Your strength and
fighting spirit
makes me think you'd
be a worthy opponent...
but your brutish technique
leads me to believe otherwise.
I'll show you brutish!
How do you still
have such power?
That's enough out of you!
Activate.
Deploying Qadesh's
Blood Seal.
There we go...
I may not be able
to pull off anything
as crazy as the
Chanter of Elegies
but this should hold him.
Though our powers
are weakened,
it should hold as
long as we isolate
the inside of the circle.
One explosion...
Comin' at ya!
I cannot believe you honestly
think you can defeat me
using the same tactic
you've already employed.
It is said that loss causes
such unpleasant fruit
to later ripen.
Jeez, shut up already!
Wait, Rebecca!
Take a look around!
What the hell is he doin'?!
Now that you have
separated my physical body
from the power I have
spread across the area,
I am no longer able
to maintain control.
That power is now dispersing,
destroying the land...
If you continue
to hold me here,
the Path of Pilgrimage
will disintegrate.
You gotta hurry and
call off your Unrestricted
Spell, old man!
Even if we
sacrificed ourselves
to make sure the
path's destroyed,
there's no guarantee the
Snake of the Festival
would end up
getting stuck here!
It's a shame I had
to foil your plan.
I must commend you
on your effort.
I guess you'll have to
come up with a new one...
I wonder who's going
to die in the meantime.
You, buddy!
I don't think so.
Now Wilhelmina!
I've had enough of you!
Blow him up, Balar!
Take that, sucker!
What the hell?!
Where did he come from?!
No way...
How did he do that?
The three-eyed woman was
kind enough to provide me
with a Rinne for
this very occasion...
Her predictions are usually
unpleasantly accurate.
Only one of you remains...
-Master!
-No need to worry...
She is my invited guest.
Yuji Sakai...
We meet again.
I'll fight the body containing
the Snake of the Festival,
while you hold
back the others.
Emblaze!
I'll stop her...
Thank you, General...
but let me handle this.
Shana...
I don't understand
why you're doing this.
Why are you so
intent to fight me?
I've told you I want to
live my life with you...
and I have vowed to
always protect you...
You know that I would never
lie to you about such things.
Nonetheless, you're so
strongly tied to your duty
as a Flame Haze,
you would dare to
stand in my way?
Of course!
The Grand Order you're
trying to bring about
is not going to benefit
anyone but the Crimson Denizens
and the power
hungry god they serve.
If it is successfully
achieved,
the God of Creation will
be granted the ability
to manipulate the world
however he sees fit...
Forever changing it...
Can't you see that if you
allow him to materialize,
he'll pose a threat to
the world as we know it?!
You're not going
to convince me
he should be destroyed.
I was a mess when
you left Misaki City,
until a friend
reached out to me...
She warned me to stop
fooling myself...
She said the time had come
to unite me with myself.
At first, I thought I
knew what she meant...
Shana and the Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter
had somehow become
two different entities.
But when I thought about it,
I realized I was wrong...
And when I spoke to
someone else about it
they clarified it for me.
They said, "There
are not two of you-
there is only one."
At the time, I
didn't understand
what they were
trying to say.
And ever since
I met you, Yuji,
I've subconsciously
pretended not to understand.
I didn't want
to fight you...
And, for some reason,
I couldn't accept that fact.
My denial caused there to
be a rift in my personality,
between the me
who had to fight,
and the me who
didn't want to.
I was afraid that I
would be forced to choose
between them someday.
But now...
I've overcome that fear
because I have found the
strongest Unrestricted Spell.
You see, I'm no
longer afraid to fight
because I've gained
an amazing power...
It's because I met you,
that I have the strength to
settle this once and for all.
Are you sure
about that, Shana?
There is something...
you need to know...
I love you, Yuji!
The love I feel for you...
is the strongest
Unrestricted Spell!
To learn this while
wielding a deadly blade...
it must've have been
a lesson from the man
who raised you.
I challenge you,
and with the strongest
Unrestricted Spell on my side,
I will defeat you!
-Is that so?
-It is...
and although I have the
power to kill you...
my only goal is to
conquer you because...
then you will be
forced to do as I say!
If the Snake of the
Festival possesses you,
I swear I'll take
him down, too.
I've never seen
her like this...
Once I've
defeated you both,
I will be the
one to determine
what should be done with
the God of Creation's power.
I'll find a purpose that's
sure to satisfy the others...
I will... and not just because
it's part of my sworn
duty as a Flame Haze...
But because I'm Shana,
the Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter!
Let's see you try!
You are mistaken if you
think you can tie up
these loose ends so easily...
You dare mock the desire
I've held for millennia
with your childish fantasy?!
I can assure you that this
is no "childish fantasy"...
This is the path
I have chosen
that we will walk together
someday, Yuji Sakai.
I will strive to
make it a reality...
Until the day
we're finally able
to share the strongest
Unrestricted Spell
just like everyone else!
It looks as though
you've found yourself
in the same situation as me.
Perhaps I should
refresh your memory...?
You once said that
as long as you were able
to keep me restricted,
it meant that you had
effectively put a leash
on the God of
Atonement as well.
So what?!
I'm gonna give you a taste
of your own medicine...
If you try to do
away with Yuji...
and you become the God
of Creation alone...
I'll use the Tenpa
Jyosai against you!
Normally I would be
forced to destroy you
for disrupting the
world's balance,
as that is my duty
as a Flame Haze.
However, I've
allowed you to live
because I know that Yuji
is in there somewhere
and I want him to walk
the path with me...
We can make it
whatever we want,
even a "childish fantasy"!
Oh no!
We've got trouble.
Which one of
you is laughing?
Does it matter...?
In this situation...
one can't help but laugh.
I'll admit, you never
cease to amaze me...
Just when I thought
I knew exactly
what to expect from you...
You suddenly
appear before me
and present this taunting,
boastful side of yourself.
I'm not boasting,
I'm being honest...
We will walk my
path together...
However, there is one
thing that concerns me.
I wanna know what you're
hoping to accomplish
by bringing about
the Grand Order!
I'm sorry, I can't say...
I understand your curiosity
but I'm not ready
to reveal that yet.
I promise the answer will
come to you in time...
However, if you insist on
badgering me about it...
The only way you
will find out
is if you can "conquer"
me as you said you would!
Very well then...!
I'll do just that!
Sabrac and Wilhelmina...
Khamsin and Rebecca...
Shana and Yuji...
Emotions clash
on the battlefield
as the Snake of the Festival
leaves the Path of Pilgrimage.
Next time, on
Shakugan no Shana Final,
"From Rift to Rift."