What the...?
Do you see that?
What is that thing?
Are those clouds?
Or maybe a mirage?
[Music]
We've come to escort
you and your guest
to the Palace of the Stars.
Master, we'll
follow your lead.
Come along.
Don't be afraid.
I won't let them harm you.
I have to go with him.
It's the only way I can
find out what he's up to.
I wanna believe he's
telling me the truth.
But I'm not sure.
I cannot thank you
enough, Yoshida.
I could not do
this without you.
But I'm just a human.
Are you sure that I'm
going to be able to help you?
I'm positive, in fact, it's
something nobody can do but you.
You see, I need the
knowledge of someone
who has worked
with the tuners
to restore Misaki City
in the past.
Don't worry.
I won't let the Crimson Denizens
lay a hand on you.
You have my word.
You've spent
thousands of years
waiting patiently for
this moment to arrive.
Your wait will be over
this evening at midnight.
In order to create the
paradise, Xanadu,
we must first open
a portal of sorts
to transfer power between
this world and the rift.
A portal?
But how?
If you'll recall,
you were asked to
participate in the tuning
because you were born and
raised in Misaki City.
The tuner was able to
repair the damage
by restoring it to the
image conjured in your head.
Now that we have your help,
we can use the Anti-Shield
Unrestricted Spell
to find the repairs
and temporarily
expand any gaps.
Once that's been
accomplished,
all of the things
in this world
will no longer connect
to one another,
and they will
cease to exist.
Think of it as a piece
of woven, silk cloth
that suddenly
has holes in it.
I see.
The power you need to
create the new world,
it will be sent to you
through those holes?
Correct.
This plan should relieve some
of the God of Creation's stress.
He seemed quite
happy about it.
I'm sure.
These portals, you're
going to open them here,
in Misaki City?
Yes.
As I told you before
this is all part of
Yuji Sakai's plan.
Now, activate!
Why do you need this?
It will show me what you
repaired in the tuning,
so it can be undone.
Welcome to the
Palace of the Stars.
Finally.
I've found a place
I truly belong.
Bel-Peol!
Sir.
I'm only trying to
protect you, Yoshida.
I'm sorry.
But I have to control
the power of the pendant
you are carrying.
I can't have you
calling her with it.
Not that she's a threat.
A single Crimson Lord isn't
powerful enough to stop me,
especially not her.
I suppose.
I should be happy,
sacrificing myself
to use Giralda
isn't an option anymore.
But without the power
of that Treasure Tool
I'm just an ordinary human.
I'm completely helpless.
I got so carried
away in the excitement
of seeing him again,
that I didn't think
about the consequences.
I never even contemplated
that he might
try to stop me.
I've finally realized I was
blinded by my feelings for him
but it's too late.
I can't let it
get to me now.
I have to stay focused.
I can't lose sight
of why I'm here.
Hello from the control room!
We're ready to
begin the process
of transferring the Palace
of the Star's functions
to the True Ruler's Shrine!
Just say the word, okay?
I don't see any
reason to wait.
Start the process now.
You got it!
All systems are go!
Domino!
I'm right here at your
service, professor...
Prepare to activate the
transformable alloy deluxe,
the miracle of science,
Excellent 252570,
Altar Shrine of the
Celebratory Ruler!
I'll press the button.
Behold! Isn't it glorious?
Bel-Peol.
Yes, sir.
Tartaros.
Synchronize with the Seal.
It's done, master.
The spell is complete.
I told you,
I intend to protect
the people of this city.
No one within the Seal
will be devoured,
no matter how brutal
the war becomes.
Oh.
That's good.
Master, with your permission,
I'd like to start prepping
the troops for battle.
Fine.
Make sure our forces are
prepared not only for the war
but the chaos
that awaits them.
Yes, sir.
Finally, the moment
of truth is upon us.
Now, my priestess.
Begin the final stage.
Yes, sir.
I am Supreme Throne, Hecate,
closest of those
to our master.
I raise my staff, Trigon,
to open a path to
the minds of others.
My loyal servants.
Look to the sky!
Behold the divinity
before you!
As one of the leaders
of this operation,
I would like to
say a few words
before we end
this meeting.
As the God of Atonement,
I have judged the enemy's
actions to be in violation
of the laws of the
world as I see them.
Therefore, they must be
condemned and punished.
I believe this operation
is our only viable option.
I would like to
thank each of you
for fighting alongside us.
Flame of Heaven,
there's no need to thank us.
Words unnecessary.
All right.
I realize the task
ahead is a difficult one
but we must stay strong
and we cannot forget that
we are fighting for justice,
and the fate of this world.
I suppose it's time we
get started as well.
I know that voice.
Is that you, Lamies?
Why yes, it is.
I'm amazed you're able
to remember my name.
I haven't seen
you in ages.
Tell me, why are you here?
I volunteered to create the
Anti-Shield Unrestricted Spell
so I'd have the chance
to speak to you again.
I recognize this pattern.
It's the tuning mark Khamsin
carved into the city.
Activating Anti-Shield.
There's no need
to be afraid.
The image you saw was
not reality, my dear.
I'm sorry; I
would've warned you
had I known it would have
such a violent effect.
Shall we try again?
Okay.
Something doesn't
feel right.
It's like...
I don't feel at
peace here anymore.
You're not experiencing
any pain, are you?
No. I'm fine.
So, what now?
Your work is done.
The preparations
are complete.
Oh, in that case,
may I ask you something?
Of course.
Ask away, my dear.
How come you've sided
with Bal Masque?
Are you helping them so
you can get into paradise?
I have been promised a portion
of the Power of Existence
the Crimson Denizens
will leave behind on
their way to Xanadu.
However, I would
never consider myself
an ally of Bal Masque.
I am simply using them
to fulfill my own desire.
Here they come;
all of the Crimson Denizens
seeking paradise.
We've reached Misaki City!
I can't believe this.
They just keep coming.
I wasn't expecting
this kind of turnout.
I've never seen so many
Crimson Denizens before!
I knew our
numbers were many
but to witness them in
motion is almost terrifying.
Their excitement is
infectious, isn't it?
Look how proudly they march
toward the Grand Order!
Wow, look at that.
We've waited three
thousand years
for this day to come.
It almost brings a tear
to your eye, doesn't it?
Yes ma'am.
I have no doubt that this
will be a splendid day
for the living and the dead.
Judging by the cards
we've been dealt
and the number of
Denizens out there,
I'd say our
chances of success
are much better
this time around.
Priestess.
We are ready to begin.
Please proceed to the throne.
The time has come.
We will now proceed
to the final stage.
I shall activate the
Psalm of the Grand Order,
then intone the
Ceremonial Prayer,
which will create
the paradise, Xanadu.
Transfer back-up functions
to the Conloquiem.
Transfer confirmed.
I guess this is goodbye,
my beloved Supreme
Throne, Hecate.
Yes.
I hope that we meet again,
my friend, Sydonay.
Is that her shadow?
It's merely a projection of
existence cast within the zone.
The reason it's wavering
is because it's been chosen
as the sacrifice for the
summoning of divine power.
She sacrificed herself?
That's the role
of the Priestess.
She's given her
life for our cause,
but she isn't lost forever.
I'm comforted knowing
she'll be reborn someday.
After the God of Creation
summons his divine power
to grant a wish,
he will sleep for a time
equivalent to the wish granted.
While the god sleeps,
the Priestess
will be reborn
so that she's present
to grant our next wish
when the god awakens.
However, she can
only appear to us...
...when our prayers have
grown strong enough
to call forth the god.
Whenever she is reborn we know
our God will soon follow.
It's a sign our prayers
have been heard.
She is treated with
the utmost respect
because she is our savior.
With the amount of power
it'll take to do this,
who knows how long it'll
be 'til I see her again.
Though it may not
be what she wanted,
she accepted her fate
without question.
I feel a strange presence.
It's a Flame Haze!
The sky is too dark.
May light rain down!
We are the stars.
The singing stars.
The stars who sing
with dazzling light.
We are the birds.
The birds who
breathe flame.
We are free to fly the
heavens as we please.
When brought together,
we birds and stars...
Become a galaxy,
dazzling and aflame.
Damn it!
They convinced the Four Gods
of the Earth
to fight alongside them?
I think we should just
sit this one out, big guy.
We can't give up
without a fight.
Let's go!
Okay, fine.
But don't say that
I didn't warn ya.
Oh no.
The Four Gods of the Earth?
Got ya!
There's no escape,
Flame Haze!
Take this!
Oh you brutes!
How could you?
You're not supposed
to attack a lady!
Stop this insanity
and return to the
Crimson World at once!
Please, I beg of you.
Thank you, friends.
What'll we do, Lerajie?
We'll have to fight her.
We don't have a choice.
That's the spirit!
Well done, my
beautiful dead!
Devour their souls
and multiply!
A banquet of blood
and fire awaits you!
Feast yourselves on the
souls of these evil spirits!
Wait! Stay back, men!
The Bright Flame
warned me about you,
Commander of Evil Spirits.
Our fellow priest,
He Who Walks with Rain,
was a kind and
peaceful soul.
Unlike us, he never
mastered the art of war
nor did he take joy in it.
He didn't deserve to
die by your hands.
That victory was
a gift given to me
by the master
and the General.
I was actually defeated
in that battle.
I had little to
do with his death.
I don't care.
You're the one who's
going to pay the price.
I'll slaughter you and every
evil spirit in your army
with my bare
hands if I have to.
Whatever it takes
to avenge his death.
And ripping you to pieces
seems like a good
place to start!
What do you say,
Commander?
Care to take us on in
a fight to the death?
You against me and
all my weapons?
How could I resist?
It's coming.
Shoot them down!
We're trying to find a
line we can break through.
Just hold on
until then, okay?
They're headed this way.
We can handle them.
I think this is a
good time to split up.
Good luck to you.
Thanks!
See you later!
Shana!
Kazumi!
You ready?
Yes, I am.
Let's finish this!
No way.
They're going to fight?
Sakai's doing this
all of this for Shana.
You can see it
in his eyes.
And I can tell
that Shana's determined
to defeat Sakai.
Each of them cares
for the other
more than anyone
else in the world.
I don't understand.
Why do they have to
fight one another?
Why?
[Music]
Shana and Yuji face off
in a passionate battle
of heart and soul.
As Yoshida watches, she
is overcome with emotion.
She takes up Giralda,
causing a mysterious wind
to blow through
the battlefield.
Next time, on Shakugan
no Shana Final:
"What the Wind Calls."