It's been a long
time, Chi You...
Or rather...
Thousand Changes Sydonay.
You've done well
for yourself...
Besting our forces
as you have.
Shame having to lose
two of the last
who still call me
by that name...
The Pennant of
Offering, Di Hong...
and Annihilator of
Bladed Flowers, Yu Xuan.
Fear not.
It's Bal Masqué who will
suffer this loss...
while sorrow and torment
befall the rest of the Trinity.
Shall we, Di Hong?!
Let's!
Yu Xuan...
Fortune smiles
on you today...
You get to witness
the Divine Metal
at Will's full power!
I do? Well Chi You...
I shall counter with my
Sacrificial Sword-Awakening!
Engage!
A beautiful technique...
But it neither moves nor
stops my beating heart.
Impossible!
He's unharmed?
You underestimate the
power of my Treasure Tool...
Divine Metal at Will
won't bend or break,
unless I will it so...
And my will is strong.
A trap?!
Beauty must die young...
Like a rose's petals fall...
Ever entrancing.
Splendid work, as
always, General...
Outlaw's Shanghai post has
been completely obliterated.
You should be proud...
Our illustrious leader
will be pleased to
hear of this victory.
I'm not so sure...
Of all the Outlaw posts,
Shanghai is was considered
the most autonomous...
Now that it's gone,
they'll simply
unite in Europe...
Under the leadership
of Sophie Sawallisch.
This is no cause
for celebration.
[Music]
I'm back.
What's this?
It's from the Braider
of Trembling Might.
Sophie Sawallisch.
She wrote me back?
Greetings, Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter.
I'm sorry, it's Shana
now, isn't it...?
Give my regards to the
Specialist of Everything...
I'm pleased to
learn you are well.
I hate to be the
bearer of bad news...
but Outlaw's Shanghai post
was recently destroyed
by an enemy attack...
We mourn the loss of the
Annihilator of Bladed Flowers,
as well as many
other comrades...
If there is a benefit
to this tragedy,
it's that it has brought
our allies together.
A threat, greater than any we
have ever known, is upon us...
I need you to be strong...
Now, in regard to
your own problem...
You've got to stop
fooling yourself, child.
The time has come...
to unite you
with yourself.
Unite me with myself?
What's that mean?
That bending means you
can't handle it at that size.
It might help if you
visualize yourself
at the size you're
trying to control.
You'll get it!
As they say,
practice makes perfect!
I don't understand...
What was Sophie
talking about...?
Why did she say
I'm fooling myself?
I didn't even
ask about me...
All I wrote
about was Yuji...
Pay attention, midget!
Come at me again!
Lord Stolas!
Ah, Pirsoyn, the Cup of
Corrupting Indulgence.
I heard that you
accompanied the General
on his mission in Shanghai...
Can't believe you're
back already...
So, was it a
secret operation?
No...
the General simply
required a messenger...
That is all.
I thought that it
might have something
to do with our leader...
I'm excited to meet him.
Where is...
the Dashing Earthly Fiend?
Why isn't
Ribesal with you?
Well... he was mad
so I gave him some
time to cool off.
Herald Stolas!
Greetings, Lord Ribesal...
Pirsoyn tells me you're
not in good spirits today.
What troubles you?
Don't play dumb with me...!
You know why I'm angry...!
We're expected to recognize
that boy as our leader?!
It's ridiculous...!
He's just a Mystes...!
Regardless of what
Treasure Tool he holds,
he's nothing more than the
husk of a devoured human,
dispelled by a Denizen!
Ribesal...! You're overst...
We know nothing about him!
Yet both the Strategist
and the Priestess
have chosen to
blindly follow him.
Why?!
How do we even know he's
qualified to be our leader...?!
Is he a better manipulator
than the Strategist...?
Can he lead us in a
more effective manner
than the Priestess...?
Is he even a more
formidable warrior
than the General himself?
Please, try to calm down...
I understand that
you have concerns...
I could always use my
position as Herald
to inform the Strategist...
that her men are apprehensive
of their new leader.
Yeah that's a great idea...
Dontcha think?
The last thing she
wants right now
is discontent
among the ranks.
I appreciate your offer...
However...
Uh?!
I have a better idea.
I find it unfortunate...
the wintertime is upon us.
If it were spring...
the flowers would all be
abloom to entrance us.
Wintertime holds
its own pleasures...
For instance, now I'm able to
hear your voice directly...
instead of divining
it from beyond.
That alone is a blessing.
"Wintertime holds
its own pleasures?"
That optimism must be how
you've endured my absence.
Winter is long,
yet it fades...
Spring is distant,
yet it draws near...
Is everything
mere illusion...?
A prank played
upon the lost soul?
We can only know
each other's hearts.
Bel Peol...
That Denizen,
was he a Herald?
Yes...
He brought a message from
Thousand Changes Sydonay.
He said the Outlaw
post in Shanghai
has been dealt with, sir...
Thanks to his success...
we're one step
closer to our goal.
Excellent...
I am relieved to hear...
Sydonay's skills have
not waned in my absence.
This loss will have an
adverse affect on
Outlaw's information network...
And, in turn, facilitate
my upcoming journey...
I can speak to her
without interference.
Then you are
going back there?
Of course.
As we proudly march
toward our noble goal...
there is only one thing
that could stop me...
the Flame of Heaven...
the God of Atonement.
It has to be done...
He is our rightful leader...
therefore, I cannot
doubt his words....
However... Why did he choose
the Mystes and not the Silver,
as his vessel?
He seems obsessed with
the Flame of Heaven
and the Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter...
Does some part of the
boy's own will remain?
You must have faith,
Bel-Peol...
We will succeed...
I promise you.
Sir.
I must apologize...
I have caused you such
grief over the years...
You spoil me with
your service,
and in the end,
I only disappoint you.
You honor me ...
But it will never
happen again...
I swear, I shall
not fail you.
There are benefits...
to being in
this human form.
I can once again stand by
your side and feel your touch.
Yes. Indeed.
Forgive me for calling you
to the world of the humans...
I realize we have
no cause to be here
but I wanted to
experience it for myself.
This vast expanse...
the real world...
This place brings
me great solace.
The breathtaking
vista brings tears...
as it brings hearts
together anew...
This... this is the world.
Tempest Hoof...
-do you bring news?
-Yes...
My honored masters...
all is now ready...
for our esteemed leader's
ceremonial audience.
Well done... Fecor.
Let the games begin.
No don't do it, Ribesal...
It's a really bad idea!
It's not our place!
"Not our place"...?!
We have the right to
question anyone's authority
regardless of rank!
Especially when
they're endangering
the very establishment
we hold dear.
Look there.
And there...
He's invited
questionable characters
into the Palace of the Stars
and given them free reign!
Why was this allowed?!
But if you challenge
our leader
you're flirting
with disaster!
You're gonna
get in trouble.
BIG trouble!
Well, then you
will be, too...
because now that
you know my plan...
I'm not letting
you get away.
No way...!
C'mon, Ribesal, lemme go!
You're crazy...! Dangit!
Your name?
Told ya...! The leader
knows everything.
Wanderer Ribesal,
the Dashing Earthly Fiend.
You will prove to me
whether you possess the
power to be our master!
You have grown...
into a powerful warrior.
The glory of
battle is yours,
Dashing Earthly Fiend Ribesal.
Master.
Now rise, my
loyal subjects!
Take heed...!
Members of Bal Masqué...
your orders are thus...!
Hello? Can you hear me...?
Hope so 'cause it's
time for orders...!
Now is everyone ready...?!
Here's goes nothin'...!
As you know,
we're at the beginning
of an exciting
new experiment!
Now, this particular experiment
is the result of years upon
years of meticulous research,
and if it's successful it will
forever alter the repute of you,
our beloved Crimson Denizens,
for the better!
Would you get
to the point?!
Everyone's waiting!
Domino!
Thanks...
I'll take it from
here, Professor.
Dammit midget!
Have you heard a
word I've said?!
Kinda like you
don't even care...
This isn't like you,
little miss.
kay, we're done here...
I got some drinkin' to do,
since it's evident
you're not interested.
No, I am.
Then focus your attack
instead of flailing it around.
Perhaps bestowing
a name upon it...
will aid in the internalization
of your technique.
Names have power.
That's not a bad idea...
But to ensure its
effectiveness,
the user should select it.
A name...
Oh man... here on the spot?
Here is an
example for you...
your predecessor found
it helpful indeed...
to call her
power "Knights".
She would always visualize
a legion of knights
clad in armor,
plunging themselves
into battle.
It will take time but as
you continue to train,
you will indeed
come to discover...
Your true self.
You've got to stop
fooling yourself, child...
The time has come...
to unite you with yourself.
Me, myself...
Whoa.
"Whoa" is right,
looks like she's got it!
Won't know 'til she
tries it for real!
C'mon, Midget!
It's been a while, Decarabia.
I wasn't expecting
to see you so soon...
Is it that bad already?
I suppose it must be if
they're calling me in.
As my representative,
I need you to do
exactly as I say.
Right.
Remember, it's not the length
of the journey that matters...
Okay, kid?
So long.
Take this.
As a human working
at an Outlaw post,
you're gonna need some help
avoiding Crimson Denizens...
'Specially when there's
no Flame Haze around
to save your butt.
This is a little
something for those times.
In simpler terms,
it's a Denizen detector...
Although, we did throw in a few
extra bells n' whistles for ya!
Long story short, if you
sense a Denizen with it...
do whatever it takes
to get as far away from
it as you possibly can...
Don't be brave and
try to investigate.
I'm sure you know this,
but if you even think
about fighting it...
I would never forgive you.
Yeah...
I know.
I know too well.
If I ever tried
to face a Denizen
without Margery's help...
I'd be a goner.
So this is the
real world, huh?
Right now, someone's
soul is being devoured
and no one will even notice.
Nobody'll remember that
'someone' once existed...
or realize they
could be next.
I have to do this...
for Margery...
This feeling...?
What is it?
Something's approaching,
really fast!
A Denizen?
What the hell...?!
Why now...?!
If it knows I'm here
I'm totally screwed.
Is it that way?
Crap!
What should I do?!
If you sense a
Denizen with it...
do whatever it takes to
get as far away as you can.
That's right...
I've gotta run...!
But where to...?
Hey...! What are you doing?
Let go of me!
Please...! Leggo!
Calm down! Take a seat!
No... Am I gonna die...?
Is it all over before
it's even started?!
Margery!
It's fine...
The Denizen wasn't
on my train...
It was on the passing one.
I'm safe...
They didn't know
I was here...
Man, this is nuts.
Wait...
Wait!
If it's on the
other train...
That means...
We've received
another summons...
but indeed, we cannot
leave Misaki City unattended.
From all the evidence
we've amassed,
it appears this city is a...
Maelstrom of Warfare.
Is something the matter?
Nuh-uh... It's nothing.
[Music]
Upon my arrival
in Misaki City...
memories of happier times
and friends I've made
come rushing back...
but that's not the
reason I've returned.
Next time, on Shakugan
no Shana Final:
"To Embark Upon a Journey."