I'm back...
Time to settle this...
once and for all.
[Music]
I'm leaving for the
Tokyo Outlaw tomorrow.
To Outlaw?
Margery says that
I need to go,
to figure out if this is what
I really wanna do with my life.
Yeah, I guess...
So... are you jealous?
Jeez I just talked
to him yesterday.
What took ya so long?!
We've got trouble...
There's a Crimson Denizen
heading into town!
That's not my
problem anymore...
Like hell, it's not!
Margery's gonna
need somebody
to help her monitor
the Crystal Altar.
Talk to her...
but don't use
your bookmark...
You don't wanna draw
this one's attention.
Wait...
Don't let me down...
Tanaka.
I swore I wouldn't
get involved again...
not after what
I saw that day.
Damn it, Sato!
I'll do it but you owe
me big when you get back!
Come on, it's the
middle of the damn day!
Don't ya think it's a
little early to start
boozin', my terrible
timekeeper, Margery Daw?
Nobody asked you, Marco.
Don't tell me you're
already missin' the kid?!
He practically just left...
Say one more word
and you're dead!
Whoa, you feel that?
Of course I do.
Ya think it's
a powerful one?
It seems to be...
Just when I thought
I might get a break.
Margery...
Eita?
You've come a
long way, indeed.
A vast improvement.
It's still not good enough...
but thanks.
You feel that presence?
It's a Crimson Denizen...
No... judging
from its power...
it's a Crimson Lord.
I see...
so Keisaku contacted you?
Yes, ma'am.
The poor guy crossed
paths with a Denizen
the moment he left town...?
Sounds like he's got a
serious case of bad luck.
It's got nothin'
to do with luck!
I bet he would've been fine
if you hadn't kept
him up drinkin'...
Shut your trap!
Let's go see what kind of
Denizen we're dealing with...
but before we
venture out...
Well, I'll be damned.
Look at you...!
Gettin' used to this
workin' as a team thing...
aren't ya... doll?
You hear that?
Indeed, it's my phone.
What made you decide
to carry a phone?
Well, everyone has them-
I didn't want to be
behind the times.
Convenient contraption.
This is Wilhelmina.
You felt that
presence, right?
Indeed, I did.
Is the midget with you?
She's right here.
Good...
I wanna see what
we're up against
so I'm going
Denizen hunting...
Just stand by until I
get back to you, okay?
We will, indeed.
Before we head out...
shouldn't we check
the Crystal Altar
for Unrestricted Spells?
We don't have
time for that...
but I sure wish we did
'cause I'd like to know
what to expect instead
of going in blind.
I'll check the
Altar for you!
Are you sure you
wanna get involved?
I'm sure.
He's serious...!
You can't turn him down now!
Fine, I'll leave
the Altar to you...
Give me a call me
if you see anything.
You got it!
She is going to
check things out.
We're on standby.
Is something wrong?
Hey Wilhelmina...
What is it, milady?
May I borrow your phone?
I've never seen
this number...
Hello...?
Oh, hi Shana!
Listen carefully...
There's currently a
Crimson Denizen on the loose
in Misaki City.
I don't have any
evidence yet...
but I have a suspicion
that Bal Masque has
something to do with this.
Bal Masque?
Unfortunately...
it looks as though we're going
to end up in another battle...
Kazumi...
will you help?
Tanaka's offered to
monitor the Crystal Altar.
Please say you'll
meet him there...
If not, you'll need to get
out of town immediately.
I'm not leaving.
I'll stay and help...
If there's one thing I've
learned from all of this mess...
it's that this is
where I belong.
I'm not gonna run
like a coward.
Thanks...
See you soon.
Here it is.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
I feel bad.
I hope they at least
received the letters.
But, at this point...
it doesn't matter anymore.
'Cause I'm here...
and I've made up my mind.
Is that...?
Yeah, it is...
What the hell?!
Hello? This is Shana.
I've got news...
But I need you to
promise you'll stay calm.
The powerful
Denizen presence
we've been sensing
is actually...
What did the
Chanter say, milady?
Request explanation.
I remember this place...
This is where
it all began.
I was minding
my own business
when everything around me
suddenly turned a deep red.
At the time,
I didn't know
I had been trapped
inside a Seal.
Delicious!
They're so tasty!
What the hell...?!
What's going on...?!
What is this?!
I got you!
It's time to eat!
Who did that? !
That's when I met her...
The girl with blazing eyes
and flame colored hair.
It may sound cliché,
but I think it was fate
that brought us together.
At least,
that's what the Yuji
who's standing
here now thinks.
I have so many
memories here...
Shame I have to
leave them behind.
Shana?
Are you certain
about this...
I haven't been down
this street in ages.
I remember this museum...
Yoshida and I came
here together.
I forget what
exhibition we saw...
I suppose I'm lucky
to remember any of it
after everything that
happened that day.
The Corpse Collector, Lamies.
No...
The Spiral Organ,
Leanan Sidhe.
I remember when the
Chanter of Elegies,
Margery Daw, first came to
this city in search of him.
I can't believe I was actually
afraid of her back then.
At the time...
I never would've guessed
that Sato and Tanaka
had chosen to
be by her side.
I'm still haunted
by the memory of the first
Denizen Shana and I defeated...
Friagne the Hunter.
At the end,
it was your voice that gave
me the strength I needed.
Well, it's good to know
I could be of some help.
Most of my existence
has been drained...
I guess I'm gonna
disappear pretty soon.
Take care now, Shana.
It was after that battle,
I first learned
of its power...
The Treasure Tool
inside of me...
The Midnight Lost Child.
We walked down this
street during the parade.
If I could go back, there's
one thing I'd change...
He can't be...
Not Sakai!
Yoshida...
What's wrong?
-This is...
-It can't be...
It can't!
I tried to keep my
secret from Yoshida...
But in the end,
her curiosity got
the best of her.
Even after she knew
I wasn't human...
That's what I like about you
more than anything else...
She still loved me...
Despite it all, her feelings
for me have never changed.
C'mon, you can do it.
That said...
Kazumi isn't the only one
who accepted me as I am.
Sato and Tanaka did, too...
and so did...
There's a secret that
we've been keeping from you.
That's why Dad felt
comfortable telling me
about my older brother
who died before
I was born...
the reason he gave
me the name Yuji...
and about...
Yeah, I did.
Mom's pregnant.
Oh...
Awesome.
Congratulations...!
Wait a sec...
This is a good
thing, isn't it?
It is...
Congrats to you, too.
Big brother.
Brother...
huh?
Thankfully, there
will be a new life...
to fill the void
I've left behind...
A little brother or sister
who will keep my
mother company.
I'm so sorry, Mom.
I wish I could stay
here with you...
But I'm afraid I'm not the
same person I was before.
Misaki...
Fight...! On...!
Fight...! On...! Fight! On...!
Misaki...
Fight...! On...! Fight...!
On...! Fight! On...!
Misaki...
Fight...! On...!
Fight...! On...! Fight! On...!
Misaki...
Fight...! On...! Fight...!
On...! Fight! On...!
Misaki...
Fight! On!
Fight...! On...!
Fight...! On...! Fight! On...!
Misaki...
I knew they would
forget about me...
But it hurts nonetheless.
Misaki...
Fight...! On...!
Fight...! On...! Fight! On...!
The decision's been made.
There's no turning
back now...
I have to do this.
When I first learned I
was no longer human,
I was overcome with
paralyzing fear...
I've since come
to grips with it
and now that fear is gone.
I know the path I've chosen
is a long and difficult one...
but it will lead me to
the future I desire.
Now I'm able to grasp
what was once
beyond my reach.
I'm not the pitiful Torch
that I was before.
My feelings for her are the
only reason I've come here.
It's because of her that
I've finally realized...
It's okay to love...
I can't believe it
took me this long
to recognize
something so simple.
I'm here...
though it was a
difficult journey.
I have come back for you...
Shana!
Yuji!
[Music]
Shana and I are forced to
put aside our feelings
as our swords
finally cross.
When faced with
the bitter truth,
how will Margery Daw respond?
Next time, on Shakugan
no Shana Final:
"Reunions and Chance Meetings."