Wilhelmina, Johann asked
me to give you a message.
"Please, my dear friend,
take care of him for us.
His name is Justus."
This child represents
the new way of being
that the God of
Guidance mentioned.
The Heir to Both Worlds.
When Johann realized
that he wouldn't
live much longer,
he suddenly had an idea.
There is one way that
we could overcome death.
A child.
A new life, Pheles,
one that we can
create together.
Then they knew,
this was the only way
they could continue
to live on together.
They joined both
their beings
to create a new life.
Dear Justus.
Beloved child.
Sweet boy.
Your parents
would be so proud.
Spiral Organ.
Was there sufficient
Power of Existence?
Yes, indeed.
There was more than enough
to activate the spell.
My work is done.
Now I understand.
The remaining Power of
Existence was your reward.
What'll you do with it?
Restore something special
that was once beyond repair.
Thanks a lot.
Before I go, I'd like to
leave you with a parting gift.
A little something
that will help to protect
your broken body.
Within that ring,
I've placed an incredibly
powerful Unrestricted Spell.
However, it will only activate
under certain conditions.
What conditions?
I have one last gift
for you, as well.
I shall name your
Unrestricted Spell,
Grammatica.
Explore the feelings
it brings to mind.
Grammatica?
You're such a silly boy.
We'll we meet again someday.
Till then.
Look, Wilhelmina.
I think it'd be best for
the Heir to Both Worlds
to be raised in Xanadu.
You should probably
leave soon.
But I can't simply
leave you behind!
Unacceptable.
Please, don't force
us to convince you.
You don't have much time.
The door to the new world
could vanish at any moment.
I can't.
If I go I can't help here.
You have a new duty.
You must protect Justus.
Eventually the Denizens might
question Shaher's oracle,
and if that were to happen,
it could put the
child in danger.
That is why we need you.
You're not only capable
of raising this child
but you will help
him flourish.
Indeed, but still.
Everybody's ready to go!
Unfortunately, there were a
few we couldn't convince.
Hey guys! Up here!
I rounded up as many
of 'em as I could,
and I did pretty good!
They're a bunch of oddballs,
ready to charge
into the new world!
One thousand, two hundred,
twenty-five Flame Haze total!
We couldn't have done it if
Sophie hadn't prevented HQ
from figuring out our plans.
That's true.
We owe her for helpin'
us do one last thing
for the old man
and his great task.
Keisaku's outside the Seal
with an Outlaw observation team.
He ended up bein'
pretty useful.
That's my boy.
This is my old home.
It's where I grew up.
It's the Heaven's
Road Palace.
You lived there?
Twelve hundred
Flame Haze, huh?
I suppose that's enough
to prove to the Denizens
that we will still be a
presence in the new world.
Well, it's not that we wanna
go after them or anything,
it's just that there's
no reason for us
to stick around here.
Allow us to take the lead.
Yeah, when you
put it that way,
we might as well
go along with you.
I believe that we
are powerful enough
to look after both worlds.
Please leave this to
us and go with them.
You have no need to worry.
The Chanter of Elegies
will remain here with us.
Someone's gotta stay
and keep the Denizens
who didn't go to the
new world in line.
Gimme a break!
Even the Flame of Heaven
can see the chains of
love that bind you...
We'll see ya!
May we meet again at
the crossroads of fate!
You've still got time to
change your mind and come along.
You're just as
odd as any of 'em.
You underestimate the
power of love, old pal.
Why do you think Chiara...
I wish you luck, Chanter.
I'm sure it'll all
work out for you.
You come out of a coma
with a boy on your arm
and you didn't bother
to give us the details?
Yeah, spill it!
Maybe Chiara can pick
up a few pointer...
Aw, that look on your
face is killin' me.
It's not like this is the
last time you're gonna see us!
We'll drink with
ya again someday!
I know, but...
Thank you for everything,
Wilhelmina.
I wouldn't be
here without you.
No, thank you.
For being such a
good friend, indeed.
Our gratitude.
Now on, he's your
purpose for existing.
Are you sure you can
handle that kind of burden?
No kiddin', rug-rats
are a pain in the ass!
Indeed, I'm not doing
this because I have to
but because, I want to.
There's a distinct difference.
Unease persists.
Even so, I know
it's right for me
and it's what I want to do.
We'll leave him to you.
But before I go,
I have something
to say to you.
I wish you all the
luck in the world,
Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter, Shana.
Yuji.
It's Sakai.
Time for our
final mission!
Now I want you to
be honest with me,
and tell me what
you really want!
I'd be glad to.
He's back to the old Yuji.
I want to use the massive
amount of Power of Existence
left behind by
the Denizens
to restore the damage
done to Misaki City.
Are you kiddin' me?
So that's his plan.
Is that possible?
It is.
You see, Lamies
left me this spell;
it's capable of restoring
that which is lost.
Death cannot be undone.
But.
It is possible to reverse
the loss of existence.
The things that we lost,
those the Denizens devoured.
They can be restored with
all this Power of Existence,
my Unrestricted
Spell, and...
The help of Yoshida,
who once tuned Misaki City.
You'll help me, won't you?
He's fast! Is that part
of his Unrestricted Spell?
It's doing something
completely different now!
Yuji, you plan to restore
your own existence, don't you?
No way, not me.
However, I'd like to
restore Yukari Hirai,
who is a part of you now.
But as long as you're
a core existence,
I'm unable to do that.
Shana, would you please
give her Torch back to me?
Since you took her existence,
if she is restored, my mom,
my dad, Ike, Ogata,
and everybody else
will forget you.
But...
She would be alive.
Then what happens?
What do you plan
to do after that?
That's all I want.
After that I'll go.
Off to Xanadu.
Do you plan to restore
the copy of Misaki City
once you get there?
That's impossible.
Though the new world
is a copy of this one,
there is no Misaki City.
Don't you remember
what I told you before?
If I were to expand the
gaps within this city,
things would no longer
be able to connect;
they would sever from
their surroundings
and essentially
cease to exist.
You see, you can't copy
what doesn't exist.
Misaki City doesn't
exist there?
If that's the case,
then why're you in such a
hurry to get there, buddy?
Transform, Sydonay!
Well, Marcosias.
There's no point in
holdin' back now!
You got that right, my
short fuse, Margery Daw!
Restore it!
Sakai!
Please, Yoshida!
Do this for me!
The Seal's coming down!
You ready, Midget?
Go grab that
pain in the butt
and knock some
sense into him!
Then do whatever you
want with the kid!
Is that?
The Judge of Paradoxes'
Treasure Tool, Tartaros,
is protecting
the entire city!
I am going to Xanadu
where this place
doesn't exist!
I'll teach the Denizens
how to live with the humans
so that they won't
ever feed on them again!
Someone has to teach them!
There's a rule in place to
keep them from doing that!
I want humans and
Denizens to coexist,
and one rule won't
make that happen!
It isn't an
unrealistic goal.
The Denizens
have shown me
this is what they
want, as well.
After living with the humans
for thousands of years,
they finally began to
accept and respect them.
That's why they wished
for the same world!
When their paradise
was created
they were the ones who
made the request
to prohibit the
devouring of humans.
I will use the God of
Guidance's oracle
and the Heir to Both Worlds
to ensure they'll never
taste human flesh again!
I don't care how many
centuries it may take me!
In a world
without this city?
That's right!
All alone?
Everyone!
Look at me!
Remember me!
All I ask is that you
remember I was here,
even if it's only
in your dreams.
Don't forget me!
So he's afraid of
being forgotten.
Once I've accomplished
all of this
only then can I
walk with you.
In my mind, I
don't deserve to
until I've made
things right.
So please, help me
bring Hirai back.
You should have
just told me.
just told me!
It's Hirai's Torch!
-Shana.
-Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!
I'm ready to walk
with you, Yuji!
Why must you wait when
you can be with me now?
I'm sorry but I
don't have a choice.
After all, I've
taken so many lives.
Flame Haze,
Denizens, Humans.
I knew what I was
doing the entire time.
I want to be with you.
But I was so determined
to change your destiny,
to protect this city,
and protect the
people of this world.
I killed anyone
who got in my way!
That's why!
You've decided wandering
around alone in the new world
is your punishment?
If we were to go there
together I'd be happy,
and then there
would be no point!
It's only a punishment
if I lose everything!
Yuji Sakai.
You mustn't blame yourself.
Fine words from the
God of Atonement!
Another Unrestricted Spell?
It's an almighty type!
We can't resist it.
We'll cut through!
Why do you want to
fix everything alone?
I told you.
If I'm not alone,
it isn't a punishment!
But I could help you!
Why can't you get that
through your head!
I would do anything for you
so why won't you agree
to go with me, Yuji?
I can't do that!
Then that's it.
Prepare yourself.
I'll attack you with
everything I have!
Here goes, Marcosias!
Let's give him a rhyme
that he won't forget!
I'm all for it!
This is our chance to
take it to the limit!
Who killed cock robin?
I said the sparrow!
Who caught his blood?
I said the fish!
Who'll dig his grave?
I said the owl!
Who'll be chief mourner?
I said the dove!
All of the birds of the air
fell a-sighing and a-sobbing!
Damn it! How much
power is it gonna take
to finally kill
this guy off?
We gotta do this
for all the Flame Haze
this jerk's murdered!
When they heard the bell
toll for poor Cock Robin!
Aw, man!
I'm dyin' here.
Nah, he is.
What happened?
Did you allow them take
your life, General?
Yeah. I did.
Deep down I think
that's what I wanted.
I know the three of us
will be together again.
Four, don't forget
about the master.
We'll be reunited someday.
It makes perfect sense,
you are underestimating love!
If love is what
inspired your plan,
I think it's okay for you
to be a little selfish.
I forced my will
on everybody.
I can't simply let
go of all that guilt
for the sake of love.
It's all right.
I love you anyway.
I love you more
than anyone.
No matter what, if I
think you're in the wrong,
I'll stop you.
If you're suffering,
I'll be there to comfort you.
If you're worried,
I'll talk through it with you.
But you have to promise
you won't ever leave me.
Shana.
I know what you're
thinking, Yuji,
but I wanna know
what you're feeling.
Tell me.
I'm sure I'll do
things that hurt you.
But if I'm suffering
I want you there.
If I'm worried
I'll talk to you
because all I ever
wanted is to be with you.
Same here.
Shana.
What's that?
I dunno.
Lamies gave it to me.
It's an Unrestricted
Spell I'm unfamiliar with.
You're not a Torch anymore.
You're a true existence.
I am?
I never thought I
could be so lucky.
I feel like I
can do anything!
Shall we go to Xanadu,
the new world?
Now Misaki City
is back to normal.
You got what you
wanted, Sakai.
[Music]