What's going on?!
No... Yuji...!
Let me go!
A single Treasure Tool...
has rendered me
completely powerless.
[Music]
In the plan
I've proposed...
Our troops would hit the
enemy's fortified positions
while a select few stand
by to counterattack.
It's a simple yet
effective strategy.
Perhaps a little too
simple if you ask me...
We need to start
thinking outside the box.
Considering our forces outnumber
theirs significantly...
why don't we strike first?
We could destroy them before
they even come up with a plan.
After their agonizing
defeat in Shanghai,
it's possible the Flame Haze
will be reluctant to
strengthen their forces.
If they do attack
with a small army,
we mustn't underestimate
their bravery
as that's what led to our
downfall during the Revolution.
You're wrong
about Shanghai...
They have no choice
but to strengthen their
forces after that defeat.
After all, we're not the
only enemy they face.
I'm with the General...
There's no way we can lose
given our superior numbers.
Just say the word
and I'll have the Jaegers
begin scouting the enemy.
A commander should
know better!
The Strategist has
provided a plan
that will ensure
our victory!
All that remains
to be discussed,
is how we'll respond
incase of an...
Please excuse my tardiness...
May I interject?
Impudence, Decarabia!
You must show yourself
if you wish to speak
before two of the Trinity!
Forgive me, I
meant no disrespect.
Judge of Paradoxes,
Strategist Bel-Peol,...
and Thousand Changes,
General Sydonay...
I apologize if I have
unwittingly offended you.
Damn you!
Calm down...! We're in
the middle of a meeting!
Decarabia...
You could learn a thing
or two from your comrades.
Now please... leave...
before you further
delay our decision.
Yes, sir...
Forgive my intrusion.
Well now, that certainly
livened things up a little.
Now, let us
begin the debate!
Lady Shana?
We've cleaned the room and
replaced your sheets...
Is there anything else
we can do for you?
Then we'll take our
leave for the night...
You may summon
us at any time.
If I tried to escape...
even that weak Rinne could
defeat me as I am now.
I don't have
Nietono no Shana...
or Alastor...
I'm all alone.
Someday...
you'll find it
for yourself.
Shiro...
It appears she's
gotten the hang of it,
Sophie Sawallisch.
Yes, Takemikazuchi.
She's a quick learner
but that's to be expected
from the Flaming- Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter.
What's next?
I suppose you could help
me write an update
to send to the Outlaw Posts...
I know...!
Why don't you write a letter
to the Specialist of
Everything, my dear?
Write to Wilhelmina?
No.
She'll be disappointed with me
if I write so soon
after saying goodbye...
A perfect Flame Haze
doesn't rely on anyone.
Are you having trouble
getting to sleep?
Yeah... but you didn't have
to bring me in here with you.
I know I didn't have to
but I thought that it
might help comfort you.
Though you won't admit it,
I can tell you're
feeling lonely.
Tomorrow is the last day
you'll spend with me.
Before we're forced to
go our separate ways...
I have one last lesson
to share with you.
When dealing with others,
always choose
but never refuse.
In other words, try to learn
as much as you can about someone
before you judge them.
If something about them
strikes you as odd...
don't run away in fear.
Whether they're a Flame Haze,
Denizen, or human...
they all deserve
the same respect.
And if they make you happy,
hold onto them...
Okay...
But...
I'm never gonna
rely on... anyone.
Because you're a perfect
Flame Haze, right?
Lady Shana-
Don't bother...
I know she'll see me.
Shana...?
I'm coming in.
It's been a while.
There's no need
to glare at me...
Talk some sense
into her, Alastor.
She has every right
to glare at you.
Alastor...
Are they treating
you all right?
Yeah... I was just
worried about you-
they haven't hurt you,
have they?
He's in good hands.
Just so you know...
I'm not forcing Alastor
to stay with me.
All you have
to do is ask...
and I'll be glad to
return your Crimson lord.
He makes it sound as though
Alastor had a choice...
Flame of Heaven,
I would be honored if
you would accompany me
so that I might
help you understand
not only Bal Masque
but our ambitions.
Please, come with me...
and then you will
see what I see.
You shall see the
true Bal Masque.
So, is there anything
that I can do for you?
You can take this
restrictive chain off of me.
I'm sorry, I can't...
I'm only trying
to protect you...
There may be Denizens here
who're looking to harm you...
I can't have you
wandering around.
If that's the case,
then you never should've brought
me here in the first place!
If I remove that chain,
you could be killed...
It's for your own
safety, Shana.
From what I've heard,
you've become a danger
to yourself lately...
I had to send my
guards after you
because you'd climbed from
the terrace to the roof...
Then you tried to cut
the chain off your wrist
with a decorative sword.
I must say, I panicked
when I heard that
you'd hurt yourself.
Shana...
What's wrong?
No!
Shana...?
What's the matter?!
I don't understand,
a single loss shouldn't
affect you like this!
Leave her alone,
Yuji Sakai!
It can't be...
You're acting
differently towards me
because I'm more
powerful than you now...
-Why Shana?
-No...!
Just shut up- you don't
know anything about me!
My, my...
If I had known I was
walking into this,
I would've knocked
before entering.
This is an ally of mine
who has agreed to help
with the Grand Order...
Lamies, the Corpse Collector...
or Leanan Sidhe,
the Spiral Organ.
Fate brings us together in the
strangest places, doesn't it?
Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter, Shana.
Did you say Shana?
I'm sorry...
but who is that?
If Bal Masque simply
intended to kill her,
there was no need for their
leader to come in person...
Indeed... There must be
some kind of Unrestricted Spell
suppressing her presence...
That's why Chigusa
didn't remember her.
Complete isolation.
I can't believe
you have to go.
Thank you for the gifts
but you really didn't
have to do all this.
It's the least I could do,
especially after everything
you've done for me.
It's a shame your work is
pulling you away right now.
I want you to promise me...
you'll come back
to see the baby.
C'mon, just double-check,
would ya? !
We have no record of any
visitors by the name Sato, sir.
Have you confused us with
another establishment?
Lady, I'm not an idiot!
Can't you just have
him paged or something?
I'm telling you,
Keisaku Sato has to be there!
Jeez, where the
hell could he be?!
He better not have been
lyin' about goin' to Outlaw.
May I come in?
Entre-vous!
Same time, every day,
just like clockwork...!
Was he there?
No, I kept askin'
but they said there
was no record of him...
Eventually they got
pissed and hung up on me.
Way to annoy the
crap out of 'em!
She's still out, huh?
Yeah... I was hoping
sleeping beauty
would snap out
of it today...
But she shows no
signs of waking.
I'm gettin' a bad
feeling about this...
Are you sure Sato
made it to Outlaw?
According to the
Specialist of Everything...
And she wouldn't have mentioned
it if she weren't sure.
That is, unless
she's playin' dumb
'cause she's hidin' something.
How can you joke at
a time like this?
If Sato's there,
why would they lie?!
What if...
instead of just calling...
We ask Wilhelmina
to pay them a visit?
It's strange she
didn't offer...
Wait a minute...
Uh-oh, what is it?
Here's the thing...
Faced with an impending war,
Outlaw's been sending summons
to all the Flame Haze...
which the Specialist
has been ignoring.
Even the Braider
of Trembling Might,
Sophie Sawallisch's requests
have gone unanswered.
But what's that got
to do with Sato?
I'm getting' there!
By not answering
her summons,
the Specialist is holdin' up
Outlaw's entire operation.
At this point,
I bet they'd do
just about anything
to persuade her
to join 'em...
even hold a friend
of hers hostage.
You think so?
Flame Haze'll do whatever
it takes to get the job done.
Sometimes that means
they gotta play dirty...
but Kiesaku knew what
he was gettin' into
when he accepted the job.
Hey... are you sure Margery'll
wake up if Sato comes back?
It's worth a try!
But only time will tell
if a kiss from her
prince charming will wake her.
If the prince knew what
was goin' on here,
he'd beat the crap out
of a legion of Flame Haze
to get back to her...!
But sometimes things
just don't work out, kid.
It's funny...
If he knew that Margery was
sleeping in his bed right now,
he would be back
here in a heartbeat.
Damn straight!
C'mon, man...
Hurry and get back here...
She needs you.
I knew it...
Hildegard cannot help us as
she's sided with Outlaw...
What now?
Personnel shortage.
Indeed, it seems
friendship among Flame Haze
is not enough to garner aid.
But the fault
lies with me...
I was foolish to think
they'd ever agree
to go along with
such a crazy plan.
Gavida, the Soaring
Tower of Quintessence...
Creator of both Heaven's Road
and the Palace of the Stars...
Once warned that the two should
never come in close proximity.
Unfortunately, it would
appear that Gavida's words
are all I have
to rely on now.
I must leave soon
as my odds for victory
grow slimmer each day.
A solemn departure.
Indeed... If only
Margery Daw were well...
I can't seem to remember
where I put my bag.
It's on your back.
I wonder whether the baby
will be a boy or a girl.
Bel-Peol...
about the master...
I thought Stolas had
already covered that with you?
I assure you,
there is currently
nothing standing in the way
of the Grand Order.
"Currently"...?
You don't seem too sure
of the situation yourself.
I could always have Decarabia's
"friend" brought in...
to do some
investigating for us.
The Spiral Organ?
That might be a good idea.
There's no need to worry.
If the Mystes tries to
interfere with the Grand Order
I'm sure the master
will stop him.
However, I will say,
his lack of communication
makes me a little nervous.
I suppose it's out
of our hands... now.
I wonder...
What could possibly
cause the master
to miss our
strategy meetings?
I think I know where
you're going with this
and I assure you, Hecate
is not with the master...
There's no need
for you to worry.
Her only concern is
completion of the Grand Order.
She's calculating the final
coordinates as we speak.
That troublesome vessel
will not interfere
with our plans again.
I see the strategy
meeting ran long?
We're orchestrating what could
be the most significant war
in known history.
There are a million different
points for us to argue.
And since most of our
soldiers are veterans
with several hundred
years of combat experience,
it took quite a while.
Now that we've
agreed on a strategy
they'll have no problem
working together.
That is, as long as
Decarabia plays nice.
Does that mean all of the
preparations are now complete?
Indeed...
Connect us to the professor.
Yes.
Can you hear me, Domino?
Yes ma'am, loud and clear...!
The engine room is
at your service!
Do me a favor and
ask the professor
how much he has completed.
Yes, ma'am!
Professor! The
Strategist wants to know
how much you've complet...
This is no time to
start being lazy,
Domino, get back
to work right now!
The Strategist wanted
to ask you something!
Oh, is that so...?!
Ask away,
Bel-Peol, my dear!
But you'd better
make it quick
because you know
better than anybody
how incredibly busy I am.
I've been working
to make sure
that the master's plan
is brilliantly executed!
Hecate is almost done
adjusting the final coordinates.
We'll be ready to activate the
Grand Order's second stage soon,
so we need you to
wrap things up.
Well then, I have
good news for you
because I finished all of
my second stage preparations
eons ago!
In fact, I've moved on to the
task of creating a failsafe
that will protect us in...
I have fulfilled the
promises made...
I do believe my
work is done.
If it's okay with you,
I'd like to return to my
post as your servant...
What do you say, my lovely
Supreme Throne, Hecate?
I asked that you stop
smoking yet you continue.
'Fraid so...
If you cannot do as I wish,
then you cannot be my servant.
Well, that's too bad.
In all seriousness,
it is not my decision.
It is good to have
you back, General.
Now, all that remains is to
bring about the Grand Order.
As I said before,
there's no reason for
you to be worried, Syd.
What are you talking about?
It's nothing, Priestess.
[Music]
Sato finally
arrives in Tokyo...
Where he gets a violent
welcome from Outlaw.
His world comes
crashing down
when he learns about
what's happened in Misaki City.
Next time, on Shakugan
no Shana Final:
"In Your Hand."