Yuji...
Shana...
this is for the best I'm
changing your destiny.
Don't fight me.
It's what I decided
Christmas Eve.
Tomorrow, December the 24th,
at precisely nineteen
hundred hours,
come to the
Illumination Fiesta
being held at
the clock tower.
When you've made
your choice,
please meet one
of us there.
You asked me to choose...
And I did!
Yuji...
That night...
Yuji vanished
from Misaki City.
[Music]
Hey Shana?
Isn't that
enough for today?
Yeah.
You know, as I was
watching you this morning...
I couldn't help but
wonder why you choose
to do all of your training
in our little yard.
You'd be better off
somewhere a bit more spacious,
wouldn't you?
What am I saying? !
Then you wouldn't have a
reason to come over each day.
I don't know what I'd do
without your visits;
I get so lonely.
You're not alone.
I guess you're right...
Once the baby's born it'll
be much livelier around here.
You should start getting
ready or else you'll be late...
That's no way to start
the new semester.
Here, let me get
that for you.
Now, it's time
for your bath!
Okay.
I noticed Yuji's
mug is gone.
It was his favorite...
He used it every
time we drank tea.
When a Torch disappears,
everything related to
the original human
ceases to exist.
Even their family's
memories of them disappear.
Unless, of course,
they happen to
have knowledge
of the Crimson World.
I'm aware of that.
Yuji doesn't live
here anymore...
Hey! I'm sorry!
It's hard to believe...
Hi Kazumi...! Did you
have a good New Years?
Jeez... where were you...?
I was gettin' lonely because
none of the gang's here.
The gang?
Yeah, Sato's absent, Shana
hasn't made it in yet,
and Ike's been at a student
council meeting all morning.
Oh, I see.
Oops! I almost
left somebody out!
How could I forget
about you...?!
I've missed ya!
Hey, you also forgot
your lover boy, Tanaka.
He can hear you, ya know!
Why're you always
trying to embarrass me? !
He's gone...
Nobody even
remembers Sakai.
Well, knock it off!
I asked you here...
To tell you
that I love you.
Happy New Year, Yoshida...
Good to see you.
Yeah the same to you... Ike.
You two- Hey!
Nakamura!
I brought this steamed
bun just for you! Try it!
Stuff the whole
thing in there!
Hi Shana...
Are you okay?
That night...
My heart broke...
I was sure Sakai had
chosen Shana over me.
Yuji's gone!
Back then...
I thought Sakai
was gone forever...
but now...
we have hope.
He may not be with us...
But we know...
Yuji is still alive.
Yuji Sakai...
What are you
thinking about?
The Flame Haze
and Crimson Denizens...
Why do they permeate
your thoughts?
There must be a way...
I'm afraid not...
When a Crimson
Denizen devours
a human's Power of Existence,
that destruction
of existence
creates a rift
within the world.
They know their actions
have dire consequences...
yet they continue to feed.
But isn't there some way?
There is not...
The tools known
as Flame Haze
were created to
protect the world
from Denizen attacks,
thereby preventing the
Great Disaster.
They are fighting a
never-ending battle.
They're tools...
in an endless war.
Precisely.
What should I do?
I don't know...
I knew that Mystes kid
was a troublemaker,
but I still can't believe he
vanished into thin air.
No joke...
We never even got
to say goodbye.
But the midget thinks
he's still alive...
We'll see 'bout that.
Sounds like a case of
denial, if you ask me.
Well, she seems
pretty sure of it.
I gotta admit, her
argument was convincing...
so much so that I even
agreed to help her beef up
her Unrestricted Spells.
Never thought
I'd see the day!
No offense, but you're
not the "teacher" type.
If I start out with a stiff
drink it should be easy.
Anyway, it seems
midget and company
are already worrying
about the next battle.
Against Bal Masque?
Yes unfortunately...
Wilhelmina suspects the
disappearance of Yuji...
and the random attacks
on Outlaw Posts
are all part of something
they're planning...
and I would have to agree.
Alastor's right
about this city...
it could be a
Maelstrom of Warfare.
You think it's attracting
misfortune...?
No wonder you and your big
butt brought us to this dump...!
You're drawn to trouble like a
moth to a flame, aren't ya?
Yeah... That's me...
I've got a
score to settle.
The demon I'm
hunting is trapped
in the Midnight Lost
Child within Yuji.
The Silver...
But I can't worry
about that now.
Our job is to
gather information.
Is that why you're
sending Keisaku to Outlaw?
You got it...
I was able to get
him a little job
working for them
as a messenger.
You sure that's
a good idea?
Don't worry, I'm
just testing him.
I need to make
sure he's capable
of following my directions.
Sometimes I think
he'd be better off
if he never got
mixed up with you.
But if he sticks
with me...
at least his survival
is guaranteed.
Bye...! See ya tomorrow!
Bye!
Ogata wanted to go by
Sato's and check on him...
but I couldn't bring
myself to do it...
I don't wanna risk
running into Margery.
I can't face her...
not after what happened...
I can't!
Yo.
Sato...! Why weren't
you at school today?
Sorry... I had some
things to get done...
I just finished
up so I thought
that I would come
by to see you.
Is there somethin' wrong?
I'm leaving for the
Tokyo Outlaw tomorrow.
To Outlaw?
You're gonna go work
for them after all? !
Yeah, as a messenger and
representative of Margery.
I think losing a friend was
the push I needed, you know?
You mean... Sakai?
Yeah... but Shana's convinced
he's still out
there somewhere...
and I think she
may be right...
so I'm determined to do
whatever I can to help.
I can't just sit
here and do nothin'.
It's funny...
Now that it's
actually happening
I'm startin' to get a
little nervous, man...
They don't trust newbs...
so instead of
the actual post,
it looks like I'll be
meeting them at an annex.
Margery says that I need
to go, to figure out
if this is what I really
wanna do with my life.
Yeah, I guess...
So... are you jealous?
It's cool, bro...
I'm glad you
feel that way.
Why?
Because if you didn't
feel anything...
it would mean that our
paths really had split.
Sato...
Listen... do me a
favor, will ya...?
Look after Margery
while I'm gone.
Every once in a while,
she needs someone
to go scrape her
off the floor of the bar.
But Sato!
I can't...
It appears we were
right, indeed.
Reports are now coming in
from all over the globe.
Danger foreseen.
There is no question that
Bal Masque was somehow
involved with the
disappearance
of the Midnight Lost
Child's Mystes.
This, in addition to their
brutal attacks on Outlaw,
indeed leads me to believe
they are plotting something.
Now headquarters...
appears to have reached
that conclusion as well.
Took long enough.
Better late than never.
Bal Masque has never
used a direct attack
like this before...
What would cause them
to start now...? ...
And why would they...
abduct the Mystes?
Crucial object.
That would indeed explain
Bal Masque's obsession
with the Midnight
Lost Child as of late.
The mistress shows no signs of
waver despite it all...
Well-being assured.
I can tell she's merely hiding
her feelings of unease...
I wish there was
something I could do.
Hey, I'm home.
Welcome back, milady.
Please brief
me on your day.
Well, they've
forgotten him...
just like all the
other Torches...
Any changes to the letter?
No.
Was there any new
information on Bal Masque
in today's reports?
Unfortunately...
they focused on
the Outlaw attacks
and didn't make mention of
the Midnight Lost Child
or its whereabouts...
but I will continue to
search them for you... milady.
Thanks.
Sophie Sawallisch...
You should write her a letter
containing your own report.
The Braider of
Trembling Might
is the provisional
leader of Outlaw.
Surely she's aware
of the matter.
Then write to
her directly.
Sophie?
'Kay!
She will advise.
Indeed, the mistress can speak
openly about her feelings
with the Braider
of Trembling Might...
Since she is unable
to share them with me.
I don't know
where to start.
I realize it's
nothing more...
than a returned letter...
But for me...
And Kazumi...
It's also a sign of hope.
I remember that night...
Yuji...
I'll tell her
what happened...
Each and every detail
stored in my memory.
I'll tell her
that the Mystes...
That Yuji...
Is still alive.
Are your thoughts
wandering again,
Yuji Sakai?
Yeah...
I don't know...
what I should do.
What is your wish?
My wish?
Isn't there anything
that you desire?
Yes...
She's using her flame...
to create a physical
manifestation of her power...
that can be wielded
like a weapon!
You're making good
progress, midget.
Maybe next time you'll
be able to attack
without thinkin'
about it first!
I'm not ready...
I've gotta learn how
to stabilize it
so it'll keep its size no
matter how hard I swing.
I wanna be able to control
it properly at its full size...
but right now I can
only handle it at half.
Don't you think
that's good enough?
No...
I need to become
stronger...
so I'm prepared to
face any challenge.
Yes...
any challenge at all.
This letter...
is the one thing
that gives me hope.
Yuji's still alive.
Are you sure?
I'm positive...
otherwise these letters
would've disappeared...
instead... they
came back to us.
Who do you
think sent them?
I don't have a clue...
Who cares...? As long as
these letters exist...
then we still have hope.
Yuji's still alive...
I just know it!
I wanna believe...
that what Shana
told me is true...
So please...
Don't let me down...
That's all I ask of you...
Sakai!
No matter what happens...
my feelings
won't change...
Yuji!
Have you made
your decision?
Yes...
I want to free her!
If that is what you
wish, Yuji Sakai...
Then you will be
the sole human...
to ever walk alongside me.
Please master...
give us your orders.
Prepare the Palace
of the Stars...
for a journey to the west.
[Music]
Shana continues
her training,
unaware that I've become
the leader of Bal Masque.
And what surprises await
Sato on his journey to Outlaw?
Next time on Shakugan
no Shana Final:
"That Which Comes."