[NANA]
"The brown dog said
'woof, woof.'"
"I will bake cookies
for our party."
"The yellow duck said
'quack, quack.'"
"Well then, I will go and brew
us some refreshing tea."
[NANA]
"The white sheep said
'baa, baa.'"
"I will go and bake
us all a cake."
[NANA]
"And then the fox came and asked
all the friends, 'KON, KON?'"
Ah, that's wrong.
Hmm?
They don't really
say that, Mom.
Real foxes say
"woof, woof."
Oh, is that so? They
don't say "kon kon"?
They've never said it.
We went to a cafe where
I heard a fox speak.
[NANA]
Huh? At a cafe? Why?
But everyone thinks they say
"kon, kon," so I think it's
fine to leave it like that.
[NANA]
Really?
"And then everyone had a
friendly tea party." The end.
Ah, that was great mom!
Oh, I'm so glad.
We're back.
Welcome home.
So what are we reading now?
[MAKOTO]
Oh?
Wow! How cute are these
things?! It's so sweet!
Mom drew all of
them herself!
[MAKOTO]
Oh? Amazing. You're
really good at drawing!
[NANA]
(chuckling) Thank you!
Ahhh...it's like
a pro drew these.
Hold up. You didn't
know this already?
Mom's a picture
book author.
Huh?! I never
knew any of this.
You...ARE a pro?
(preening) That's right.
[NANA]
Just now, I was getting
Chinatsu's opinion on whether
kids find this interesting.
[MAKOTO]
Ahhh..
You seem to really have a
knack for this sort of thing.
You've got real talent.
I feel most
honored, dear.
[MAKOTO CHINATSU]
(slight giggle)
[NUAKI]
(landing effort into sigh)
Oh...
♪♪OPENING SONG♪♪
[NANA]
Really?
For real! Japanese
lantern fruits are
a real favorite
treat for foxes!
TO] We saw that
firsthand, didn't we?
(doorbell rings)
[CHINATSU] Yeah!
[NANA] Huh?
[NANA]
Coming!
Ah, thank you.
[NANA]
Oh! You're welcome.
[NANA] Makoto, there's someone
here to see you.
[MAKOTO] Oh?
[MAKOTO] 'kay.
Ah. Hey, Inukai.
Hello.
Is Akane here?
She's not here
at the moment.
Oh, I see.
Please come in
and sit with us.
Thank you,
that's very kind.
It's our pleasure.
Akane just went out to visit
some place called Burkina Faso.
Where's that?
I don't even know.
[CHINATSU] (happy)
[KEI] Oh!
[CHINATSU]
It's Inukai.
How are you
doing, Chinatsu?
Hello.
You still haven't
turned back?
No... not just yet.
(greeting squee)
[CHINATSU]
Ah! Hi there Al.
[INUKAI]
Say hi, Al.
(lifting squee)
[CHINATSU KEI]
Huh?
Hweeeiii!
Wow! That was
so impressive!
[CHITO] (evil mew grrr)
[AL] Hei!
[CHINATSU]
(worried)
There's nothing to
worry about here.
Chito told me that her days of
attacking mice are behind her.
[INUKAI]
Is that so?
Eiihhhh...
(soft threatening mew)
[AL] (terrified) Eiiii!!!
[CHITO] (threaten mew
intensifies)
(freaking out) Eiiii!
[CHITO] (nice kitty mew)
[AL] (terrified) Ei, ei, ei...
[NUAKI] (apprehensive sigh)
[MAKOTO] See!
Mm. Oh, I forgot.
Huh?
Here you go.
I brought some delicious sweets
for everyone to share.
Ah, thank you
very much.
Oh?
Are they cookies,
by chance?
[MAKOTO] Hmh?
[INUKAI] Huh?
I guess not.
That's not surprising.
She's talking
about the book.
Ah...So I see that.
You look good
in white.
It's my daytime
outfit.
Lovely.
[INUKAI]
Thank you.
Thank you very
much, Nana.
Can I eat?
Hmh? Of course!
This is my apology.
[CHINATSU] Yay!
Thanks for the snack.
[MAKOTO] Apology?
For all the trouble
I caused last time.
And I'd like to
provide my services.
Oh? Fortune telling?
Yeah. I didn't actually
get around to reading
your fortune, remember?
Yeah, now that
you mention it.
If it's okay. I'd
like to try it.
You really want too?
That's great!
Lucky you!
It goes without saying that
I'll read both of you.
[CHINATSU]
Really?! For free?!
For free, silly.
(happy)
[INUKAI]
My fortune telling techniques
have been mostly self‐taught.
Just think of it as some
advice to consider along
the path you travel.
[KEI] I notice girls really tend
to get into fortune telling.
[CHINATSU] What is that thing?
[INUKAI]
They sure do. It's no surprise
that most of my customers are
females.
Remember...back when animal
fortune telling was popular?
Oh, wow I remember.
I loved that stuff.
[KEI]
I was a lion.
[MAKOTO]
I was a TANUKI.
[KEI]
Ah, that suits you.
What are you on about?
You were just a baby,
so you won't remember.
I'm pretty sure
you were a pegasus.
A pegasus...?
Pegasuses were
free spirits.
What animal were
you, Inukai?
Hmh (embarrassed sigh)
...monkey.
Exact opposite
of a dog.
[INUKAI]
Yeah...
Aren't they
enemies...?
[CHINASTU]
Hmhhh?
(mewing contently)
(panicked squees)
[INUKAI]
Well, let's get started.
Tell me if you have any
worries or decisions you
want answers for.
[MAKOTO]
Okay. Umm, lemme think
on it... Hmmm...
I'm good...
[INUKAI]
Seriously?
Give me a few
moments please.
I'll have it. Hmm...Worries,
worries, any worries...
Ah! Fix my bad
sense of direction!
I can't... I can only
read your fortune.
Oh, that's right.
[CHINATSU] My turn!
[INUKAI] Go ahead, Chinatsu.
I'd like to know what's
for dinner tonight!
[INUKAI]
Then ask your mother.
I've got this really hard
test next week and I‐
[INUKAI]
Then how about you study?!
I guess you're right...
(sigh) Hmh.
Wow, you guys really
are blessed here...
not that that's
a bad thing.
(breath) Let's take a look
at your fate for tomorrow?
Ah, good idea. That
will be interesting.
Alright then, let's begin...
First, take these stones and
hold them between your hands.
'kay.
Mm.
Then, if you would please drop
the stones inside the circle
while thinking to yourself,
"Please tell me my
fortune for tomorrow."
[INUKAI]
Your fortune is based on each
stone's type and placement.
Cool!
What's the name for
this style of reading?
[INUKAI]
It's called
Stone‐throwing.
Oh, that figures.
Alright.
(concentrating)
[MAKOTO]
Oh!
[CHINATSU] Ah!
[MAKOTO] Hmmm...
Odd or even, guys?!
How do you even
know that?
I saw it on TV
the other night.
The guy was like, "You lousy
cheat. You'll pay for this!"
[KEI] Uh...
[MAKOTO] So what's
it say, Inukai?
Hmm...
[INUKAI]
The stones are indicating: trip,
element of surprise, unneeded,
creativity, problem,
reunion, and gift...
Umm... I dare say that when
you head out tomorrow you'll
be met with an unexpected
ordeal that arises.
[MAKOTO CHINATSU KEI]
Hmmm...
But when you overcome it,
you'll be awarded with a
fantastic result
that will help you
grow... So I think.
Ah...I wonder if something's
going to happen at school
tomorrow.
[KEI]
Yeah, maybe.
Alright then, Chinatsu,
you're next.
(excited) Yay!
(excited)
(concentrating)
Ha!
[MAKOTO] Hmh.
[CHINATSU] Hm?
Hmm...Now let's see...
[INUKAI]
Two‐facedness, trip,
tradition, the dark unknown,
folly, meaningless, and
treasure. I see, I see...
There will be an incident that
allows you to uncover a new side
of yourself.
[INUKAI]
In the end, I see that it will
become something you honor and
treasure with respect.
Wow.
That's a really good
reading, Chinatsu.
Thank you! Not that
I know what it means!
Well, it's time
for Kei.
[INUKAI] Ah... if you study
hard, it looks like you'll
score well.
[KEI] (pleased)
Hmh! Ah! Inukai is back
to her beautiful self.
Uh? Oh...
[MAKOTO] Ah, our
beautiful Inukai.
[INUKAI] Wha..?
You're right. Beautiful
Inukai is back.
(nervous intake) What's with you
guys? You're freaking me out.
Well... it's starting to get
pretty late, so I think I'll
get going now.
(soft mew)
(terrified squees)
See ya later!
Thanks again, guys.
Say "hi" to Akane.
[CHINATSU]
I'm heading out.
I hope our fortunes
come true.
I've got butterflies
in my stomach.
What does a new side
of myself mean anyway?
Maybe I should have
changed my hairstyle.
An unexpected ordeal...
[MAKOTO]
Whatever happens, I've
got to overcome it!
[KEI]
(nervous) U‐uh...
(courtyard chatter)
A bit small, don't you think?
[NAO] (angry huff)
[MAKOTO] Oh!
No no, I didn't
mean those.
[MAKOTO]
I was just thinking that your
bento is kind of small today.
Yeah... yeah, I know.
Cause you see, I've put
on weight recently.
Huh? You look the same as
you always do. Maybe you're
getting a bit taller.
Yeah, well I'm not
so sure about that.
In any case I'd like
to get a bit slimmer,
so I'm on a diet.
It's not good for your
body if you don't eat.
My grandmother always told me,
a healthy body makes girls more
attractive to look at.
She would actually tell you
that kind of stuff? Your own
grandmother?
She also told me that having a
bit of meat on your bones makes
you more popular with the boys.
[NAO]
For real?!
I guess I better eat up.
Do you want some
of my omelet?
Sure, that'd be great.
[MAKOTO]
That was a nice meal.
(GIRLS chattering)
[MAKOTO]
Are you free later today?
[NAO]
Yeah.
[MAKOTO]
Wanna come over to my place?
[NAO]
Oh, sounds good.
Excellent. I've been raising a
bunch of vegetables at home.
Oh yeah? That's
pretty cool.
Right now, I have flowers
blooming from my edamame plants.
[MAKOTO]
Have you seen Edamame
flowers before?
Uh...No, I haven't.
They're just the most
adorable little flower.
I would love for you
to come see them.
You know, sometimes
I have to wonder,
if you really are just
a girl in high school?
[MAKOTO]
Huh?
[NAO]
It's like I'm talking
to my grandma.
[MAKOTO] Huh?
(AKANE sleeping/snoring)
Hm?
[MAKOTO]
Oh, my big sister's back home.
[NAO]
Huh? Your big sister?
Wha...? I didn't know
you had a sister.
Is she also a witch?
Yes, she is.
(roll over, continue sleeping)
[MAKOTO]
Welcome to my vegetable garden!
[NAO]
Whoa...
Amazing! This looks
so professional.
[MAKOTO]
My uncle teaches me
all about gardening.
[MAKOTO]
Look here.
These are the edamame
flowers I was talking about.
[NAO]
(giggle) You weren't kidding.
They're cuter than I expected.
[MAKOTO]
Right?
I'll give you some edamame
when they're ready, kay?
You mean it?
Thank you so much.
What else do you
plant in here?
Ummm oh! I planted crops
that are supposed to be
good for beginners,
such as tomatoes,
bell peppers and corn.
[NAO]
Awesome. I just
love tomatoes.
[MAKOTO]
Ah, that's not all. Over
there is that mandrake I
pulled up before.
[NAO] (Nervous)
[NAO]
That... really loud one?
[MAKOTO] That would be the one.
I read in one of my witch books
that if you plant the part with
the leaves a new mandrake will
grow in its place.
I'm testing it out right now.
You're trying to
make more of them?!
[MAKOTO] Yeah, they are very
valuable after all.
(soft MANDRAKE gurgle)
[MAKOTO]
It's now putting out a scent and
has gotten much bigger.
Which reminds me, would you
like to take it home with you?
[NAO]
Like I said before:
No thanks.
[MAKOTO]
You sure? I recently learned
how to use one to brew tea that
isn't bitter at all.
[NAO] It's not really the taste
that I'm concerned about‐ Wah!
[MAKOTO] Shall we take a look?
...No, I'd rather
you not do that...
Huh?
(soft MANDRAKE gurgle)
[MAKOTO]
I'll go get us some drinks.
[NAO]
Ok, Thank you.
Hmh?
Hmm...?
[cHITO AKANE KENNY]
(Sleeping/snoring)
(sleep purring)
(snoozing)
[KEI]
Oh, what are you
doing over here?
Just hangin' out.
I saw the garden. It's
pretty awesome, huh?
(laughing) Yeah it is.
[NAO]
When's the harvest?
[KEI] Hmm... Around July?
[AKANE] (waking up)
Cool. That should
be lots of fun.
[KEI]
Pretty soon it'll be time to
plant the eggplant seeds,
so it will only get harder.
[NAO]
(giggle) You love this...
[AKANE]
Heyyy...
[NAO] Hmm?
[KEI] Oh! You're home?
(crawling efforts)
(weird alien gibberish)
(guttural zombie cry)
(grinning insanely)
[KEI] Hmm?
[NAO] Huh?! What
was that?! Freaky!
[AKANE] (giggling)
[MAKOTO] Look who the cat drug
in. Or should I say, welcome ho‐
(giggle) You gotta hear
what's going on in the
other room. (laughing)
[MAKOTO] Oh!?
[NAO]
Are you serious?!
My sister thought that
Kei had brought his
girlfriend over
to see his house
and meet his family.
What Me? His girl?
That's right.
Oh whatever.
That sorta guy isn't
my type at all.
I'm not "that sorta guy!"
You see! I told you
you're wrong, Akane.
(annoyed)
(weirded out)
Mmmpm?
Mph! (door shut)
Ugh!
She's an
interesting one.
Yeah...both sisters are rather
unique to say the least.
Wha...?
[NAO]
Hey there, Chito.
(greeting meow)
[NAO]
What's this guy's name?
[MAKOTO]
That's Kenny.
[NAO]
Nice to meet you, Kenny.
[KENNY]
Mraow!
I made it back.
Hey, there's my
favorite little witch.
Ah, I didn't know Nao
was coming over?!
Welcome back, Chinatsu.
Makoto, did you check
out the radishes?
[MAKOTO]
Ah, I forgot.
How are they doing?
Almost ready
to harvest?
For sure. They look
ready to eat now.
[MAKOTO]
Oh, well then
let's go pick them!
So I guess you're growing
radishes too, huh?
The more, the better. Come
help pick them with us!
Uh, sure.
Hey Kei, do
you wanna go?
[KEI]
No, I'm at a good
part right now.
Well then let's head out.
[NAO]
You know I actually
use to raise radishes
back when I was in
elementary school.
Yeah?
Did you grow them in planters?
We did. We planted
a lot of them,
so please take a
bunch home with you.
[NAO]
Whoa.
That's quite a lot.
(embarrassed laugh)
I guess I got a little
carried away with planting.
We'll be eating for
free for a while.
[NAO]
Huh? You're planning
on only eatting radishes?
Can you really
eat all these?
Well I do plan on giving
some away and pickling
some of the others.
Oh. That's a nice one.
Look how big
this guy is.
It's huge!
We should definitely
eat this one later.
[NAO]
You gonna eat it raw?
[MAKOTO]
Yeah, they taste good raw.
[MAKOTO] Ah, that's right Nao.
[NAO] Oh?
I read in a book that
eating radishes can
help reduce swelling,
while also boosting your
metabolism for weight loss.
Oh? Really?
They should make
you nice and slim.
Uh‐are you serious?
Radishes are awesome.
[MAKOTO]
Yeah, and they also help
clear up your skin.
[NAO]
What? That sounds amazing!
Huh. Radishes are truly
incredible. Can I please
take a whole bunch of 'em?
[MAKOTO] Go right ahead.
[CHINATSU] (inspecting radish)
(happy)
♪♪
[NAO] Look. It's white.
[MAKOTO] Hmm?
That's from a
different variety.
Ohhh...
Whoa... that's quite
the harvest there.
And that's only a
portion of them.
There was no way we could have
been able to pick them all.
Can I?
Go ahead. Let's
all eat some.
[MAKOTO] For beauty!
[NAO] Mhm.
[NAO]
For beauty!
What's that
all about?
(biting)
(Chomp!)
(bite, gulp)
(chewing)
[MAKOTO NAO] Spicy!
[CHINATSU] Yummy!
[CHINATSU] Hm?
[MAKOTO NAO] (whimpering)
[KEI]
Seems some are
better than others.
[MAKOTO NAO]
(toughing through it)
[MAKOTO]
(sigh) Done.
Hmh! that's right. I totally
forgot about Inukai's fortune
telling for today.
An unexpected ordeal arrives...
Did anything like that happen?
(tap tap)
Hmh?
Hmmm...
Huh?
Oh!
[AKANE'S VOICE]
Bam‐bum‐bum‐baaam!
[MAKOTO] Hmmm?
[AKANE'S VOICE] Akane Kowata is
waiting for you. Please come to
the living room immediately!
[CHINATSU] Wha...?
[AKANE'S VOICE] Please come to
the living room immediately!
[KEI] (sleeping/snoring)
[AKANE]
Hey, thanks for coming.
What are you doing
up so late, Akane?
Well, it's the jet lag...
it made me sleep through
the afternoon and now I'm
wide awake.
Which totally means...
(laugh) it's time
for presents! Yay!
Yeah!
Eheh...
[AKANE]
Ta‐da!
Hmmm...
Innit neat that the backside
is written in Japanese?
[MAKOTO]
Wow... Th‐thank you.
Chinatsu's is pretty
cool, too, huh?
So heavy...
(breath catch)
Unexpected ordeal!
(breath catch) A new
side of me... whoa!
Hmh? Hmh?
♪♪Closing Song♪♪