(Birds chirping)
♪♪
(Water flowing)
♪Opening song♪
Hmm...
Hm?
Hm.
Hmm...
Oh!
Huh?
♪♪
Hey, Mom, I'm home!
(Gleeful sigh)
Oh! Welcome home, Chinatsu!
Thanks, Mom!
[NANA]
That looks pretty tasty.
Do you mind if I have some?
Sure.
Omm. Mmm...
(Chuckles)
Delicious! Thank you!
Are you headed
out somewhere?
Yes, I'm actually getting
groceries for dinner.
Do you want to
come with me?
No, that's okay.
There's a TV show I want
to watch, so I'll stay here.
Well, is there anything
you want me to buy for you
while I'm out?
Hmm...
Yeah! Pudding!
Oh? But you're
already eating some.
I meant some for
Kei and Makoto.
I see. That's very
kind of you.
You're such
a good girl.
(Both giggle)
(Chinatsu laughs)
(TV jingle)
(Door opens and closes)
Hm?
I'm home safely!
Welcome back.
So, get this, Chinatsu!
I made it back home
all by myself!
And without even
getting lost once!
Ah, now that you mention it,
where IS my brother?
Kei and Nao had some things
they needed to do today.
I decided to see if I
remembered the way here
and came back on my own!
So, it looks like my
sense of direction
has really improved a lot.
Oh! OH!
I've gotta write about this
in my journal before I forget!
My room's this way.
(Chinatsu sighs)
Do you write
in it every day?
Every single day.
(Doorbell)
Hm?
Huh?
I'll go get the door.
[MALE VOICE]
Hello, anyone home?
[CHINATSU]
I'm coming!
Uh.
(Birds chirping)
Ah, thank‐
(Slam)
(Clack)
[MAN]
Uh... Huh?
(Door rattles)
E‐excuse me!
Hmm...
Who was that over
at the door?
Um... I think it
was a salesman.
[CHINATSU]
Makoto...
what's the number for 110?
Huh?
The number for 110
is 110, Chinatsu.
Ahh!
(Frantic breathing)
W‐wait! Ple‐
(Dejected sigh)
H‐hi there,
little girl.
I'm not dangerous,
I promise.
It's not like I'm gonna
snatch you up and eat you.
(Groan)
[MAN]
Please, can you just
open the door for me?
Ah.
(Ominous resonance)
Ah! Scary! He's definitely
a weird, evil, bad guy!
(Dejected sigh)
Makoto! 110! What's
the number for 110?!
(Frantic screams)
Chinatsu, please calm down.
Huh?
Everything is going
to be alright.
[MAKOTO]
That guy is nothing
to worry about.
Hm?
Hmm... This isn't good...
I was told this was
the correct house...
Oh!
Ah, I had a feeling
it was you.
How are you?
Oh!
You're a harbinger...
right?
Yes, that's right.
If you know who I am,
you must be the new witch
who recently moved here.
Yes, I am indeed.
I'm so sorry about
all the confusion.
(Chinatsu groans)
[MAKOTO]
It's her first time
ever seeing a harbinger,
so I guess you frightened her.
[HARBINGER]
No, no, it's my fault for
showing up out of the blue.
I'm sorry for
scaring you.
Uh!
(Slam)
Ah! Oh my.
It seems she really
doesn't like me.
(Makoto chuckles)
Chinatsu...
(Groan)
Please, you don't need
to be so scared of him.
Let me introduce
you properly.
This is the great and
wonderful Harbinger of Spring.
Mm‐hmm.
"The Harbinger... of Spring"?
[MAKOTO] He bids
farewell to winter
and ushers in the new season
He's really quite magnificent.
Oh, I'm nothing special.
So, you...
usher in spring?
That's right! He's kind of
like the fairy of spring
and what it means.
[CHINATSU]
A fairy...
(Soft laugh)
[CHINATSU]
That's not how
I pictured them.
Anyway, what's the reason
you came around here today?
Oh, that's right.
I almost forgot.
My work in this
area is all done now,
so I'll be leaving town soon.
I had heard rumors of there
being a beginner witch nearby,
so I came to say hello.
Oh, I see. Well, thank you
for taking the time to come
and visit with me.
Not at all. Also, I was
hoping to receive a tonic
if you happen to have one.
Ah! I actually just recently got
my hands on something special.
Please wait
here a moment.
I shouldn't be very long.
(Yelp)
(Panting)
Hm?
Hmm...
Well, here you go.
Thank you.
Wow, amazing! It's a mandrake!
I've extracted
all the poison,
so you just need to
chop it up and brew it
in hot water.
Thanks.
But are you sure it's
okay for me to have this?
It's so valuable.
I would be honored
if you took it.
Every year, you usher in
the beautiful spring season
for all of us to appreciate.
Well, it's thanks to the
support of witches like you
that I'm able to do my job
to the fullest.
If anything comes up,
feel free to stop by.
Okay. Well, it's time
for me to get going.
Thank you very much.
Oh, I almost forgot...
Huh?
Is that little girl
also a witch?
No, she's just a relative of
mine, but she's not a witch.
I see.
Anyway, I'd like to apologize
for frightening her earlier.
[HARBINGER]
Would you please give her
this gift for me?
(Door slides open)
Him showing up so suddenly
like that really startled you?
Where is he now?
He left not long ago.
[MAKOTO]
Does he still scare you?
Hmm...
Well, his face is
still kinda scary...
I see.
Here you go, Chinatsu.
Huh?
Ah, so cute!
Where did you get these?
It's a special present
the Harbinger of Spring
wanted me to give you.
Huh?
He said he hopes
you won't be scared
of him anymore.
Oh...
Makoto...
Yeah?
Will the Harbinger
come next year, too?
(Seagulls squawking)
(Light breeze)
[NAO]
Makoto?
Huh?
How's it goin'?
Hey, Nao!
How are you?
What are you doing down
here in Yokohama?
Whoa!
You're soaking wet!
What happened?
Oh, well, you know...
I just swam here
from Aomori.
Huh?! All the
way from Aomori?
Yep, I mostly did
breaststroke.
Uh, that's pretty
amazing of you.
Yeah, I'm pretty good
at swimming distances.
(Amazed gasp)
Actually, there's something
I've been really meaning
to show you lately.
Will you take a look
at this for me?
You see it? What is it?
Oh?
It likes like you
have a red mole.
Look at it closer.
Hmm...
Ah! Ahh...
[TEACHER]
'Kay, now I want to see
you attempt to complete
this math problem
within one minute.
You may begin.
(Soft groan)
[CLASSMATE]
It's from Kowata.
Oh, okay. Thanks a lot.
Uh... Huh?
[NAO]
A dream?
So, how does hearing about
your dream have anything
to do with my problem?
Well...
it's not merely just a
regular dream, you see?
Are you followin'?
Nuh‐uh. What
do you mean?
For years, witches' dreams
have been long said to be
prophetic visions!
Witches can almost discern
anything about the future
from what their
dreams reveal to them.
What? Really?!
So, then does that mean...
I'm going to be super lucky
for the rest of today?
Even though it's
already late...
Um, please don't put too much
faith in all this hocus‐pocus.
Honestly it's just
kind of a superstition
between all the witches...
I can't say whether it
will come true or not.
But it's a premonition coming
from a real‐life witch.
It's gotta come true!
Ohh!
Huh?
Kei, what are you doing?
[KEI]
Makoto, come here for a second.
Okay...
[KEI]
Do you know about bakke?
Bakke?
[NAO]
Around here, we call giant
butterbur sprouts "bakke."
Huh?
Hey! Do this many
usually grow
by the roadside
like this?
Well, they grow
all around this area.
Hmm...
Wow!
Yeah, spring is really here.
It sure is.
Hey, Makoto, have
you ever eaten bakke?
No, I've never tried it.
[KEI]
Well then,
let's pick some.
They're super tasty when you
fry them up as a tempura.
[NAO]
You sound like an old man
or something...
[NAO]
Are they in season now?
Yeah, they are,
but you can also
eat them after the
flowers are past bloom.
They go well
with miso then.
The bitter taste they release
is good in its own way.
You ARE an
old man...
I take it that your father
likes to eat them a lot?
[NAO]
Uh? Now that you mention it,
he hasn't for a long time.
Then you should
pick some, too.
Uh... Gathering plants on
the way home from school
sounds like something
bumpkins would do.
Well, we are country folk.
Hm?
[KEI]
Hey, Makoto!
Yeah?
Don't pick the ones
near telephone poles.
Why's that? These are so big...
They look delicious.
Because they get covered
in dog pee and other things.
AHH!
[KEI]
Yeah... We got a
whole bunch of 'em.
Huh?!
What is it?
How come you aren't
carrying any school supplies
in your book
bag at all?!
Oh...
She's right about that.
Huh? Yeah... I leave
them all in my desk.
[MAKOTO]
Nao, are you going to
come over and eat with us?
Nah, I'll pass!
I've got a super
lucky day ahead of me!
See you later!
[KEI]
I'm home.
Hey, you two!
I'm back!
It seems you made
it back safely again.
Yeah, thankfully, I had
Kei with me today.
Kei's finally managed
to make himself useful, huh?
What's that
supposed to mean?
Whatever, take
a look at this.
Hm? What have you got?
Well, I'll be...
Those are bakke!
Makoto said she's never had
any before, so we picked some.
[NANA]
I see! This will
be your first time?
Yes!
I'm gonna use the
kitchen, if it's okay.
If you cook with the frying oil,
be careful, alright?
[KEI]
Okay.
Well, I'm going off to do
some grocery shopping.
[MAKOTO]
Take care.
How is bakke normally
prepared, Kei?
Your mom mentioned
frying oil without
you saying anything.
(Kei and Makoto discuss bakke)
[NANA]
Huh?
What a second here.
He didn't have anything inside
his bag other than bakke?!
Ah!
(Water running)
Is one egg
gonna be enough?
Hmm... for this many,
I'd say two.
Okay.
I'll put them
over here.
Thank you.
Hey. I'm home!
Hi there, Chinatsu.
Oh, welcome home!
What are you guys
making? Is it sweets?
Chinatsu, take a
look at these things!
Cute!
We're going to fry up
giant butterbur sprouts.
Ugghhh...
You can have some if...
Hmph!
You okay?
Chinatsu really isn't
a big fan of bakke.
Oh, I see now.
I'm so sorry.
(Sigh)
So...
it's already that
season... Great.
Bakke has a taste
only grown‐ups like.
That taste is
no good for us kids.
Oh...
(Light sizzling)
When lots of bubbles
start coming up,
you know it's hot enough.
Oh...
[MAKOTO]
Did you just put ice
in the bowl?
Yeah. Putting some in
the batter really helps
the bakke fry up crispy.
(Amazed gasp)
(Sizzling)
Alright, lookin' good.
Hey there, Kei, you seem
like a pretty good cook.
Hmm. I wouldn't go as
far as saying I'm good,
but I do cook quite a bit.
Ah‐ha! I knew you were
holding something out on me.
[MAKOTO]
With skills like yours,
I was thinking you'd
make a great girl.
[KEI]
You for real? I bet
I'd be pretty popular.
[KEI]
Do you cook?
[MAKOTO]
Well, I only tend
to make sweets.
Really? Next time, you'll
have to show me how to do it.
Are you trying to boost your
girly charms even more?
[KEI]
Okay, they're ready.
They look delicious!
Well, 'cause they are.
How'd it go?
Hm?
Did you happen to mess up
and burn it all to pieces?
Th‐they came
out fine, Chinatsu.
[KEI]
Makoto, you wanna try some?
[MAKOTO]
What? You don't mind
if I have the first one?
[KEI]
They're even better if you
put a little salt on them.
[MAKOTO]
Heehh...
(Groan)
Here we go, I'm just
gonna dig in...
Ohh...
Ugghh...
Don't worry, you'll be fine...
they don't taste bad.
OOOHHHHH!
Alright! Here I go.
(Crunch)
Mm... Mm!
Mmm! Mmm!
(Happy laugh)
Ah! Delicious!
Glad to hear it.
Ugghhh...
They have a nice,
firm texture to them
and the aroma of the fresh
leaves goes well with
just a touch of salt.
And that slightly bitter
aftertaste they have
is actually quite
surprisingly pleasant.
Hahaha! Nice speech.
I really mean
what I just said.
I'm sure. You sound
like a real gourmet.
A gourmet? Me?
I guess Makoto is
a grown‐up, too.
Anyway, I can't believe
that something this delicious
is just growing
on the side of the road.
Omm.
Mmm!
(Happy sigh)
Can I have another one?
Of course. Go ahead and eat up.
Well then, there might
not be enough left after.
Ugghhh...
[KEI]
As it continues to get warmer,
other edible wild
plants will come out,
so let's pick
and eat those, too.
Do you really
mean that?!
Mm.
Ahhhh!
(Gleeful chewing)
Ah, I'm so happy right now.
(Bark bark bark)
♪Closing song♪
Today, I'm super lucky.
I wonder what happiness
will look like...
Maybe a good‐looking guy?
Is a handsome customer
going to come in?