[MAKOTO]
Wow!
Aren't the cherry
blossoms beautiful?
But it's not nearly as
beautiful as you are, Makoto
Uh! Thanks,
Chinatsu...
Where'd you learn
a line like that?
[MAKOTO]
(Relaxed sigh)
There's hardly
anyone else here.
Seeing this before the upcoming
holiday is one of the perks
of being a local here.
Yay, us!
You're full of energy
today, Chinatsu.
I take it you
like it here?
Oh, yeah!
I can eat candy apples,
chocolate‐covered bananas,
and takoyaki!
(Laughs)
So you would rather
hustle to get at the food
than the flowers?
Hmm? I need to do
the Hustle there?
Uh... "Hustle" like "hurry,"
not like the dance.
Makoto means that you
would rather eat food
than look at
cherry blossoms.
Oh... If only
flowers were delicious.
Just like a true glutton.
(Laughs)
[MAKOTO]
Ah! Look over there!
Hirosaki Castle!
Isn't that a lovely view?
I think we should all
take a photo together!
Please, Kei?
Oh, good idea.
Ready?
Kei, you're not
gonna be in it too?
We've come all this way,
so there's no reason why
we can't ask someone to
take a picture of us.
Hmmm...
[KEI]
Excuse me.
Oh?
Could you please take
a photo for us?
Oh, of course!
[KEI]
When we're ready,
just tap here.
(Chinatsu greets)
Okay. Right here?
Alright. Get ready!
One, two, three!
(Shutter sound)
[ALL THREE]
Thank you!
You're welcome.
(Humming)
Thank you again
for helping us.
[KEI]
Let's take a look.
Hm?
(Disappointed groans)
[KEI]
No castle?
♪Opening song♪
♪♪
[KEI]
Okay. This is what
Mom specifically gave
us from her savings.
Hi there, Ichiyo!
(Giggle)
Let's show some appreciation
for Mom and Dad
who worked really hard
to earn this money
by doing our best and
trying not to be wasteful.
(Applause)
With that in mind,
let's start by
getting some food.
You wanted a candy apple,
chocolate‐covered banana,
and takoyaki, am I right?
That's right!
Here you are.
Thank you!
It's a shame, but I
might be full after
eating all of this.
You have plenty.
(Laughs)
Oh, my gosh! I almost forgot
all about the cotton candy!
You don't need to stuff
your face like that...
You just don't get it.
Eating cotton candy at
a festival is special.
It's just like how ice
cream is so good after
taking a bath.
Oh, I get it now! I
think I'll eat some too.
Huh?
[CHINATSU]
The stall's over there.
They have the prettiest colors.
Do you have a favorite?
(Taiko drums in distance)
Ah, that was delicious!
Sure was.
Well then, what's next
on the plan, ladies?
I know! Let's play the lottery
game where you pull the string!
[KEI]
Uh, the lottery game?
Those strings are definitely
not connected to anything good.
Hm?
[CHINATSU]
We'll never know
if we don't try it.
[KEI]
I'm telling you,
it's a waste of money.
[CHINATSU]
Hey, how do you know?
Hey I've got an idea, guys.
You wanna try out
the haunted house?
It looks pretty interesting.
(Eerie music)
(Happy gasp)
Hold up! You win,
Chinatsu!
Let's go do the lottery game!
The one where you pull a string!
Sounds fun. You can't
win if you don't even try.
I can see that now.
(Malicious laugh)
Hold on a sec...
Heh!
[KEI]
Please, just wait a minute.
I call timeout! Come on...
Uh, guys? Guys!
(Eerie music)
(All scream)
(Panting)
(Laughing)
That was pretty scary,
wasn't it, Chinatsu?
You were in front and
kept getting us lost,
so it was extra scary.
Hey, Kei?
Is it over...?
We're already
safely outside.
Phew...
Well, that wasn't
the least bit scary.
Oh?
You liar.
[MAKOTO]
You're not very good with
haunted houses, are you, Kei?
I never would have guessed.
[KEI]
Yeah, I'm not very
good with surprises.
They make my heart
skip a beat.
(Inhale)
(Sigh)
(Squeaking)
[WOMAN]
We're not getting
any business, Al.
(Distressed squeaks)
(Woman laughs)
With the cherry blossoms
blooming early this year,
I thought we'd get some
customers, but I was wrong.
(Ee‐ee‐ee!)
Ah...
That's true, Al.
It's not customers
I'm looking for.
You're totally
right about that.
HM?! Uh...
(Worried groans)
[CHINATSU, DISGUISED]
Lately, my luck has
been extremely good.
(Scared squeaks)
I'm not sure what to
do about it.
No matter how hard I try,
I can't help but get lucky.
[KEI]
Hey, cut it out, Chinatsu!
Please excuse her.
She won the lottery
game and now she wants
to boast about it.
My brother said I
wouldn't be able to win,
but I won on my
very first try.
Pretty awesome, right?!
Sure...
Hm?
So, do you really do
fortune readings right here?
Uh... well... it's just
like the sign says.
[MAKOTO]
Do you mind if I get my
fortune read as part of
my studies?
Huh? Oh, that's right.
Yeah. Go ahead.
Very well then,
let's get started.
Could you please share with
me what my future holds ahead?
Sure. First I'll tell
your fortune on the
basis of your name,
so please write it down here.
Okay.
Are you a woman
under there?
Huh? Yeah, I am.
But why are you
dressed like that?
Because it's what
fortune tellers wear...
You're not hot in that?
Not really.
Ohh...
How old are you?
Older than you.
Why did you become
a fortune teller?
Because I could.
Can I pet your cute
little mouse?
No. And he's
a hamster.
So, why do you‐
[WOMAN]
Are you like Little Red
Riding Hood or something?!
Stop it.
[MAKOTO]
Here. Is this alright?
Yes. Let's see...
Makoto Kowata.
So I believe you wanted
to know about your future.
Well then, let me tell
your for...TUNE!
[ALL]
"Tune"?
(Hysterical laughter)
I see now..
So, that's how it is...
Why, of course it
would be... Finally!
Finally, the time has come...!
(Maniacal laugh)
Uh... Is it something
in my future?
Um Uh... to more accurately
tell your fortune,
there is one more thing I'd
like you to write for me.
O‐okay...
For the time being,
I need you to write down
your phone number,
postal code, address,
family structure,
blood relatives,
and anything else about
yourself you can think of!
(Heavy breathing)
Uh... I think that's maybe
asking a bit too much.
This is some crazy stuff.
Is this legit?
Oh! Ah, yeah, you're right.
I guess you don't REALLY
want to give out all your
personal info to a stranger...
But please, tell
me just one thing.
Are you Akane Kowata's
younger sister?
Whoa, amazing.
She's right!
Incredible! You are right...
My sister's name IS Akane.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Yes! Yes! Yes! YES!
AWESOME!
So, uh...
what about my fortune?
I couldn't care
less about that!
What?!
I was never telling
your fortune anyway!
Why?
You're a witch,
aren't you?
[KEI] Whoa...
Uh! Uh... why do you...?
That's crazy! I'm not a...
You don't have to hide
it. I'm a witch, too.
Huh?! You are?!
Yes. I came up to this
area five years ago.
Oh, that makes you
Makoto's senior.
Ah! This is great!
I never thought I would ever
meet a fellow witch here.
I sure hope we
can get along!
HMPH!
Don't act all
friendly with me!
Uh...
Makoto Kowata...
let me tell you what
happened a year ago.
Last year? Tell me.
It happened at last year's
Cherry Blossom Festival...
(Hysterical laughter)
Inukai, you're doing fortune
telling now? That's cool!
Well, it's just on
the street.
But, yeah, I do
it now and again.
I've actually become
quite popular with a
lot of my predictions.
You should come around sometime
so I can read your fortune.
(Gulping)
Ahh!
Oh, really?
Are you sure you're
TELLING fortunes
and not just trying
to MAKE a fortune?
(Laughs)
What are you talking about?
Anyway, what's the occasion
for you coming up here and
visiting this old town?
Hmm... Well, you see,
my lovely little sister is on
the road to becoming a witch,
and might move up here,
so I wanted to check
the place out first.
[INUKAI]
Your younger sister, huh?
If you happen to ever cross
paths, be nice to her, okay?
Of course I will!
Alright! Huh?
Just leave it to me, Akane!
Aha! Great!
Cheers to that!
(Inukai laughs)
You sure you haven't
had too much?
Oh, I know! As a way
of saying thanks,
I'll show you some magic
I've been working on recently.
It's pretty awesome.
I promise!
You sure about that?
(Hysterical laugh)
Yep. And cheers to that!
(Tink)
(Laughs)
Basically, you had a good
time drinking, right?
Wrong!
One of Akane's momentary
whims resulted in me
transforming into this
maddening and hideous form
taunting me forever!
(Amazed gasp)
How am I supposed to live
with this body of mine?!
(Heavy breathing)
She's so cute!
AH!
[MAKOTO]
Uhh...
[INUKAI]
Chocolate?
You'd think so, right?
But they're actually
infused with magic.
Someone I know wanted
me to make some,
so I thought I'd make
a trial batch.
Oh? So what kind of
effect do they have?
They can turn people
into animals.
Huh?! That's pretty advanced
magic you're working with!
That's what I've been told.
But I wanted to give
it a shot anyway.
(Laughs)
You really are a mad genius!
A witch your age who can do
that kind of magic is
practically unheard of!
Hehe! That's simply not true.
Anyway, they've never
been tested so I don't
know if they work.
Why don't you try
one out for me?
No way! Are you crazy?!
I don't wanna be
your guinea pig!
(Birds chirping)
(Light snoring)
(Groans)
What happened? What the...?
I can't remember anything
from last night. Ugh.
Except that my head
is really killing me.
Alcohol is bad news,
that's for sure.
Hm?
(Confused groan)
WHAT?! WHAT IN THE WORLD AM I?!
Hey, Akane!
Akane! AKANE!
That's what happened
last year.
So my sister's magic has
made you turn into that?
Well, we were both pretty
drunk at the time,
so she probably just got carried
away and fed it to me.
Fortunately, the
magic was imperfect,
so I return to my human form
when the sun goes down.
But it's really been a huge
hindrance to my private life.
Ooh...
Stop doing that.
How exactly do you
know my sister?
We're just very
old friends.
But since
she's been wandering around
the world for such a long time,
I can never seem to pin
down her whereabouts.
I thought that maybe
she'd come back here,
so I've been fortune telling
on the side of the street.
And then you just showed up
today right out of the blue.
Hm...
I'm sorry about yelling
at you earlier.
I was just so surprised
that I just kind of lost it.
Oh, that's okay.
Please don't worry about it.
Ah... I'm glad we met.
Now the magic can
finally be undone!
You're her little sister, so
you probably know how to get
in touch with her, right?
Would you mind giving
her my cell number,
so I can call her?
I don't think she carries
a cell phone with her.
Uh?
And no one in our family
ever knows her whereabouts.
Oh...
[CHINATSU]
I'm home!
Hm? Hmm.
Hi, Momma!
Well, you're back
earlier than I expected.
[CHINATSU]
This is my mom.
Oh my, what a cute guest you
have brought here.
Is this a friend of yours?
[CHINATSU]
Yeah! Her name's Inukai!
(Squeak)
I'm Chinatsu's mother.
Thank you for looking
after my kid.
(Sad squeak)
Y‐your welcome...
[NANA]
Looks like teatime!
Makoto said for you
to wait here.
Your mother didn't
seem surprised at all.
I hear when people get old,
they aren't easily surprised.
Where... is...?
Ah, here it is.
Thank you for
the tea, Ma'am.
[MAKOTO]
Hey, I found it!
Oh?
[MAKOTO]
We should be able to fix
your problem using this.
Hm...
The complete book of magic for
changing animals into people...
[INUKAI]
You using this on me?
Yes, I plan to reverse
my sister's magic.
You don't have to do that.
Just let Akane
know to contact me...
This is my sister we're
talking about,
so who knows when she'll
be back!
I consider my sister's
blunder to also be my own,
(Intrigued squeak)
so please let me take
responsibility for it.
[INUKAI]
Uh...
But this magic looks pretty
difficult to master correctly...
(Chinatsu gasps)
It'll be fine!
It's not like I'm lightheartedly
jumping into this.
Or that I'm using
this as another excuse
to practice magic.
I'm going into this with
a serious mindset that's
ready, willing, and able.
(Crackling)
(Worried moan)
Wow, how witchy.
Yeah, it's really witchy.
Um... that's
because I AM.
[MAKOTO]
Okay...
Lastly, it needs
a drop of this.
(Bubbling)
(Light poof)
Whoa!
(Chi?)
(Meow)
It should be
ready now.
[CHINATSU]
They look like konpeito!
[INUKAI]
Will this cure me?
No, it's not supposed
to cure you completely.
But this medicine
should temporarily change
you back into a person
for the rest of
the day at least.
It would allow you to
remain in your human form
even when the sun is out.
I guess it's better
than having no options.
Do you think this
stuff will be safe?
I believe so! I'm sure
it'll work fine!
(Worried moan)
(Excited giggle)
(Meow)
(Squeak)
(Apprehensive sighs)
(Excited sigh)
Om!
(Light groan)
I think you made it worse.
I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry!
I'm so sorry!
(Stifled laughter)
[INUKAI] What am I
supposed to do with this?
[MAKOTO]
You just had the one candy,
so you'll most likely
turn back soon!
(Sigh)
Thank goodness!
I'm back to normal.
Well, not really
normal, per se...
I'm so very sorry
about that.
Really, it's fine.
You didn't mean to do it.
But I guess it will
be quite a while before
I can be cured of this.
I'll contact you as soon as
my sister comes back here,
so please try to
wait until then.
I wonder when
she'll show up again.
Well, she dropped by
here not too long ago,
so I can't say for sure
when we will see her
back down here again.
Huh?
[INUKAI]
I see...
Guess all I can do is
wait patiently.
I'm sorry.
It's not like you
did anything wrong,
so don't worry
about it.
'Kay...
(Laughs)
You two sure don't look
anything alike for sisters.
Yeah, I know.
People often say that.
Oh? I personally think
we look a lot like sisters.
(Both gasp)
Especially since
we're both beautiful.
Okay!
(Terrified squeak)
Sorry for pulling out
the lame joke for you.
You... finally...
Long time no see,
my friend!
Oh! What in the world are you
even doing here anyway, Inukai?
Did you forget?!
Last year, you told me to
come get my fortune read!
UHH!
I went all the way to
the festival grounds
and couldn't
find you anywhere.
I was forced to enjoy
it all by myself!
Uh!
Anyway, you want some
of this takoyaki?
Did you really have to get so
angry right after seeing me?!
You're the one who made me
look like one of your sick
little jokes!
You have any idea how much I've
suffered through all of this?!
Huh?! Do you?!
Huh? What are
you talking about?
You did that all to
yourself, you know?
What?
(Drunk laughter)
Come on, Inukai,
you've had too much.
Meow, meow,
meow, meow, meow.
Drinking with you is so much
fun that I always lose track
and go way overboard.
Oh, my bad!
(Gnawing)
Hm? What are you
chewing on there?
A skewer.
(Continued chewing)
Akane, I want some
more snacks!
More snacks? So sorry,
but I'm all outta money.
Then let's make some
using magic, with
leaves or something!
(Laughing)
Because we'd get arrested.
(Groan)
[INUKAI]
Wait, you had that
chocolate, right?
Yeah, but I won't
let you eat that.
Come on! Earlier,
you were trying to get me
to test it out for you.
Ow, ow... Cut it out, Inukai!
That was just a silly joke
I was playing on you.
(Hungry groans)
Here it is!
Uhh!
I'm not playing around!
(Giggling)
You're really turning
into some sort of animal!
It's fine.
The first kanji in my name
means "dog,"
so I've been thinking maybe
I should be more like a dog!
[AKANE] (Laughs)
That's some
crazy person talk.
Looks yummy!
Ah, no, no, no! Don't!
Time for a little snack!
(Groan)
You remember now?
Yeah...
Then when morning came and
you saw your new appearance...
I have a feeling I was actually
really happy with it, wasn't I?
[AKANE]
Yup. And then you
went back to sleep and I
couldn't get you to wake up
no matter how hard I tried.
You think... I'll get cured?
Not anytime soon.
But the effect will
eventually wear off,
so try not to lose it
in the meantime.
Okay...
(Bugs chirping)
I'm so sorry for causing
so much trouble!
[AKANE]
I've also been searching
for a way to reverse
the magic, Inukai.
I'll let you know
what I find.
Great, thanks.
Huh? Inukai,
your face changed.
Oh, yeah, it's already
nighttime, isn't it?
Well, this is my true
appearance looks like.
(Squeak)
Remember that, okay?
(Light chuckles)
Well then, I guess
I better be going.
Please come and
visit us sometime.
'Kay. I'll see you
again, Chinatsu.
What a day.
She was totally
my type.
Oh?
Her cuteness can sure get
on my nerves sometimes.
Lucky girl!
(Giggle)
♪♪
Ah, I need to take it
easy on the alcohol.
(Hii hii)
You're always right, Al.
We should give a proper
apology one day.
♪Closing song♪