[CHINATSU]
Yummy!
[KEI]
It sure is.
We need to bring Nao with us
next time we come here.
Totally!
Agree. (chomp)
(savoring sigh) Oh?
(weirded out)
♪♪OPENING SONG♪♪
I'm going to go park
the car, Sweetie.
[ANZU]
Okay.
I'm home.
[HINA]
Welcome home, Anzu.
[ANZU]
Thank you.
[HINA] We have customers...
[ANZU]
Uh?
What's with the mask?
Oh, sorry.
[ANZU] Were
you fine here on your own?
[HINA] Yes.
[HINA]
Anzu, there are
customers inside.
[ANZU]
Already? He's early today.
Did he order his usual?
[HINA] Uh, no. Actually, he
hasn't arrived yet.
[ANZU] Oh?
[CHINATSU] It truly
is delicious!
Can I get
one more?
[MAKOTO]
I don't know
about that...
You can really
shovel it in.
[CHINATSU]
I'm a growing girl with
a healthy appetite!
[KEI]
Sure you're not just a glutton?
Not what I expected...
Mhmm.
[HINA]
I think that girl with
long hair is a witch.
Uh? She's
not familiar.
Perhaps she might be the
beginner witch that has
recently moved up here?
Ohhh.
It appears she's a fellow
witch around your age,
maybe you two should get
to know each other.
Yes, I'll go and say hi.
[ANZU] Welcome.
[MAKOTO] Oh!
[ANZU]
Would you care for a
refill on your tea?
Ah...would you happen to be
the resident witch of this
establishment?
[ANZU]
Um...well...I guess.
[MAKOTO] Wow! (happy sounds)
[ANZU] Oh? Uhhh..?
Pleased to meet you!
This is great!
Thank you. You, too.
Hi my name is Makoto Kowata.
I've been training here as a
beginner witch since April.
Ah, so you're
the new witch.
These are my two relatives,
Chinatsu and her brother Kei.
I've been staying at their
family home, while training
to become a full witch.
[CHINATSU] Nice to meet you.
[KEI]
Likewise.
Anzu Shiina.
Pleased to meet you.
[ANZU] Hold on?
[MAKOTO] Huh?
[ANZU]
You said "Kowata."
Are you related to Akane?
Yes, Akane is
my older sister.
Ah.
I heard from my sister
that you are quite the
skilled and gifted witch.
It would be such a great
honor to learn from you.
Mm?
I'm not so special.
Oh come on now. There's
no need to be humble.
Uhh...
I can feel it. Your
aura is so powerful.
You will do great
things. Amazing!
What are you sayin'?
[ANZU]
Well anyway...please relax
and enjoy your time here.
[MAKOTO]
Thank you very much.
[ANZU] Hmm?
How'd it go?
Ah...now I get it.
Huh?
[ANZU]
That girl...
she mistook me for my mother.
[HINA]
Oh my!
Come to think of it, she
asked about the owner.
[ANZU]
Well, if Mom comes
let her know, okay?
Alright. I'm going
to go prepare this.
Did you get some good stuff?
[ANZU]
Yes.
They're bigger than last week's.
I'm sure he'll be
pleased with them.
[KEI]
So that girl is a skilled witch?
She's seems even younger than
us, don't you think?
[MAKOTO] No, I don't.
[CHINATSU KEI] Hmh?
I think at her age it
would be quite difficult
to use magic to change the
appearance of a building.
[MAKOTO] I bet she's also
using magic to make herself
appear younger than she is.
[KEI] Seriously?!
[MAKOTO]
I've heard that some
witches use magic
to make themselves appear
younger by looking like
they're just wearing makeup.
What? Cool! I'd
like to try that!
You're plenty
young enough.
[CHINATSU]
So does that mean she's
actually an old woman?
[MAKOTO]
Could be.
[KEI]
She did seem quite dignified.
[ANZU'S MOTHER]
I'm home.
[HINA]
Welcome home.
I apologize for asking
you to look after the cafe.
[HINA]
Not at all.
[HINA] Um...
[ANZU'S MOTHER] Yes?
[HINA]
We currently have some
customers,
including a beginner witch
who would like to meet the
owner of the cafe.
[ANZU'S MOTHER]
Okay. I'll go say hi.
[MAKOTO]
Excuse me.
Where can I find the restroom?
[ANZU'S MOTHER]
Welcome!
Oh!
(dumbfounded)
Hmm?
Eh?
Oh?
[MAKOTO]
Um...Are you Ms. Shiina?
[ANZU'S MOTHER]
In the flesh, and you?
Uh?! (freak out)
[MAKOTO]
Oh no! Ms. Shiina!
Yes dear?
Um, are you quite
alright, ma'am?
Your magic...it seems
to have worn off.
[ANZU'S MOTHER]
Oh dear...you mean the
cafe's magic?
[ANZU'S MOTHER]
Don't worry, that's normal.
It changes back to looking run
down after people have entered.
[MAKOTO]
No no, not that, ma'am. I think
it's gotta be your height, or
maybe your age.
I just get the feeling
you're taller now than
when we first met.
[ANZU] Hina.
[HINA] Hmm?
[MAKOTO ANZU'S MOTHER] Huh?
[ANZU]
I can't find that
plate anywhere.
[MAKOTO] Oh...
[HINA] What plate?
[ANZU]
The red plate.
I'd like to serve
some food on it.
[HINA]
Ah... that one is
on the top shelf.
(MAKOTO freaking out)
[KEI CHINATSU] huh?
[MAKOTO]
T‐there are two of you!
Two of you! One! Two! One!
[ANZU] Uhhhh...
[MAKOTO] Magic? Ninjutsu?
(more freaking out)
[ANZU'S MOTHER] Ehehhh...
(MAKOTO freaking out)
[ANZU'S MOTHER]
Are you okay?
[AKANE] All finished!
Alright! Time to try
this out somewhere safe.
[AKANE] Kenny.
Mraow!
[ANZU'S MOTHER]
(laughing)
Oh, now I get it.
You thought I was actually
Anzu posing as a young witch.
[ANZU]
I figured.
[MAKOTO]
I'm very sorry about that.
I didn't know you were
mother and daughter.
[ANZU'S MOTHER]
(laughing) It's quite alright.
You two really look alike!
Thanks.
What do you think?
How do you like
our cake here?
It is the most delicious
cake I've ever tasted!
Ohhh, that's great to hear.
[ANZU'S MOTHER]
You hear that, Hina?
[HINA] (embarrassed)
[ANZU'S MOTHER] Good for you.
[CHINATSU] Did Ms. Ghost
bake it herself?
[ANZU'S MOTHER]
That's right. And
her name's Hina.
[HINA] (embarrassed
to mortified)
(pinging sound)
[KEI] (surprised)
[ANZU'S MOTHER]
(laugh) She's a bit shy.
[MAKOTO]
Ms. Shiina, can I...?
[ANZU'S MOTHER]
Yes dear?
How long ago did this cafe
first open for business?
I guess, around 200 years ago.
[MAKOTO]
A whole 200 years...
[ANZU'S MOTHER]
Yeah...it has long
been a meeting place
for those on the
other side to gather.
The other side?
...You mean like ghosts and
other things like that?
[ANZU'S MOTHER]
Exactly. That's why we witches
use magic to hide the cafe.
Lest normal people walk in
and witness the strangeness.
Ah! Does the Harbinger of Spring
perhaps come and eat here, too?
Yeah, he does. I see
you know of him?
[CHINATSU]
I'm actually an
apprentice witch.
[ANZU'S MOTHER]
Oh, congratulations.
He's the coolest.
What does he eat?
[ANZU'S MOTHER]
He got his hands on something
really good last time.
Brought out a rare mandrake.
Hina was able to brew a
delicious tea.
[MAKOTO]
Ah?
[ANZU'S MOTHER]
Did you perhaps give it to him?
[MAKOTO] Yes.
Great job extracting the poison!
Hina was really able to
bring its sweetness out.
Sweetness, huh?
I've never been able to brew
anything sweet from a mandrake,
it always tastes bitter to me.
[ANZU'S MOTHER]
Hina has her own special
brewing method she uses.
[MAKOTO]
Oh, that's amazing. Please,
would it be alright if I learned
it from her sometime.
[ANZU'S MOTHER]
Sure, I'll have her teach you.
[KEI] Pardon...
[ANZU'S MOTHER MAKOTO] Hmh?
[KEI]
Um... Is it a problem for
me to be hearing all this?
I'm just a regular guy.
[ANZU'S MOTHER]
It's quite alright. You're
hanging around witches, so
you're actually not so normal.
[KEI]
Oh? You serious?
[KEI] Sis... It seems I'm not a
normal guy anymore.
[CHINATSU] Huh?
[CHINATSU]
(giggles) That's pretty cool.
[ANZU]
Oh?
Welcome my friends.
[MAKOTO]
Those Ladybugs?
Welcome back.
[MAKOTO]
Are they customers?
Yeah, they're
regulars.
[HINA]
Anzu...
Wow! Look!
[ANZU]
Thanks for waiting.
Take your time and enjoy.
[CHINATSU]
So they eat flowers?
Yes...they tell me that
thistle is their favorite.
So you're able to
talk with them?
[ANZU]
Well, Mom can.
[MAKOTO] Wow...she's amazing!
[ANZU'S MOM] You two
are so close.
[KEI]
Are they... together?
[MAKOTO]
Is one male and
the other one female?
[ANZU]
Yep. Apparently, this is
one of their date spots.
[MAKOTO CHINATSU KEI]
Ehhh...
[MAKOTO]
I wonder if they're
speaking right now?
[KEI]
And what are they saying?
[CHINATSU (MALE BUG)]
Delicious, simply delicious.
[CHINATSU (FEMALE)]
Is it tastier than my cooking?
[CHINATSU (MALE BUG)]
I couldn't possibly
compare the two.
Where'd you come
up with that?
This is so relaxing.
[ANZU]
Did you know that ladybugs
bring happiness
to whomever they
choose to land on?
[CHINATSU KEI MAKOTO]
Huh?
(CHINATSU excited)
(MAKOTO getting up)
(determined)
[MAKOTO CHINATSU]
Wah!
Huh?
(CHINATSU jumping and straining)
(MAKOTO straining)
[MAKOTO CHINATSU]
(trying very hard to
touch the ladybugs)
[MAKOTO CHINATSU]
Huh...
Hey thanks...appreciate it.
Almost...
Mm‐hm.
[MAKOTO CHINATSU]
Huh?!
(MAKOTO CHINATSU straining)
[ANZU'S MOTHER] Eh!
[KEI] Over here!
[MAKOTO CHINATSU] Huh?
(KEI pointing)
[MAKOTO CHINATSU]
Oh?
Wha...! (running)
[ANZU'S MOTHER]
(small giggle)
(trying to get the
ladybugs attention)
(CHINATSU laughing)
Thank you very much
for visiting.
(KEI laughing at those fools)
[MAKOTO]
They didn't try to
land on any of us.
[CHINATSU]
That's too bad!
[KEI]
Excuse me. Do those ladybugs
pay for their food?
Well not with cash. But instead,
they get rid of all the bad bugs
that are feasting in
the fields around here.
[KEI]
Oh, like aphids?
Right. And that's good since
we have a kitchen garden.
I wonder if that means they're
out there protecting my garden
from bad bugs, too?
They probably are.
[MAKOTO]
Wonderful! I'm grateful
for your assistance.
[ANZU'S MOTHER]
Welcome.
[MAKOTO] I'm grateful,
so grateful.
[CHINATSU] Oh! Uh!
(CHINATSU scared yelp!)
[KEI MAKOTO] Huh?
[CHINATSU]
Ohhhhh?
[KEI] A g‐ghost...?
[ANZU]
No, that's the Veil.
[MAKOTO] Oh? Incredible!
[CHINATSU] What's the Veil?
[MAKOTO]
This is the first
time I've seen her.
[MAKOTO]
I take it she would be
the Veil of Night?
[CHINATSU]
What does this Veil of Night do?
[MAKOTO]
She's the one who
ushers in nighttime.
Wha? WOW!
[ANZU]
She's a regular
customer of Hina's.
She doesn't have much to do
until the evening, so she
comes here for tea.
[CHINATSU] (impressed)
[KEI] ...She seems quite
dignified.
[CHINATSU] (run giggling)
[CHINATSU]
What are you reading?
Mhm!
Oh... Uh...
[KEI]
Is it okay if she talks
to her like that?
It's fine, she's a very
kind and loving being.
[CHINATSU] Thanks!
[KEI] Oh?
[CHINATSU]
(slight laugh) I have candy!
[MAKOTO] Ohhh... Nice!
[KEI] Cool!
[MAKOTO]
Good for you.
[HINA] (smile)
(scratching on door)
[HINA] Oh!
[MAKOTO CHINATSU KEI]
Oh?
[ANZU]
Ah, he's here.
[MAKOTO CHINATSU KEI]
Huh?
Oh...
(door opening)
[ANZU] Welcome.
Welcome.
[MAKOTO CHINATSU KEI]
Oh...
[ANZU]
Hello.
The usual today?
Hina.
Here you go.
[ANZU]
Please enjoy the food.
It's not so easy getting a hold
of these during this time.
[MAKOTO] Excuse me, Anzu?
[ANZU] Oh?
Can we...
Can we come a bit closer?
[ANZU]
Go ahead.
Wow!
What food is
he eating?
They're lantern fruits.
He loves them. He comes
every Sunday to eat them.
Will he be mad
if I pet him?
No, go ahead.
(excited)
[CHINATSU]
Ah...
SO soft.
Lucky you.
Let me pet him.
Ah, I wanna pet
too...please.
[KEI]
Ohhhh..
[MAKOTO]
Ahhh..
[MAKOTO KEI CHINATSU]
(happy petting)
[CHINATSU]
Hey...what does the fox say?
Meow, meow?
Foxes say "KON, KON"
didn't you know that?
No, they say
"KON, KON"?
I would love
to hear that.
(dog bark)
♪♪Closing Song♪♪
[AKANE]
Ah, there's someone.
Hey!
Huh?
[AKANE]
Well hi there.
I would really like to borrow
this boat you have here.
Uh...
This boat...right here!
I wanna take it
out...and ROW away.
Just me alone.
Mm‐hm, mm‐hm.
How much?
Mmhmm.
Hmh?
No way. That's way
too much for that.
Uh?
[AKANE]
This should be enough.
Argh. Mnmm, mnmm..
Hm?
(sigh)...well
[AKANE]
How about this?!
Uh? (sigh)
Hm.
Yippee!
[AKANE]
CAM ON, CAM ON.
Mraow, meow...
You're always right.
We can't see this kind
of scenery in Japan.
Meow, meow...
Huh? Ah, I wouldn't
forget about this.
[AKANE]
Time to try it out.
Mraow?
Well...Chinatsu asked me...
"Why is it that the
ocean is blue, anyway?"
And that made me think it
doesn't really have to be
blue, does it?
[AKANE]
So I decided to make
a magic potion.
Mrow.
Exactly.
That's why I wanted
to test it out
in a place with
great scenery.
Seems it's a huge success!
(laughing)
Meow?
Don't you worry about it?
It'll turn back in uhhh..
Ohhh?
[AKANE]
This is... pretty strong...
Well?
Let's take a photo of this.
Mraow.
Ah...we don't have anyone
to take it for us.
Meo‐wow.
Oh yean, Kenny,
that's a great idea!
[AKANE]
Alright! It's done.
Well...I'll be right back.
Meow...
(MAKOTO snoozing)
[AKANE]
Makoto. Makoto.
(MAKOTO groaning)
I brought her back here.
[MAKOTO]
Ready? One, two,
three... (sleepy)
Thank you sis. Will you take one
more for us, just to be safe?
(winding up camera)
(MAKOTO sleepy)
[KEI]
Thank you for the meal.
[CHINATSU]
Look, look. It's
a lantern fruit!
[KEI]
(slurping) I see that.
[MAKOTO]
That's really cute.
(laugh)
[CHINATSU]
Thanks for the meal! Woof!
[MAKOTO]
Thanks for the meal.
[MAKOTO] Oh?! (worried sigh)
[CHINATSU] (happy chewing)
[KEI]
What is it?
I had the strangest
dream last night.
[CHINATSU] (slurping)
[KEI] Oh? What about?
[MAKOTO]
Um, well... I was inside a
Chinese ink wash painting
taking a photo of Akane,
or something weird like that.
[KEI]
What in the world?
Sounds pretty surreal.
[MAKOTO]
Yeah... you're right.
[AKANE]
(laughing) Vietnam is the best!
[AKANE] (laughing)
(chugging her drink) (laughing)
Well, well. You're
hardly drinking at all!
[AKANE]
Come on! Drink up!
Now we're talking.
Chug it, chug it!
[BOAT MAN]
Ugh!
(AKANE laughing like a
deranged drunk person)