[CHINATSU] Oh!
[AKANE] He's arrived.
(getting up)
[AKANE] Morning.
Oh? Uh... Hello,
good morning sir.
[CHINATSU] He's huge...
[AKANE] Thank you for coming
all this way. One paper, please.
[AKANE]
Thanks.
[CHINATSU]
...That's the Newspaper Carrier?
[AKANE]
Yep. If a witch waits outside
their front door in the morning,
he'll come to drop off a paper.
[CHINATSU]
So is this a regular newspaper?
[AKANE]
No, it's a newspaper put out
by those on the "other side."
[AKANE]
It features a lot of news you
won't find in a normal paper.
[AKANE]
And it's the most popular
newspaper among witches.
[CHINATSU]
Cool. The Newspaper
Carrier looked kind
of like the Harbinger.
[AKANE]
Ah, well they're practically
relatives, after all.
Hmm?
Hey, good morning
you two.
[AKANE] Good morning, sis.
[CHINATSU] Makoto, good morning.
What were you two
doing just now?
[AKANE]
Introducing Chinatsu to
the Newspaper Carrier.
Ahhh. I haven't read that
paper in quite a while.
Wow!
You really
should keep up.
[AKANE]
It's important
to stay informed.
Yeah.
[AKANE] Oh!
[MAKOTO CHINATSU] Hmm?
Seriously?!
[AKANE]
It's flying right
over us this year!
[AKANE]
Awesome!
♪Opening Song♪
[CHINATSU]
Wow! It's flying in the sky!
What is that thing?!
It's a flying whale.
A whale?!
Yeah. I still haven't
been able to see it
with my own eyes, yet.
It travels all
around the world,
so it's a bit difficult
to track it down...
But this year will
be different.
It'll be flying pretty
close to where we are.
Wow! Are you sure about this?!
[AKANE]
Yeah. And apparently it's going
to be flying pretty low.
Awesome!
Let's figure out the
timing and go there!
Yeah, definitely!
So... when is it
coming close by?
Tomorrow?
Uh, let's see...
Ah!
Shoot! It's already pretty
close to being around!
[MAKOTO CHINATSU]
Huh?!
Um, we don't
have much time,
so let's get
ready quick.
Meet me by the front
door in seven minutes!
Okay?!
[BOTH]
Okay!
[CHINATSU]
Mom, Mom!
Well hello to you. What are
you so worked up about?
Is it okay if I
head out for a bit?
Sure, but where
are you going?
I'm gonna see a whale!
Uh... oh?
See a whale...?
[MAKOTO]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Everyone ready?!
Chinatsu, you ride
with me, okay?
I haven't been flown
in quite a while!
Mmph!
Wow!
Flying doesn't
hurt anymore?
Nope, I've
mastered it.
It's forecasted to pass
right over this section.
I really hope it
hasn't already passed
on through here.
Oh yeah. I almost forgot this.
You both need to rub this
ointment around your eyelids.
[AKANE]
It's camouflaged as a cloud,
so you won't be able to see it
unless you use this.
[AKANE]
Chinatsu, hold
your bangs up.
Okay.
Perfect. You rub
some on, too.
Sure.
(sniffing)
It doesn't seem to
have a scent to it.
(CHINATSU sniffing)
[AKANE] (sigh)
Still not here...
[MAKOTO] Uhhh... Ah! Akane?!
Is that it over there?
[CHINATSU] Huh?
[AKANE] Hmm?
[AKANE]
Which one?
[MAKOTO]
Look! Over in that cloud!
[AKANE CHINATSU]
(straining to see)
There's a small
bit sticking out.
Hmm... Uh... Is
that really it?
Where is it?
It's the only cloud
shaped like a whale.
That's gotta be it.
Shall we try to get
a bit closer to it?
Huh?
(AKANE excited)
[CHINATSU] Wow!
[MAKOTO] (amazed)
(whale moans)
Whoa! So cool! That
whale is flying so
high in the sky!
Whoa!
So big!
Are you ready?!
Let's go ride!
[BOTH]
Huh?
[MAKOTO]
We can ride it?!
[AKANE]
Excuse me! Will you let us
ride up top for a bit? Please.
(whale groaning)
There's grass here?
Oh?
Wow!
[CHINATSU]
Whoa!
[MAKOTO]
Amazing. Are these ruins?
[AKANE]
Yep. I hear that in the distant
past people used to live here.
Cool.
[CHINATSU]
Wow! It's huge!
[MAKOTO]
What is this place...?
[AKANE]
I think it's probably
some kind of temple.
Hmmm... Oh?
Hmm? What is it?
[CHINATSU] Wha..?
[MAKOTO] (excited gasp)
(happy breath)
Ah! (giggle)
(giddy giggle)
[CHINATSU]
I can't believe we're so
high up off the ground. Wow!
Ah, look over there.
That's where we picked
the ostrich ferns.
[CHINATSU]
Huh? Where exactly?
[MAKOTO]
See? That's the spot.
[CHINATSU]
Huh? No it isn't.
Ehhh?
[CHINATSU]
Ah, it's a whale!
[AKANE]
No kidding...
So they really have been
around since ancient times.
[AKANE]
Looks like it.
(whale moans)
[AKANE]
This here must be the tip
of the whale's head.
[CHINATSU]
Ah, someone else is here.
[AKANE]
Seems they beat us.
[MAKOTO]
Hello, Good morning.
Uh!
Oh good morning
to you, as well.
Ah!
Oh?
You're... uh...
Hello!
You're...
You're Anna!
Anzu.
[MAKOTO]
Ah... forgive
my rudeness.
[AKANE]
Oh! Anzu. Nice to see you.
[ANZU]
Akane, long time no see.
[MAKOTO]
So I take it you came
here to see the whale?
[ANZU]
Yes. I've been wanting to see it
in person for a long time, so
this is exciting.
If I remember correctly,
you have a thing for
learning all about history.
Yes, I do.
Cool! You have
a refined taste.
[AKANE]
Wow, we have the best seat!
[AKANE] Wee! We're up so high!
[ANZU] Apparently in the
past the whales used to fly
together in a pod.
[MAKOTO] Interesting...
[ANZU]
Once people stopped
living aboard them,
each whale began to
travel around the world,
living freely on its own.
[MAKOTO]
So there are a lot
more of these whales?
There have been three
other whale sightings
confirmed recently.
But people suspect there
are more whales out there.
You sure know a lot
about this, Anzu.
I'm just sharing
what I've heard.
I think you're
really amazing.
[MAKOTO]
Are you planning to be an
archaeologist someday?
Ah... I'd like to be one.
Cool! Does that mean you
practice using mine carts
and stuff?
Huh?
Are you going to practice
running away from huge
boulders and stuff!
[ANZU]
I don't think archaeologists
actually do those kind of
things...
(stomach growling)
I'm starting to get
pretty hungry.
We still haven't eaten
breakfast, have we?
(stomach growling)
(embarrassed) Uh...
Now that you bring
it up, I haven't had
a chance to eat yet.
Well... I hate to leave
now... but maybe it's time.
I think you're right.
[MAKOTO]
Hmh?
Good bye.
(camera clicks, snaps picture)
[CHINATSU]
Bye‐bye.
Anzu.
Oh?
Why don't you come
over to our place for
a cooked breakfast?
[ANZU]
Uh?
Yeah. Please come and
eat with us, Anzu.
I would love to hear
more of your stories
about the flying whales.
Come on!
Mhm, mhm!
Uh. Sure. I'd love to come over.
[MAKOTO]
I've got something really tasty
I want you to try out.
[ANZU]
Sure!
(car starting)
[NANA]
Wait up, Dear!
[KEIJI] Huh?
[NANA]
(out of breath)
Here's your bento.
[KEIJI]
Ah, thanks for
takin' the trouble.
Where'd Chinatsu and
the rest get off too?
(giggle) She said they
were off to see a whale.
To see a whale...?
Yep. A whale.
[KEI] (Big yawn)
(telephone ringing)
[KEI] (soft groan) Oh?
[KEI]
Yeah, yeah...
(accepts call)
[KEI]
Hello.
Oh, Makoto.
Yeah... good morning. Hmh?
Well where are you guys?
You're not at home?
[KEI]
Hmm... yeah. Huh? A whale?
Really? Did you go
out to the ocean?
Huh, a guest? 'kay...
[KEI]
Ah... yeah that should be fine.
Whoa!
[ANZU]
Is this where you live?
[MAKOTO]
Yes, the Kuramotos
have taken us in.
Lucky you. What
a residence.
It does have a
special charm to it.
You're right... it
most certainly does.
You think so? The
house is pretty old.
Exactly, that's what
makes it so great.
If it's okay. Can I
take some photos?
Yeah, go ahead.
(pictures snapping)
(door opening)
Oh!
[MAKOTO]
We're home.
Come on in.
Welcome home.
[ANZU] (in awe)
[MAKOTO] We made it back.
[KEI] Welcome.
[ANZU] Oh!
[ANZU]
Ah, thanks for
having me.
Do you remember
Kei? He was with
us at the cafe.
[ANZU]
Yes... he's the guy
who's scared of ghosts.
(embarrassed)
Shoot, she knows.
[AKANE] Nana, let me help.
[CHINATSU] Kei, what's for
breakfast?
[NANA] Oh, thanks.
[KEI] Hotcakes.
Oh, we haven't had
those in a while.
Are you sure? Didn't we
have some the other week?
[CHINATSU]
The other week? That was
a whole month ago.
[KEI] That is the
other week to me.
[KENNY] (meow)
[ANZU]
Oh? Ah, Kenny.
Wow! It's been quite a
while? How have you been?
[KENNY] (meow)
Hold on? You two
know each other?
[ANZU]
Yes, he often comes to visit
the cafe with your sister.
[MAKOTO]
Oh, I see.
(talking meow)
Mhm... Right... you
heard that correctly.
[ANZU]
The whale was just as
amazing as you said it was.
I did a bit of poking around,
and the theory you gave me on
why people stopped living there
is probably the best
argument I have heard.
[KENNY] (talking meow)
Oh, I understand now.
There's still so many
mysteries surrounding it.
(talking meow)
(ANZU laughing)
Kenny also seems to know
quite a lot about the whales.
[AKANE] Oh? Makoto,
you didn't know?
[MAKOTO] Huh?
Kenny has been studying
anthropology for a number
of years now.
[MAKOTO]
Is that so? Kenny,
that's so amazing.
[AKANE]
And he's traveled all around
the world on his own.
He's gone to see the whale
and study it dozens of times.
Mraw!
Whoa! I had no idea.
He's been my teacher
for a while.
Oh wow! He's Master
Anzu's teacher!
[KEI] A cat who willingly
studies anthropology...
[ANZU] I'm not your teacher.
[MAKOTO] Well that's
another story altogether.
[NANA] Welcome!
Ah?
My, my, what a cute
little witch you are.
Oh, thank you. That's very kind
of you. My name's Anzu Shiina.
I'm Kei and Chinatsu's
mother. Nice to meet you.
My apologizes... for
coming over so suddenly.
Quite alright. We don't
have anything special
prepared,
but please feel free
to eat whatever we have.
Ah! That's right.
I forgot that I've got something
I would like you to try, Anzu.
[KEI]
Let's see... I still need eggs.
I wonder if this'll be enough.
(MAKOTO humming)
[KEI] Huh?
Hmm?
[MAKOTO] (giggle)
[MAKOTO]
Here... these are
some pickled radishes.
Makoto grew
those herself.
Really?
That's cool!
Oh, it's nothing.
I don't think they will go all
that well alongside hotcakes.
Ahhh. I think you might
be right about that.
(chomp) (chew, chew, swallow)
[ANZU] Ah, they are quite tasty.
[CHINATSU] (chomping)
[MAKOTO]
Thanks. I made a ton of them,
so eat as many as you want.
[NANA]
Hmmm? What's with this
newspaper? It's incredible!
[AKANE]
Isn't it?
[ANZU] Oh?
[MAKOTO] That's Chito.
[ANZU] Oh... hi there.
[CHITO] (meow)
[NANA]
(laughing) Hey, is
this potato singing?
[AKANE]
Yeah, it's a new variety that
was just discovered.
(NANA &amp; AKANE laughing)
[ANZU] Uh..
You'll get an
upset stomach.
Shh!
[KEI]
Alright...
Lookin' good...
Are you ready to be a
"hotcake‐making machine"?
[KEI]
Yes... I am good for
nothing else but making
hotcake after hotcake.
What are you
talking about?
He's the best. He
makes hotcakes like
nobody's business.
He can make really
delicious thick ones,
so I like to call him a
"hotcake‐making machine."
Uh... is that really so?
[MAKOTO]
Huh? You're adding more batter?
[KEI]
Yep. If you drip some more
in a donut‐shape like this,
the hotcakes get thicker.
Now I feel like
having some donuts!
You were right.
They're super fluffy.
[KEI]
Now to put on the lid and
cook 'em a bit more.
(ALL yummy eating)
[ANZU]
Kei...these are good!
[AKANE]
You'll make a good
wife someday.
[KEI]
A "wife," huh?
[CHINATSU]
Anzu. I've a question.
Do you know about the
history of hotcakes, too?
(clearing throat)
There are varying
accounts...
[KEI] You actually know them?!
[MAKOTO] Oh?
[ANZU]
They're said to have
originated in ancient Egypt.
They were made by heating
a mixture of sugar, flour,
and water.
The custom was introduced to
Japan around 70 years ago.
The first hotcake mix sold in
Japan didn't include sugar so
that it could also be used to
make manju buns.
[ANZU]
But hotcakes failed to become
popular and didn't spread around
the country.
Sometime later, a mix containing
sugar went on sale and hotcakes
became increasingly popular.
With the Japanese diet becoming
more westernized. Hotcakes
eventually spread to households
throughout the country.
Wow!
[ANZU]
By the way, although we call
them "hotcakes" in Japan,
they're mostly called
"pancakes" throughout
the western world.
Yeah, that's right.
Huh? So pancakes and hotcakes
are really both the same?
[ANZU]
Yes, they're basically just the
same thing.
Though there are
variations in cooking them.
"Pancakes" get the "pan" part of
their name from "frying pan,"
as they are cakes that can
easily be cooked in one.
[ANZU]
So hotcakes cooked in a frying
pan are therefore pancakes.
[ANZU]
Technically, they can be
differentiated by thickness.
The thick ones are hotcakes,
and the thin ones are pancakes.
[ALL]
Wow...
So the ones Kei just made us
are really hotcakes, then.
You're right, those are
considered hotcakes.
Wow Anzu... you seem
to know just about
everything, don't you?
(giggle) Well I hardly know
everything there is...
(talking meow)
[KEI CHINATSU ANZU] Hmh?
[ANZU]
Oh that's right. They were
introduced to Japan in the
Meiji period,
which is earlier than I stated.
(affirmative mews)
Are those ones for
Chito and Kenny?
They are.
[KEI]
Here.
[CHITO] (meow)
[NANA]
Anzu, where do you live?
Ah... My mom and I
live in a cafe
that's just a bit further down
the road, on the other side
of the wooden tunnel.
Oh? There's a
cafe over there?
It can be pretty
hard to find.
Can I stop
by sometime?
Please do.
It's incredible there.
The waitress there is a real
live ghost from the past.
Ah, it must be the cafe
you were telling me
about the other day.
She disappears like
"Poof" in front of you
and "Poof" she's back.
Hey cut that out will ya.
If you keep talking like
that, a bunch of ghosts are
gonna come wanting your soul.
No they won't.
Ah!
What's the matter, Anzu?
I just realized I need to
call my mother and let her
know I'm here...
You better get to it.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Do you mind if I use
your phone for a sec?
Go ahead... it's
right over there.
What a good friend
you have.
Ah, Mom?
It's me, Anzu.
Hmm. I saw it. It was
incredible.
Anyway, I happened to
meet up with Makoto there.
Right... that girl.
[ANZU]
She treated me to breakfast at
her family's lovely home.
So I'll be a bit
late getting home.
Oh I see now. That is
great dear. Just make sure
you thank her properly.
[ANZU]
Yes, I know. See you later.
[ANZU'S MOTHER]
Ah, Anzu, hold on a sec!
[ANZU'S MOTHER] Is Akane there
with you by any chance?
[AKANE] (happy chewing)
Hey, is everything
alright?
Yes.
Uh...Is it okay if
I open the windows?
Yeah, go right ahead.
Need a bit of fresh air?
Lately, it's been getting pretty
warm a lot earlier in the day.
Uh... yes.
Hmh?
[ANZU]
Ah, she's here!
[MAKOTO]
(surprised gasp) Oh!
Wow! There's
an owl!
What's this?
Oh...
[CHINATSU]
Anzu, is that your familiar?
Yes.
[MAKOTO]
Ah, so you're a familiar?
You surprised me.
That is amazing!
[ANZU]
I'm sorry. It seems my mom
wants Akane to look at
something important.
("Oh? For me?")
[NANA]
(amused) (enchanted)
Long time no see, Orel.
[AKANE]
Thank you.
Let's have a look at that...
What could it be folks?
[AKANE]
"Your tab is rather large.
Please stop by and pay."
(AKANE laughing uncomfortably)
♪Closing Song♪
[MAKOTO]
Oh! Huh?
Yeah!