(NAO groaning)
(STUDENTS chattering &amp; laughing)
Hey there.
I'm about to go.
[MAKOTO]
Nao?
[NAO]
I'm sorry, but Nao Ishiwatari is
closed for the rest of the day.
Hm?
What are you talking about?
[NAO]
Ungh!
Please save me!
What?
♪♪OPENING SONG♪♪
(STUDENTS chattering)
(big exhale sigh)
You alright? Are you
not feeling well today?
No... Ah, Makoto
that's not straight.
Thank you for
fixing that.
(big sigh)
Oh...
[TEACHER]
Alright. Please be very careful
with using the knives
and watch your flames
while cooking.
[STUDENTS] Okay.
[KEI] Let's do it.
I look forward
to this.
Whatever...
[MAKOTO]
Let's first decide who will
be in charge of each dish.
[KEI]
Sounds good.
By Ghost Leg
lottery?
[KEI]
Sure.
Seriously?
Hmh?
Uh, I'm... really bad at cooking
and might blow something up.
Or at the very least burn
into an unrecognizable crisp.
I was thinking the salad
would be nice and safe.
Don't worry about it.
You'll be fine.
None of this stuff is that
difficult to cook anyway, Nao.
Let's just do our
best together!
(nervous ummm)
Okay, It should
be ready to go.
[KEI]
Pick one.
Uh, hey Kei?
Hm?
Which one of these dishes
is the easiest to mess up?
Uh...The Hamburg
steak, I guess.
[NAO]
Okay...
I'll take this one!
It doesn't seem very Hamburgy!
Ohhh! Come on nice salad!
Salad, salad, salad, salad,
salad, salad..
[KEI]
And you, Makoto?
Oh, it's one on
the right, Kei.
[KEI]
Last one is mine.
[KEI] Let's take a look.
(uneasy)
[KEI]
Nao, take this.
This one's yours.
[NAO]
Huh? You put onion
inside Hamburg steak?
You've eaten one before.
[NAO]
You mean I don't just mix up the
ground meat,
and slap it into a round
balls, and grill it up?
Seriously? You've never cooked
a Hamburg steak at home?
Well, you see. When I was
little I helped to deep fry
some croquettes and messed up.
I mixed up the vinegar and
frying oil and caused a
disaster. It's been a source of
trauma ever since
[KEI]
How you do even mix
these two up?
Since then I stay out of
the kitchen to make sure
I don't cause my family
any more harm.
[MAKOTO]
So, you haven't chopped
an onion either...?
[NAO]
Nope.
[MAKOTO] U‐oh...
(NAO straining)
Hmm...
(NAO straining uncertainly)
[NAO] (aggressive grunt)
[MAKOTO] Ah!
There. M'kay!
Now to cut it in half...
[MAKOTO] (bewildered)
(NAO straining)
[NAO] (aggressive shout)
(MAKOTO yelp)
(sigh)
You're scary.
A‐are you alright
there, Nao?
[NAO]
It's like I was saying:
I'm no good at cooking.
[TEACHER] Is something wrong?
[MAKOTO KEI NAO] Huh?
What's with the
yelling back there?
Did you cut yourself?
Uh... no.
Cut the onion vertically into
thin slices, and be sure to hold
it very close together.
Mhm. Like?
(straining) this?
[TEACHER] Start from
the easiest side.
[MAKOTO] Huh?
[TEACHER]
That's it.
Make sure to curl your fingers
and cut nice and slow.
You're doing
really well, Nao.
Next, starting from one end,
cut along the horizontal.
[NAO]
I get it now! Huh!
[TEACHER]
It's easy if you just
stay calm. Good luck.
[NAO]
Th‐thanks!
I always knew you
had it in you!
(determined)
[KEI] Nao, you know‐
[NAO] Hold on! I'm trying to
concentrate!
Hmmm...
(NAO starting to sniffle)
[MAKOTO]
Really, Kei? You're putting
that in the microwave?
[KEI]
Mhm. Before cutting an
onion, if you heat it
up in the microwave...
(sniffling)
...you can avoid having
THAT happen to you.
NOW you tell me!
I tried to tell
you earlier.
[NAO] Ah, I see now.
[MAKOTO] (slight giggle)
(chattering &amp; laughter)
Sprinkle some salt
and pepper on it...
[NAO]
Whoa, what's with this texture?!
It's DIS‐GOOD‐STING.
Blergh!
DISGOODSTING?
It feels somewhere between
disgusting and good...
I've never felt
anything like it before.
[NAO]
Now I need to add
sauteed onions, an egg...
[NAO]
Hmm...
Huh?
(confused) (straining)
[MAKOTO]
Nao...if you tap it lightly on
the bowl it will break open.
Oh.
(tap‐tap)
(crack)
[NAO]
Now to mix this up.
(grossed out)
(giggle)
Ungh!
Okay next...Add the milk‐soaked
panko‐breadcrumbs...?
Is this really gonna end
up a Hamburg steak?
It will turn out just fine.
Huh?
Also you should probably try
to squeeze out some of the
milk first.
(sizzling)
[NAO]
Oh? It feels real
nice and smooth.
Uh, next I need to...
"Divide into four parts
and roll into balls.
Use your palms to try
and squeeze out the air"?
Pretend the meat's a ball and
you're playing catch with it.
Just like so...
[NAO]
Ah, I get it. I've seen
that on TV before.
[NAO]
Divide into four equal parts...
[NAO] (CM reax)
(throwing meat ball)
[MAKOTO] Ohhh..You're doing so
good.
(more confident tosses)
[NAO]
(giggle) Girl, this
is a piece of cake.
(splat)
(disappointed)
This will be Kei's.
[KEI]
Hey!
(excited)
[NAO]
Alright, the patties are done.
[MAKOTO]
Look, one of them is shaped just
like a heart. That's cute!
[NAO]
That one is packed full
of my undying love.
[KEI] It's the bad one...
[NAO]
Ta‐da! Cooking oil! Woo!
I won't make the
same mistake!
I can't believe
you did that.
Go away...is this
one a tablespoon?
Yep. Now hand over
the teaspoon, please.
What the..?! You're putting
honey in the curry?!
It helps mellow out the flavor.
But I do need to cook it
longer or the curry won't
be thick enough.
Why do you even know stuff
like that? You're such a girl.
(sizzling)
(haughty sigh)
Well, well, this whole Hamburg
steak thing seems pretty easy.
Oh, it's really
coming along nicely!
(slight laugh)
I know, right?
[MAKOTO]
I'm gonna go ahead
and wash these.
[NAO]
Huh? Makoto, are you already
finish baking the cookies?
No, I'm just wanting the
dough to rest a bit longer.
Then, after that all I
need to do is cut out
the shapes and bake 'em.
Wow, you work fast.
I bet they're made from
magic, and that they're
insanely delicious
Good point.
Wait guys...
please don't set such
high expectations.
Hey Makoto.
Do witches have a kind
of traditional cookie‐
that they always bake?
Hmm...
I wouldn't say it's
traditional per se,
but we witches do have a
pretty interesting cookie.
[NAO]
What's it like?
[MAKOTO]
It's a called a
"Witch's Pinkie."
[NAO]
"Witch's Pinkie?"
Very true to its namesake,
it's supposed to look just
like a witch's pinkie finger.
Among us fellow witches...it's
a good luck charm for romantic
relations.
Oh, for real?
That's pretty cute.
Since I'm making cookies...
let's add them in too!
I've got all the
ingredients I need already.
[NAO]
Oh, sounds good.
I want to try one.
[KEI]
Nao, those are burning.
Uh! Oh shoot! Ugh!
(STUDENTS chattering)
(concentrating)
(sniffing)
(content sigh)
That should do it.
[NAO]
It's done! Ahh...
Oh?
You did an
excellent job.
One more left.
[MAKOTO]
That looks great!
[KEI]
Tasty.
I can't believe I made these.
They turned out great for
your first time. Wow!
You know...you've really
have a talent for cooking.
(laugh) Really?
Thank you.
(stomach growling)
[MAKOTO] Huh?
[NAO]
That was me. Ugh...
I'm like super hungry now that
I'm not so nervous anymore.
Wah! Ah! What's that you're
holding, Makoto?!
[MAKOTO] Hmh?
[NAO] THAT!
[NAO]
A finger?!
Oh, you mean this?
[NAO]
Wah! Gross!
What's with that thing?!
My cookie? It's a Witch's
Pinkie I was talking about
earlier.
[NAO]
Huh? That's a cookie?!
[MAKOTO]
Yeah, that's all it is.
The nail's made from an almond.
And the trick is trying to make
them look as real as possible.
[MAKOTO]
Like this.
Ugh, that's
too realistic.
It will look more
real once I bake it.
[NAO]
This helps with relationships?
I envisioned something adorable.
[STUDENT] Hm? Uh!
[MAKOTO] (smile)
Hey! Once your group finishes,
feel free to eat, okay?
[KEI]
Curry's ready.
Let's show the teacher.
Way to go. Can we just eat
already? I'm dying over here.
It all looks good.
[NAO]
All I want to do is have a big
huge helping of delicious rice.
[MAKOTO]
Nothing wrong with that.
You worked up an appetite.
[NAO]
You're right. I've earned
myself a reward today.
[NAO]
Uh... Who was in charge
of cooking the rice?
[KEI]
We never did decide...
(AKANE sleeping)
[MAKOTO]
Kei, what should I take with me?
[KEI] Let me think... At least
take some work gloves.
(AKANE snoring)
(waking up)
(stretching, groan)
[MAKOTO]
Will these clothes be okay or
should I wear something else?
[KEI] They're fine if you're
okay with them getting dirty.
(AKANE sleepy shuffle)
[MAKOTO]
Ah, Akane.
[AKANE]
Huh? Where are you going
so early in the morning?
[CHINATSU]
We're going to go thin
out the apple trees.
Thin out? (big yawn)
What's that?
[MAKOTO]
It's the job of picking
the apple blossoms.
I think you slightly
misunderstood.
[MAKOTO]
Huh? That's not right?
[KEI]
Well, you'll see
when we get there.
Akane, you should
come and join us.
Hmm, let's see... I don't
have any other plans.
Yippee! I get to hang
out with Akane!
Kids! Time to get a move on.
[MAKOTO AKANE CHINATSU] Okay!
[KEI] Alright.
[AKANE]
Hmm...What a nice breeze.
[MAKOTO]
(inhale) It smells
so nice out here.
[MAKOTO]
Hey, how far along
are the blossoms?
They're in half‐bloom.
You know you are pretty
amazing, Chinatsu.
You sure know a lot.
[CHINATSU]
(giggling) Makoto,
you're even more amazing.
You can fly all around!
Yahooo!
That's dangerous!
I'm fine, really!
They're here.
(AKANE getting up &amp; stretching)
Mmph!
(car door opening and closing)
[LADY A]
Good morning.
[NANA]
Good morning to
you, Ma'am.
[LADY A]
Good morning.
[LADY B]
And who's this
young lady?
She's a relative of mine.
She's here to help us out.
[MAKOTO]
I look forward to
working alongside you.
[LADY A]
My...what sweet manners
you have there girl.
[CHINATSU] She says
you're sweet.
[MAKOTO] You're too kind.
[LADY A] Oh my, there's
also a foreigner here.
[CHINATSU] Oh?!
(laughing) Despite my exotic
looks, I'm actually Japanese.
(bees buzzing)
[LADY C]
Cats?
[KEIJI]
Sooo...
I betcha we can finish up the
thinning out there before the
day's over.
Let's get'er done, okay?
Well then, I'll see
ya'll in them fields.
[ALL]
Okay.
This is for you two.
[MAKOTO]
Wow...it's so beautiful
here, isn't it?
It is... really something.
[AKANE]
I always imagined apple
trees being taller.
[KEI]
We prune the branches, to
make sure they will all grow
out to the side.
[AKANE]
Ah, I see now! So if
they're left alone they
end up growing taller?
[KEI]
Right. And it's a lot easier to
tend them when their branches
are closer to the ground.
When you're walking around the
farm grounds, be sure to watch
where you're going or you might
bump your head.
[AKANE] Got it.
(THUMP) [MAKOTO] Ow!
(whimpering sounds)
[CHINATSU] Ouch.
[AKANE KEI] Huh?
[AKANE]
(slight laugh) What happened?
Don't tell me you
bumped your head.
I was looking at the blossoms...
(AKANE laughing)
Come on, Kei was just telling
us to watch were we're going.
I swear you can be such
a klutz at times.
(MAKOTO whimpering)
You've gotta watch
where you're going. Ah!
(AKANE fighting off the pain)
[KEI]
Hey dad?
Hmm?
[KEI]
Where should we start?
Well, why don't you guys
start with that there tree.
[KEI]
Okay.
[KEIJI] MAKOTO...Akane.
[MAKOTO] Huh?
[AKANE] Hmm?
[KEIJI]
This here is how you thin out a
tree.
See these bunches of flowers
clustered on this here branch?
[KEIJI]
Each one of these here
will grow into an apple.
But let 'em all grow and
trouble brews. You ain't
gettin' a single keeper.
So ya gotta do some clippin'
to make sure them nutrients
all get in there.
[KEIJI]
Just like this...
Ya'll leave the big guy in the
middle and snip off them other
ones real good!
[KEIJI] Yer aimin' for this.
Got it?
[AKANE MAKOTO] Oh..?
[BOTH]
Um..? Huh?
[MAKOTO]
Sorry. You lost me after the
first part about thinning out
the trees...
[MAKOTO]
I still have trouble
with long sentences.
Hmph!
(AKANE laughing)
Uncle, try explaining
it in English!
You can't just start
speaking French.
That wer' English!
Guess ya ain't ready. Kei!
Huh?
[KEI]
Each one of these will
become an apple.
[MAKOTO AKANE]
Yeah?
But if you let them
all bear fruit,
then the quality
won't be as good.
So we need to thin out the
flowers to make sure nutrients
flow to a single flower.
Just like I'm doing, leave the
healthiest flower, the central
one, and snip off the rest.
[KEI] Got it?
[MAKOTO AKANE] I get it now!
[KEIJI] (frustrated)
[CHINATSU] There, there now.
[AKANE]
What about the flowers
we snip off?
[KEI]
Just throwing them on
the ground will be fine.
[AKANE]
I see.
A sad shame. You'll never
get to grow into apples.
[MAKOTO]
It's such a harsh world.
Come on don't say that.
It makes me feel I've
done something awful.
[KEI]
They'll become nutrients
for the soil and still
prove useful... I think.
♪♪♪
[CHINATSU]
Kei...I wanna work on the top.
'kay.
Here you go.
Thank you.
(exertion)
Mmph!
Chinatsu, you're not scared
up there, are you?
I'm perfectly safe.
Hup!
You look so cool up there
like some kind of ninja.
[CHINATSU]
Really? I think I'll be
a ninja when I grow up.
Oh? I thought you were
going to be a witch?
that's right. I guess I'll
need to become a witch ninja.
[AKANE]
Sounds good.
[KEI]
A witch ninja?!
That sounds pretty cool!
Is it... alright for a witch
to become a ninja, too?
It's okay by me.
Ah...
Kei? I wanna go work
on the treetops, too.
Good. Be careful.
Yep.
(THUMP!)
(MAKOTO yelp)
[MAKOTO] (wimper)
[KEI] Watch it.
Oh...
[MAKOTO]
Oh? Wow!
What a view.
[MAKOTO]
Granny!
[LADY B]
I'm not that old, child!
(LADIES laughing)
Yes. That should do it
for this apple tree.
You done? I wanna
use the stepladder.
Sure. Whoa...
Stepping down
is kinda scary.
(MAKOTO timid step)
(jumping down and landing)
You know you usually fly
a lot higher than that...
This is altogether a different
experience than us flying.
You think so?
Oh?
Hey Kei...what's that
stuff over there?
[KEI]
Hmm? That's a hive for
horn‐faced bees.
Those are bees?
That's right. Huh?
Let's see...
Ah...there we go.
[KEI]
See?
[MAKOTO]
Whah! Is it okay to do that?
You won't get stung by it?!
[KEI]
Totally safe with them.
These guys don't sting at all.
In the process of collecting
pollen for their food,
the bees pollinate the
apple blossoms for us.
[KEI]
We keep the beehive box here
to make it easier for them.
[MAKOTO]
Wow! Those are some
hard‐working bees.
Is it okay to let
one land on my hand?
[KEI]
Here.
(happy sigh)
[MAKOTO]
It's so small and cute!
[KEI]
It'll fly away once it gets
to the end of your finger.
Eh?! Ouch, that hurts! It's
biting me really hard, Kei! Ow!
Ah, I hear they bite when
they're agitated. First
time I've seen it.
S‐so even though they
don't sting, they bite?!
(blowing)
Oh!
[KEI]
I guess it's best not
to pick them up.
[KEIJI]
Hey, 'bout time for a break!
[LADIES]
Okay.
[NANA]
Here you go.
(excited chatter)
(AKANE laughing)
Hey...this is nothing
to laugh about, okay?
[MAKOTO]
Oh, that's right.
[KEI] Looks like the
next one is over there?
[MAKOTO] Ladies.
These are some finger
cookies I made at school
yesterday.
Feel free to help yourselves.
Oh my, what
might that be?
Oh look at this. This one
looks just like our fingers.
Eating one of these cookies
might give you good luck in
love relationships.
It's the cookies. The reason
the bee bit you, I mean.
[AKANE] It was overcome by
your matchmaking magic.
[MAKOTO] Eh?
Well, come try some.
[MAKOTO] Ah, honey!
[AKANE]
Oh, this is your fated match!
[MAKOTO] Don't mind if I do.
(chomp)
Delicious!
That's a match
made in heaven!
♪♪Closing Song♪♪