♪♪
(Nao sighs)
(Giggle)
♪♪
(Mwor...)
(Footsteps approaching)
(Mer?)
(Meow)
Oh?
Hey! I didn't
see you there.
You're, um...
Chito, right?
(Meeooww)
Hi there. Do you
happen remember me?
(Mwor)
(Giggles)
I don't know what
you said, but sure.
(Purring)
(Delighted meowing)
Huh?
(Annoyed meowing)
Hey, Chito, did you happen
to put on some weight?
(MWOR!)
(Distressed moaning)
Seems like you might've
gotten a little bit bigger
since I last saw you.
♪Opening song♪
I bet it's still
pretty cold up in the mountains.
I wonder if you'll
need a scarf, too.
I think it would probably be
a good idea to take one.
Off to pick some
plants, huh?
Ah, sounds nice.
They're in season now.
Would you like to
come along with us?
Nah, I'll pass.
[AKANE]
I've gotta
catch up on my TV dramas.
(Doorbell rings)
Oh, she's here.
Shall we go?
[MAKOTO]
Sure!
[AKANE]
Ah... Bring something
back for me!
[CHINATSU]
Okay!
(Groaning)
Hi, Nao! 'Sup?
H‐hi there, Chinatsu...
[KEI]
What's going on here?
I don't really know.
She suddenly just jumped up
on me and won't get off.
Chito, what's
your problem?
You can't just hop on
top of people like that.
(Disgruntled meow)
Ohh... She says she's a bit
angry with you right now...
(Fwap)
(Sigh)
I'm sorry, Chito...
(Mer!)
[CHINATSU]
Chito is coming with us?
It's a chance for
her to exercise.
I've never seen a cat
riding a bus before.
So, um, how old
is Chito, anyway?
[MAKOTO]
Hmm... Let's see...
I think she's
about seventeen.
(Annoyed meow)
Are you meaning just
seventeen in cat years?
No, I mean she's been
alive for seventeen years.
Huh? What?! She's a granny?!
(MWOR!)
Uh, I‐I'm sorry.
She does look quite young
for being that age...
[MAKOTO]
Witches' familiars are kind
of special in that way.
(Affirmative meow)
[NAO]
So, I guess that would make
her the eldest of our group.
(Purring)
[KEI]
"Ms. Chito" to us
Hi, Ms. Chito!
(Meow)
(Giggle)
[BUS PA]
Thank you for riding with us.
The next stop is
Shimo‐oaki Iriguchi.
(Ding)
[CHINATSU]
Hmm?
(Confused meow)
(Bus engine idling)
(Doors close)
(Engine revs up)
[KEI]
'Kay, let's get going.
♪♪
(Birds chirping)
(Wonderous sigh)
[KEI]
We're here!
Whoa...
[MAKOTO]
(Amazed gasp and giggle)
So, it's okay to pick plants?
This is my friend's
land, so no problem.
(Amazed gasp)
[NAO]
I never knew about this place.
[MAKOTO]
This is a really great spot!
(Gleeful squeal)
You love places like
this, don't you?
Uh‐huh!
Hey, Chito, check out
the stream here.
You can see the
fish so clearly.
Isn't it so beautiful?
Wow! See that?
It's terraced over there!
I bet it was once
used for farming!
(Reluctant meow)
Ah! Chito, look over there!
[NAO] Look at that.
Makoto sure does
seem excited.
I hear that witches
pep up when they visit
nice places like this.
Huh?
(Gushing continues)
(Moaning continues)
[KEI]
There are four general rules
when picking wild plants.
The first one is:
Don't pick too
many wild plants.
Just take what you need.
If you pick too many, the plants
will not grow next year.
The second is: Don't pick
plants you can't identify.
Every spring, people die when
they eat poisonous plants
they mistook for edible.
Scary!
Let's start with
ostrich ferns and
Japanese royal ferns.
[TOGETHER]
Mm‐hmm!
Third one is:
Don't head off by yourself.
Don't go off into
the mountains...
and always stay within
sight of someone else.
[KEI]
It's likely Makoto
will never find her way
back if she gets lost.
Agreed!
Uh...
And... number four is:
Beware of bears.
Bears?!
(Gleeful laugh)
To let bears know that
people are around,
we should always
carry a bell with us.
Mm‐hmm! Mm‐hmm!
But...
I left the bell at home
on the coffee table.
Say what?!
Ah!
(Music on TV)
(Crunch)
[KEI]
Man, I'm such a dummy.
I had it all ready to go
and everything.
I put it on the table right
before we left.
H‐hold on a minute.
This sounds awfully risky...
(Nervous sigh)
Come on!
Let's catch a bear!
Huh? Are you insane!
You're going to get eaten!
I'm sure it
will all be fine.
I haven't heard of any bear
sightings in these parts.
Even if one is around,
it shouldn't bother us
as long as we
talk really loud.
You've gotta
be kidding me...
Yes, sir!
Let's get going!
(All sigh)
[KEI]
Ah, found some.
These are ostrich ferns.
[MAKOTO]
Ah, they're so cute!
[NAO]
They're everywhere.
These taste great
with sesame seeds.
(Delighted gasp)
[KEI]
Alright, let's start picking
the ostrich ferns growing here.
[MAKOTO]
Okay!
(Snap)
Nao, have you ever
gone out to pick some
wild plants before?
Nuh‐uh. No, I never have.
Today will be my first time.
So, do you come
here often?
Yep, I came here with
my big brother last year.
Oh, I see now.
So you like wild plants?
Nuh‐uh...
No, not exactly.
Huh? Really?
I think it's pretty
fun to pick them,
but I don't really
care to ever eat them.
But Akane said I wouldn't
be a good witch
if I'm being too picky
with eating my vegetables.
So I'm challenging myself
to eat some of it.
What a good girl!
Huh? Being a witch...?
Oh!
Hm?
Mmmmm. MM!
(Soft croaking)
So adorable!
Go show it to Nao.
She likes frogs, too.
Oh, she does really?
Hey, look, Nao!
Check this out!
[BOTH]
Hm?
Aaahhhhh!
It's a frog!
(Terrified moan)
(Laughs)
If we're making this
much racket,
there's no way
a bear will show.
No! No! No! No! I can't
stand those creepy things!
Really? But Kei said
that you really like them.
You little...!
(Echoing)
You little...
(Mwor?)
[MAKOTO]
Well then, what should
we pick next, Kei?
Good question...
How about we pick some
victory onions next?
[MAKOTO]
Are they tasty?
[KEI]
They're delicious!
But, um, eating them makes
your farts smell really gross.
(Laughs)
Do they effect
you that much?
That sounds
kind of fun.
Ugh...
'Kay, why don't we go look
for some when we're ready?
I'm gonna pass
on that, thank you.
[CHINATSU]
Nao!
Hm?
You should try to get over
your fear of frogs.
What...?
Why are you so
creeped out by frogs?
Don't you think
they're cute?
No, no, no. No way!
I just really don't like
the texture of their skin.
It's wet and slimy...
And they give you warts...
On top of that, they have
stringy little legs...
(Distant scream)
♪♪
[CHINATSU]
Bye‐bye, Nao!
[NAO]
Bye‐bye!
(Grinding)
(Water boiling)
(Excited sigh)
Here, try one.
(Gasp)
Ahh...
(Chewing)
So, do you like it?
(Swallow)
Mmm!
Good, good.
Ostrich ferns are pretty tasty.
I know!
(Akane hums)
(Beer can opens)
(Gulping)
Hmm...
YEEAAH! So good!
The food or beer?
Um, you know it's not good
to be drinking alcohol
in the afternoon.
Hmm?
(Laughs)
It's even better
in the afternoon.
[AKANE]
The fact it's frowned upon
just makes alcohol taste better.
You guys should try
it for yourselves once
you're old enough.
[KEI]
You sound like
an old man.
Hmm...
(Groan)
Om!
Oh, she ate it.
(Groaning)
Mm...
(Sigh)
(Chuckle)
(Gasp)
I ate all of it!
Ahhh...
(Clapping)
[MAKOTO]
Wow! Way to go, Chinatsu!
Hmm...
But I still think they
taste like something
adults would eat.
(Both chuckle)
I don't think they're
made for kids' tastebuds.
(Laughs)
Maybe you're right.
You might like the taste
better once you've gotten
a bit older, Chinatsu.
Om!
(Happy humming)
(Groan)
[AKANE]
I've got an idea.
Huh?
Want some cake to get rid
of that aftertaste?
(Happy gasp)
Do I?! That sounds good!
(Akane chuckles)
[KEI]
Lucky you! I want some, too.
[MAKOTO]
Did you buy some earlier?
Nuh‐uh.
Nope. But there's a delicious
cafe not far away...
that serves cake!
Huh?!
Hm? I don't recall there ever
being a cafe around this area.
It's kind of hidden
from the regular public.
It's run by a witch and is
a nice place to go eat at.
Oh?
A witch runs it...?
Huh?
So cool!
It'll be a good
chance for Chinatsu
to get a look into
the witch world.
And the witch there
is quite skilled,
so it should be a good
learning opportunity.
[AKANE]
Go and say hi!
[TOGETHER]
Okay!
♪♪
[KEI]
Seriously. I don't
remember seeing a cafe
anywhere near here.
[MAKOTO]
I'm so excited!
[CHINATSU]
Yeah!
(Chinatsu laughs)
[KEI] Okay... It should be
somewhere around here.
Hmm... I don't see
it anywhere.
Hmm...
Huh?
Is this it?
(Crows cawing)
This place is a
lot uglier than I
thought it would be.
I think it's got bigger
problems than that.
It looks like
it's pretty run‐down.
Hey, Kei, did we take
a wrong turn back there?
As you recall,
I do that all the time!
(Groan)
According to Akane's map,
this is the right place.
Huh?
[GIRLS]
[KEI]
"When you arrive, bow twice,
clap twice, bow once."
What's that about?
Two bows, two claps,
and one more bow...
What's that mean?
Well, that's how you would
go about praying at a shrine.
Ohh! How do you do it?
First, you should
bow twice, like so.
Next, you are going to
clap your hands twice.
(Clap, clap)
Hm...
Now you're going to make a wish,
and finally bow one last time.
That's how we "bow twice,
clap twice, bow once."
Cool! I'll try
it next time!
Oh?
(Amazed gasp)
(All gasp)
[CHINATSU]
Amazing! It looks
so pretty!
[MAKOTO]
Oh, I get it now.
The building itself
was under a spell.
The ritual we just
performed revealed the
building's true appearance.
Incredible!
(Chinatsu giggles)
[CHINATSU]
It says the cafe
is this way!
Wow...
Chinatsu, here,
put on these slippers.
[KEI] This place is more
a mansion than a cafe.
(Chinatsu hums)
Maybe it's also being
used as a place to live.
(Door squeaks)
Hm?
Please excuse us!
Wow, it's lovely!
(Makoto and Kei gasp)
Hm...
I don't understand;
there's no one here.
Huh?
What's this?
"Welcome to Conclusio.
Please take a seat wherever you
would like within the cafe."
Um... sure.
Is there no waitstaff
around here?
If that's to be the case, then
how will we place our order?
Hmm...
(Ice rattles)
[ALL]
Huh?
[GIRLS]
Ohh...
Hmm...
(Akane humming)
(Fuming poof)
Uh!
(Phone rings)
(Groan)
(Ringing continues)
[NANA]
Akane! Phone please!
'Kay!
(Ringing)
Hello. Kuramoto residence.
[MAKOTO]
Hey, Akane?
Oh, what's up?
[MAKOTO]
Really?
Yeah, uh‐huh...
Oh, now I see!
[KEI]
What'd she say?
It's just as we suspected,
the waitress is a ghost.
Wow!
(Kei grunts)
(Nervous)
You for real?
The witch that owns
this place hired her on,
but the ghost is
quite shy, so she's
concealing her appearance.
Having a real ghost as our
waitress is truly wonderful!
No, no, scary is
what it is.
Kei isn't a big fan
of ghosts, remember?
(Girls gasp)
Guh!
I guess we better
order something.
I wonder if she's
over there.
(Scared sigh)
I'll have the chocolate
cake for me.
[MAKOTO]
I'll have the apple pie that
was posted on the sign.
Kei, what are you having?
Uh... well...
the same, please.
(Thunk)
(Kei grunts)
(Dishes rattling)
(All gasp)
I'm sensing our
waitress here.
I'm really excited to
finally have a chance
to meet a live ghost.
I want her to
sign an autograph!
(Dishes rattling)
[CHINATSU]
I wonder what kind of person
our ghost waitress is.
[MAKOTO]
I hear you. I'd like to get
a good look at her too.
She wouldn't be as scary to you
if you could see her, right?
Uh, yeah... I guess
that would be okay.
Hmm...
Oh, I know!
(POP)
(Marker squeaking)
Hey, you've drawn
that before.
That's right. It's a magic
circle I'd like to try out.
Okay, this should
allow us to see her.
Excuse me, Ma'am!
(Door squeaks open)
(All gasp)
[MAKOTO]
Uh! Well...
Is the witch who owns
this place around here?
(Speechless grunt)
(Amazed gasp)
(Light chuckle)
[MAKOTO]
Oh, thank you
for telling me.
Hey, I've got
a question!
Ms. Ghost, can you tell
me how old are you?
I see. So you're from
the Meiji period.
What's "Meiji"?
It's an era about
100 years ago.
Wow! You're from
100 years ago?!
That's so awesome!
(Ghost chuckles)
Ah, so that's why!
That must be the reason why
you're wearing a kimono!
Hm?
[HINA]
Huh? Does that mean...
you can see me?
I'm sorry...
I used some magic...
(Nervous sighing)
[HINA]
The cake...! I'll
go get it right now!
Awesome! We saw a
real live ghost today!
Whoa...
(Glass shatters)
(All gasp)
[HINA]
Please excuse me!
(Chuckles)
Maybe that wasn't very
nice of me to do.
♪Closing song♪
[HINA]
H‐here's your apple pie.
And, uh, this is
your chocolate cake.
Well... then...
(Group moans)
Please, take your time
and enjoy our
delicious food.