I love you.
And you're all I can think
about, my darling.
Let's spend the rest of our
lives together, just
the two of us.
Yes, Miyabi.
I'm so happy.
Excuse me, Miss?
The Master has returned home.
Miss?
Renge?
You certainly love those
video games, don't you?
Is that so wrong?
No, not at all.
I'm your father and I want you
to feel free to live your
life however you please.
You know that I'll let you
do anything you like.
I've always promised
you that freedom.
Yeah.
Did your business trip
in Japan go well?
I think so.
I had a lovely dinner meeting at
the home of one of my
clients while I was there.
I made sure to get a photo.
Take a look.
They have a boy in high school
who's about the same age as you.
He's the one.
I'm going to marry the
boy in this photo!
Don't forget, you promised me
that I could do whatever
I want, Father!
Uh. But, Renge.
I'm coming for you,
my prince charming!
Renge!
Attack of the Lady Manager!
Oh, Tamaki.
My dearest Tamaki, why
are you so beautiful?
I'm hoping to catch your eye,
even if for just one second.
Then why is your voice so
very sweet and mellow?
To set your nerves at ease so
that my true feelings might
reach your heart.
Why are your eyes filled with
tears every time you look at me?
Because, the sight of your
beautiful smile causes the
fountain inside me to
start overflowing.
Oh, Tamaki.
I think it's adorable that
you're wearing matching kimonos!
Our mother designed everything
the hosts are wearing today.
If you see something you like we
can take an order for you.
Our grandmother even
helped us put them on.
But you know the only one who
will be undressing
you is me, Kaoru.
Hikaru you're embarrassing
me in front of everybody.
What a tender embrace!
They're up to that
nonsense again.
Haruhi!
You look so cute in your kimono!
Almost like a girl!
Thanks.
Haruhi, you've booked
another appointment.
It seems you've had a pretty
steady flow of new
customers lately.
Keep up the good work.
I'm not going to charge
you interest on your debt
like I normally would
so keep this up
and you should be
able to pay it off.
Although, the rental fee on that
kimono you're wearing is
nothing to sneeze at.
He's like some kind of
heartless tax collector!
Hello, Kyoya.
I can't get over how great
you look in that kimono.
Are you planning to release
any more picture books
of the Host Club?
Unfortunately we don't have
anything planned at
present, ladies.
But doesn't the club
make a lot of money--
--from the sale of
promotional items?
That's true but the
items are poor quality.
Those picture books
were full of nothing
but amateur hidden
camera shots.
However, if we want to
create some higher-quality,
money-making products,
I'm afraid we'd have to
draw money from the
school's budget.
If it wasn't for
Kyoya the host club
would spiral into the
depths of bankruptcy.
Haru-chan, Haru-chan.
I don't know how but I
lost one of my sandals.
But you were just wearing
them, weren't you?
Mitsukuni.
Takashi.
I noticed that you dropped it.
Takashi!
How sweet.
Isn't it, though?
Looks like tears are popular
with the ladies today.
But how are they all
able to cry so easily?
What's this?
For your information,
it's common for a host
to use eye drops.
No woman alive can resist a
man on the brink of tears.
That's cheating.
Oh, don't be such
a party pooper.
Here, Haruhi.
This is for you.
It's for me?
Aren't you the cutest?
I didn't know you
liked sweets, Haruhi!
Well, to be honest with
you, I don't really.
But you know.
I think it would be
a nice memorial offering
for my mother.
How admirable of you!
Such devotion to your
mother's memory.
Please Haruhi take as many
of these as you like.
Let me guess, the
tears are fake?
How could you?
My tears are always
genuine, Haruhi.
Being able to cry without the
use of eye drops is the
mark of a true host.
Tell me, do I impress you?
Have you fallen for me yet?
You wish.
My romantic overtures do not
seem to be reaching
you for some reason.
Perhaps I should
add a little more
panache to my character, huh?
Looks like the host club
has a brand-new guest.
Come on in.
What are you waiting for?
Watching from afar is no fun.
Please miss?
Stop that!
How many times do I have to tell
you boys to be more courteous
to our first-time guests?
Please, you don't have to
be afraid, my princess.
I welcome you to the
Ouran Host Club.
Yes?
No!
Don't touch me!
You're phony!
What do you mean I'm phony?
Just what I said!
You're phony!
I find it hard to believe that
someone like you is the prince
character of this host club!
You shouldn't go spreading your
love around so easily
like that, you stupid!
You must be a
dim-witted narcissist!
You're incompetent!
You're a commoner!
You're disgusting!
He's created a new technique!
One-man slow-motion!
I don't suppose you are--
It's you, Kyoya!
Oh, how I've longed to meet you!
My one and only prince charming.
Your fiancée?
Kyoya-senpai?
Of course.
My name is Renge Hoshakuji and
I'm transferring into Ouran
Academy's 1st-Year,
Class A tomorrow.
Why is he sulking?
Because Mommy was
keeping a secret from Daddy.
Whatever.
Why does everyone insist on
referring to us like
we're husband and wife?
Ours is a story of
love at first sight.
I couldn't resist the way you
were adoring those flowers in
the backyard when you thought
no one else was looking.
And how sweet it was when you
reached out to that poor,
little injured kitten.
She serious?
Could you have the wrong person?
No way!
I could recognize
my love anywhere!
He's a gentle man who's
kind to everyone
but doesn't ask for
anything in return.
He likes solitude but in fact,
sometimes he gets lonely.
He looks like the star
of the popular dating sim,
"Uki-doki Memorial"!
You're my real life
Ichijo Miyabi!
Uki?
Doki?
Otaku!
Otaku?
I've never seen one!
I get it now.
You're in love
with that character.
You're projecting that love onto
me, and you've somehow deluded
yourself into thinking
that we're engaged.
I assume this Miyabi character
probably wears glasses as well.
So she made it up?
You're not really
her fiancée, right?
Well no, I don't remember ever
asking for her hand in marriage.
Besides, this is the first time
I've ever met the woman.
According to my research, I
understand that you're in charge
of managing the club,
is that true, Kyoya?
That's right!
Kyo-chan is our director.
You're the club's director?
That's perfect!
Oh wow!
I've always wanted to wear
a sandwich board to
advertise a business.
We don't advertise.
We're just a host club.
I've made up my mind.
From now on I'm going to be
the manager of this host club!
Um, listen Kyoya.
Miss Hoshakuji is the only
daughter of a very
important Ootori family client.
So please be polite and try
not to offend her, alright?
Well boys, I can't
wait to work with you!
I thought about it
a lot last night
and maybe having a lady
manager isn't such a bad idea.
Why do you say that?
Well it's fairly
obvious, isn't it?
Renge just transferred into
the same class as Haruhi.
So, if Haruhi has a girl friend
around could bring out
the female within her.
Renge's girlish air of
tenderness might be able
to stimulate Haruhi's own
sense of femininity.
Good grief.
Now is our chance to help Haruhi
get in touch with
her feminine side!
This is an important
project, men!
She doesn't have any
friends in class right
now except for these
two shady twins.
That's no good for her.
Like you have room to talk.
Hey everyone!
You'll be happy to know that
your new manager, Renge,
has baked all of
you some cookies.
Isn't she ladylike!
I'm so moved by your generosity!
I didn't bake these cookies
for you, you phony prince.
I'm sorry I burnt
them a little bit,
I did the best I could
and I already know what
you're going to say.
Anything that you
make for me is
going to taste
delicious my dear.
Oh, you're always so
sweet to me, Kyoya.
She wasn't kidding.
These cookies really are burnt.
Don't eat that Mitsukuni.
It's bad for you.
She's scaring me!
They're not that bad at all.
They've got a good
flavor to them.
May I try?
Uh-oh Haruhi, you've got
crumbs on your face.
Did you see what they just--
And suddenly the
trio of classmates
are closer than they've
ever been before.
You know, you could've just told
me and I would've wiped it off.
And if you wanted to try
one there's plenty here.
That's not the way you're
supposed to react, Haruhi!
You have to stay strong
and reject them.
Then casually brush
them to the side!
Do you understand?
This is sexual
harassment, Senpai.
Sexual harassment?
If that counts as
sexual harassment
then they're twice as guilty!
Someone call the police!
Cut it out, boss.
We're sorry.
Renge-chan, Renge-chan.
Want some?
It's milk.
Lukewarm.
Every single one of you!
Except for Kyoya, all of your
characters are lukewarm!
Each of you needs
to have some sort
of "dark" side, you understand?
Girls are vulnerable to handsome
young men who are troubled!
If you keep carrying on like
this it's only a matter of time
before the girls
get tired of you
and stop coming all together.
Are you trying to ruin my
precious Kyoya's business?
As your manager, it's
my duty to change
your character backgrounds.
Let's start with you!
If all you are is
cute, inside and out,
then you're no
different than a baby.
Therefore, from now on,
you are the baby faced thug!
And Mori-senpai, you're his
childhood-friend; the flunkie!
The twins will be
basketball players,
enslaved in their own world!
Haruhi, you're an honor student
who's constantly being bullied!
And as for you Tamaki, you're
the school idol who's admired
for your good looks but you
actually have an inferiority
complex you're hiding
from the world.
The lonely prince!
And Kyoya you're perfect
just the way you are now.
So I want you to stay as kind
and affectionate as ever, kay?
Thank you. I'm honored.
"The lonely prince."
It's true, that title
is perfect for me.
Yeah right, she couldn't
be farther from the truth.
Come on, Kyoya-senpai.
You've gotta do something!
Why? It seems like the
boss is up for it.
How does this look, Renge?
Do you think these poses
work for a lonely prince?
Oh wow, you're pretty
good at that, Tamaki!
But you know, it would be even
more effective if you
were standing in the rain.
Let's just wait and see
how things turn out.
I bet it'll be interesting.
It always is.
Get a stretcher!
Take him to the
infirmary immediately!
Kaoru?
Kaoru!
You've got to get back
in the game, Hikaru.
We need you!
Shut up!
Hikaru.
Listen to me,
please don't worry.
There's nothing you can do.
You can't share my pain.
You're not the one who got hurt.
Now go on.
I can't!
It hurts.
It hurts, Kaoru!
Your pain is my pain.
It doesn't matter to me if
no one else understands.
As long as we have each
other, we can go on living.
I'm sorry but I'm envious.
The way the two of you
support each other like that.
But Suou-senpai.
How can you be envious of us?
You're the school's idol.
An idol, right.
I hate that people
all worship me
for something so superficial
as my appearance.
I think it would be much
better for me to be alone.
One lonely heart meets another.
They pass each other,
wounding one another.
What are the hearts of
these young men made of?
You can't run away forever.
I'm gonna show you what happens
to anyone that crosses me.
Don't do it, Mitsukuni.
You should have
realized by now that
whenever you hurt others you're
really just hurting yourself.
I didn't ask you for any advice.
You want me to put you
over my knee again?
Will it be the
light of salvation
that ultimately
awaits these boys?
Or will it be something else?
You know, it really
pisses me off
when people don't
know their place.
I'm so sorry, Haru-chan!
I can't do this anymore!
Cut, Cut!
Cut!
What's wrong with you?
You've got to stick
to the script!
But I can't!
Stop rolling, cameraman!
Yes, boss.
I want the rain to
make things seem tragic!
How'd we go from
changing our characters
to shooting a movie about them?
And why is there an entire
film crew here to shoot it?
Apparently, she flew
them in from Hollywood.
Don't you recognize
the director?
He directed the vampire
movie, "Millennial Snow."
It was the number-one
grossing box-office hit
in America last year.
Damn these rich people.
And another thing,
how come this stupid script
portrays Kaoru as the pitcher?
Yeah.
What does that mean?
If you don't know, never mind.
Pitcher?
Haruhi. So how was I?
Did you like my performance?
It was pretty awesome.
I'm surprised you were able to
get into your
character like that.
You were really believable.
I've discovered a new,
darker side of myself.
I'm starting to think it might
be a good idea to explore it.
Are you sure about that?
Because I think you're fine just
the way you are now, Senpai.
You do?
Well.
If you say so, Haruhi.
If he gets in touch
with his darker side,
he'll be that much
more trouble.
Hey, Haruhi!
You're on!
Coming!
Over here!
These two gentlemen
have just agreed
to make a special
appearance in our film.
In your film?
What are you talking about?
After all, we're going to need
some tough guys for
the big climax!
That's when all of the club
members come together
to fight against the real
villains at their school!
According to the script,
these two are from
a wealthy family
that got their wealth by being
a part of the Japanese Mafia.
Don't you think that's a
brilliant casting choice?
What's with this girl?
Whatever my dad does
has nothing to do with me!
Wait a minute, Renge.
Just come over here
and wait for your cue.
Hey!
You think you can
push me around?
You don't even know me!
Watch out!
Are you okay, Haruhi?
That guy was right, Renge.
You can't do that,
if you judge people
by their appearance
you're stereotyping them
and you'll never see
the person inside.
Um.
I don't understand what
you're trying to say.
What happened, Haruhi?
So which one of you
jerks started this?
Wait, Suou!
It's not what you think!
That girl started it!
She was giving us a hard time!
He's telling the truth, Senpai.
It wasn't their fault.
They were provoked.
Let's get outta here!
Haruhi, are you any in pain?
Yeah.
It's my contact.
Your contact?
Yeah.
I guess it must've slipped out.
I see how it is!
You're able to cry
without using eye drops.
So you're a
full-fledged host now!
You, you.
Please tell me you
got that, cameraman!
Yes, boss!
Other than Haruhi's
contact falling out
that was an ideal final scene!
All it needs now is a moving
narration by my sweet Kyoya.
No!
What'd you do to my camera?
What?
Is something wrong?
I'm terribly sorry but
I cannot allow there
to be any record of a club
member engaging in violence.
I think you've caused enough
trouble around here, Renge.
Please stop being such a pest.
A pest?
But you're supposed to
pat me on the head
and tell me not to worry!
You're supposed to be kind
and affectionate, Kyoya!
Why are you acting
so differently now?
Tell me why!
Because that's not
the real Kyoya.
Does it really matter?
Who cares if Kyoya is
a little different
than you expected him to be?
Take a good look at
the person inside
and get to know him
little-by-little.
It's a lot more fun that way.
Long time no see, Renge.
Why are you so down?
Come on, please smile for me.
Today's going to be
a beautiful day.
After all, today you've learned
a very important lesson
that will help you live
happily ever after
and I'm so glad that you
finally understand.
I think you're ready to move on
to the next level, Renge.
Hello ladies, come on in.
I bought the video of
that film you made!
I bought it too!
And so did I!
You did?
That scene in the rain
was just phenomenal!
I love the lonely prince!
And the loving relationship
between Hikaru and Kaoru
was so sweet!
I want to see Honey act
like a thug again!
It was so cute!
I couldn't get enough of
Haruhi's poignant expressions!
Mori was definitely--
Kyoya?
I may have broken
the camera's lens
but the footage that we had
already shot wasn't damaged.
But naturally, I did cut out
that one violent scene.
Sales have been
pretty good so far.
That Hollywood film crew
did a fantastic job
but then I guess
that's to be expected.
So is this what you
meant by "interesting"?
It's best to have as much money
as we can in the club's budget.
And just when did he start
calculating all of this?
Good day, everyone.
Renge?
But I thought you had gone
back to France already.
I can't believe I didn't
realize this sooner.
It was so chivalrous of you to
risk your life to protect me.
I could feel the love
when you lectured me
about judging people.
When you said it was fun to get
to know people little-by-little
you were talking about me!
Yeah.
Come on Haruhi,
let's go to my house and
play some games together.
I think it's time you
got to know me better!
What?
Hey. Kyoya-senpai.
You okay with that?
Why wouldn't I be?
Everything Renge said is true.
No it isn't!
But I thought you were the
one who wanted her to have
a female friend in
the first place!
Well yeah, a female companion!
Not a girlfriend!
Come on, Haruhi!
Let's go play together!
No wait!
Don't take Haruhi from me!
I'm so sick of your face!
Your haircut's stupid!
Sex pixie!
Sicko!
What's going on?
What's up with Hikaru and Kaoru?
Next time, "The Twins Fight"!
The Ouran Host Club
will be waiting for you!
We'll see you then!