Hikaru. Your phone. Hikaru.
Answer it for me, will you?
No way. Don't you
recognize that ringtone?
You've got to be kidding
me. We're only three days
into summer vacation. Why
can't he let us sleep in?
He's probably been
up since dawn.
Yeah, what?
She's gone! My beloved
daughter has vanished off
the face of the earth! She
must have been kidnapped by
a band of gypsies, I just
know it! Contact the police!
We have to request an emergency
deployment of the SDF!
Wait, slow down. You're not
making any sense. Now what?
What do mean
Haruhi's gone?!
Huh? So Haru-chan is
really missing?
And her family
is bankrupt.
It's the only explanation! I've
been trying to get through
to her home phone and
her father's work for
the past several days and no
one will answer!
They've been evicted and forced
into indentured servitude!
We have to
rescue them!
Haru-chan!
Boss please, not so loud.
Have you tried calling
her cell phone yet?
Cell phone?
Why on earth would she have
a cell phone?!
Of course! She was issued one
by a secret underground network
of commoners known as
"The Plebeian Exchange."
Not to interrupt your
delusion, but Haruhi
is currently in Karuizawa.
Haruhi was turned out
of her home,
kidnapped by gypsies,
and forced into servitude
in Karuizawa?
Moron.
Thank you. Have a nice day!
Hi! Good morning!
Ah. Who would've thought
working at a bed-and-breakfast
could be the ideal way to
spend my summer?
The Refreshing Battle
in Karuizawa.
So she's gone off and left
us, huh?
Looks like it.
Good Morning, masters.
Good morning.
Breakfast is waiting for
you downstairs
Alright- we'll be down in
a minute
Very good, sirs.
It's just no fun without her.
What are we going to do now?
At first I was a little
apprehensive about
not telling the guys my
plans for the summer.
But it isn't like
they really have
the free time to keep tabs on
me anyway, right?
This is place is so tranquil.
Fresh air. Quaint setting.
The perfect highland getaway
for a girl to catch up
on her studies.
It's going to be great.
Haruhi!!!
Despair not! Daddy's come
to save you!
And by "great," evidently I
mean "a nightmare".
Oh my! What dashing young
men you are!
These hunks must belong
to Haruhi!
Another fluttering tranny?
Why don't you Call
me Misuzu-chi!
He's an old friend of Ranka's.
They used to work together
at the same shop
years ago.
Well, naturally you
would know.
Kill me.
I went into business for
myself two years ago
and believe you me running
this adorable little pension
is like living a fairytale!
So then, is Haru-chan like
your indentured servant?
She's more like an
unpaid employee.
This also happens to be
Ranka's preferred method
for keeping track of
his daughter while he's
busy working.
What the-? How do you know
all of this stuff?
Kill me.
Take my little girl under
your wing, he says.
He practically begged me.
And since I still can't afford
the expense of hired help,
it works out for everyone.
She's a model employee, really.
It's such a shame I can't pay
her anything. Oh. Tell me
what you boys think of this
cute little apron she's
wearing. I made it myself!
You are quite an
exquisite seamstress!
A job, huh?
I don't get it. You turned
down our invitation
to Bali for this?
And we even asked
her to go with us
to Switzerland didn't we?
We did.
Yeah well, I still don't have
a passport remember?
Which is precisely why I
recommended one of our
domestic resorts. And at
a discount no less.
Traitors. Asking Haruhi to go
on summer vacation with you
behind my back. Have you
no feeling of loyalty?
Of any solidarity?
Togetherness is our guiding
principle. I work myself
to the bone upholding that,
and this is the thanks I get?
Why was your cell phone-
-turned off?
I just don't think about
it really.
Did you say you have a
cell phone?
We convinced her she
should borrow one of ours
so we could keep
in touch.
It's part of a special
friends and family plan.
Yeah, we're in each other's
top five.
Top five?!
La-la-la.
Friends and family?
But I'm Haruhi's daddy
and buddy so I'm part
of the plan too, right?
Senpai, whatever planet
you're on, come home.
Speaking of which, why are
you even here? I'm gonna
have to see you guys everyday
when the new term starts.
Don't I have the right to
spend my summer vacation
the way I want to?
According to the handbook,
jobs are prohibited.
I, uh... had no idea.
Hey, Did you hear? Haruhi
went and got herself a job
without the school's
permission.
No way...! That's grounds
for expulsion.
I think Karuizawa is way better
than Switzerland anyway.
And overseas travel is
so exhausting.
Of course, you do have the
right to spend your vacation
as you please.
But then again. Like it or
not, so do we.
And you know, I for one
find Pension Misuzu to be
exceptionally charming.
Nooooooo!
Rise and shine, my
sleepy-headed Senpai.
Haruhi's made a special
breakfast just for you.
Oh. How lovely. Come sit
with me. Stay a while.
No. I can't. I'm an employee
here and you're one of
our honored guests.
It's not allowed.
But who's to find out, if
it's only the two of us?
Stay here with me and silly
rules will no longer matter.
Senpai.
Uh, Senpai? Hello?
I'm so sorry, boys. I'd love
to have all of you as guests,
but I'm afraid there's only
one vacant room left.
Only one room, you say.
Well, that settles it.
I'll have to stay here
to represent the club
Hey! That isn't fair!
Have you no feeling of loyalty?
Of any solidarity, boss?
Togetherness is our
guiding principle.
My own words twisted and
thrown right back in my face.
Here's an idea. We bet
you'll like it.
Why not hold a
little competition?
Call it "the guest
relations odd-jobs contest
at Pension Misuzu."
It's very simple. We all
just lend a hand around
the place for the afternoon.
And whoever makes the best
impression on Misuzu-chi
g ets to sleep in the
vacant guest bedroom
That's Brilliant! I think it's
an absolutely delightful idea!
Yes. The winner of the
contest will be determined
by how refreshing they are.
Remember: refreshing is
the name of the game
in guest-relations!
Refreshing! Refreshing! Yay!
Now. Don't think this is going
to be a walk in the park.
'Cause I'm planning on
working you boys to the bone!
Sounds like a blast.
You may not believe this,
but this is the first time
I've ever held a
hammer in my life.
Just watching you work makes
me feel tired!
You there! No complaining!
Three-point deduction!
Oh the pain. The pain.
And no whining either.
That'll be another three-
You think that's gonna
change our minds?
Welcome!
We- We have reservations made
for a second-floor bedroom.
Yes, of course. Right this
way, ladies.
We've been
expecting you.
Although, we weren't expecting
you to be so young and pretty.
Fine, fine. Not exactly subtle,
but they do get the job done.
So, Five refresher points
for them- Ah-ha, Mori.
The legs on this table
are wobbly.
Would you Be a dear and fix
it out back please?
Sure thing.
Nothing wasted in word or
deed! Five refresher points!
So what's a
refresher point?
Haruhi. What do you think
guests are after when
they come all the way out
to vacation in Karuizawa?
Let's see. The
nice weather?
Oh, it's much more
than that.
They come for what they
can't get in the city
-refreshing air,
refreshing scenery,
and refreshingly
gorgeous young men!
And now, thanks to your friends
and their little contest,
my Pension will earn a
reputation for being the
premiere hot spot for
vacationers in search of
the finest eye candy
Karuizawa can offer!
Okay. Sounds like
you have a plan.
And it's uncanny how
much you remind me
of someone else I know.
Why does it always end
up feeling like I bring
the Host Club with
me wherever I go?
Kyoya-senpai. You're keeping
your distance from all this.
Of course. Winning means I'd
end up staying here alone,
which frankly doesn't appeal
to me. I'll just sit back
and watch things unfold,
then head for the cottage.
The Cottage? You mean,
your family's?
That's right. We all have one
in the area.
Then why make such a fuss
about staying here?
So who's your favorite to
win? There must be someone
you have in mind. Do you Care
to bet?
No thanks. I don't
have clue.
Really? It's easy enough to
tell at a glance.
Honey-senpai's brand of cute
doesn't quite fit Misuzu's
notion of refreshing.
So I'm afraid he's out.
Tamaki comes a little closer to
the ideal, provided he keeps
his mouth shut. But we both
know the likelihood of that.
Ordinarily you'd figure
Hikaru and Kaoru.
Then again, seems we have a
dark horse.
Oh my.
Gorgeous!
That's twenty more
refresher points to Mori!
So then you think he's
the one?
Except that if Honey-senpai
drops out, Mori-senpai is bound
to along with him. His
competing in the game at all
is more or less
conditional to that.
Which means.
Victory will be ours.
Well Maybe not. I couldn't
help but notice that
the only room still available
is a single bed,
so if you did win you
couldn't both stay.
No big deal. We can just
bring another bed over
from the cottage.
Yeah- Or we could even
squeeze into the single.
How sweet. I guess
you guys really are
always together, huh?
Always.
The two of us have been
together since we were born,
so we haven't ever
needed anybody else.
We never bothered making other
friends until a few years ago.
We thought the world
was made up of idiots.
Oh really?
But then.
Well, That was before we knew
you. We'd totally let you
sleep with us.
Thanks, I'll pass.
The contest isn't quite
decided yet.
There are still a
number of ways to make
this game more interesting.
This guy's always got
something up his sleeve.
Does that qualify
as "refreshing?"
Oh yeah? Thinking about
helping the boss, are you?
We're not going to lose.
It's no use.
There. All in a day's work.
Ugh! Your Repairs are
totally un-refreshing.
Three-point deduction.
He used up all of his energy
in trying to be refreshing
that his work suffered for it.
Is he alright in the head?
He's never had an actual
job before, you know.
Hey, cut it out!
That's cold!
We have to chill
the watermelon.
That's how our guests
like it.
So refreshing!
I'll lose to those two idiots
if this keeps up.
Failure is not an option!
Haruhi's respect for me
is on the line!
She... She has to understand
that I'm worthy of
being considered part of her
Top Five!
Grandiose ambitions aside,
I think your approach
to winning is a bit skewed.
Kyoya. Can't you see that
her esteem for me as
a father-figure hangs in
the balance?
If I may offer
some advice.
There is something that only
you can pull off.
That is, if you choose the
right music.
Oh, let's stop
in for some tea.
Alright.
So much for us.
Kaoru?
You're out here alone?
Where's Hikaru?
He went to get some trash
bags for us.
Oh.
Do you still think
you'll win?
I don't know.
Kyoya-senpai's
created a monster.
The boss didn't even know
this place had a piano
before he pointed
it out to him.
Look out!
I am so sorry! Are you
two alright?!
Don't worry,
we're okay.
Right?
Yeah. Thanks, I'm fine.
Kaoru!
You're hurt!
Let me see!
I'm fine. It's only
a little cut.
Hikaru?
Don't scare me like that.
Hey, I'm sorry. Do
you forgive me?
Bravo! Bravo!
One-hundred points for
refreshing brotherly love!
A perfect score!
And the Victory goes to...
the Hitachiin Brothers!
So begins the long, dark
night of my soul.
Congrats, you guys.
Oh, it was
nothing really.
What the-? Hang on a second!
Was all of
that staged?
Well now, who
could say?
I'm okay. I promise.
You should be happy that we
won without having to
resort to the "quarreling
brothers" strategy. Right?
Come on, I said I was sorry.
What do you want me to do?
I didn't mean to kick you out
of bed. It was an accident!
Accident or not, my back
is killing me.
Get us some breakfast please.
I'll have two pieces of
baguette toast with
clarified butter
and garnet seal syrup.
I'll take poached
eggs with bacon,
and a bowl of
whole-grain cereal.
The kind with those little
pieces of dried fruit in it.
Hold on!
We don't even have that stuff
on the menu.
Behave!
Just who in the world do
you think you are?
Acting like members of some
privileged aristocracy
on holiday.
We are aristocracy.
So are you, boss.
You are missing the whole
point of travel. When in Rome,
do as the Romans do that's
what I say. Just look at this!
Karuizawa cuisine
fit for a king!
Cold pasteurized Jersey steaks.
Fresh juice,
Highland vegetables.
Smoked salmon cooked over
cherry wood -
the local pride, I might
add. And last but not least,
freshly baked breads with
homemade jam. Bon appetit!
Since when have you-
-been such a
connoisseur?
Since he started
picking Misuzu's brain.
He's been in the kitchen
all morning long.
We arrange them like so.
Brilliant!
While you two were sleeping the
day away I decided to start
a "refreshing host" workshop.
I even wrote a manual.
You really need a life.
While you are acting as my
apprentice, you may not treat
me as your Senpai. That is the
first rule I have written.
Really?
Hey, wait. Have you got to
rule number five yet?
It says We have to be up by
6 a.m.!
Have Kyoya-senpai and
Honey-senpai read
through the manual yet?
Hey, look, we're sorry, boss.
We didn't mean to stir
up painful memories.
Good morning.
Arai Produce.
Good morning to you.
Working boy, eh?
A High Schooler?
Yes ma'am. I'm helping out at
my Uncle's shop for the summer.
How refreshing! Haruhi,
would you put these
in the refrigerator for me?
Okay.
Haruhi Fujioka?
Hey, Arai.
What do you mean you two
are going out on a date?!
Where would you like to
go first, Hikaru?
All kissing is forbidden! And
no sharing ice cream!
Next time, "Operation Haruhi
and Hikaru's First Date."
The Ouran Host club will
be waiting for you.
We'll see you then.