Haruhi-chan.
Please come out and play.
Sorry, we have
the wrong apartment.
Hey. Hey, wait a second!
Don't act so traumatized
'cause you're seeing me
without my makeup on.
Even trannys get stubble--
--first thing in the
morning, which is more than
I can say for any of you.
You're so funny!
My dear Ranka,
I hope this day finds you
in excellent health.
Ranka, please.
That's my head.
Oh, silly me!
I forgot my manners!
Please forgive my appearance.
It's so wonderful
to see all of you!
Is Haru-chan here?
I'm afraid not. She's out
with the girls today.
They picked her up this
morning, and you know women--
heaven only knows
when they'll be back.
So she's not home?
Well, I guess Haruhi
is entitled to spend time
with her old friends
from middle school
once in a while.
I can't believe
she has friends.
This is why I was
against a surprise visit.
You know, come to think
of it I'm not sure that
I recognized any
of her new friends.
But, then again you
never can tell, can you?
Haruhi always
has made friends easily.
Just imagine it,
my little girl out and about
with students
from Lobelia Academy.
Did you say--?
Lo-
-Be-
-Li-Ah!
Ah!
Lobelia.
St. Lobelia Academy.
High school,
second year Benio Amakusa.
Lobelia.
Second year student
Chizuru Maihara.
Lobelia.
And, first year
Hinako Tsuwabuki.
Lobelia.
Together, we are
St. Lobelia Academy's
illustrious White Lily
League, also know as--
The Zuka Club!
Oh Lady Benibara!
Good morning to you!
Why good morning, my dears.
You look ravishing.
I--
I took it upon myself
to prepare a lunch
for you today,
Lady Benibara.
It's your favorite,
little octopus-shaped
cocktail weenies!
Thank you. Oh the irony.
Why my dear, you're just
as red and adorable
as the octopus.
Could it be you wish for me
to feast on you?
Lady Benibara,
I volunteer to be eaten!
Simmer down, people!
Keep your places in line!
Oh! Pick me! Pick me!
Hey, I said no passing
notes without permission!
Please remain calm, everyone!
Those in front, crouch down.
The rule is to allow--
Your fan-club executives
certainly run a tight ship.
They must be exhausted.
I don't envy them one bit.
Chizuru.
Where's our guest?
In the changing room, of course.
How's that size?
You're gorgeous, Maiden.
I mean, Haruhi.
"The Lobelia Girls'
Academy Strikes Back."
You look absolutely beautiful!
Seeing you in that dress,
I'm convinced your place
is here with us!
Oh my dear.
You and that uniform were
destined for each other.
It's most befitting an
innocent girl like you. Yes.
One still unfamiliar with young
love's first tender kiss.
Oh no!
What if the Zuka Club
entices Haruhi to do
something outrageously
scandalous?
Entices her?
Something scandalous?
Just suppose she's
forced to kiss somebody?
Kiss?
As I recall--
--there was that
dance party where--
Ha! Aren't they a laugh!
What exactly goes on at that
Host Club of yours, Suou?
Why nothing that a loving
father wouldn't approve of!
We must rescue
Haruhi without delay!
Maiden--
Hey, would you wait a minute!
Stop it! Get off!
Now hold on, what is this?
Could someone explain it
to me? 'Cause one moment
I'm on my way to the
supermarket and the next
I'm brought here.
I'll be back in a bit.
Be careful.
Target--
--captured.
Wait! What the--?
Wow. Lobelia.
Good. Bring her in.
Roger.
Hold on, where are we going?
The three of you have
about as much subtlety
as the Host Club does.
How dare you, Maiden! We are
nothing like those idiots!
Oh, forgive my outburst.
It's only natural for you
to be upset. After all--
--in our haste, we whisked
you away this morning
in your nightshirt.
Those weren't pajamas,
you know. That happens to be
the way I usually dress.
Does rudeness just
come with the territory
when you're rich?
All theatrics aside, Maiden.
We have a small favor
to ask of you.
As you may know,
one of our responsibilities
at the Zuka Club is to arrange
the regular performance
of musical numbers
and original plays.
Today is called Pink Carnation
Day, when we celebrate
the birth of the White
Lily League's founder
by putting on the most
glorious production
of the entire year.
We've been rehearsing
non-stop in preparation
for today's performance.
Tragically, the lead actress
in our play was in
a terrible accident and is
currently in the hospital.
But even so, without her,
you know what they say,
"the show must go on."
Which means.
This is your big opportunity
to be a part of the theatre!
I can't.
Not a chance.
I'm sorry.
You would only have to
memorize a handful of lines.
For most of the play
the character you'd be
portraying is silent.
The role is actually
more symbolic than anything.
She just stands
there looking beautiful.
You can manage that,
now can't you? We promise
it'll be the
easiest thing ever.
I'll let myself out.
Forgive me. I will forever
fall short of your legacy.
You must be
so ashamed! Oh Mother!
Benio--
Don't talk like that!
So then your mother--?
Benio's late mother was
a distinguished graduate
of St. Lobelia
Academy, prominent in
the White Lily League.
To this day, it's said
no woman looks lovelier
in men's clothing.
That's right.
To honor her, we celebrate
Pink Carnation Day with the
same flair for pageantry
that made the woman's
name synonomous with
the Zuka Club.
Her whole life, Benio has
dreamed of nothing more
than to follow in
her mother's footsteps.
If today's performance
is cancelled, that dream
will be dashed against
the craggy shores of fate.
That sounds just awful.
If my daughter is held captive
in there, I'm not going to
sit back and do nothing.
But we have to play it cool.
The Zuka Club is ruthless.
Once you've become tangled
in their web of lies,
you could go bankrupt trying
to get yourself out again.
How do you know so much, sir?
Haruhi doesn't really seem
like the type who that would
get involved with their kind.
You're right but neither
did Kotoko. She'd always
seemed like she was
such a strong woman.
Kotoko?
Haruhi's late mother- someone
she's always looked up to
very much and unconsciously
attempts to imitate.
There may be some
connection between her and
the infamous Zuka Club.
I was so blind then. We were
newlyweds and I was in love.
So what're we having for
dinner, my Reason For Living?
Miso soup with mezashi
and rice, sweetheart!
That's excellent! You both
need your calcium!
What's mezashi?
They're dried, salted sardines.
Don't interrupt my flashback!
One day, while cleaning,
I discovered my wife's
dirty little secret.
What?
Her collection
of Zuka Club memorabilia!
What are we going to do?
What if Haruhi wants to join
the Zuka Club so she can be
more like her mother?
Is Haru-chan really
going to go bankrupt?
She's practically broke already!
Oh, don't worry. Our girl's
worth a small fortune in cute.
I know I'm flat as a board.
But if you'll please
just take pity on me.
That's even worse!
Kyoya, order us some
Lobelia uniforms right now!
We're going undercover!
Overruled!
Men who only dress in women's
clothing recreationally
are an insult
to us professionals.
You don't want to insult me,
do you? Do you?
Now listen up! To infiltrate
Lobelia, you'll have to do
exactly as I tell you.
Exactly.
Um, can I get up now?
Oh Marianne, how many
lonely nights have I prayed
that we would
be together again?
And how many times,
have the powers that be
demanded that we remain apart?
That our love is forbidden?
Oh my Lord Frederick.
I'm slain by this fatal
gunshot wound. Alas,
I'm to draw breath no more.
My Lord Frederick.
Marianne. With your arms
holding me close,
all this pain becomes naught.
I am overwhelmed with peace.
Lovely angel. Your gaze is
my paradise and you are
the very image of
my beloved mother.
Dying will be--
This guy sure does talk
a lot for someone who's
supposed to be dying.
I wonder how long
he can hold out.
You'd think there'd be time
to get him to a doctor
or something.
My Lord Frederick.
Can you see her?
What's she doing?
It looks as though she's
playing the heroine of some
sentimental tragedy. But--
My Lord Frederick.
She sounds like a robot.
A boring daikon radish.
Even as her father,
I can't stand this!
Someone please make her stop.
My Lord Frederick.
How many times is she going
to repeat that line?
I think she's about
to start singing!
No! Her grades in music have
always been absolutely awful!
Here in this moment,
I am losing nothing,
Even if you leave me,
I won't be alone.
Because love has taught me,
That this life
is still worth living,
Empty skies
above can't stop me,
Oh I'm sorry, my foot
got tangled up in the cord.
Be careful.
Ah, she's lip-synching.
Lip-synching?
Hey newbies!
If you want to be part
of the Benibara Fan Club,
you have to follow the rules!
Now up on your feet!
To be a full-fledged member
your conduct must be
beyond reproach at all times.
Now, altogether.
With enthusiasm.
Let me her those
fan club mantras!
Lady Beneebara,
please hang in there for
your adoring fans today!
Lady Benibara,
you look magnificent!
Lady Benibara
please hang in there for
your adoring fans today!
Okay, now that we're in,
what's the rest of your plan?
Blend in. If you want to
get close to the Zuka Club,
you've got to prove
you're a diehard fan.
And watch yourself,
these girls get pretty
competitive. Even more
than you could imagine!
Lady Benibara please hang
in there for your adoring--
Right. Let's give it a rest.
Glad to have you, newbies!
What do you like most
about Lady Benibara?
Oh, only everything!
The way she walks and sings
and the way she
looks in coattails.
Why even the shape of her head!
I think so, too!
He's a professional. He's got
blending in with the ladies
down to an art.
I'm just so excited to see
the play! It's supposed to be
a tragedy.
"It's called The Senorita's
Love" Lord Frederick
fakes his own suicide
as revenge against
his father for coming
between he and his lover,
Marianne. But the gun
he uses, supposedly filled
with blanks, is actually
filled with live rounds.
Oh, that's so terrible.
I have my suspicions about the
girl playing Marianne, though.
Whoever she is. If she
ruins Lady Benibara's play,
our very own Maiden Warriors
will be waiting
patiently in the wings to
"critique" her performance.
If Haruhi has to put on
a performance in front
of these psychos,
she'll be done for!
They'll beat the
daylights out of her!
Haruhi!
Don't you worry.
We're going to get her
out of that place.
And yet--
--even as we speak--
--the curtain's rising
is nearly upon us.
So you've wormed
your way in after all.
You vulgar,
incompetant host club.
My dears, it's almost time.
Now I'm counting on you.
Remember I want us to think
of today as our audition
for "The Crimson Goddess".
Hold on. Where'd
Kyoya run off to?
Now that you mention it,
I haven't seen him in a while.
Hey look! He's up there!
It is such an honor
having one of the Otori boys
dropping by to
pay us a visit.
That jackass.
He moves quickly.
Very nice setup.
And that's the
orchestra pit, I take it?
That's right.
And just above that we have our
fully equipped
digital backdrop. Here,
let me show you.
We can project any
high-resolution image
and use it as part of the
scenery without unnecessary
set changes. Isn't
technology just amazing?
Yes.
At this point, we'll just have
to rescue Haruhi mid-show.
Here's her entrance.
I, I can see the sky,
The sun and mountains high,
Heavy!
Your makeup's too heavy, Haruhi!
I can't bear to
see her like this.
Enough! I'm getting
her out of here right--
Wait a minute.
Just look at her up there.
She's so much more radiant
than she was in rehearsal.
Well, her cheeks are rosier.
That'd be the makeup.
And her skin looks
like it's glowing!
That'd be the lights.
You're right. We can't
interfere in the middle
of her performance.
She's having the time
of her life.
Let her have her moment.
We can sneak her
out of here afterwards.
Oh my Lord Frederick!
I am slain by this
fatal gunshot wound. Alas,
I'm to draw breath no more.
My Lord Frederick!
Marianne. With your
arms holding me close,
all this pain becomes naught.
My soul is--
The kiss scene is coming up!
But the scene falls just short
of their embrace, right?
Of course. Lady Benibara
would never actually
kiss her.
Kiss scene?
In "The Senorita's Love"
Lord Frederick fakes suicide
to take revenge against
his father for coming
between he and
his lover, Marianne.
Kiss scene? Revenge?
Ah, and yet--
The love I bear for you, and
the desire I have for revenge--
-- are not things which can
so simply be forgotten.
Senpai? And Dad?
Right before his eyes,
I'll steal your first kiss.
All for the sake of revenge.
No Lady Benibara!
You can't really kiss her!
Never in a million years,
will Daddy allow his Haruhi,
to be used in such
a despicable way!
Banana?
Victory is mine.
You poor incompetent
buffoon. Now behold
while we embrace!
Haruhi!
My love.
You're crazy lady.
Yes. Please forward that
photo to me immediately.
Stop it! Get off me!
Oh no!
That picture is--
--from the dance party!
So, as you see--
--see Haruhi's already
had her first kiss.
Haruhi!
So is that what goes on in
that degenerate Host Club!
Hearing that from
her transvestite father--
--seems kind of ironic.
You're going to explain
this photograph to me
right this instant young lady!
Maiden. You mean to tell me!
Haruhi!
Jump down!
I'll catch you!
No!
Haruhi!
I'm sorry, Senpai.
Haruhi! How could you do this
to your adoring father?
Not so fast Marianne.
Must protect my Haruhi.
Don't let her go!
This is not over yet!
I don't care how
many kisses she's had!
The next one will be mine!
And all I wanted to do
today was go shopping.
So, why did Hikaru and
Kaoru joing the Host Club?
Because I, the Host Club
King, personally scouted
them out.
Don't get an ego or anything.
Next time, "The Door
the Twins Opened."
The Ouran Host Club
will be waiting for you.
We'll see you then.