This can't be right.
Hey everyone.
Why don't you come in?
I know it's not much, but
please, make yourself at home.
I'll make us some tea.
Um. I'm sorry; we don't
have enough cups but
we do have some bowls.
Here ya go.
Hey boss. What's with
this place? She lives here?!
Maybe it's some kind of set.
You know, like in the movies?
I-I-I-I-I-I hope so.
Calm down you guys. I bet
this is the storeroom.
I'm positive infinite cosmos
is just on the other side
of that closet.
Then should we try to open it?
Now's not the time.
Right.
Since you guys decided
to come by at lunch time my dad
said it would be rude
if I didn't offer you something
to eat. We've been fasting
for 3 days to save up money
to buy something suited
to your taste but it's all
worth it as long
as you guys like it.
Ta-da! A sushi sampler!
It was marked down at the
supermarket! How about that?
Sorry we came to visit
Haru-chan don't make us eat it!
Be strong men, Haruhi
has suffered for our benefit
so it's the least we can do.
But sir, I'm not even
sure this is fish.
Wow!
I can't believe it isn't this
is a piece of fancy tuna?
I've never tasted it til now.
It's delicious!
What?! No Haruhi,
that's just regular old tuna!
It's by no means fancy!
Just a dream.
Morning, Master Tamaki.
Anything we can do for you?
I need to get going.
Please bring the car
around front at once.
Yes, of course, sir.
I beg your pardon, Master
Tamaki, but what would you
like for breakfast this morning?
I don't want any! I already
told you I have to get going!
I can't shake that nightmare
I had this morning.
I respect the privacy of
our club members so I've
never intruded into
their personal lives but-
What if Haruhi really
is living in poverty?!
What if that hovel is
her home?! I have to go see
Haruhi and try to get
the truth out of her.
I've got to get to school.
Hold it right there,
Master Tamaki!
I can't let you leave
the house like that.
You're still wearing
your pajama bottoms and
your house slippers.
Well, he's not the
brightest young man.
Thank you, Shima.
I'll be going now.
I hate to be a bother, Master
Tamaki, but today is Sunday.
Which means you don't have
to go to school today, sir.
Oh, really? Well why
didn't you make me aware
of that fact earlier?
As your maid it's my duty
to help you, however,
I want you to become
a fine gentleman.
So you must be able to
recognize your own mistakes.
Since you suddenly have some
free time on your hands,
why don't we work
on your manners?
But I have to make a call!
Someone bring the phone!
Sure!
Hey Kyoya, there's something
I need to talk to you about.
"A Day in the Life
of the Fujioka Family"
That was some sale!
There's no better time
to hit the supermarket
than a Sunday morning.
Now all I've gotta do when
I get home is clean and
do some laundry.
What's going on? Why're they
in front of our apartments?
Check out that car...
Here you are, Master.
Wow, so this
is where Haruhi lives?
It's pretty big, huh?
Bigger than I thought it'd be.
Yeah! Look at all the rooms!
This building is what you might
call an aggregate commoner
dwelling. Haruhi's home
is just one of many units
in this building.
Kyoya! Why?! Why'd you
bring these idiots with us?!
Especially those
two doppelgangers!
Well you see. I knew you
didn't have the courage
to come here alone
so I thought it'd be best
if everyone came along.
Alright, let's go home.
I guess I underestimated
our great leader.
What?! I'm not going home!!
I'm sorry. Don't leave.
I don't want to be alone.
Is this for some kinda
movie shoot or something?
Rich people! Rich people!
Now listen up, men.
Don't you forget!
We must be polite. This is
a casual "we just happened
to be in the neighborhood"
kind of visit.
We're not here to judge the
Fujioka family's lifestyle.
The words "shabby,"
"cramped," and "run-down"
are absolutely forbidden!
Right! Yes, sir!
Don't say anything that might
offend Haruhi or her father
and cause them
to ask us to leave.
Well it's too late
for that- go away!
Haruhi!
That pink dress is pretty cute!
Shut up! Get
the hell outta here!
Haruhi's so mad
she actually cursed at us!
--All of this is your fault!
--Hey, It wasn't us.
Excuse me, Haruhi,
but is everything alright?
Oh hi, Miss Landlady.
Those young men are driving
such fancy foreign cars
they're not Yakuza, are they?
No, they're not.
Do you want me
to call the police for you?
Pleased to meet you, madam.
My name's Suou I'm one
of Haruhi's friends.
Really? My goodness, well
aren't you just adorable?
And he's got her.
We're just stopping by; we
didn't mean to cause a scene.
I'm sorry.
Oh, it's no problem.
I'll stop by later with some
snacks for you and your friends.
See you later!
Okay, here's the deal,
I'm only giving you guys
a quick peak. 3 seconds.
Then you all go home, got it?
Look, I brought you
a gift Haru-chan.
I know how you love cake;
there's both chocolate
and strawberry! I think
we should have some!
Fine, guess I'll make some tea.
At least it's
better than my dream.
What a hovel.
Shut up!
A wood-built 2 bedroom unit.
That's normal for
a commoner family of 2.
Haruhi's such a pipsqueak,
At least we know she won't
hit her head on
the low ceilings.
Well, I think it's
a super cute, little room!
You don't have to struggle
to compliment it.
Hold on, are we supposed
to take off our shoes, too?
Please, if you don't mind.
Did you hear that? We have
to take our shoes off!
It's kinda like going
to the dojo, huh?
Yeah.
Do you have any slippers
for us, Haruhi?
Wait, the room's covered
with tatami mats.
In that case,
we don't need slippers.
Great; thanks
for inviting us in!
Yeah, thanks.
It's greatly appreciated.
Yes, thanks Haruhi.
Whoa! Talk about small!
Ow.
Be careful. That light bulb's
just hanging from the ceiling.
This place is quite
unpleasant but I think I may
have underestimated
commoner housing.
I know it's a tight fit
in here men but just
pull your knees in
and sit gym-style.
Commoners have specially
developed this position
to conserve space.
I just gotta get
through this visit.
I should've expected
this from them.
I'm gonna go
make us some tea.
Hey. Here's an idea.
Why don't you make us this?
It's black tea that
our father brought us
as a souvenir from
Africa. Here.Try it.
Um, sure, no problem.
It's best served as
a milk tea. Do you have milk?
I think.When was the last time
that I bought some milk?
Stop it! What the
hell are you doing?!
Don't be so mean
to her, you idiots!
What do you mean?
I know you're trying
to embarrass her by asking for
that African tea.
Look! She has no idea how
she's supposed to prepare it!
She doesn't even
have a teapot!
And she's too embarrassed
to tell us that she doesn't!
I'm sorry, Haruhi. You don't
have to go to all that trouble.
We don't need any tea,
We'd be fine with
a glass of water.
What? It's no trouble,
besides. I've already made it.
Oh, well then in that case.
Man, that was
a close one, boss.
We have been rescued
by commoners' wisdom.
What do you mean, sir?
Nothing we know to be true in
our world holds true here.
We have to be
careful how we react.
One little offhanded
remark could
break Haruhi's heart.
That means, in this fight.
The first person
to embarrass Haruhi loses.
While your antics are amusing
I don't understand why
you feel the need
to turn this into a contest.
Okay guys, the tea's ready.
I'm sorry that not
all of the cups match.
At least she's not using chipped
bowls and measuring cups.
Come on, Haru-chan!
You can choose your cake first.
You sure Honey-senpai?
Go ahead. We're rich- we eat
this kinda stuff all the time.
Well in that case.
I was trying to
be considerate!
I'll have the strawberry.
She's so cute!
Okay Haru-chan...
I wish I could tell her how cute
she is but there's no telling
what might offend her.
The traps of the commoner's
world are terrifying!
You like strawberries,
right? You can have mine.
Thanks! That's nice
of you, Mori-senpai.
Why didn't we think of that?!
I should've been sharing
strawberries with her!
Why'd we let him trick us?!
Eating all that cake
sure wet my appetite.
Yeah, isn't it
lunchtime about now?
Well then,
what's for lunch?
Would you guys quit being so
happy-go-lucky all the time,
please?
We'll take care of it.
We did drop in unexpectedly.
So we'll pay for lunch,
why don't you just order
all of us some of
your favorite sushi.
Thanks but no thanks.
I know that if I let
you guys pay I'll
only regret it later.
Oh, don't worry, Haruhi.
We'll just pay for it
using the profits
from the photos of you
we auctioned off.
So I'm really paying
for it after all.
Well, if that's what you want,
I do have a friend who runs
a nice little sushi shop
nearby so I can just give him
a call. Their stuff's
pretty high quality.
"Be careful, Haruhi. Just
because the sushi's packaging
says 'premium' doesn't mean
that it's high quality."
I'm not stupid. I could
figure that out on my own.
How could you do that?!
Daddy even attempted to look
casual and not embarrass you!
I'd really love it if you'd
make us something for lunch,
Haru-chan!
No, Honey-senpai!
How could you ask that of her?!
Don't upset her!
Try to restrain yourself!
I guess I could whip
something up but
it's gonna take me some time.
We can wait!
Why didn't we think
of asking her that?!!
This means that we'll get
to eat Haruhi's cooking!
I'm gonna have to go
to the supermarket again.
We're coming with you!
We want to see
a commoner's supermarket!
Me, too! Me, too!
This could be
a learning experience.
Yay! Commoners' supermarket!
Commoners' supermarket!
This is gonna be fun!
Well, that's it. So much
for having the day off today.
Hey, senpai?
Aren't you coming with us?
I am I just wanted to pay
my respects to your mother
before we left.
Thank you.
You don't have to do that.
Looks like you
take after your mom.
I guess. That's what
my dad always tells me.
She was a beautiful woman and I
bet she was a smart one as well.
I'm not really
a good judge of beauty.
But she was smart.
She was a lawyer.
Oh yeah? No doubt
she was a great lawyer!
I can tell. Trust me, you
can't fool my eyes, Haruhi.
I don't know if
I trust your eyes, Senpai.
But my mom.
Well, Haruhi, your mom's gonna
go out there and do her best.
Watch, we're gonna
win this one!
She was a great lawyer.
Everyone's outside
waiting for us,
we should probably get
going, don't you think?
That hurt.
Are you okay, Haruhi?!
I'm fine, but you
are kinda heavy.
I'm home, Haruhi! Hey,
why'd you leave the door open?
Welcome home, Dad.
At that moment
her father came home.
From his shift
at the tranny bar.
He saw his
daughter pinned down.
Or so it appeared.
Forcefully being held.
By some strange boy.
"Dad"? You gotta be
kidding! This transvestite
is Haruhi's father?
So Dad, how was work?
Just stay calm.
It was an accident.
I'm sure he'll understand
if I explain what happened.
I'm sorry.
I hated having to
leave you alone last night.
You must have been lonely.
That sound.
He really hit hard.
Oh, dear, my left arm
has been bothering me lately.
It's so sore- like I went
hand-to-hand with some
ferocious beast. Maybe I've
just been working too hard.
Please, sir. It's not
what it looked like.
Hot tea?! I'll get it for you!
Do you use firewood
to boil it, Haruhi?
Help me out-
your dad wants tea!
Oh my. Would you look
at that, I seem
to have come across
a little pest.
Would you like to tell me
why you're addressing
my daughter with such
informality, young man?
Hey boss, what in the world
is taking you so long?
Whoa, check it out, that
person we passed downstairs
is Haruhi's father!
Hikaru! Kaoru!
Help me out here!
It's nice to meet you,
Haruhi's dad. We're good friends
of your daughter's,
the Hitachin Brothers.
So you're a transvestite,
aren't you?
You're the first real
transvestite we've ever seen!
You finally put the moves
on Haruhi, huh boss?
Sorry about him. He's a ladies'
man if you know what I mean.
He's a pheromone machine. In
fact, I bet he's fooled around
with more ladies
than you can count!
He likes to fool around, huh?
No! I'm not a ladies man! I'm
a nice guy! I care about her!
Is he confessing his love?
I'm being
completely honest here.
I care about Haruhi
like she's my own daughter.
I get it. You must be the Host
Club I've heard so much about.
You certainly are a fine
looking bunch of young men.
I'm not sure which
of you I like best.
What about you, dear?
I tell you what,
why don't you boys
go ahead and call me Ranka?
That's the professional name
I use at the transvestite bar
I work at.
Professional name?
You mean, like a stage name?
Exactly like that, Mitsukuni.
Hold on! How did
you know my name, sir?
You two are 3rd years
Mitsukuni Haninozuka
and Takashi Morinozuka.
And the two of you are first
years in the same class
as Haruhi.
You're the Hitachin twins, but
I'm not sure which one of you
is which! I've heard
a lot about you!
What? So Haruhi's
told you about us?
No. Kyoya told me about
you two over the phone.
You know, you're really are
a beautiful person, Ranka.
Say what?!
Kyoya.
We've been entrusted with the
care of his precious daughter,
it is only natural
that we introduce ourselves
and give him periodic reports.
Ordinarily, that would be
your job, wouldn't it?
I'm impressed the Club
has such a capable president.
But wait a minute,
you're only the vice-president
aren't you Kyoya? I guess
that president of yours
is pretty much good
for nothing, huh?
You never mentioned
this to me, Dad!
Why didn't you say
that you've been
getting calls
from Kyoya-senpai?!
What am I supposed
to do Haruhi?
You rarely tell me
anything about school.
So that makes it okay
to talk behind my back?
C'mon senpai would you please
stop growing mushrooms
in other people's closets?!
Haruhi, the thing
about you is--
You're cute
even when you're angry!
I don't know what it is
about him but Haruhi's dad
reminds me of someone.
This explains why she's
so good at handling the boss.
Wait, Haruhi,
where are you going?
The supermarket, alright?
I have to go shopping
and I wanna do it by myself.
So all of you just stay here
and try to behave yourselves,
Wait! We want to go to the
commoner's supermarket!
I wouldn't push it.
Once she's made her mind up
she'll never change it!
When she decided she wanted
to go to Ouran Academy
she did all of the enrollment
paperwork by herself.
While I respect her independent
spirit I wish she'd
be a little more dependent
on me sometimes.
Haruhi!
So Why didn't you
tell me that today was
"bring your parents
to school" day?
Sorry Dad, but I didn't tell you
because I didn't want you to go!
What? She's not goin'
through a rebellious phase.
Listen, I hate to be the one
to break it to you buddy,
but I have a feeling
she didn't invite you to school
with her cause she's embarrassed
her daddy's a tranny.
So I like to wear women's
clothing! What's it matter?!
I'll never love anyone
the way I loved Kotoko
and she never had a problem
with it! So lay off, would ya?!
Hey, Haruhi!
I brought your dad home!
He's drunk himself
stupid again!
Hello my darling! I'm home!
You smell like a bar.
He's pretty upset
about not getting to go
to "bring your parents
to school" day today.
You should invite him next time.
I can't.
I didn't invite you
'cause you work so hard
I thought you could
use the time off.
I know that you're
pretty tired, Dad.
So I thought you should use
your day off to catch up
on your sleep.
I want you to take
better care of yourself.
I hope you boys know
how grateful I am.
Since she's found,
you she seems to be happier,
she's enjoying herself.
Wouldn't you agree,
Tamaki Suou?
You know who I am?!
Well of course I do,
Haruhi's told me a thing or two
about you. You're the Host
Club's bumbling president,
right?
So, she talks about the Host
Club at home, after all.
Come to think of it you're
the one who didn't realize
Haruhi was a girl until
the very last moment.
You're clueless, aren't you?
Pretty pathetic.
Now that we've gotten all the
introductions out of the way.
How would you boys like
to have a little fun?
Why didn't he tell me?
I had no idea that
Kyoya-senpai's been calling
my dad and giving him updates.
So we're going to follow
her to the supermarket?
This is what
you meant by "fun"?
Yes! I call it
the stalking game.
What an attractive group
of young men!
In all honesty.
I have a completely selfish
reason for bringing you
out with me. I want to be seen
with a bunch of cute boys!
Sure enough. Those two
are definitely cut
from the same cloth.
Do you really think it's
necessary to follow her
around like this? Are you
that worried about her?
As you know, Haruhi lost
her mother at a young age
and afterwards she took on
all of the household chores
and shopping by herself.
I decided to start following
her whenever she would
leave the house. Maybe I'm
just being overprotective.
I worry about her all the time.
I'm the only one who
can protect her, you know.
Hold on.
Hey, what're you
doing here, Dad?
Oh, it looks like
you caught me Haruhi!
I followed you here
so that I could carry
your shopping basket! You know
how daddy loves accessories!
Now why don't you
just hand it over?
You're so weird.
Either she doesn't know
how to depend on others
or she refuses to. She's
always been so independent
and so strong.
And she has this uncanny
ability to affect others
without even realizing it.
That's true. I've seen it.
I understand.
What do you mean,
"I understand"?
Don't think you're
gonna win me over
just because you're
handsome. I'm warning you
I'm not ready to let go yet!
You could at least
let go of my face!
You've got some nerve!
You barely even know Haruhi!
That means-
From this day forward,
you're my enemy!
What the? Hey, what're
you doing here, senpai?
Oh, it looks like
you caught me, Haruhi!
I followed you here
so that I could carry
your shopping basket!
You know how daddy
loves accessories! Now why
don't you just hand it over?
You're so weird.
What's with the mushrooms?
Weee! Faster, Takashi!
So, does double-coupons
mean I need two of them?
Ah, there's a whole stack
of commoners' coffee.
Was there anything particular
you wanted to eat?
How 'bout a stewpot?
One with lots of meat in
it and no chrysanthemum.
Yeah, That's a great idea.
A stewpot would be good
since we need to feed
a lot of people. It's
kinda warm for it, though.
I know it's going
to happen eventually.
One day my precious little girl
will be all grown up.
And she'll want to have that
special someone by her side.
Just thinking about
it gets my blood boiling!
Here Tamaki,
chrysanthemum, your favorite.
What's going on here?
We didn't know you had
a younger sister, boss!
As of today I will be
your big brother!
You know, you really
should think before you make
promises like that. Next time,
"Big Brother is a Prince".
The Ouran Host Club
will be waiting for you!
We'll see you then!