Now you've done it!
It's done, all right.
But it wasn't our fault.
What?! You idiots! You're the
ones who bumped into it, right?
Only because Haruhi
was running away.
We were trying to catch her
cause we wanted have some fun
and dress her up in cosplay.
So what- we cosplay
all the time!
We weren't going with
the usual Host Club costumes.
We want to see in bunny
cosplay disguised as a girl.
Disguised as a girl?
You'd like to see it too,
wouldn't you?
I'd definitely want to see
that-What am I thinking?!
There's no time
for stuff like that right now!
I know what you're up to.
You're trying to distract me
from the mess you've made!
Get away from
Haruhi, you punks!
No way!
Let me go!
Excuse me. We don't have
any guests at the moment
so I don't mind if you make
a racket but please.
Be careful. You don't want
to wake Honey-senpai.
He's a 3rd year who
still takes afternoon naps?
Well, we're gonna have
to tell him about the bunny
at some point. Let's just
wake him up and apologize.
No, wait! Don't get any
closer to Honey-senpai!
Come back.
It's safe over here!
What're you talking about?
Honey-senpai wakes up in
a very bad mood after napping.
This may be just a rumor,
but the HAHneenozuka family
once visited a U.S. military
base to give combat training.
Supposedly, Honey-senpai
slept through most of it
because of his jet-lag.
Hey, master,
are you doin' okay?
Then a soldier came in and
carelessly tried to wake him up
since he had been
sleeping for so long.
I'm still sleepy.
Oh dear god!
On that day, he wiped out two
entire platoons of soldiers,
and not just any
soldiers-green berets!
And I've heard we've
had diplomatic issues with
America ever since that day.
How terrifying.
And we've got a bigger problem.
Usa-chan was hand-made
for Honey-senpai
by his deceased grandmother.
You've seen the way he carries
it around, that little bunny
is his most prized possession.
I can't imagine how
he's going to react
when he wakes up and sees
that his precious
Usa-chan is ruined!
He's gonna do to us what
he did to those green berets!
You're exaggerating.
It's imposible for that story
to be true, I mean, come on.
It is, and there's other
evidence that Honey-senpai has
an evil side to him.
Listen to this.
His blood type is AB-
how do you like that?!
Yeah, so what?
But Haruhi, that means he's
the same blood type as Kyoya!
What's the matter? Do you
guys have a problem with
my blood type?
Oh, those of you
watching with type AB,
please don't take
any offense to this.
Man. This is bad. We have
to do something quick before
he wakes up. Hikaru, Kaoru.
Sir!
Go get your folks' Cessna.
Fly to Osorezan and bring back
a medium. We'll channel his
grandmother and she can
guide us through it.
We can make a new Usa-chan
for Honey-senpai!
Take this map of the
Aomori Prefecture with you.
And don't forget to bring back
apple juice, apple jam
and Nebuta souvenir dolls!
But we don't
have that much time.
We're used to your crazy ideas,
but you should come up
with something more practical.
Alright, how about this, we'll
send Usa-chan to the cleaners.
Haruhi!
You're going to have
to wear the bunny suit.
Yeah, good idea, boss!
Forget about it!
I'm not wearing
that stupid bunny suit!
It's not gonna work!
He'll know it's me!
No he won't. He won't
be able to tell the difference
if he's just
waking up from a nap!
Well then why don't
you wear it, Senpai?!
It won't be as cute
if I wear it! C'mon this
is the least you can do.
Since we can't get
another bunny you're gonna have
to step in. Besides, if the
twins hadn't been chasing
you none of this
would've happened!
He's awake! We'll have to use a
substitute! We've got no choice!
No! Not my teddy-bear!
He's gonna come after us next!
He just spotted
his bunny rabbit!
Who's responsible for this?
Who got Usa-chan dirty?
Someone help! Mori-senpai!
Don't let him hurt us!
He wanted tea, so Usa-chan
decided to have a drink.
I see. So that's why his face
is all dirty, isn't it?
Hey. Do you think
he wants some cake, too?
"Honey Senpai's
Three Bitter Days"
Honey, how do you like
to have chocolate?
Mousse? Bonbons? Wait,
I bet chocolate cake
is your favorite, huh?
Um. let's see. Well. I like 'em
all! I love anything chocolate,
Usa-chan and all of you ladies!
He's so cute!
Mitskuni Haninozuka,
otherwise known as Honey-senpai,
age 17. Ouran Academy
3rd-Year, Class A and
member of the Host Club.
Favorite things include cake,
chocolate, and bunnies.
He's famous for his enchanting
boy Lolita characteristics.
That was a close call
earlier, huh senpai?
No kidding! I'm glad
we settled that Usa-chan issue
without any violence.
Honey-senpai's catch phrases
include, "I love candy"
and "I love cute things". And
while some find this charming,
I'm not quite sold on
his cutesy loli boy image-
it's not exciting enough!
It feels like something's
missing in his character arc!
Honey-senpai. You can't keep
eating nothing but sweets
all of the time,
you know, you're gonna end up
with a cavity.
Oh, don't worry.
I always brush my teeth.
Honey-senpai, is it?
Nah, it's nothing, 'kay?
Lemme just take
a look in your mouth.
Hold still.
Honey-senpai,
please quit squirming.
There's nothing wrong! Quit
messing with me! Leave me alone!
Yes! That's it! That's it!
That's what was missing!
It's moe!
So is it a cavity?
Yeah.
Oowie! Ouchie! Oowie!
Ouchie! Oowie! Ouchie!
It's all right. I'll be okay.
Tamaki.
Yes, you're right.
I'll take care of this.
Until Honey-senpai
gets over his cavity,
I'm afraid he can't
have sweets.
Therefore, we'll be supportive,
and ask that you kindly
refrain from eating snacks
in the club room until
this ordeal is over.
No, no, don't, Takashi. Please
don't take my snacks away.
You can't. Don't do it.
What'll I do without them?!
I can handle it!
Please don't take away my cake!
No more cake.
And that's how it all began.
One little cavity and
suddenly Honey-senpai's
life became a living hell.
Poor Honey-senpai looks
so miserable. It's a shame
the Host Club banned snacks.
It must be really
difficult for him.
I hope this doesn't
seem insensitive.
I know he's in pain but-
He's so cute!
Mitsukuni, bag.
I can carry it.
Yes, you can. Hand it over.
I was just looking.
I wasn't gonna eat them.
Really? If you're
just looking, then try this.
I'll keep the real stuff.
Aw man, that was rough.
I can't help but
feel sorry for him.
You know, I had no idea that
Mori-senpai could be so brutal.
You wouldn't expect it. I
thought his principles kept him
from doing anything
to upset Honey-senpai.
And to think that he could get
the boss to go along with him.
It's too bad, Tamaki.
I wanted to give you some of
the chocolates specially-made
by our new pâtissier.
My family just hired him
from France, but I can't
share them with you because
you're not eating sweets.
Do not fret my princess.
For the present I must abstain
for poor Honey-senpai's sake,
but eventually we'll
be able to share
chocolate together again.
The friendship you boys have
is absolutely beautiful.
I believe things will work
out for the better this way,
my dear.
I'm sure it's delicious
but no chocolate could ever
be able to withstand
the heat wave of my love.
So it would all
melt and go to waste.
Oh, Tamaki.
Impressive, boss.
That was quite an act.
Missing sweets, aren't you?
Buzz off.
The club's number one priority
is our guests. All that matters
is their happiness.
You had better watch yourselves
out there. Don't give any
sweets to Honey-senpai
no matter what tricks
he resorts to.
Oh, and incidentally those
instructions come from
Mori-senpai.
This isn't my doing.
So is it just me, or does
he seem to be enjoying this?
I just can't hide it any longer.
I have to get this off my chest.
I need to know what your
feelings are towards me
and if you'll accept my love.
Will you, please? Unless of
course there's someone else.
Please tell me. Is there
someone else who's dear to you?
There is, isn't there? Huh?
I should've known.
Look, Takashi!
My cavity's all better now!
You sure?
The swelling
has even gone down!
Has it?
So do you think I can have a
piece of cake? Just one? Please?
You're not fully recovered yet.
What are you ladies drinking?
Um. Darjeeling tea,
it's really good.
Yeah? What are you
gonna have to eat?
Well, I was going
to have a sandwich.
Know what you need? Some
sweets! That tea would go well
with something sweet!
Like maybe some cake! C'mon!
What d'you say?
Well. It would be
good with cake.
It sure would.
We're so sorry, Honey!
But it's for your own good!
Wait!
Honey-senpai.
Haru-chan, am I a bad person?
I just don't understand why
God hates me. What have I done?
Okay, fine,
but only this once, got it?
Is it a snack?
Yeah.
Here.
It's the same color
as chocolate. Try it.
He's gonna crack.
Would somebody please talk
to him. He's scaring me.
He's headed for the candy!
No need to worry.
We emptied out all the sweets.
Kyoya-senpai, you seem
really chipper today.
He keeps doing that
to my teddy-bear!
Well, there he goes.
Three days and he gives up.
Um, Honey-senpai?
Somebody help me!
He's eating my arm off!
Mitsukuni, don't take
this out on other people.
You saved me.
I thought I was a goner.
It's disgraceful.
Takashi.
You idiot!
A little bit isn't gonna
hurt me! You're so mean!
You're such a hardhead!
That's it, I hate you!
I hate you Takashi!
Honey-senpai!
Hey, Mori-senpai.
That was harsh.
Will you be alright?
I hate you, Takashi!
Wow, senpai, it looks
like he really got to you.
I don't know what's going on,
but it seems like
you're self-destructing.
Maybe Honey-senpai wouldn't
hate you if you hadn't been
so hard on him
in the first place.
It was on purpose.
Mori-senpai, by any chance,
have you been acting like this
because you're trying to get
Honey-senpai to hate you?
Why would he do that?
It makes no sense.
That would be like the end
of the world for Mori-senpai.
Why would he do it on purpose?
Well maybe because he was
trying to punish himself.
I'm right, aren't I?
Yeah, you are;
this was my fault.
Mitsukuni has a cavity
because I'm careless.
Twice before his naptime
I forgot to make him
brush his teeth.
But that's not really
your responsibility.
He should know better.
But if Mitsukuni has to get
false teeth, it'll be my fault.
Don't worry.
That's not gonna happen.
Wow, what a pessimist.
I wouldn't be able to live
with myself right now
if he hadn't thrown me down.
Because he felt at fault,
Mori-senpai wanted some sort
of punishment from
Honey-senpai to make up
for his failure.
Well, while that certainly makes
for a nice story and everything.
It was just
a little cavity, right?
Well, there you have it,
Honey-senpai.
What will you do now?
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry, Takashi!
I promise! I won't forget
to brush my teeth again!
I won't forget!
A few days later,
Honey-senpai recovered
from his painful cavity,
so the Host Club decided
to lift their ban on sweets,
and Honey-senpai could greedily
stuff his face once more.
What's with Kyoya-senpai?
He looks depressed
about something.
Cause Honey-senpai's back
to eating snacks again.
All those sweets get expensive.
Excuse me.
Oh my, looks like we have
a new guest, gentlemen.
Are you a fan of Mori-senpai?
It's that girl.
Well, Mori, I understand now.
I know who you feel so
strongly about, and it's okay.
I must say I find it a little
surprising that it's Honey.
To think he's so special
to you, I don't know.
It's just so. I can't
explain it- it's so-
Congratulations. You've just
taken your first big step
into a brand new world.
Mitsukuni, you've made a mess.
That's right ladies,
it's moe! It's the greatest!
I just can't get enough of it!
You know, even though this
whole thing may look and feel
just like a happy ending, I'm
not sure everyone out there
would think moe is a good way
to wrap things up.
Moe!
Oh, good grief.
Tamaki-senpai, why are you
wearing a silk hat?
And Kyoya-senpai, why are you
on top of a mushroom?
You're not doing a very
good job of keeping up
with the story line.
Next time,
"Haruhi in Wonderland"!
The Ouran Host Club
will be waiting for you!
We'll see you then!