Young Lord, we wish
you good morning.
Young Lord,
please return to us safely.
Please return to us safely.
Young Lord,
have a good day at work today.
Have a good day at work today.
How many times have I told ya?
I'm not goin' to work
I'm goin' to school,
you idiots!
Sorry, we got it mixed up again!
Young Lord, what about your car?
Forget about it. I'm gonna
walk to school today.
Tetsya. You gotta be more
careful about how you
speak to the
Young Lord, alright?
Especially 'cause
his glaring power's got
even more scary!
What do you wanna bet it's
cause he's got a beef with
some stupid kid at school?
Today's the day.
Takashi Morinozuka.
Welcome to the Host Club.
Tamaki, you're dressed
as Riyoma Sakamoto, right?
He's so wild and handsome!
Yeah, I'm handsome,
I'm wild, and I'm gonna
steal your hearts,
pretty ladies.
We love it when you talk
like a samurai, Tamaki!
Why's he speaking
in the Tosa dialect?
You know I never would've
thought that late Edo era
cosplay would be this popular.
C'mon you can't be serious.
That's like one of the basics.
There are plenty of girls
that find the late Edo era
totally fascinating.
Particularly the Shinsengumi.
And most of the girls who
like it are complete maniacs
about it!
Are they popular because
of the noble nature in which
they sacrificed their
young lives for their country?
Or could it be because
of their stoic determination?
Their choice to live out
their lives by the Bushido code?
Or could it be.
Don't die.
I'm done for, brother.
Let me go.
That we're intrigued because
the worship of this group
of renegade young men
is somewhat forbidden.
The Ikedaya Inn may be
well-known but it's only
because of Hijikata.
Just imagining him after
the battle at Tobafushimi;
his back to the north,
as he sorrowfully
wandered the streets of
his homeland attempting
to defend the honor of
the Shinsengumi all by himself.
I could eat three
giant bowls of rice!
That was one hell of
a history lesson, Renge.
Not having us cast ourselves in
specific roles was good advice.
Allowing the guests
to just be free to fantasize
on their own was truly
a brilliant idea, Renge.
I'm very impressed.
I told you it would work.
But you know,
I think dressing Haruhi
as Soji Okita was perfect.
He's wonderful as the handsome,
evanescent young swordsman!
Haruhi! Please don't die!
I couldn't handle it!
They're having a sale on pork
at the supermarket today.
I hope I can make it.
So Mori has to be Kai Shimada,
don't you think?
No way. He's totally Yamazaki.
I think it'd be super cool
if he was Soma!
Mori-senpai!
Why the sudden lunge?
You not getting
enough attention?
Please calm down, Mori-senpai!
I know you're upset that you
only have one line an episode.
We're &gt; through the
season and you haven't
had your own episode,
is that it? I'm sorry!
No.
We have a trespasser.
Takashi Morinozuka!
A surprise attack?
Senpai! Please take me on
as your apprentice!
"Mori-senpai Has an
Apprentice Candidate!"
Ritsu Kahsanoda,
1st year, Class D.
Heir to the 3rd-generation head
of the Kasanoda Syndicate,
the most powerful gang
in the Kanto area.
He was admitted this year into
Ouran Academy's high school.
He has long red hair,
a mean-looking appearance,
is reserved and
has few friends.
It is said, if your eyes meet
his you'll have bad dreams
for three months.
If you bump into him you'll
end up in the hospital.
And talking back to him
sends you to an early grave.
He is so feared by his
classmates that they call him
"the walking blizzard".
Seriously? But why would
a human weapon like yourself
wanna be Mori-senpai's
apprentice?
Well, because--look,
I may be tough but I'm not
a "human weapon".
I was just born with
a face that makes me
look mean all the time.
Well at least you're
aware of it, Casanova.
It's Kasanoda!
Bossa Nova?
I said it was Kasanoda!
Do you wanna die?
Man, he really is mean-looking!
Sorry 'bout that.
This always happens
'cause of the way I look.
I've always had this mean look,
ever since I was born.
Even when I was just
a tyke my dad would say--
Just you wait, my son's
gonna be the greatest gangster
of all time.
Young Lord, you gonna rumble?
And so, ever since I was kid,
I've been taught how to be
the godfather of a gang.
Don't be too friendly talkin'
to other people.
They'll look down on you.
Ah.
You've got it all wrong.
AH!
See? Now you give it a try.
Not bad. Nice and gangsterish.
Now let's try this.
Ma!
That's not a gangster!
That's from that show
somethin'-or-other-Robo!
When am I ever gonna use
that stupid catchphrase?
My pops was a good teacher and
he made me a true gangster.
That's great and
all but everyone's
afraid to come near me.
Even my fellas are
scared of me.
So I'm all alone.
It's like they forget I'm
young, and sometimes I just
wanna play.
I wanna get out with my
fellas n' play a game
of kick the can.
A good game
of kankeri is awesome.
But I've been livin' the life
of a gangster and I don't
know how to interact
with regular people.
Aw, that poor guy.
Morinozuka-senpai, that's
why I need you to show me.
How do you manage
to have so many friends?
When you're just
as mean-looking as me?
You're expressionless, distant,
and you hardly ever talk.
Plus you've got
a mug that looks like
a watchdog from hell.
So how come you've
got so many friends? What're
you doin' that I'm not?
Please, teach me your secrets!
I'm begging you!
Hey Takashi, are you okay?
I'm just a little lightheaded.
What now, boss?
Don't you think we should
do something about this?
Just leave him alone,
don't get involved.
Like he said, he wants to be
Mori-senpai's apprentice.
So that means, Mori-senpai
decides what to do.
This isn't something
that any of us should
be interfering with.
Tamaki.
Well, in that case, since
you insist Mori-senpai, I,
Tamaki Suou,
promise you, I will do
whatever I can to assist you.
Yeah, right. He wanted
to get involved so badly
he couldn't bear it.
Now lift your head,
Bossa Nova.
Listen, it's Kasanoda.
From now on you may address me
as king, okay, Bossa Nova?
That's not my name!
Are you listening
to me, Bossa Nova?
Yeah.
There are many differences
between you and our
beloved Mori-senpai,
but there is also
one very definitive thing
that you are lacking and
that is a lovely item!
A lovely item?
Bossa Nova, I would like
to introduce you to--
--a lovely item
named Mitsukuni!
Sure, Mori-senpai may be
kind of mean looking and
he may seem distant
when you first meet him
but what if we put
Mitsukuni on his shoulders?
Suddenly it's like
he's a forest teddy-bear
that all the
little animals adore.
In addition, this lovely item
also plays up Mori-senpai's
strong and silent character.
Even without saying anything,
just by placing Honey-senpai
next to him people begin to
have a new found admiration
for Mori-senpai.
Suddenly he's seen in a
positive light as a nice,
quiet, young gentleman.
That's the plan.
I'm not exaggerating
when I say most of
Mori-senpai's charm
is directly related
to his friend Honey-senpai.
Yeah, you're right!
Now that you mention it,
Mori-senpai--
--doesn't really do anything.
Yeah, his position's
totally a bust.
Takashi.
Have you really been
using me this entire time?
I'm sorry, but Honey-senpai
is on a long-term lease
to Mori-senpai right now so
I can't let you borrow him.
Is Tama-chan telling the truth?
Are you renting me?
Don't worry, I'll come up with
something to take his place.
So, the next thing
we need to discuss--
--is your disturbing
"Yankee" fashion sense.
Now Hitachiin Brothers.
Sir!
It's your job to make
this man more fashionable.
Roger!
Thanks for cleanin' up, Tetsuya.
Oh. Young Lord, welcome home.
How was your da--?
Welcome home, Young Lord.
Yeah, welcome home, Young Lord.
Uh-huh.
Young Lord, what the
hell's going on?
Somethin' happen
at school today?
Wait. Young Lord.
Damn it! This is
completely wrong, ain't it?
Those jerks lied to me!
You tellin' me that kid
is the 4th head of
the Kasanoda Syndicate?
So what are we gonna do now?
I mean we can't go
bustin' into their estate.
We'll get him at school
tomorrow. We gotta make sure
that punk pays
for what he's done.
It's getting' dark out here.
Looks like it's gonna rain.
Uh-oh. Then I hope the Young
Lord took his umbrella today.
Big brother, Morinozuka!
I just wanted
to say good mornin'.
Good mornin' to you,
Bossa Nova!
Right back at cha,
Haninozuka-senpai!
Back at cha.
Want me to carry your bag
to your classroom, senpai?
That's okay. I can manage.
What the hell are you--?
Mori, you're not hurt, are you?
You okay, Morinozuka?
Who would do
something like this?
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah.
Everybody loves him
even though he's scary lookin'.
Nevermind that,
I've got bigger things
to worry about.
Huh? Somebody's out
to get Mori-senpai?
No doubt about it. I was
there and saw everything.
He's obviously gotten
on somebody's bad side.
Nah, that's impossible.
There's no way Mori-senpai would
ever be on someone's bad side.
How can you be so sure?
You don't know that!
Don't you worry your pretty,
little head about that.
"Operation Bossa Nova's
total image make-over"
is in full-effect
as of right now!
Yes, sir!
Hold on! What the hell
are you talkin' about?
Whaddya mean you're startin'
"right now"? You tryin'
to pretend that
yesterday never happened?
Thanks to yesterday's
"makeover", people were even
more afraid of me
than they usually are!
Now hold on a second.
Let me explain, Bossa Nova.
We all support you
and we're behind you
one hundred percent.
Yesterday, the twins were just
getting a little carried away.
I hope you'll forgive them.
They support me?
I'm sorry. I will follow
your lead from here on out.
All right, so does
anyone have any ideas?
What should we do
about his look?
Hey Casanova?
Just thought I'd warn you--
I wouldn't put too much faith
in that bunch if I were you.
Well thank you but
Morinozuka recommended
these guys to me.
Besides, I don't have
much of a choice,
without their help
I got nothin'.
Hey, I don't think
I've met you before.
What was your name?
I'm Haruhi Fujioka.
We're both 1st-Years.
Just like you, I was admitted
when I got to high school.
Guess we're buddies.
Buddies?
So Haruhi, do you like
to play kick the can?
Well, um, to be honest,
it's not my favorite thing
in the world.
But you know--
--it might be fun
once in a while.
What is it?
He reminds me of a chick.
Bossa Nova!
Yes?
I think we've finally
come up with something
that'll change
your "tough guy" image.
A cat-monster.
Well that didn't work.
I don't know what went wrong.
Renge said the kitty ears
were all the rage!
She said that they were
a perfect lovely item!
What could've happened?
Be realistic. Putting kitty
ears on him isn't going
to affect how people
perceive him.
He still looks mean.
No kiddin', that was
pretty lame, boss.
For real. If you're going
to take it that far--
--you might as well go
all the way and make him
a kitty-eared maid!
Are you guys making fun of me?
Sorry to bother you but
is the Young Lord Kasanoda
in here?
So here you are.
Sir, it's no big deal.
You can do whatever you want
in your spare time.
What? Do you think this
is a hobby of mine?
Damn it! I can't
take this anymore!
Young Lord? Young Lord!
It's like they forget
I'm young and sometimes
I just wanna play.
I wanna get out with
my fellas n' play a game
of kick the can.
Maybe an image change isn't
really what Casanova needs.
I think you're right.
I sure hope he
realizes it soon.
Kasanoda is always
in such a bad mood.
I know! He's so scary!
They say you can't
look him in the eye.
Why am I always so--?
Here ya go. I brought
you somethin' to eat.
Now let me see how that
wing of yours is doin'.
Hey, it's lookin' pretty good!
Is that a sparrow?
Haruhi? What're you doin' here?
So what happened to him?
Your sparrow?
I saw it fall from it's nest
the other day. I could tell
it was hurt so I
took it to the vet.
They said he'd
be fine in no time.
So, uh, do you mind
if I feed it?
Go ahead.
I'm Haruhi Fujioka.
We're both 1st-Years.
Guess we're buddies.
You know, this guy doesn't seem
to be afraid of me at all.
He's got such big,
dark eyes and sparkly.
He really is like a chick.
Chicks are especially afraid of
me. I've never had the chance
to talk to a girl
like this before.
Holy crap! What's gotten
into me? What the hell
am I thinking? Haruhi's a dude!
Look out!
It flew away.
Haruhi, what happened?
That's not blood, is it?
Would you calm down?
It's just a little paint.
Hey are you sure you're
all right, Fujioka?
Let go of me, you bastard!
Damn it! You big behemoth!
You're playin' dirty, Kasanoda!
First you go and kidnap
our gang boss's kid and then you
make us deal with your damn
musclebound lackies?
We know that you
kidnapped the kid.
Just give him back, now!
We've heard enough outta you!
We'll shut you up!
Tying tying tying tying tying!
What the hell is goin' on here?
Don't you get it?
See Takashi wasn't
on anyone's bad side.
These guys were after you.
Until we caught them,
we decided not to
say anything to you
Because we didn't want you
to have to mess with them.
I can't believe it.
So, you helped me?
But how come?
We can tell who the bad guys
are by lookin' at 'em.
I should probably go back
and change clothes.
Want us to come help you?
Drop dead.
You dumbasses!
Sonny!
Shut up! You've
said enough today.
Don't you get it? The reason
I left was cause I was
sick of hangin' out
with the likes of you.
Now get lost, ya hear me?
Tetsuya, what's goin' on?
I'm sorry I've kept this
from you, sir.
I'm Tetsuya Sendo. I am
the son of the godfather
of the Sendo Syndicate.
But I've always been opposed
to the cutthroat way
the Syndicate goes
about handling it's business.
One rainy day about a
year ago my old man and
I got into a fight and
I ran away from home.
I've never felt as anxious
as I did that day.
It was terrible.
I had nowhere to go and
the people who passed me on
the street just ignored me.
They pretended like I
wasn't even there.
And that's when I met you,
Young Lord.
The second I saw you
I knew exactly what kind
of person you were.
After that, when I decided
to join the Kasanoda Syndicate,
you kindly accepted me.
Young Lord, I know that
you're more self-conscious
and awkward than most people
but I also know that you're
more kind-hearted
than most people.
And it's not just me, everybody
in the whole syndicate knows it.
They just don't say anything
cause it would embarrass you.
I, Tetsuya Sendo, realized
that I wanted to become
more like you.
That's why I cut all ties
to the Sendo Syndicate
and instead joined
the Kasanoda Syndicate.
I hope, Young Lord,
that you will allow me
to remain by your side.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Your umbrella.
The weather was lookin' bad so
I figured you might need it.
We don't want our
Young Lord catchin' a cold.
Everyone would worry.
Who would've thought--
I'll just keep that with me.
Yeah.
What a great story!
It's so touching!
I should apologize to Fujioka.
After all, it is my fault
he got paint on him.
Haru-chan went back to the
club room to change clothes.
Yeah? Thanks a lot.
I'll be right back.
'K. Hey Young Lord, think we
can play kick the can later?
Yeah!
We did a good thing, guys.
What're you talking about?
You didn't do anything, Boss.
Don't any of you care that
Kasanoda went to see Haruhi
who is changing clothes?
Hey, Fujioka?
Aw man, maybe he's
in the prep room.
Fujioka?
Hey, you okay? I'm sorry--
Get out!
Ma--
Ma!
Bossa Nova's started visiting
the Host Club as a guest!
And he asks for Haruhi
every single time!
If Bossa Nova starts
chasing after Haruhi--
Do something, boss!
Next time, "Tamaki's
Unwitting Depression!"
Ouran High School Host Club
does not need any
male guests coming in
next week! Ya got that?