This place has
four library rooms.
You'd think one of them
would be quiet.
How're things
in Heaven, Mom?
I can't believe it's been
ten years already.
I'm beginning to think that
rich kids only come to school
to have a good time.
An abandoned music room.
I guess this is the only
place I'll be able to study
in peace and quiet.
Welcome!
When I opened the door,
I found the Host Club.
"Starting Today,
You Are a Host!"
Only those with
excellent social standing
and those from filthy rich
families are lucky enough
to spend their time here
at the elite private school,
Ouran Academy.
The Ouran Host Club
is where the school's
handsomest boys, with too
much time on their hands,
entertain young ladies who
also have way too much time
on their hands.
Just think of it
as Ouran Academy's
elegant playground for the
super-rich and beautiful.
This is a Host Club?
Oh wow, it's a boy!
Hikaru, Kaoru, I believe
this young man is in
the same class
as you, isn't he?
Yeah, but he's shy.
He doesn't act very sociably so
we don't know much about him.
Well, that wasn't very polite.
Welcome to the Ouran Host
Club, Mr. Honor Student.
What? You must
be Haruhi Fujioka!
You're the exceptional honor
student we've heard about!
How did you know my name?
Why, you're infamous.
It's not everyday that
a commoner gains
entrance into our academy.
You must have
an audacious nerve
to work hard enough to
fight your way into this school
as an honor student,
Mr. Fujioka.
Well uh, thank you, I guess.
You're welcome!
You're a hero to other
poor people, Fujioka!
You've shown the world
that even a poor person
can excel at an elite
private academy.
It must be hard for you to
constantly be looked down upon
by others.
I think you're taking this
"poor" thing too far.
Spurned! Neglected!
But that doesn't matter now!
Long live the poor!
We welcome you, poor man,
to our world of beauty!
I'm outta here.
Hey! Come back here,
Haru-chan!
You must be like
a superhero or something!
That's so cool!
I'm not a hero.
I'm an honor student.
And who're you
calling "Haru-chan"?
I never would've imagined
the famous scholar
would be so openly gay.
Openly what?
So tell me what kind
of guys you're into?
Do you like the strong,
silent type?
The boy Lolita? How about
the mischievous type?
Or the cool type?
I, uh. It's not like that!
I was just looking for
a quiet place to study!
Or maybe.
You're into a guy like me?
What do you say?
We were going to feature
that Renaissance vase
in an upcoming
school auction!
Oh, now you've done it,
Commoner.
The bidding on that vase
was supposed to start
at 8 million yen!
What? 8 million yen? How
many thousand yen is that?
How many thousands
are in a million?
Uh, I'm gonna have
to pay you back.
With what money?
You can't even afford
a school uniform.
What's with that grubby
outfit you've got on, anyway?
Well, what do you think
we should do Tamaki?
There's a famous saying
you may have heard Fujioka.
"When in Rome, you should
do as the Romans do."
Since you have no money,
you can pay with your body.
That means starting today,
you're the Host Club's dog!
I don't know if
I can handle this, Mom.
I've been captured by
a bunch of boys that're
calling themselves a host club!
Poke, poke.
Um, Tamaki, what's
your favorite song?
What song? The one
that reminds me of you,
of course.
I baked you a cake today.
Would you like to taste it?
Only if you'll feed it
to me, darling.
Oh wow. You're so dreamy!
May I have a word
with you, Tamaki?
I've recently heard
the host club is keeping
a little kitten
without a pedigree.
I don't know
if I'd call him that.
Speak of the devil!
Thanks for doing the
shopping, little piglet.
Did you get
everything on our list?
What? Piglet?
Hey, wait a minute,
what is this?
Just what it looks like.
It's coffee.
I've never seen this
brand before.
Is this the kind
that's already ground?
What do you mean?
It's instant coffee.
It's instant?
Whoa. I've heard of
this before.
It's commoner's coffee.
You just add hot water.
I didn't know
there was such a thing!
So it's true then.
Poor people don't even
have enough free time to
grind their own coffee beans.
Commoners are pretty smart.
100 grams for 300 yen.
That's a lot less than
we normally pay.
I'll go back and
get something else.
Excuse me for not buying
you guys expensive coffee.
No, I'll keep it!
I'm going to give it a try.
I will drink this coffee!
Alright Haruhi!
Get over here and make some
of this commoner's coffee!
I hate all these
damn rich people.
Oh, Tamaki, now you're
taking the joke too far.
Your palate won't be able
to stomach that crap,
you don't have to drink it
just because he bought it.
I'm sorry. I was
talking to myself.
Haruhi!
I'm comin'.
Here.
Let the tasting begin!
I'm a little scared
to drink this stuff.
I'm afraid if I drink this
my father will yell at me.
What if I let you drink it
from my mouth?
Well, then I would drink it.
This is
ridiculous.
So he had this nightmare
that made him bolt up right
out of bed.
Hikaru! Don't
tell them that story!
I asked you not
to tell anyone that.
Why are you so mean to me?
I'm sorry, Kaoru.
I didn't mean to upset you
but you were so adorable
when it happened I had
to tell them. I'm sorry.
I forgive you.
I've never seen brotherly
love quite like that!
What're they so excited about?
I just don't get it.
Sorry, we're running late.
Hello Honey! Hey Mori!
We've been waiting here
for you guys. Hi!
I'm sorry. I was
waiting for Takashi
to finish his kendo
meeting and I fell asleep.
And I'm still not
completely awake.
So cute!
Is that boy really
a 3rd year student?
Honey-senpai may seem
young and childish
but he's a prodigy.
And then Mori-senpai's allure
is his strong and
silent disposition.
Haru-chan!
Hey Haru-chan,
do you want to go have
some cake with me?
Thanks but I don't
really like cake.
Then how would you like to
hold my bunny Usa-chan?
I'm not into bunnies.
Are you saying
you don't like Usa-chan?
I guess he is
kinda cute, huh?
Take good care
of him, okay?
You'll notice that our
club utilizes each man's
unique characteristics
to cater to the desires
of our guests.
Just so you know,
Tamaki is number one
around here.
He's the king.
His request rate is 70%.
What's this world coming to?
And in order for you to pay
off your 8 million yen debt
with us, you will act as
the Ouran Host Club's dog
until you graduate. I'm sorry.
I meant our errand boy.
You can try to run away
if you want to, Haruhi,
but just so you know,
my family employs
a private police force
of 100 officers.
By the way, do you
have a passport?
You're going to have
to work hard to pay off
that debt, my little nerd.
Please, don't do that again.
You need a makeover
or no girl's going to look
twice at you.
Yeah, well, I'm not trying
to get girls to look at me.
Are you kidding me?
That's the most
important thing.
You have to learn
to be a gentleman
and please the ladies, like me.
I just don't think
it's all that important.
Why should I care about
appearances and labels anyway?
I mean, all that really
matters is what's on
the inside, right?
I don't understand why
you even have
a host club like this.
It's a cruel reality,
isn't it?
It's not often that God creates
a perfect person like moi;
beautiful both
inside and out.
Say what?
I understand how
you feel since not everyone
is blessed as I am. But
you must console yourself.
Otherwise how would
you go on living?
And think about this Haruhi.
Why do you think they put
works of art in museums?
Because beauty should
be shared with the world!
And those born beautiful
should promote--
There's a word to
describe people like him.
--in the first place.
I did it for those who are
starved for beauty--
What is it?
--day and night
pursuing beauty.
And although--
Aw, man, I wish I could
remember that word.
--I have chosen to share
my expertise with you.
Here's a tip. When
setting down your glass,
extend your pinky finger
as a cushion.
And that way when
you set it down,
you won't be
making a lot of noise.
Gentlemen do not--
Maybe "A pain in the neck"?
No, there's something
that fits him perfectly.
But above all else Haruhi,
you must remember--
--how effective a glance
to the side can be.
I got it!
Oh, did I strike a chord?
"Obnoxious!"
Uh, I'm sorry,
Tamaki-senpai.
You're a hero, alright!
Uh-huh!
But he is a pain in the neck.
I'm sorry senpai but your
lesson did strike a small chord
with me.
Really? It did?
Let me teach you
more, my friend.
Well, he got over
that with quick.
Boss?
Call me "King"!
You can teach him
all the basics of hosting--
But he's not going to get
very far with the ladies
if he doesn't look
the part, you know?
He's not exactly host club
material but maybe if
we took off his
glasses it'll help.
Hey! I need those!
I used to have contacts
but I lost them on
the first day of school.
Hikaru! Kaoru!
Got it!
Kyoya, my hairstylist!
Mori-senpai, go to the eye
doctor and get him some
contact lenses!
What about me Tama-chan?
Honey-senpai.
Yes sir?
You go have some cake.
It's just us Usa-chan.
Everyone else
said they were too busy.
Here! Change
into this uniform!
What? But why?
Don't ask questions!
No way! Okay,
fine! I'll change!
But you two
have to get out!
Um, Senpai?
Aren't you done changing yet?
You sure it's really okay for
me to keep this uniform?
Cute! You're as pretty
as a girl! Adorable!
Haru-chan,
you look so cute!
If we had known that's
how you really look--
--we would've helped
you out sooner.
Who knows? Maybe he'll
draw in some customers.
You know, that's just what
I was thinking!
Our errand boy is
moving up the ranks!
Starting today,
you are an official member
of the Host Club.
I will personally train
you to be a first-rate host.
If you can get 100 customers
to request your service
we will completely forget
about your 8 million yen debt.
A host?
So tell me Haruhi.
Do you have any hobbies?
What do you like to do?
I'm curious,
what kind of products
do you use on your skin?
Yes, it's so pretty.
I can't do this anymore.
I have no idea
what I'm supposed to do!
So why did you join
the host club Haruhi?
All I have to do is get 100
customers to request me
and they'll forget about
my 8 million yen debt.
I know just the story.
I see, your mother was sick
and passed away 10 years ago?
Who does the chores
around the house?
Oh, I do them myself.
My mother taught me.
She was an amazing cook.
And when she went to the
hospital she left me
all kinds of great recipes. It
was fun to create each dish,
especially when they
turned out well.
And it made me happy
to see my dad enjoy it.
I've had a hard childhood
but Dad and I have
managed to make it
through okay.
So uh--
Is it okay if tomorrow--
--we request to sit
with you again?
Yeah, I'd really
appreciate that, ladies!
Why's he so popular?
He's a natural.
No training needed.
Have you forgotten about me?
Oh no! Sorry Princess.
I'm just a little bit concerned
about our newest host.
Well, that's obvious, Tamaki.
You sure have been
keeping an eye on him.
Of course. I have to.
I'm training him
to be a gentleman like me.
Haruhi! Come here
for a minute.
What's up?
I'd like you
to meet someone.
This is my regular guest,
Princess Ayanokoji.
It's that girl
from earlier.
Miss, it's a pleasure
to meet you.
That was so cute!
That air of bashfulness
was very good!
Super good!
Amazingly good!
Um, Tamaki?
You're so cute!
I'm never gonna let you go!
Mori-senpai! Help me!
Mori-senpai, you really
didn't have to go that far.
Come on little one,
let Daddy give you a big hug!
I've already got a dad.
I don't need another one!
Hey, what happened to my bag?
Are you kidding me?
But how did that happen?
I didn't think there were
bullies at this school.
Guess they're everywhere.
Oh, it's you again.
I bet you love having
Tamaki making you over
and fawning over you.
It's useless though,
you're always going to be
a second class citizen.
I have a feeling that girl's
the one who threw my bag
in the pond.
I can't be bothered with her
right now though. I've
gotta find my wallet
or I won't have any money
for food this week.
Hey, commoner!
You've got some nerve
skipping out on
the club like that!
Why is your bag all wet?
It's no big deal. I got it.
I just can't find
my food money.
Hey, you don't have to do
that, you'll get wet!
A little water
never hurt anyone.
Besides, people are always
telling me that I'm dripping
with good looks.
Oh! Hang on a second!
This what you're looking for?
What's the matter? You're
staring off into space.
You're not falling
for me, are you?
No way!
How did your bag end up
in the pond anyway?
Well, uh, I guess
I accidentally dropped it out
the window at some point.
Oh really?
That must've been terrible!
I can't imagine what I'd do
if my bag fell into the pond.
Why did she request me when it's
obvious she doesn't like me.
And you actually made
Tamaki search that dirty,
old pond with you?
How astonishing!
You do realize he's a blueblood
and not a commoner, right?
The only reason he's
paying attention to you
is because he's trying to
turn you into a gentlemen.
Don't start thinking he
cares about you just because
he's doting on you.
Now I understand.
You're jealous of me.
No Haruhi! Leave me alone!
Somebody help.
He just attacked me!
Someone do something!
Teach this commoner a lesson!
Why did you do that?
Do something Tamaki!
Haruhi just assaulted me!
I'm disappointed in you.
You threw his bag
into the pond, didn't you?
You don't know that. Do you
have any proof that I did?
You know, you're
a beautiful girl.
But you aren't classy enough to
be our guest, dear. If there's
one thing I know, Haruhi
is not that kind of a man.
But why, Tamaki? You idiot!
Now how am I
going to punish you?
Because it is
your fault, after all.
Your quota is now 1000!
One thousand?
Come on.
I've got high expectations
for you, my little rookie.
This is the only spare
uniform we have.
Sorry but it's better than
a wet one, right?
Thanks a lot you guys.
I'm gonna go change.
Haruhi, here you go.
I brought you some towels.
Haruhi.
Yeah?
So, you're a girl?
Biologically speaking, yeah.
Listen Senpai, I don't
really care whether you guys
recognize me as a boy
or a girl. In my opinion,
it's more important for
a person to be recognized
for who they are rather
than for what sex they are.
Well, isn't this an
interesting development?
Oh yeah!
You know, I have to say Senpai,
I thought you were
pretty cool earlier.
Now, I could be wrong,
but I think we may be
witnessing the beginnings
of love here.
Being a host and getting fussed
over by a bunch of girls
might not be that bad. I
wonder how I can pull it off?
I've got it! I'll just call
everyone dude and bro now!
Don't start getting full
of yourself just because
you're popular. If you're
going to be a host--
Wow! Another customer's
requested me!
Don't take my customers!
Next time, "The Job
of a High School Host".
The Ouran Host Club
will be waiting for you!
We'll see you then!