Excuse me.
Are you a member of
the Host Club?
Could you ask 3rd-year
student Mitsukuni Haninozuka
to meet me out here?
Who? Honey-senpai? You sure?
Yes.
Oh, look! It's Chika-chan!
So what's up? You rarely
come over to the high school
like this to see me.
Prepare yourself, Mitskuni!
Hey! C'mon, cut it out
you guys! Mori-senpai!
Whaddya mean, "hm"?!
Whoa! Did you see that?!
Honey-senpai dodged Chika's
preliminary attack!
This is gonna be good!
What's going on?
Honey-senpai is able to fly
through the air with such grace!
He's like a modern-day
Ushiwakamaru! Whoa!
Chika attacks again without
even giving him a chance
to regain his balance!
Incredible! He dodged his
attack and tripped him!
Neither of them is gonna give!
They keep lashing out with
ferocious techniques!
So they're at it again?
I wish they would've chosen a
better location to do this.
Wait, why are
you guys so calm?!
Things're getting serious
now! Chika's got a weapon!
Hey! No way! The use a weapon
should be against the rules!
Whoa! He knocked him
out of the park!
This may be his first win!
I gotcha!
Sorry.
But I don't think so.
The winner of this fight
is Honey-senpai!
Renge's right about that.
See? He got you.
How the hell did he do that?!
In the heat of battle,
Honey-senpai was able to attack
with his shuriken before
Chika noticed!
He uses shuriken?
His attack has left Chika
utterly defenseless!
What a great fight!
Can't wait for the next one!
Until then, see ya!
Hey, guys.
I'm completely lost- you wanna
tell me what's going on here?
Who's that kid and why'd
he attack Honey-senpai?
What? You mean you can't tell
just by looking at his face?
He's Honey-senpai's
younger brother.
Chika's 'Down With
Honey' Declaration!
The Haninozukas
are a noble family.
We excel at martial arts.
We've combined styles
over the years,
to create our very own
method of fighting.
When we're away,
we study karate and judo,
but when we're home,
we work hard to master
the Haninozuka technique.
So to make sure that
we always stay alert,
we have been taught that
whenever two family members
come face-to-face,
they must engage
each other in battle.
I get it now. They were
fighting because their family
makes them.
Go on, Yasuchika.
We saved you a piece of cake!
Thank you, but I don't
care for sweets.
Besides a basic principle
of the Haninozuka technique
is refraining from selfishness.
So to let myself
indulge in sweets would
be out of the question.
But one little piece of cake
isn't really going to hurt you.
Hold on- I happen to know
of a sweets-loving,
overly-pampered little
loli boy who happens to be-
- the next head
of the Haninozukas-
-and he's sitting
right over there.
Let me just say,
there's no way I'm ever going
to recognize a dimwit
like Mitskuni as the
next head of our family.
There's no doubt my
older brother is strong,
but he lives a decadent
lifestyle and has failed to show
any self-restraint.
He no longer has the right
to be called a Haninozuka.
I can't allow someone
who arbitrarily quit
the Karate Club only
to become hooked,
on cake and stuffed
animals; to be the head
of the Haninozuka family,
even if he is my older brother.
I've been meaning to make
that clear for a while.
And another thing, Mitskuni.
I've said it before and
I'll say it again stay away
from me at school, got it?
Senpai. Are you doin' okay?
Honey-senpai, so what should
we do with this cake?
I'll eat it!
Yay!
I guess everyone has their
own strange family issues
to deal with.
So, you used to be in the
Karate Club Honey-senpai?
I had no idea.
What made you decide to quit
and join the Host Club?
Why did you just say
the Host Club like that?
What're you getting at, huh?
Well, no matter how you
cut it, the Karate Club
is a much more reputable
club than ours, senpai.
If you really wanna know-
-we'll have to take a little
trip down memory lane.
It was long before the Host
Club had been established.
Listen up and we'll tell you
the legend of Honey-senpai,
the captain of the Karate Club.
Oh, so the eldest son
is in high school now?
I heard he's already been made
captain of the Karate Club
and he's only a 1st-Year.
That is outstanding.
I know he's a growing boy
but doesn't he seem small
for his age? He may not
be respected as head
of the family
if he stays that small.
Mitsukuni, you are aware
of what the others are
saying about you, right?
Yes.
You must work even harder to
maintain your self-discipline.
Completely cast aside all
weakness and leniency
and take hold of your
true strength.
Right!
From that day forward,
Honey-senpai
tried his very best.
It was difficult,
but he worked hard.
So he spent more time
working on martial arts moves?
Wrong!
Well aware of what the others
were saying about him,
Honey-senpai worked hard to
follow his father's orders.
He sealed away all
of his cute possessions,
so as to not seem weak.
Then, he decided to take on a
hard and fearless disposition,
that of a manly-man.
However, it was obvious to
everyone around him that
his efforts were failing.
Excuse me Haninozuka,
would you like me to get you
a piece of cake?
What're you doing?! He can't!
No thank you,
I don't like sweets.
He's upset! See what you did?
He was exercising self-control!
I totally forgot; I'm so sorry.
He's trying so hard to resist!
You can tell he's
really struggling!
Oh wow, it's so touching!
And so, the girls were so
touched by seeing him resist
the things he loved that their
Moe senses went into overdrive.
Not long after that the
Haninozuka fan club was born.
I don't understand what
any of that has to do with
the legend of the Karate Club.
Let us explain.
Okay guys, take
a ten minute break!
Sir!
Hey. You know Captain
Haninozuka is such a strict
and manly captain!
His technique is awesome
and he always keeps us in line!
No joke! He's the
best captain ever!
For real, though!
He's a super manly-man!
That story's such a
tear-jerker!
You gotta be kidding?
How is that a tear-jerker?
Never mind, just tell me
what happens, would ya?
Why, hello there,
Haninozuka-senpai.
I know this is kind of
sudden but I was wondering
if you'd join a new club
I'm starting.
Aren't you Suou? Tamaki, right?
You're from the middle school.
What kind of club
are you starting?
I can't tell you how happy I am
you asked Haninozuka-senpai!
Come on senpai, don't you
think it's about time that
you start using your
charming, good looks to get
more out of life?
Why waste your time
fighting when you could use
your cuteness to give solace
to young girls
with too much time on
their hands.
With tons of stuffed animals
and all the cake you could want!
I promise that if you join
we'll always have plenty
of sweets on hand.
Really? I mean- No. I don't like
sweets so you can forget it,
and for the record, I don't
like cutesy things either.
No way. Not into cutesy
stuff. Don't like it, at all.
I don't know much about martial
arts so please forgive me,
but I was wondering. Do you
think you could tell me
what true strength is?
I may be out of line but
hiding your true self and
putting on airs doesn't seem
any different than
running away to me.
I would think that embracing
the things you truly like and
being able to enjoy them-
Is worth more than anything.
To just be yourself.
I believe that's what
true strength really is.
I'll be back to ask you again.
Please consider it, senpai.
What is it that you wanted
to talk to me about?
Well. There's something
that I've been
a little confused
about, father.
Can you please tell me
what true strength is?
I will show you my son, so you
can experience it directly.
Come with me to the dojo!
It has been said, that
Honey-senpai's father
is the most talented fighter
in the Haninozuka
family's history.
And... begin!
If I remember correctly,
Honey-senpai had already
attained his current level
of martial arts prowess.
Which is quite extraordinary.
Well, am I right?
Uh-huh!
Rumor has it, the referee that
happened to be officiating
was Japan's Secretary
of Defense at the time,
and he begged Honey-senpai to
never fight in public again;
at least not at his
full potential.
Why would he do that?
If the world ever saw
Honey-senpai's true abilities
they'd suspect Japan
of possessing a weapon
of mass destruction. The
Secretary was afraid it might
upset the U.N. and then
they would take it out
on all of Japan.
How awful!
So, Honey-senpai
quit the Karate Club-
-and decided to become a
member of the Host Club.
All things considered, Honey
senpai's behavior is too
unconventional for even the
Haninozuka's to contain.
So because of that, his younger
brother had a more strict
upbringing- one more in
keeping with the
Haninozuka standard.
Sometimes I think
Chika-chan hates me because
I'm not following
the family rules.
All right, gentlemen!
Time for Operation Haninozuka
Brothers Reconciliation!
I knew he was gonna say that.
Alright, ten minute break!
Sir!
Y' know, Captain Haninozuka
sure is a strict captain.
No matter how hard we try it's
like he's never satisfied.
I really don't
think I can take it.
Tell me about it.
He's a tough captain. But
he's nowhere near as skilled
at martial arts as his
older brother, Mitskuni.
You will not talk about
my brother in my presence
do you understand?
Look! It's Chika,
he's sooo adorable!
Oh wow, he's so
totally cute!
Yeah, Chika's not bad but he's
no match for his older brother,
Honey. He's the cutest
thing we've ever seen!
What are you idiots
looking at?!
Get started with
the next drill!
But, we're still on
our break, sir!
You've barely broken a sweat.
You bums don't need a break.
Start working harder
before you're all out!
Sir!
Well, so far it looks like a
simple inferiority complex.
He's always being compared to
Honey-senpai so that's why
he feels such animosity towards
him. His older brother is
more attractive, more popular
and a better martial artist
than he is. I think he's
just letting his jealousy
get the best of him.
It's totally normal
and way boring.
We're gonna go find
something more entertaining.
Hold on!
Come back here you two!
Why are you suddenly
being so uncooperative?
Well, we thought
there'd be an interesting,
secret reason they're
fighting. This is just lame.
So Honey-senpai and
Chika's feelings
aren't exciting enough?!
It's okay Tama-chan, really.
But, Honey-senpai.
It's alright;
don't worry about me.
So what if
Chika-chan hates me.
I would be happy just seeing
him grow up to be strong
and healthy; he is
my brother after all.
Um, he's already a lot taller
than you Honey-senpai.
Yeah, he's pretty "grown up"
and plenty "healthy".
'Scuse me, could you guys
please keep it down?
What're you doing here?! I
thought I had told you to
stay away from me at
school Mitskuni!
You alien.
Just leave me alone!
But Chika-chan.
What's he mean "alien"?
Why would you call him that?
Just because your brother
is stronger than you are
doesn't give you the right to
call him an alien!
Yeah, why are you so upset
about cake and stuffed animals?
Well If it was just about
the cake and stuffed animals
I would never have
said anything.
Let's get this straight, I
didn't call my brother an alien
because he's stronger than me.
Have any of you ever seen
him devour an entire cake?!
Don't tell me that you guys
think that's perfectly normal!
He has 3 whole cakes after
dinner every night for dessert!
Seriously- three cakes a night!
And he never gains weight!
I humbly accept
this yummy dessert!
That was delicious!
So Honey-senpai eats
that way at home, too?
And then something crazy
occurred last week.
I happened to wake up in
the middle of the night.
And I noticed that the light
was on in the dining room.
What's going on? It's the
middle of the night, you know.
Hey, Chika-chan.
No way! He's eating cake-
at this hour??!
I'm glad you're here. Once a
week I have a special cake
night where I eat all the cake I
want. Usa-chan here helped me
to come up with the idea.
Would you like to join us?
C'mon, be honest.
You know there's no way
a regular human being
can eat that much cake!
Aren't you terrified?!
I bet he gets signals from his
home planet through that weird
bunny of his! Why can't you
see that he's an alien?!
When you think about it-
-everything Chika
just said to us-
-suddenly makes perfect
sense, doesn't it?
I don't know though.
There was a time when Mitskuni
and I got along really well.
While it's true that my
brother's always had a fondness
for cute things and more
of a sweet tooth
than I have. I still respected
his ability to avoid
that stuff even though
he loved it.
And then this idiot came
along and brainwashed him
with some ridiculous nonsense.
Something about acknowledging
who you really are
and just being yourself.
That that's true strength!
Not long after that he fell
apart and became the alien
he is today.
Oh, I see, so all
of Chika's troubles-
-can be traced right back to
you, isn't that true boss?
What are you talking about?!
I didn't mean to!
There's gotta be some way
we can fix this!
Come on, you guys!
There is a way
to solve this, you know.
You've got it figured out?!
So Mitsukuni,
you know what to do.
Listen, Chika-chan,
I never meant to upset you.
I didn't know that you
hated sweets that much
and I'm very sorry.
Oh no, it looks like he
completely missed the point.
Nobody can make me
change who I am.
I'm really grateful
to Tama-chan and all
of the Host Club because
they've shown me that.
So.
Let's settle this like men,
in the Haninozuka style.
Yasuchika.
Since when does Ouran have
a field like this?
And don't forget Chika-chan,
this is a one-point match.
So what happens if I win?
If you win I'll
stop eating cake
in the middle of the night.
All right.
Are you ready for battle,
men? Then, you may begin.
Is it just me? Or is this
fight turning out exactly like
the one they had earlier?
Yes, but this time
their roles are reversed.
Mitsukuni's already planned
how this entire fight
will pan out.
Yasuchika will attack with
his shuriken any moment now.
Whoa, he called it!
Uh, Mori-senpai, where do
they hide these shuriken?
I have been watching these two
brothers spar for many years.
And it didn't take long
before I noticed that
in every match Yasuchika
incorporates moves
that Mitsukuni used
in the previous match.
Mitsukuni realized it as well,
and he always tries to give
his brother the opportunity
to practice
those new techniques.
He may call him an alien,
but as far as martial arts
are concerned, Yasuchika
has a deep respect for
Mitsukuni and his abilities.
I think all he really
wants is to be like his
older brother. They are
connected just as two
siblings ought to be.
And personally, I think
a little sibling rivalry
is perfectly normal.
There's no need to worry about
the outcome of this match.
I can already tell you that
Mitsukuni's planning to
throw the fight and let
Yasuchika beat him.
Trust me, I know everything
there is to know about him.
Defend yourself!
Yay! I'm the winner!
Cake! Cake! Cake!
I have an idea! Since I won,
I think we should
start having special cake
night three times a week!
Don't let it get you
down, Mori-senpai.
So Honey-senpai's
love of cake exceeds
his love for his brother.
Man, he's a horrible person.
I would think that embracing
the things you truly like and
being able to enjoy them is
worth more than anything.
To just be yourself.
I believe that's
what true strength really is.
I love you!
What?! The Zuka Club
from Lobelia Academy has
kidnapped Haruhi?!
Don't you worry, Haruhi!
I'm on my way to save you
right this minute!
Next time, "Lobelia Girls'
Academy Strikes Back"!
Until then, the Ouran Host
Club will be waiting for you!
We'll see you then!