Do you remember the first
time we played that game?
It was so long ago.
Hey! You wanna make
a snowman with me?
Which one of us
are you talking to?
To both of you, silly.
There's nobody here
named "Both of you".
Okay, then I'm talking
to Hikaru and Kaoru.
Oh really?
Which of us is Kaoru?
And which of us is Hikaru?
Can you tell?
Let's all play the
"Which one is Hikaru" game!
So, can you tell which one
of us is Hikaru?
Well, it's hard to say.
You're identical!
Many ladies have tried
to tell us apart, but so far
none have succeeded.
That's the dumbest game
I've ever heard of.
What? Have you got
a problem with it, Haruhi?
Not really, I just don't
understand why the two of you
are so popular.
That's not very nice.
I'm disappointed.
Apparently you don't
understand the merits of
having a pair of twins as
members of the Host Club.
Listen up. Having a couple
of good-looking guys
with homosexual tendencies
earns the club high points.
It also helps if the
two struggle between
their attraction and
their friendship.
And in our case, because
we're twins, our relationship
is taboo and therefore
more intriguing.
And besides, who hasn't
fantasized about twins?
Having two loves is better
than one, don't you think?
It's a young woman's
romantic fantasy.
Well. Um, yeah, you're right.
I can't take it!
Hikaru! Kaoru!
When I gave you control
of the club's website
I did so on one condition-
that you'd take it seriously!
We take our job
very seriously, boss.
In fact, last night we
worked on it 'til dawn!
Is this what you worked
so hard to create?
You look great,
Haru-chan!
Tell me when!
When did you take
naked pictures of Haruhi?
Yes, that pose is perfect, and
your expression is beautiful.
Once we're done with this
shoot, we'll let you have all
the fancy tuna you want. Fancy
tuna, as much as you want.
You bribed her, didn't you?
You're imagining things.
It's obvious that the
photo's been altered.
It was photoshopped?
We did a pretty good job, huh?
We've got some major
photoshopping talent.
You idiots! That's
a waste of your skills!
Have you no shame?
But if you're going
to do it anyway,
can you photoshop her into
this idol photo-book? Please?
Don't be ridiculous,
boss. Why don't you just--
--ask her if she would wear
an outfit like one of those.
I never thought to ask her.
What do you think
about this, my dear?
What're you doing
with that dress?
He looks so handsome!
Yeah, he does but I have
to agree with Tamaki.
I'd love to see what
Haruhi looked like if he
dressed as a girl!
Oh, he's so cute,
I'm sure he'd look great
no matter what you put him in.
Now cut it out.
No more making weird
pictures of me, you got that?
Just what do you guys
take me for anyway?
Isn't that obvious?
You're our toy.
The Twins Fight!
As we were saying,
in order to entertain oneself
in this otherwise
boring life-
-one must find himself
stimulating toys.
I am not your toy, okay?
You want a toy?
Toys, toys. If you like
toys then you should
come and visit my
Black Magic Club.
We've opened
a marketplace that boasts
black magic items
from across the globe.
We're also holding mass
around the clock.
If you visit right now,
I'll even throw in
a free curse doll, you can have
Belzenef as your free gift.
Why's he talking to us
through a crack in the door?
Wait a second, has that
door always been there?
Nekozawa-senpai likes to hide.
He doesn't really care
for brightly-lit places.
Don't get involved
with that guy, Haruhi.
If you do, you'll end up
being cursed.
Do you have any basis for that?
Yes. It happened during
final exams at the end
of the last school year.
It's terrifying just
to talk about it.
Good morning, Tamaki.
Good morning!
On that fateful day.
I accidentally stepped on
that weirdo Nekozawa's
cursed doll, Belzenef.
Afterward, I took my exam
and the entire test
was written in some strange
lettering. I looked to the
others around me for help and
realized I knew none of them!
I was all alone in
a different dimension!
Scary!
Did that really happen to you?
That only happened
because you were so scared
you accidentally walked into
the Beginning Greek class
and took their exam.
No! It was a curse!
I know it was because
three days later I woke up and
my legs were as heavy as lead!
Just how do you explain that?
Your legs were heavy
because you ran a marathon
the day before, remember?
You shouldn't underestimate
the dark powers of Belzenef
the curse doll.
All you have to do is write
the name of someone
you hate on his back. Then
that person is certain to come
face-to-face with misfortune.
Wow, this guy really
is dark in more ways than one.
Supposedly he hates bright
lights, I wonder what
he'll think of this.
How on earth could you
do such a thing?
Obviously the two of you
don't know the true terror
of black magic!
Uh, I am so bored.
Isn't there anything fun
we can do around here?
My dignity as the club's
leader is being ignored.
Hey, Haruhi! We've got
a favor to ask you.
What is it?
The next time we get a day off-
-can we come over
to your place to hang out?
Why would you wanna do that?
We're curious. We want
to see where you live.
No way.
Aw! Pretty please?
No way. You guys're
just gonna make fun of me.
No matter how much we beg you?
No way.
I too have been thinking
that it's about time
I pay my respects to our
beloved Haruhi's family.
No way in hell, Senpai.
We can settle this
with a game!
If you can't pick out
which one of us is Hikaru,
then your penalty will be
the two of us coming over
to your house later tonight.
Okay, so which one
of us is Hikaru?
This one's Kaoru;
this one's Hikaru.
Uh-oh! You got it wrong!
No, I know I'm right.
You guys may look alike
but you're very different.
How'd you do that, Haruhi?
Whenever they wear those hats
to cover which way they part
their hair, it's practically
impossible to try and
figure out which twin is
Hikaru and which one is Kaoru.
How can you tell
them apart?
Well, how do I put it? It's
kinda difficult to explain.
But Hikaru's speech and
actions make him come across
a little more
mischievous than Kaoru.
I'm sorry, Hikaru!
I don't mean to laugh.
Well, I don't see
what's so funny.
I'm honest, I speak my mind
and I don't hold back.
It's sneaky people like Kaoru
who are the trouble makers.
Don't turn this on me, Hikaru.
After all, I'm the one who's
always going along with
all of your selfish games.
I may suggest them
but you're the one who
really gets into them, Kaoru.
If you hate it so much
then why don't you just stop?
Because I'd hate to see you
make an ass out of yourself
in front of everyone. It was
your idea to call Haruhi
our toy, but I noticed you were
quick to make a pass at her.
Admit it Hikaru. You're
actually in love with Haruhi,
aren't you?
What?
You've got it all wrong,
Kaoru! Man, you're such
a freakin' idiot!
Yeah! There are some things
in this world
that must never be said!
Why would I fall for her? I
mean she looks like a tanuki!
How dare you call her
a raccoon dog!
You're gonna
pay for that!
Awesome! This is just perfect!
Our beloved Haruhi is in
the middle of a beautiful
yet poignant four-sided
romantic relationship!
And to make it even
more exciting two of
Haruhi's admirers are
twins, torn apart by love!
Just the thought of it could
make me eat three bowls
of rice!
Oh butt out, otaku.
You guys are meanies!
You shouldn't say
something like that
to your manager!
But Renge, I thought you had
feelings for Haruhi, as well?
Oh, I do, but I have
no problem with Haruhi
having a homosexual
relationship on the side.
I'm confused, I thought
that you had decided
to go back home
to France, Renge.
Well, I was going to start up
a host club of my own but,
I don't think France is ready
for a host club just yet.
Cut it out already!
You're the one who's always
crawling into my bed!
Talk about annoying!
I only do that cause
you look lonely.
I wouldn't choose to sleep
in your bed, you idiot!
Who are you calling an idiot?
You're the one
who sucks at math!
Oh yeah? Well,
you're failing your
foreign language classes,
you big dummy!
The way you grind
your teeth is deafening!
At least I don't toss and turn
so much that I fall out of bed!
Sex pixie!
Sicko!
Your mama wears
too much makeup!
That's it! We're over!
Hey Haruhi!
Good Morning.
Hikaru. What in the world
happened to your hair?
Why is it dyed pink?
Cause pink suits me.
Don't you think it's cute?
From now on I'm
the pink haired twin.
I didn't want to be mistaken
for that Kaoru for
the rest of my life, you know?
Good morning, Haruhi.
So Kaoru's
the blue twin?
I was finally able to sleep
all by myself last night
but I ended up
having a nightmare.
I dreamt that my stylist
had dyed my hair pink.
It was so garish and
ridiculous looking-
I woke up screaming.
I'll have the A lunch.
No!
Give me the B pasta
and the D salad!
I'll take the F cappellini with
the barbarie duck. Hold on!
Make that a foie gras
in périgueux sauce!
Stop copying me! Why don't
you just leave me alone?
Amazing. Perfect unison
even when fighting.
I was wondering what
all the fuss was about.
I can't believe the two
of you are still fighting.
You're a disgrace
to the host club.
Hey, look who it is.
Oh! I love them!
I've never seen them
all together like that!
We've had enough of this!
You're both to blame
for this fight.
Hika-chan and Kao-chan I
want you to make up and go
halfsies on this cake, 'kay?
But I wanna have a piece
too so I guess we're gonna
have to go thirdsies. We're
not gonna be able to split
the strawberry on top, though.
What should we do? Maybe I
should just take it. After all,
strawberries are my favorite!
I forgot to ask.
Hika-chan, Kao-chan,
do you like strawberries?
You're just making
it worse. Leave them alone.
Oh, Haruhi! I didn't
expect to run into you
in the dining hall.
I was worried about those two
so I followed them here
without even thinking. I
always bring a boxed lunch,
and I was just gonna
eat it in my classroom.
A boxed lunch?
Here darling,
your boxed lunch.
I hope you're
not too embarrassed,
but I decided to make it
in a heart shape for you.
I love you!
I don't care if my boxed
lunch is in an embarrassing
heart shape! I will eat it!
I have no idea what
you're talking about,
but it's evident
that your fantasies
are completely incoherent.
Haruhi, you want
to sit here with me?
Uh okay.
So what's that?
What'd you bring for lunch?
Yesterday's leftovers,
and a rolled omelet.
You wanna switch with me?
I had to order
something different than Kaoru
so I ended up with stuff
I don't really like.
That's fine with me.
This is really magnificent.
I've never tried
anything like this before.
Delicious. It's delicious,
isn't it Haruhi?
I'm so glad you like it. I want
you to eat like that every day.
Well played, Hikaru.
As a reward, I'd like
to trade you my lunch for
your boxed lunch.
No way.
C'mon, trade with me.
Forget about it.
So Haruhi, is that any good?
How would you like
to taste mine?
Here.
Quit butting in.
Get lost, Kaoru.
I think I'm gonna eat
in my classroom, after all.
Looking at the numbers, if
this situation isn't resolved,
I'm afraid we're going to have
to stop offering our brotherly
love package. We're down
one pair of loving brothers.
Oh, Haruhi, I just want you
to know there's no reason
for you to feel responsible.
Even though it was
your tactless comment that
started this whole feud between
the twins in the
first place, right?
Clearly he blames me for this.
It's weird for Hika-chan and
Kao-chan to be fighting
like this. It's never
happened before.
They've never fought before?
I've known Hika-chan and
Kao-chan since we were
in pre-school. We weren't in the
same year, so I never really
got to talk to them, but I
remember that the two of them
always played together.
Yeah, that's true. I mean I've
only known the twins since
they were in middle school but
they definitely stood out.
It seemed like they kept
everyone at a distance except
each other. Believe it or not,
they were even more warped
back then. When you stop
and think about it,
maybe this fight is
a good thing for them.
Maybe it means that the twins
are expanding their horizons
a bit. We should just leave them
alone and let them work it out.
Who knows? Maybe it is a turn
for the better. But if this
really is their first fight,
they probably need someone
to tell them when it's time
to give in and call it quits.
And if they've never fought
before, would they even know
how to make up?
Don't you guys think that
maybe, it's time you give up
all this fighting?
It's driving me insane!
What'd you say?
It's driving you insane?
You've got to be kidding me-
how do you think I feel
right now? Every time I look
in the mirror I see his face.
I'm sick and tired of
constantly being mistaken
for you, Kaoru! The truth
is I hate your guts!
You took the words
right out of my mouth.
In fact, I hate you
so much I bought this.
Belzenef, the curse doll!
I'm going to complete
the curse, Hikaru.
I'm going to write
your name on his back.
From this day forward,
you're going to experience
nothing but
misfortune and sorrow!
Will you guys knock it off?
What do you think
you're doing?
You don't bring something
like this into a petty fight!
Both of you are at fault
here but what's really sad
is that you've brought
everyone else around you
into your big mess!
Now apologize to each other!
If you don't make up
right now I'm never gonna let
you come over to my house!
Have I made myself clear?
So then what you're saying
Haruhi is that if we make up
we can come over to your place?
I'm so sorry, Kaoru.
Even though I was just
following our script, I said
such awful things to you.
I'm not fit to be your brother.
Don't say that, Hikaru!
I was so worried.
I couldn't live with myself if
I ever thought I had hurt you.
Kaoru, I'll never
let you go again!
Hikaru!
You've gotta be kidding?
You mean you guys were
faking it this whole time?
We didn't have anything else
to do, we were bored.
They totally fooled me.
Twins with too much time
on their hands--
--are the devil.
I'm so glad they made up!
Okay, it's time to play the
"which one is Hikaru" game!
I know! The twin with
the pink hair is Hikaru!
We have a winner!
So are you two going to
keep your wild hair color
even though you've made up?
It's much easier to tell
the two of you apart now.
Huh. No, it isn't.
Today the pink one is Kaoru
and Hikaru's the blue one.
You swapped colors
for the day, huh?
Do you realize what's happened,
Hikaru? Until now, there were
only two groups of people: "us"
and "everyone else." But for
the first time, someone's
crossed into our world.
Rejoice, Haruhi! You're going
to have an underclassman.
Someone new wants
to join the club.
But he's in
elementary school!
I wonder what he'll
be like all grown up!
Next time, "The Grade-School
Host is the Naughty Type!"
The Ouran Host Club
will be waiting for you!