I'm happy to say you're
daughter's future here
at Oran Academy is
assured. Her test scores
are nothing short of brilliant.
That's the trouble; she's
too smart for her own good.
She insisted on going through
the entire application process
without my help. After she'd
aced the entrance exams,
she even tried to persuade me
not to come with her today.
Can you imagine?
Is that right?
Miss Fujioka. Would you
mind if your father
and I spoke privately?
You're more than welcome
to explore the grounds,
if you like. Of course, most
of the students are gone
for Spring Break, but you might
make some new friends even so.
Go on, sweetheart. Let Daddy
and the nice Dean here
handle all the boring
paperwork for you, okay?
Alright, thanks, Dad.
She's quite an
independent spirit.
Children of her
intelligence often are.
It must be lonesome for you.
I wonder if she'll
enjoy herself here.
A rabbit? But it's stuffed.
Hey! Wait! Hold on a minute!
Haruhi in Wonderland.
I'm okay.
Ow-w-w-w.
Oh, come on.
That isn't fair.
Excuse me.
I got myself kinda
stuck in this thing.
If you wouldn't mind
giving me a hand,
I'd really appreciate-
Hey! Where are you going?
He disappeared!
Wait, please come back!
Where'd that thing come from?
There's got to be some other
way out of here, right?
Unless.
Female?
Banana?
Okay; so now I'm in a pool?
You've cried quite a bit, huh?
You must have, to fill a pool
this size. See, this water
is an accumulation of all the
tears you've shed in life.
It's rather
impressive, actually.
Looks as though you've
been through more
than your fair share
of hardships.
Speaking of which, I'd get
out of there if I were you.
It isn't safe.
What in the world?
What were those things?!
This place is way more
dangerous than I thought.
Hang on; am I back
to my original size?
Not yet. But we can take
care of that for you,
if you're interested.
What are you
talking about?
It won't be cheap, though.
Ah. We have guests.
Yes, hello. Might my
little sister and I have
a bit of mushroom?
Of course. We can settle your
tab at the end of the month.
You know, I think you're
the most shrewd caterpillar
I've ever met.
What kind of stuff are you
always writing down in
that book of yours, huh?
Oh Anything. And Everything.
That's odd. You said
"always" just now, and yet
you and I have never met.
"Always?" Did I?
That's weird, isn't it?
I'm getting smaller.
I'm getting bigger!
I'm sorry, That's not exactly
what I had in mind about
getting back to size.
Hey, look! That little baby's
crawling away all by himself!
It's not any of my business.
Nice going!
You may refer to me as Duchess.
The woman making banana
soup over there is my cook.
And this worthless
lay-about is my cat.
Pretty amazing cat. I've never
seen one smirk like that before
Why do I have to be
the stupid cook?!
It's not fair! I quit!
You're always having fun and
I always have to play
the villain!
Tamaki, you idiot!
So, does this mean
you're the baby's mother?
Are you concerned
for the child?
I'm just glad
he found his way home.
It's the best thing for him.
Being with your mother
is always the best thing.
Well, I'm afraid
I must be off now.
Would you look after him
while I'm gone?
For how long?
I couldn't say. I've been
summoned to appear in court.
Court?
You know she's just pulling
your leg. That doll
doesn't really even belong
to her in the first place.
Hey, what happened to--?
Mr. Cat.
Wait!
Over here.
Pretty neat, huh?
Um, sure.
I can disappear.
And reappear. Anywhere.
That's great.
So, listen, I'm a little
turned around.
Do you mind telling me the
best way to get out of here?
That all depends-
On where it is
you're trying to go.
Home, of course.
Back to where I was before.
I'm afraid leaving here without
an audience with the Queen-
-Is strictly forbidden.
An audience with the Queen?
You might say-
-That the Queen-
-Keeps close tabs-
-On all her subjects.
This is ridiculous. If you
wanna talk, come out
and stand still,
both of you.
Both of us?
What do you mean?
Never mind.
I hope he comes back soon.
'Scuse me.
No room.
Yeah. No room
left, sorry.
There's no --
Room. I got it.
Hey you! Don't just
brush us off like that!
We were only kidding! There's
plenty of room left! See?
Can I ask you guys a
question about this place?
Your hair's pretty
long, huh?
What?
That's actually a rather
good look for you.
Be that as it may, you'll
still have to wear it
much shorter in the
future you know.
And why exactly do you even
care about my hair?
So you're wearing a
skirt today?
Yeah, well, believe it or not,
I am a girl.
Not that matters
either way.
You know, if you keep scarfing
down junk food like that,
you're gonna
get cavities.
Be sure to Brush your teeth
when you're finished.
Okay.
So I guess nose bubbles
do pop.
A riddle!
A riddle?
In what way are lean and
fancy tuna alike?
Aren't they the
same thing?
Incorrect! They're not the same
thing at all! Even in dreams,
commoners are
still commoners.
Hey! Would you like a glass
of red wine?
Sorry. The consumption
of alcohol by minors
is against the law.
I guess getting her to play
Alice was a bit of a stretch.
She's just not feeling the
part. Still, though.
She's kinda cute.
Yes, she is.
It's always
Three O'clock here.
Which means it's always
snack time!
So, then.Where is this
place we're in anyway?
I mean, a little while ago
I was at Ouran Academy
filling out the enrollment
paperwork with my Dad.
Riddle me this. What do
your father and I share
in common now because
of you?
Because of me?
Wait, this is Ouran
Academy, isn't it?
What will you do once
you've enrolled?
After you've enrolled here,
what will you do?
What will I? Study
I suppose--
And What else?
What else?
Yes. Is that all?
Well yeah.
What for?
What?
See, there's something specific
I want to be when I grow up.
That's why I'm enrolling
here at Ouran;
to prepare myself for
a bright future.
That's really sweet.
So what do you want to be
when you grow up?
Well my dream is
to be--
What good are dreams if all
you do is work?
There's more to life
than hitting the books,
I hope you know.
But, I have
to study to do well.
That's all fine, but what
about having a good time.
Having a good time?
Having a good time.
Having a good time!
What was that for?
The Queen is now
holding court.
The Queen?
The Duchess is scheduled
to be executed.
That's an outrage!
One does not fight the
Queen's whim. Trust me.
Well, I can't sit here
and do nothing!
Even when she's dreaming,
Haru-chan is still Haru-chan.
Uh-huh.
Duchess. You stand before us
now, accused of coming to
the royal music festival
by invitation.
Do you confess to
your transgression?
What transgression?
Who disrupts this court?
I do! I'm here as legal
counsel for the accused!
With all due respect, your
Majesty, it is my duty
to attend the royal
music festival!
Even if it means leaving
your precious child alone?
Your crime is not a question
of attendance,
but of abandonment. This act
is unforgivable.
To cause such loneliness in
a child.
Your Majesty, the child
wasn't abandoned.
When a mother has to be away
providing for the family,
her children know that
she's doing it out of love.
Sure, they might get lonely
from time to time,
but they understand! Besides,
if you execute the Duchess,
how is her child any
better off?
Silence yourself, young
lady! There's no room
for your emotions
in this courtroom.
That's impossible!
Passing judgment
without emotion!
You might as well be left up
to a machine!
Astounding insolence. Tell me.
Precisely how long have you
been in the legal profession?
Are you even qualified to
practice law in this court?
Are you not in fact
guilty yourself?
Why don't we discuss
your crime?
What are you
talking about?
I submit one Renaissance
vase, destroyed by you.
That's the vase
from earlier.
But it was definitely in
one piece at the time.
I couldn't have been the one
who broke it.
A likely story, but if not
you, then who's the culprit?
I have no idea. But I'm
telling you it wasn't me!
What the?
Or was it?
Witnesses! Those party to the
crimes of this so-called lawyer
are commanded to come
forward and testify!
It would be my privilege,
Your Majesty.
What are you
doing here?
This girl has what might
be charitably called
a drab approach
to student life.
What?
School work, school work,
school work!
She won't let the slightest
bit of fun offset her routine.
Oh yeah? Well at least I have
a routine, Tamaki-sempai!
What's going on?
Now how is it
you know my name?
My name; how do you know it?
Yes, how is it that you know his
name? However do you know it?
How do I know?
Yeah; and somehow
you knew we were twins.
And about my little black
book, lest we forget.
And about my cavity.
How is that?
Well, I?
Hasn't it sunk in yet?
You've made a lot of wonderful
friends here, Haruhi.
Now haven't you?
Dad, you're the King?
Then does that mean?
Does that mean- It couldn't be.
You've gotten so big.
Where does the time go?
I'm sorry. I made it
so hard for you.
And so. Now is the time to
make up for that Haruhi-
don't be afraid to enjoy
yourself, alright?
Mom.
Haruhi?
Wow. I don't think I've ever
seen you doze off before.
Hurry up and get ready. We have
guests coming any minute now.
You guys have way too much
fun, you know that right?
I have to admit it,
though. Around here,
I can hardly even
tell when I'm awake!
Isn't this exciting, Haruhi?
The Host Club is about to bask
in the warm glow of
full-scale media coverage!
Media coverage? Don't you
just mean the school paper?
Next time: "Covering the
Famous Host Club."
The Ouran Host Club
will be waiting for you!
We'll see you then!