There might be a big,
nasty monster out here.
I'd better hurry up, and try
to find my Big Brother.
My Big Brother is a
strong, handsome prince,
so I'm sure he'd be able to
defeat a monster for me.
Welcome!
Oh my, what an
unusually young guest.
Well, glad you're here,
my little lost kitty-cat.
When I opened the door,
the police were there
waiting for me.
"Big Brother is a Prince"
Little kitty-cat, why have
you come to see us today?
It's a reverse harem!
This is a
reverse harem!
That can't be right.
I must've heard wrong-
maybe there's still some
water in my ear from when
I went swimming.
Water in the ear-
that's gotta be it!
I'm sure we just heard
her wrong. There's no way
this cute, little girl said
the words 'reverse harem'.
Something's going on
with our ears.
There's debauchery here!
Yay! There's debauchery
here, isn't there?!
You're the glasses character!
You're the boy Lolita!
And the stoic type!
Twincest.
And the bookworm!
Big brother?
My brother's blond-
you must be him!
You never told us about this.
Since when do you
have a little sister?
I don't- I'm definitely
an only child-
at least as far
as I know...
The more I look at you
the two of you do look
a lot alike. You are
both blond, after all.
I want to know if 'glasses
character' is superior to
'big brother'.
But does it really matter?
I can't believe she
called me a bookworm.
'Scuse me. You want to tell
me your name, little one?
Kirimi.
Kirimi?
Kirimi-chan. I'm afraid
you've made a mistake.
I'm really sorry but, I
don't have a younger sister.
Are you sure?
You're blond just like me.
Well... that is true.
I give in! As of this
moment, I'm your new
big brother! You're
so cute! You're so cute!
I know you get
carried away by emotion,
but don't you think it's
irresponsible to make
such empty promises?
Don't you listen to that mean
Haruhi! I'm not irresponsible!
Come home with me
and I'll look after you.
What do you think
we should do Kyoya-senpai?
We should probably try
to find out if she actually
has a brother
at this school.
Kirimi. Kirimi.
Hey, uh, who the hell are you?
He's looks like
a foreigner!
What's up
with that?
How come the door looks
different all of a sudden?
Oh, Kirimi.
Master.
You forgot your cloak.
Nekozawa-senpai?
Master Umehito is terribly
vulnerable to any kind
of bright light.
For that reason, if he doesn't
shroud himself in black,
he will fall victim to
the brightness of the
outside world and will
undoubtedly collapse.
And just to be comfortable,
he even has to cover
his beautiful blond hair
with a dark wig.
On the other hand,
his sister, Mistress Kirimi,
is frightened of dark,
dimly-lit places.
So this little girl
is Nekozawa-senpai's
younger sister?
You are quite insightful.
Yes, that would be correct, sir.
Kirimi, so this is where
you've been hiding.
Brother, save me
from the monster!
Please don't be scared.
I'd like to introduce you
to someone.
This is Belzenef. The
Nekozawa family has
worshipped cats
for generations.
You know, I get the feeling
she's not scared of the puppet.
Call me crazy but
I think it's, you.
It's probably your clothes.
We'll help you change, 'K?
Don't do that! It's far
too bright! I may die!
I know! Why don't we
just darken the room?
Don't do that!
I'm afraid of the dark!
Don't worry, little one.
So either way,
someone's unhappy.
It's a tragedy that
these two siblings
are such polar opposites.
As a result they have
come to be known as
the Nekohzawa family's
Romeo and Juliet.
But Romeo and Juliet
weren't brother and sister.
I think their situation
was a little different.
Oh, I'm well aware of that.
To be honest it's something
I just came up with on the
fly- pretty impressive, huh?
I thought it might make
the story more dramatic.
Oh, I see.
We were sent by the Master's
family to get our beloved
Mistress Kirimi
back home safely.
Is the rest of the family-
-as out of touch
as the three of you are?
How dare you say
such a terrible thing?!
The Nekozawas are
a distinguished family-
they're descendents of the
Tokarev dynasty of Russia!
Tokarev, huh?
Wait, you mean
Romanov, right?
There's a legend that says
once every few hundred years
a Nekozawa child is born.
A child who is destined
to be possessed by the
darkness, exactly like
our Master Umehito.
That legend may
or may not be true.
What do you mean
it may or may not be true?
Is it or isn't it?
Mistress Kirimi fell in
love with the handsome,
fairy tale prince of an
older brother she had seen
in portraits. However, as
a result of his condition,
the master is unable to go
near his sister without being
shrouded in black.
Once she learned that her
older brother was enrolled
in the high school here, she
decided to go looking for him.
That's what brought her
to your Host Club.
We've tried to keep her
comforted by reading her
bedtime stories about princely
characters like her brother.
But we ran out of stories. So
recently we decided to start
reading her shojo manga
that had princely
characters in them.
And I'm afraid she's
become completely addicted!
Shojo manga?
There's debauchery here!
Yay! There's debauchery
here, isn't there!
I see, so that's
where that came from...
Is there really
debauchery in shojo manga?
But Sashimi-chan's so young.
Not Sashimi!
It's "Kirimi"!
So Kirimi-chan doesn't
know that you're her
real older brother,
Nekozawa-senpai?
Yes. We've talked to her but
she refuses to believe us.
That's so sad.Well, no wonder
Neko-chan is so upset!
It's painful. That's why
every night I offer prayers
in hopes that one day
Kirimi will come to embrace
the darkness.
I think you've got
it backwards, buddy.
You should try to get
accustomed to the light.
What're you trying
to do to your sister?
Come along,
Mistress Kirimi.
It's time to go home.
I'm not going with you!
I don't wanna go home!
I wanna stay
with my Big Brother!
Nekozawa-senpai.
Don't worry about me Suou.
All I want is
for my sister to be happy.
Make sure she gets
the love she deserves!
But wait a minute! Senpai!
Sibling relations are a source
of problems in any family.
Even so, I'm kinda jealous.
I grew up an only child
so I can't really relate.
But I can't imagine how tough
it must be to have a sibling-
-that's so different
from you that you can't
even spend time together.
Is something wrong?
Tell me big brother.
I'm sorry, Kirimi, but I'm not
the big brother that you've
been looking for.
But don't worry,
he's still out there.
Believe it or not, you have a
big brother that's even more
handsome than I am,
and I promise you-
he's a real prince.
But Senpai.
Once she stepped foot in
this room, Kirmi-chan became
a guest of the Host Club.
And-
It's our job to make all
of our guests happy.
It's an absolute tragedy to
see a brother and sister
at odds this way!
We have to do
something to help them!
Starting now, "Operation:
Change Nekohzawa-senpai into
the princely character
of Kirmi-chan's dreams"
is underway!
Are you serious?
But, sir.
You want to change Umehito
from a prince of darkness
to a prince of light? I don't
know if that's even possible.
Senpai. Quit getting carried
away by your emotions!
Don't make promises
you can't keep.
Oh ye of little faith.
Have you forgotten that we
have an expert on our side.
Someone who knows
the importance of
changing characters.
You don't think?
He's talking about-
Yep, sure enough.
Your golden locks
glow in the candlelight.
Your skin like ivory.
Your smile,
mysterious as a flower,
illuminated by the moonlight.
Such beauty. It's as if-
You're a cursed wax doll
shrouded in darkness
and filled with
malevolence!
No way- you've got it
all wrong! You numbskull!
Who told you to say
something like that?!
How many times
do I have to tell you,
you're not allowed to use
any occult terms!
I'm really sorry, but my
vocabulary is a bit limited
without those words.
You're not allowed to talk
back to me either, you got it?
A princely character would
never try to come up
with a sissy excuse
like that!
Remember, it's okay
to have a dark side-
some girls like that.
Cute, brooding male characters
always go over well
with young girls. However,
refferencing anything
related to the occult
is out of the question.
Mori-senpai, go ahead and
add that to the board!
Wax doll.
Looks like Renge is really
on top of things.
Yeah, she's on a roll.
But I'm not sure the
lines she's feeding him
are appropriate to
use on his sister.
You just going to sit
and watch, boss?
Of course! I don't want to
end up with a curse on me!
Okay, it seems that you've
memorized most of your
new character lines. I think
it's about time we moved on.
Are you ready, senpai?
Oh please no!! It's too soon.
I can't handle it yet!
Evil beam!
Don't let a simple flashlight
get the best of you!
Work up your nerve! It's not
physically affecting you,
so that means it must be
psychological. Even Edgar
was able to face the cross
once he built up his courage.
But I thought
you rejected the occult.
Occult fiction is good.
Occult fashion is not.
Is that so?
Don't judge him.
You're the one who's always
wearing weird cosplay.
You've gotta put
your heart into the
delivery of these lines.
You have to imagine that you're
talking to Kirmi-chan's.
That's easy for you to say,
but that doesn't look
anything like her.
Would you quit complaining?!
Look at her through
the eyes of your heart!
The eyes of your heart!
That's right! Remember
why you're doing this.
It's all for Kirmi-chan's
sake! Just give it a shot.
It'll look like her
if you use your imagination.
Here ya go, boss!
We got this one ready,
just for you.
We think you should go ahead
and confess your love
to this Haruhi doll.
Wait. This doll is Haruhi?
You should teach him
by example!
Haruhi. I--
Yes, Senpai.
Excuse me.
Haruhi! You're the real one!
But when did you get here?!
Kirimi-chan came
to the club room
looking for you again today.
If you've got time to do
disgusting things like this-
Surely you can spare
the time to hang out
with her for a while.
What? Disgusting?!
Why don't you keep her
company Haruhi?
What's wrong-
don't like children?
Well no, it's not that
I don't like them or anything.
Read more, bookworm!
"I have finally made all of
these fine men my love slaves.
Oh, my, who shall I pick
to have entertain me
this evening?"
She's made me read about
50 volumes of shojo manga
to her over the last 3 days.
And to my surprise,
those things really are full of
reverse harems and debauchery.
Big Brother?
This room is dark and scary!
Oh, Kirimi-chan! I asked you to
wait for me in the other room!
What's wrong, little one?
There, there, calm down.
You see? There's nothing
to be afraid of.
Here we go!
Senpai?
I am a handsome, princely big
brother- I am a handsome,
princely big brother- I am a
handsome, princely big brother-
I am a handsome,
princely big brother-
princely big brother!
And I'm not afraid of this
flashlight! Self evil beam!
He did it!
Nekozawa-senpai's
come a long way.
He's able to shine
a flashlight in his own face.
Bravo, senpai! Bravo!
Good job! I'm impressed!
You did it! Your little sister
is going to be so thrilled!
Look there,
Kirmi-chan. That gentleman
is your real big brother.
Big Brother!
Kirimi!
You're just
complicating things.
Could you please cut that out-
it's not gonna help, you know.
Huh? Did you
just say something?
Never mind,
Kirimi.
Kirimi, wait!
So I guess shining the
flashlight in his face-
Scared her and
sent her running.
Oh, Kirimi.
Nekohzawa-senpai.
I've had enough. Even if I
continue your special training,
there's no guarantee that
Kirimi will ever accept me.
I think she'd be better off.
If you acted as her big
brother in my stead, Suou.
But that's ridiculous-
you're the big brother
she's looking for.
If you care about her,
you'll do whatever it takes
to win her over!
Hey look! Kirmi-chan hasn't
made it out of the courtyard!
But there's something
down there with her.
Oh, it's just a cat.
Your family
sure does love cats.
Even strays warm up
to you guys.
What'd you say?!
They're revered by our
family- it's true, but Kirimi
wouldn't participate in
something like that.
Something as occult as
befriending a stray cat.
Kirimi is afraid of animals,
and cats are the creatures
she fears the most.
Kirimi!
Nekozawa-senpai!
But he's not wearing
his black cloak!
Someone help.
Kirimi!
Big Brother!
Would you look at that!
This is all thanks
to my special training.
There's no need
to be afraid, Kirimi.
I promise it won't come
anywhere near you now, alright?
His name is Belzenef, with this
puppet's power, I can--curse.
Nekozawa-senpai.
He probably got more sun
than he ever will again
in that one day.
That may be true, but he
immediately went running
for the darkness again.
Yeah, we should've known.
What a waste.
He's back to wearing all
those black clothes again.
But even so.
Now I know that if
a monster ever appears-
I'll be just fine.
I have a princely
Big Brother who will fight
to protect me, even if
it means dashing out
into the sunlight. The one
thing he fears most of all.
I love sweets!
Be careful, Honey-senpai.
You're gonna end up
with cavaties.
Ow!
See, what did I just tell you?
This is my fault.
Next time,
"Honey's Three Bitter Days!"
The Ouran Host Club
will be waiting for you!
We'll see you then!