Good evening, Tamura.
We can try to hide them,
but they can't be suppressed,
can they?
The strongest signals
that we emit
are those which
harbor animosity.
I know of your intentions.
Get on with it.
Why did you not make
any attempt to escape?
Because I was intrigued.
I fell prey to my curiosity.
Though I must wonder,
are there any others who
support your actions?
No, it's only the three of us.
Hirokawa and Goto know nothing
about what we're planning.
[TAMURA] I see.
And your reason?
Call it an instinct.
I believe that, going forward,
you will prove to be an
extremely dangerous
liability for us.
Very well, then.
You remind me a lot of Mr. A.
Mr. A?
We parasites have a tendency
to think and operate
in a manner that is normally
quite logical and
uncomplicated.
I thought that temperament
would make it easy to create
a united organization,
but I was mistaken.
Still, for the parasites,
myself included,
to have such
individual differences ‐
or rather, such personalities ‐
makes me very pleased.
I'm actually moved by your
decision to eliminate me.
Well then,
shall we get started?
With only three of you,
I hope you have some sort
of plan in place.
(huh?)
Stop her! Kill her!
(sounds of parasites fighting)
(hmm?)
The muscle strength of my host
is superior to yours.
Therefore, even in single
combat, I would win.
You seem so certain.
Too slow...
Huh?
(ungh!)
You can keep that.
(maniacal laughter)
What is she thinking,
splitting in two?
I'll go after her.
(waah!)
Tamura entered his body.
Are... Are you okay?
Yeah.
(maniacal laughter)
[BOTH] (huh?)
(aahhh!)
[TAMURA] (maniacl laughter)
(dog howling &amp; barking)
[WOMAN] (nervous whimpering)
Right there, that's her!
Uh, excuse me!
Huh?
[BOTH] (gasps)
(sighs of relief)
Why are you putting rocks
in your bag?
[TAMURA]
It's dangerous out here.
(nervous chuckle)
Did you just see...
We saw the weirdest thing
back there.
We saw a lady just now who
looked like she only had half
her head, and she was, uh...
she was running around laughing
and it was crazy.
Just half of her head?
Oh dear, how strange..
I still...
I still have my head,
but it's empty inside!
See?
[MAN &amp; WOMAN] (gibbering)
[TAMURA] (maniacal laughter)
She's lost her purpose,
and can no longer
think rationally.
There's no way half a parasite
can maintain control of
the host body.
It's suicide.
Such a waste.
For one so famed
for her intellect,
how sad for her to
die this way.
[MAESAWA] (ungh) (waah)
My legs...
I can't feel my legs!
[MAESAWA] (kyaa!)
[HIKAWA] (gasps)
[MAESAWA] (gibbering)
What is this?!
[MAESAWA] It's not me! Not ME!
(arrrggghhh)
[HIKAWA] (ungh!)
One of us is dead.
[TAMURA] (evil chuckle)
[HIKAWA] (gasping in pain)
[KUSANO] Ah, you can survive
by burrowing inside.
But now, can you really take
over completely when you're
split in two?
Will you be able to defeat me
using a body that's so
badly damaged?
(urk) Stop it! This is MY body!
Stop it! NO!!
[KUSANO]
Who am I even talking to now?
Is it Hikawa?
Or is it Reiko Tamura?
[HIKAWA] Please stop!
I'm on your side! It's me!
Really, then why are you
moving toward me?
[HIKAWA] Dammit! I can't control
anything below my neck!
[KUSANO] Just give in.
And die along with that
fragment of Reiko Tamura!
But I am on your side!
(ungh!) (urk!) (aahhh!)
[HIKAWA] (dying)
What have you done?
[KUSANO]
Is this really your strategy?
The body you attempted to
take over now lies in shreds.
Just, come out!
How long do you plan to
keep hiding in there?
(huh?!)
(urk!) (gasping for breath)
The human part of our body
is our weakness.
You should make your strike
without all the grandstanding.
[KUSANO] (bleh! bleh!)
[TAMURA] (laughs)
[TAMURA] Even if the host body
is destroyed,
our parasite cells survive
for a short time on their own
and emit brainwaves.
You're obviously experiencing
this phenomenon right now.
The strongest wavelengths
we parasites emit
are animosity and
murderous intent,
as you're well aware.
The ability to detect these
is quite important.
It's how we determine whether
an individual who's outside
our range of vision
is friend or foe.
But you cut your own ally
into pieces,
thereby surrounding yourself
with fragments of her flesh,
all of which continue to
emanate her signal.
[KUSANOU] (nnggghh...)
[TAMURA] That's right.
All those fragments were
acting as camouflage,
masking my transmissions
as I approached you.
[KUSANO] (urrrggg...)
Goddamn you, that's impossible!
Do you know where you came from,
[KUSANO] (dying gurgles)
and where it is you're
ultimately headed?
Have you ever pondered
about such things,
as a human being might do?
(dying gurgles)
[TAMURA] Goodbye, Kusano.
[TAMURA] Hmm... cannibalism...
Hmm? It's unlocked.
You are more troublesome than
I thought, Mr. Detective.
(mouse clickling)
[SHINICHI] Huh? He left?
Well, when did he
leave the hotel?
(mouse clickling)
(phone ringing)
[SHINICHI] Dad,
what are you doing at home?!
[TAMURA]
I'm afraid he hasn't been here.
(huh?)
Why the hell are you there?!
[TAMURA] Good morning.
[SHINICHI] (on phone) I take it
you're there to kill him.
[TAMURA] (soft laugh)
As a matter of fact,
it's quite the contrary.
[TAMURA] (on phone) I was hoping
to contact YOU regarding
a personal matter.
You know where
Hikari Park Number One is?
(mouse clicking)
It's very important that you
meet me there this afternoon,
at 5:20 PM.
[SHINICHI] (on phone)
What are you talking about?
I need to give you something.
Seeing as how you're something
in‐between human and parasite,
it's perfect for you.
A mother...
It's not right!
Something's very wrong!
Who are you? Ryoko!
Where is my Ryoko?!
(doorbell chiming)
No one's home today, either.
I wonder if
something's happened?
(huh?) Uh, hey! Um, Ms. Izumi?
Where is...
Where is Shinichi?
Sorry, he isn't here.
I see...
So, are you, uh,
Shinichi's mother?
I'm not.
Do I really look
that old to you?
Uh, no.
But please tell me.
Do you know what's going on?
Shinichi...
He's caught up in
something bad, isn't he?
What do you mean by bad?
Well, I, uh...
I can tell that something
is definitely messed up.
Shinichi would never say
anything about it, but still...
You're worried, aren't you?
Worried about him?
I'm quite jealous.
Huh?
Don't trouble yourself.
Shinichi's actually much
stronger than he looks.
And he'll be back home
very soon, perfectly fine.
But when is "soon"?
(uh!)
Where have I seen her before?
[YUKO] Seriously though,
where did Shinichi run off to?
It's just weird.
[AKIHO] I swear.
Doesn't he know how worried
we are about him?
[SATOMI] He'll be back, soon.
It could even be today.
You... you will...
come back, right?
[SATOMI] He'll be back.
Hey!
It's okay.
You don't have to worry, Murano.
He will...
He has to!
[SATOMI] (gasps)
What's wrong?
[AKIHO] Where you going?
[SATOMI] Sorry!
Go ahead without me!
[SATOMI] I think this is...
this is where Kana lived.
I wonder if she knew...
the Shinichi that I don't.
(gasps)
[SATOMI] No, please wait!
(panting)
What the...
How is that girl so damn fast?!
[MAN] Hey!
[SATOMI] (gasps!)
Goodness, young lady.
A nice, young girl like you
shouldn't resort to using
such foul language.
Uh...
[HIRAMA] Hmm?
[MITA] What's this?
(birds cawing)
[KURAMORI]
Ah, there, there, there.
Hey, little fella...
[TAMURA]
You're good with children.
Well, my wife was the only one
with a job there for
quite a while.
So I spent lots of time
with my little girl.
[BABY] (fussing)
Aw, you're okay, you're okay.
[SHINICHI] I guess I must've
gotten here too early.
[MIGI]
Then walk around a little bit.
I'd like to get a layout
of the terrain.
Sure.
[KURAMORI]
Even a cold‐blooded monster
still values her child.
I've been doing some extensive
research on you humans.
And on some level,
I'm able to comprehend your
rather irrational behavior.
Really?
Well, I guess that's good.
But you know, you'll never fully
understand, right?
You don't know what
it means to be human.
How it really feels
to be a parent!
How could you possibly grasp
the depth of the sadness
that comes with
losing everything?
Everything that's ever mattered
to you in your entire life?!
You can't do it!
Because I could kill this
innocent child right
here and now,
and you wouldn't even so much
as bat an eye, would you?
You'd just move on
like nothing happened!
And you know it!
This baby can't really
be yours anyway.
This baby's human.
[MIGI] What is this?
I've never felt this sort of
signal from one of my kind.
It's Reiko Tamura's brainwave,
but...
What is this emotion?
[KURAMORI]
You could never love it.
You're completely
cold and dead inside.
If I could just make you feel
even one tiny shred
of the grief I've had to
suffer through, then...
(urk!)
(ungh...)
I... I wouldn't do it.
I would never...
No human could ever kill
a helpless child.
You... you don't...
I didn't think...
I didn't think
a monster like you...
(weak chuckle)
Th‐that was a sur‐surprise.
(ungh...)
(wet splat)
Yes, I'm rather
surprised myself.
[MIGI] Reiko Tamura has
started moving.
She's headed for the corner
on the opposite side.
So, over this way?
What am I even doing here?
I can't believe
I came all this way.
(brakes squealing)
[WOMAN] (screams)
[HIRAMA] (huh?!)
[WOMAN] (sobbing hysterically)
There's a... There's a man!
He's over there!
(running footsteps)
[HIRAMA] Kuramori!
Are you okay?
Are you able to talk to me?!
(weak moans)
Ah, hey there, Detective...
Where are they?!
Are they up on the hill?!
Just go! And if you spot one
of them, do not hesitate!
[DETECTIVES] Yes, sir!
(running footsteps)
Was it Reiko Tamura?!
Did she do this?
Does Hirokawa know
what she's up to?!
There's a... a woman...
She's dressed in white...
She's holding...
And she's holding a little baby.
And there's some blood...
My... my blood got
on the baby's clothes.
[HIRAMA] Right!
We won't let her get away!
There's one more thing
I need to know.
You mentioned you had
a "partner" in your report.
Is he a human?
What's his name?
Please, you gotta tell me!
[KURAMORI] He is... human...
Like me, he had a small family,
and it was taken from him.
He too...
He also s‐suffers...
(ragged breath)
Talk to me!
Tell me who he is!
(soft chuckle) Yoko... Yumi...
I'm coming home.
I'll see you soon....
[HIRAMA] Kuramori!
Stay with me, buddy! Come on!
I... I would never...
I wouldn't do it...
The baby...
No! Stay with me!
Kuramori, please!
You were an honorable man...
one of the greatest of heroes.
And I swear you will NOT
have died in vain,
Detective!
I understand!
White clothes, holding a baby.
(screams)
Don't move!
What's your name?
Answer me, now!
[HIRAMA] I just pray that
Hirokawa's group
hasn't found out about
what we're planning.
We cannot let
Reiko Tamura get away.
We have to finish her off.
Now!
[SHINICHI]
Next time:
"More Than Human"