(gasps)
Mitsuo?
[MITSUO] What's his problem?
Ah...
(grr...)
Hey, don't!
[MITSUO] Shut up!
If I wanna fight this jackass,
it's none of your damn business.
Shimada?
Huh? (ack!)
[SHIMADA] I went easy on you
this time because I'd prefer
to avoid trouble.
However, if you decide to
show up again and pick a fight
with me for no reason...
I'll end you.
(gasps)
(huh?)
(gasps) Yes!
[SATOMI] Shinichi?
[SHINICHI] (huh?)
You... are Shinichi Izumi,
aren't you?
[SHINICHI] Huh?
I, uh...
Oh, sorry!
My mistake, I'm sorry.
Uh! What?! Yeah, that's me!
Who... who're you?
I'm Satomi? Satomi Murano?
We both took our entrance exams
in the same room.
Oh, sorry, that's right!
I was so nervous that day
I didn't notice anything else.
Well, I'll see you
in April then.
Maybe we'll be in
the same class!
Yeah, maybe so.
(footsteps)
(huh?)
[SHIMADA] His parasite's
"signal" is weak again.
I wonder why?
Is it sleeping?
Perhaps if I emit
a signal of my own,
it should respond reflexively.
Especially, to murderous intent!
(sudden flight of birds)
Interesting...
[AKIHO] Mm, mm, mm, that Hide.
He's kinduv a hottie, huh?
[YUKO] (huh?)
[YUKO]
Oh! I, uh, don't really, um‐
Oh, c'mon,
don't even try to hide it.
I know you drew his face
in your sketchbook, Yuko.
[YUKO] (ah!)
Akiho, that is mine!
[AKIHO] (ah!)
I mean,
he's super cool, isn't he?
I think we have a new
hottest guy in school.
I bet he's a model.
Do you think he's a model?
S'like he's not real.
Like he's fake or something.
[YUKO] (huh)
Oh, Yuko, do me a favor.
Draw a picture of him
for me, too.
Ha! Thanks! (giggles)
[YUKO] "Fake"?
Why? What do you mean
I can't tell anyone?
In this situation, our greatest
fear is that we would cause
wide‐spread panic
due to a lack of
credible information.
When people stop
trusting one another,
it inevitably leads to
discrimination and fear.
And soon after that...
misinformation and
mass hysteria will follow.
That's my son, Shinichi.
Uh, hello there. How are you?
[GOV MAN]
In any case, we still have no
way to distinguish them from us.
And given that, there's simply
nothing to be gained by going
public at this time.
We are truly sorry about
the loss of your wife.
Nevertheless, to be blunt
about the current state
of things,
this is a problematic situation
of having a few thousand
violently dangerous killers
roaming around the country.
[AIDE] Please, take a look.
Yes... That's exactly what
the thing looked like.
So, it's able to morph into
just about anything it wants.
[TAMURA] It seems the rumors
have become widespread.
[HIROKAWA] It appears so.
[TAMURA] That outcome could have
easily been foreseen.
But if we continue this practice
of preying on them like
mindless insects,
we will all eventually be hunted
down and completely wiped out.
Our species is truly weak...
Our imperfections are troubling.
[HIROKAWA] It's hardly
surprising that you would have
pondered over and
worried about such things.
[TAMURA]
I only have one question.
I want to find out
the real reason.
Why is it we parasites
even exist?
[HIROKAWA] The answer to
that is quite simple.
The human race has now become
toxic to the planet Earth,
which has created
a need for balance.
So what you're saying is
this thing I'm currently
nurturing within me
is a poison?
(door opening)
So I guess they left, huh, Dad?
"Mass hysteria..."
[SHINICHI] (huh?)
[IZUMI]
I need to tell you... the truth.
It's about...
It's about your mother, Son.
[SHINICHI] I sat there quietly
and listened.
I nodded as my father spoke.
And told him nothing
about what I knew.
Then, finally...
Dad told me outright
for the very first time.
That Mom...
was dead.
We've asked Professor Bigg
Mouth for his opinion on
when to brush your teeth.
Morning or at night!
(audience laughter)
Professor Bigg Mouth,
please stop that!
(beep)
Aww, he's asleep again!
Hmm?
What is this?
That's just nasty.
(huh?) Ah! Gimme that!
It's part of an investigation.
Oh, is that what your suspect
looks like this time?
[HARUKI] How could THIS possibly
be a suspect? It's a monster!
Anyway, what's going on, Yuko?
Do you need something?
Yeah...
Could you take a look at
something for me?
This your friend?
That's pretty nice work.
You're getting better
and better at this.
[YUKO]
So, do you sense anything?
[HARUKI] (hmm...)
Like, his personality or
like his attitude?
Since you draw faces
for a living,
I just thought maybe you
could tell me about him.
Come on, Yuko.
It doesn't really
work like that, y'know.
Oh, 'kay.
(baseball game sounds)
(gasps)
He's alone again today.
Is he waiting for someone?
Or maybe he's
watching someone...
(bat hitting ball)
[PLAYER] Hey! Look out!
(gasps)
[PLAYER] Hey, buddy!
Dude, are you all right?
Yes.
(whimpers)
I... I don't believe what I...
what I just saw.
Man, I really have to patch
things up with Murano today.
Murano!
[SHINICHI]
About the other day,
that was...
that was nothing serious.
That girl was just...
she was... making fun of me.
So, I mean... (huh?)
[MIGI] Shinichi...
[SHINICHI] Jesus, Migi.
Now's not the time!
[SATOMI] Uh...
[MIGI] I sense Hideo Shimada
projecting murderous intent.
I believe I made myself clear,
but if you insist.
I'm sure that you'll agree,
we should find somewhere away
from prying eyes.
[MIGI]
He has four to six targets.
Most likely all human.
The probability that this
will turn into a massacre
is quite high.
Shinichi?
[MIGI] If you wish to intervene,
I can give you their location.
What would you like to do?
[SHINICHI]
What choice do I have?
[SATOMI] (gasps)
Shinichi?!
[THUG] Man, I don't think
I've ever met a guy so eager
to get pounded.
Hmpf! Maybe he doesn't really
understand how much trouble
he's actually in here.
Listen up, nobody touches him.
I'M takin' him down.
It's okay.
You can all attack together.
[ALL] (huh?)
[SHIMADA] I'm afraid a
distraction is on his way here.
If you want to do this,
do it now.
(running footsteps)
They're right over there.
(umphf)
[BOTH] (huh?)
This guy again?!
[SHIMADA]
He just jumped three meters.
Is his parasite empowering him?
That doesn't make sense.
So, Shimada! It looks like
you've finally shown
what you really are!
Let me guess...
This means that you
want to fight me then.
Look, I didn't ask to be
involved with any of this.
Turns out, I'm the victim here.
Aren't I?
[SHINICHI] You should go.
I'll take care of things
around here.
[SHIMADA] Oh? Well,
I'll leave it to you then.
(urk)
[THUGS] (huh?)
[MITSUO] You frickin' serious?
You're just gonna run away?
(hmph) Well now,
aren't you the big hero?
Pretty nice of you to get your
ass kicked for you buddy!
My "buddy"?
You idiots have no idea
what you're getting into.
So, why don't you just go home?
And don't ever
go after that guy again.
I'm talkin' to you.
[SHINICHI] You are the leader of
all these guys, aren't you?
[THUGS] (huh?)
[MITSUO] What the...
How did he know that?
There's no way he's
ever met Yano before.
Heh, what'cha looking at,
pretty boy? (hyah!)
(huh?! aahh...)
[SHINICHI]
Morons without a clue shouldn't
be mouthing off like that.
If they won't listen to reason,
then I'll have to try
something else.
(ungh...)
[YANO] Let's go!
Uh, Yano?
Hey, dude, where ya going?
He'd kill me.
If we fought, he'd kill me.
(grr...)
(footsteps)
Murano...
[SATOMI] Here.
Thank you.
(waahhh!)
What is it?
I was curious about what
happened to those males.
That doesn't concern
you anymore.
Did you use your new friend?
I imagine you beat them all
senseless, didn't you?
(soft gasp)
[SHINICHI] I did no such thing!
Look! Just go!
(grr...)
[SATOMI] Ow!
[SHINICHI] Oh! Sorry!
[SATOMI] Um, did something
happen between you and Shimada?
Can't stand that smug bastard!
He tries to act like
he's all harmless,
but he is full of shit!
[SATOMI] Shinichi...
You're acting different again.
And you've never been the type
of person to talk like that.
It's just not right.
"Not right"? What d'you mean?
[SATOMI] Well, it's like...
The Shinichi I know just isn't
this kind of person.
When you act like this,
it feels like you're forcing it.
Yeah, well, I'm not, okay?
Either way, you're a completely
different person than
the one I knew.
You have changed.
I guess that maybe I have.
But still, I'm not forcing it.
So who is it
you're trying to be?
You just snap your fingers
and change who you are?!
Are you...
Are you still...
Shinichi?
SHUT UP! (echoes)
Fine then...
I liked you better before.
(running water)
It's because of the hole
in my chest, isn't it?
[MIGI] Or the hole in your back,
depending on your perspective.
In my opinion, however,
you've actually grown
stronger as a life form,
if not so as a person.
You're able to maintain
your composure.
You recover quickly
from sways in mood,
and your thoughts
are quite logical.
When viewed by others, it's no
wonder they would perceive
that you've changed.
Migi, you don't even know
what you're talking about.
[MIGI] In any case, this mental
resilience is a definite
plus for you.
Is this supposed to be
your attempt at trying
to cheer me up?
[MIGI] Perhaps.
But if need be,
I will consider alternative
ways to improve your psyche.
[SHINICHI]
Well, how very nice of you.
I know what I saw...
It was real.
(gasps) He changed clothes.
Where's he going?
(whimpers)
Oh, my God, his face...
[YUKO] How can he do that?
He can turn into someone else?
That's impossible!
That's like...
(gasps)
No... It can't be!
(audience laughter)
(door opening)
[YUKO] I'm home.
Oh, hey there, Yuko.
Are you still in
your school clothes?
I need to ask you something.
[HARUKI] The truth is,
we don't have a clue what
these things really are.
Some of the theories are that
they could be aliens,
or mutants, or even bio‐weapons.
But there's one thing you do
know for sure, right?
That they can
change their faces.
[HARUKI] Yeah, that's what
the witnesses all say.
Also, these things can
speak our language,
and they kill people for food.
[YUKO] (gasps)
Do me a favor, be extra
careful if you're out
walking at night.
Now granted, their numbers are
relatively low compared to
the whole human race,
so it's pretty doubtful
you'll even run into one,
but, y'know.
Yeah, I guess so.
(nervous chuckle)
[HARUKI] (sighs)
If only we could just catch
one of these things alive.
[YUKO] Killing people for food?
Is that what Shimada's doing?
I should tell my brother.
But what if it turns out
I'm wrong about him?
Okay...
I'll just have to ask you
myself, Shimada.
Hmm...
These aren't gonna work.
(sighs)
Perfect!
[SHIMADA] So, what did you
want to talk to me about?
[YUKO] I'm not sure
if you know who I am,
but I've kinda had my eye on you
since you got here.
I watch you all the time.
And that's how, well...
I saw you.
[YUKO] Now I don't wanna believe
you're from another world
or anything,
but there are some
crazy rumors out there.
If you really, do, um...
kill people... and...
and eat them...
Yuko...
[YUKO] If... If you do...
then I'm asking you to go away.
And don't ever...
come back here again.
I... I mean it!
I don't want anyone else
to get hurt!
Have you told anyone else
about this?
Tell me!
Do you really do all those
horrible things to people,
Shimada?
[TEACHER] So you see, modern
and classical Japanese are
actually quite different.
You have to learn the rhythm
of the verbs in order to...
[MIGI] Shinichi...
Not good...
Not at all.
(gasps)
No...
Shimada!
(terrifed whimpering)
[SHINICHI] THAT SON OF A BITCH!
[SHINICHI]
Next time:
"What Mad Universe"