[A]
Was that meant as some
sort of barricade...?
The only thing you've
accomplished is to
block off your escape.
Surrender now...
Without complete control
of that body,
there's no way to defeat me.
[A]
Aside from your
right hand,
the rest of your
body is useless,
afraid of pain.
A‐ahh...
If you allow yourself to become
flustered during the battle
it will only hold me back.
And we will lose.
That's what he's doing.
He's trying to get in my head
and throw me off.
Ahh!
Migi...
I can't...
I cannot be afraid.
They're so fast I can't even
see what's happening.
How can I do this?
[MIGI]
We delegate our roles.
I will act as if I'm attacking,
but I will actually be
focused on defense...
That will allow me to protect
you from his assault.
But if you're focused on
defense, who will attack?
Shinichi...
I'm attacking!?
An analysis of Mr. A's
actions thus far
has led me to believe he
underestimates human ability.
He will naturally
be wary of me,
but he has given
no consideration whatsoever
as to your capabilities.
That is his weakness.
I will be on defense,
and you will be on offense.
It's the most effective way
for us to achieve success.
[Blades clashing]
[SHINICHI]
Approach him gradually...
move very slowly...
Very slowly...
Trust Migi...
He will protect you.
Uuh...
[MIGI]
That's right, Shinichi.
We will do what
Mr. A cannot...
We will share roles.
[SHINICHI]
It's like Migi said...
This guy doesn't think
I can do anything.
Well I can...
And I'm gonna do it.
He's still...
he's still a human
from the neck down...
If I don't do this...
he will kill us.
Uh‐ugh...
Uh! Ahh!
Uh!
Aaah!
Uh... urgh...
I don't understand this.
[Grunting]
We did it.
That much blood loss
will be fatal.
Impossible...
How could a feeble little human
runt find a way to attack me?
Uh... Ah!
Hold on. Let's wait and
see what he does next.
[Grunt]
[Gurgling sounds]
His behavior seems
quite erratic.
[A]
He punctured an artery
quite close to the heart...
I must stop the bleeding...
Err... Gah!
Ah!
I understand...
Pushing it all the way through
has closed off the wound.
[Crashing sound]
Ah!
[Struggling]
All right. Let's follow him...
We need to finish him off.
Ah! No...!
We've already done enough!
It's not a good strategy
to let him go.
Look, if we go
after him and do it,
then that'll officially
make me a murderer!
Uh... Hmm?
That's not a person, Shinichi.
[A]
I'm going to be killed by a...
by a human...?
That doesn't make any sense.
[Labored breathing]
This isn't working.
My host is inoperable.
I must relocate.
If that's even an option now...
Yes. Ryoko Tamiya!
I will share her host.
Where is she?
[Crowd chatters]
[Police sirens]
[AKIHO]
Huh? Hey! The police are here!
[Labored breathing]
[A]
Five more meters...
Hm...
[Gas leaking]
Huh?
[Explosion]
Uh?!
[Sirens]
[IZUMI]
Hmm...
How's Shinichi?
[NOBUKO]
I dunno.
He hasn't gotten
out of bed yet.
Sigh...
Well, I'm just
glad he's okay.
Hm...
[SHINICHI]
I can still feel what it was
like when I stabbed him.
It really wasn't that long
before things settled
back down again...
And classes at our
school resumed.
Funny how quickly
people forget.
Ms. Tamiya must have
killed Mr. A...
But she's still teaching
as if nothing happened.
I haven't heard about any
murders being reported
in her area...
but I'm sure she's out
there killing nonetheless.
I can't sit back and
let this happen.
[PRINCIPAL]
Yes, well, um... Ms. Tamiya.
Ahem. You see, the fact
that you have become,
uh, pregnant is certainly
just cause for celebration.
I mean uh, congratulations.
...however‐
You don't even know
who's it is!
The fact that you
are unmarried and
refuse to reveal
the father's identity
is most unsettling.
It's because you can't reveal
who the father is...
not that you don't know
who it is, right?
I didn't expect this...
I had never imagined that
our time together was
going to end this way.
[Gasps]
Huh?!
I cannot afford to
attract attention over
something like this...
I think Ryoko Tamiya's
days are done.
U‐uh...
Ms. Tamiya, wait! Please...
[SHINICHI]
We should kill Ryoko Tamiya.
[MIGI]
We can't win...
Well, isn't not likely.
Also, the child that's
growing within her
is undeniably a human...
Would you be able to
kill her baby as well?
Shinichi?
[Ryoko]
Ryoko Tamiya no longer exists...
Thus, all those in her circle...
and that includes
you, too...
Now have no particular
reason to be kept alive.
Why do you keep
killing people?
My hand lives off
the nutrients in
my bloodstream...
It survives on a diet
of normal human food.
That means the rest of you...
The rest of you can
sustain yourselves
without eating people.
Hmm... It could
indeed be possible.
Well, all right then!
A fly knows
how to fly
without ever being
taught to do so.
Huh?
Just as every spider
knows how to spin a web
and every fish can swim...
Why is that?
Mm... Well, I uh...
Here's what I think.
I believe that
flies and spiders
are simply following
a directive.
In fact it's my belief that
every single life on this planet
lives by a directive
of some sort.
What are you talking about...?
Do you get this?
[RYOKO]
So then, you feel humans
have no directive?
Uh! I still don't know
what you mean...!
Like God or something?
Huh?
When I first took control
of this human host...
I instantly received
a directive.
To devour your entire
species... Now...
Gah!
Look. Just please
answer me one thing.
What is it you plan to do...
with your baby?
Give birth to it.
[Sigh]
Possibly use it for
some experimentation.
Arrg...
If it proves useless,
it's food.
Uh! Ahrr...
[MIGI]
Calm down, Shinichi.
This distance is not optimal.
You've become something
of a nuisance...
Goodbye.
Uh... Oh shit!
[MIGI]
She has more than
two morph patterns.
Not good.
Ah...
[Nervous breathing]
Interesting...
It would appear you two
are conjoined.
Uh...
Ever so slightly.
I won't be killing
you after all.
H‐hey, hang on!
Uh...
Wha...
[Doorbell]
[Door unlocks]
Ah...
Oh, Ryoko!
What on Earth's going on?
I got a phone call from
the school, so I rushed over
as soon as I could.
Ryoko Tamiya's mother.
I'm sorry, but I was
actually just about
to leave...
Could we perhaps talk
about this later, Mother?
Ryoko...
I'm not going far,
I'll be back soon.
[Mother]
Wait. Please.
I need you to look at me.
Uh...
Please, dear...
I need you to talk to me.
Huh...
It's not right...
Something's very wrong!
Who are you?!
Ryoko?!
Where's my Ryoko?!
Tell me!
Wh‐what did you do
with my daughter?!
No, no!
I'm calling the police!
Ahh!
[RYOKO]
She saw through me so quickly.
My face and my voice
should be a near‐perfect
match to Ryoko Tamiya.
Strange...
I doubt this woman
had any special sensory
abilities or anything.
[Birds chirping]
Uh... Mm...
Uhh...
Migi?
Hmm...
[SHINICHI]
WAAHH!
Oh...
Huh...
Uh? Ah! Aahh!
Uh? Ah!
Please don't
frighten me like that.
What?!
Frighten you?!
You okay?!
Why were you yelling?
Ah! Uh, it was a dream!
A bad dream!
Uh, it was really, really bad!
Oh...
Just go and wash up alright.
What are you doing?!
It seems to be three
minutes is the limit,
the longest I can
be separated.
So, what, you went on
a little morning walk?
No, not a walk.
But a movement analysis.
Wait, movement...?
Hey! You're not testing
to see how to move up to
my head are ya?
I already told you,
that's not possible.
I matured without
eating a brain,
therefore I would not
know how to control
an entire body.
But still, perhaps
I should give it a try.
Ah! Quit screwin' around!
Hm? Wait a second...
So, then does that mean
the ones who've managed
to take over a brain
can move from
one head to another?
In theory, yes.
But there's always
the possibility
of rejection,
so swapping heads
would be quite
dangerous.
I really doubt anyone
would risk it.
Oh...
[SHINICHI]
A trip?
Uh‐huh. Looks like I can
finally take some time off.
So, we'd like you to keep
an eye on the house.
The way your father
is always working,
we haven't had a chance to go
on a vacation in a long time.
You don't...
think it's risky?
You mean, because of
the Mincemeat Murders?
Looks like those have
finally stopped.
It's nothing to worry
about anymore.
But that doesn't mean the
killer's not out there!
Dad, how can you just go off
to some strange place,
it's dangerous.
[NOBUKO]
So, you're against it?
Mm...
Huh?
I am...
Hey, don't tell me
my big, old boy
is going to be lonely
without his mom and dad.
No no! Y'know it's just
that they're not gonna...
Who the hell is "they"?
Ah... I, uh...
Look Shinichi...
If you really feel that
strongly about it,
then we can
cancel our trip.
Aw, come on, Baby.
Sweetie...
I've noticed that something's
been bothering you
for a while...
Is there something
on your mind
that you'd like to
talk to us about?
No. There's nothing to
worry about, I'm fine.
[NOBUKO]
Is it one of your friends?
Or maybe...
I said it's nothing okay!
I'm going out for bit.
[Door opens and closes]
Hmm.
[MIGI]
Shinichi...
There's something
we need to make clear.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
If I ever told my parents the
truth about what's happened...
there's no telling
what Migi might do.
The only reason
he tries to protect me...
is because I'm his lifeline...
But my parents are a
different story all together.
He'd eliminate them
without any hesitation.
Migi has no concept of
affection or love...
All said and done,
there's really no difference
between him and
Mr. A or Ryoko Tamiya.
I know that boy is
hiding something from us.
Well of course he is...
Shinichi is a senior now...
I mean it's only natural
that he keeps a few secrets
from his parents, right?
If anything, he's probably been
a little too good up until now.
He hasn't even really gone
through some rebellious phase
and told us how he hated us yet.
Well, if you
really think so...
Hmm...
You know hon, he might be...
he might be having some more
guilt about your scar.
Huh?
You really think so?
I mean, that happened
such a long time ago...
[YOUNG SHINICHI]
Mommy, can I have
a silver plate?
A silver plate?
Yeah, it's for an experiment
in science class tomorrow.
Oh! By "silver," you mean an
aluminum foil plate, I see.
Uh‐huh! That's it!
Sure, of course...
But they're up there
on the top,
and I'm making
tempura right now,
so you'll just
have to wait until‐
I can get it!
Mhmm...
[Stool shaking]
Uhh... Ahh...
Would you please just wait?
Shinichi!
Uhh... Waa..
Be careful!
[Thud]
Oh! Uh...
Ah, that hurt...
[Sliding sound]
Ah!
[Splash]
Oww! Ahh...
Huh?
Are you okay, Shinichi?
Did you get any on you?!
Are you hurt?!
You didn't get burned
or anything? You're okay?
Uh, uh‐huh.
[Sigh]
Nobuko, your arm.
Huh?
Aah! Ooh!
[Water running]
[Nobuko crying]
Ow! Hmm?
Your mom's hurting much
worse than you are.
[SHINICHI]
Huh? What do you mean,
I shouldn't be that worried?
It's true.
Simply consider
the probability.
My kind prefer urban areas
where food is plentiful.
Furthermore, their targets
are normally people who
are out by themselves.
If your parents travel out to
the countryside, they will be
safer than they are now.
Yeah, okay...
Guess I shouldn't
have been so against it
when they brought it up.
Shinichi?
Ah! Wh‐what now?!
Were you, uh, just talking
to somebody in here?
Nah, just to myself!
What do you want?!
Huh? Well... dinner's
going to be ready soon...
Oh, okay. I'll be down
in just a few minutes...
And, uh, Mom?
Huh?
The next time
you come up here,
could you knock before you
just open up the door!
Can I have some privacy?!
Oh... Okay, son.
I'm sorry.
Ahh... I seriously thought
I was gonna have a heart attack!
If that were to happen, it would
be an inconvenience for me.
Your son was yelling
at me just now.
Well, he's probably up there
whacking off or something.
Oh!
[Dish breaking]
[Dog barking]
[SHINICHI]
Um, I know I said
I was against your
trip this morning,
but I take it back now.
Honestly, I think
it's a good idea
for you guys to get
away from everything
and go relax somewhere
with some nice fresh air.
Mmm...
So, when do you leave?
Uhh...
Hmm...
I don't get it.
Huh?
I just...
don't understand you, Shinichi.
Ah...
[NOBUKO]
What on Earth is
going on with you?
You were so dead set
against it this morning...
I mean you were very adamant...
And now you're saying something
completely the opposite.
So now you're not so worried
about your parents, is that it?
Oh, now I get a guilt trip?!
Maybe you're the one with
the problems here, Mom!
I don't get this...
In fact, I don't get
anything about you anymore!
Something is just...
Something is different.
And it's... like you're
not my son anymore.
Baby, please.
[Crying]
Please, why won't you tell me?!
What's happening to you?
Uh...
[Crying]
Shinichi.
I didn't want
to be alone...
At least, I didn't
this morning.
Huh?
But when I talked to
a friend about it,
he just laughed at me.
And I changed my mind.
So I think I'm feeling
better about it now...
If I do get lonely,
I can just invite
someone to come over.
That's really
all there is to it.
Mm‐hmm...
You guys understand, right?
[Crying]
Mm‐hmm...
[SHINICHI]
The taxi should be here
in a coupla minutes.
This'll probably
be the first time
we've been gone
this long...
It should be
really fun.
Y'know...
Back when we were living
in the old apartment,
we couldn't even
afford to take trips.
Right, we could barely
afford the apartment itself.
It was in that little
bitty kitchen, where
I wound up with this.
Oh! Hmm...
[Car pulling up]
Oh? Hehe...
[Taxi honks]
Uh... Well, take care
of the place.
Uh... Mm‐hm!
And be sure to
turn off the stove
and lock the door.
I will.
And don't be worried
about us, okay buddy?
Okay.
We'll be back!
[RYOKO]
Huh...
It moved...
[SHINICHI]
Next time:
"The Stranger"