[MIGI]
I'm sorry but I have some
bad news for you, Shinichi.
What is it Migi?
What's going on!
You need to hurry up,
right now.
[SHINICHI]
Are you sure it's him?
[MIGI]
These signals are very
intense and focused.
And given the speed of approach,
he must be in a car.
Here. Take a right
at the corner.
[SHINICHI]
Great!
Now I'm a thief.
[MIGI]
Such matters are
trivial at this point.
So, uh, Migi...
I have to ask,
when did you learn
to drive a car?
I did master human language
in a single day, if you recall.
Okay, I need a
favor from you.
Please take us
out to somewhere
less populated.
If we try to fight him
in the city, a lot of
people could die.
Very well.
Also, I have an idea
that's definitely
worth a shot.
Hm?
[SHINICHI]
Well?
[MIGI]
It didn't work.
He's still alive.
He's extremely resilient.
Let's get out of here.
Where can we go?
Just run.
[MIGI]
Okay. Stop here.
[Catching his breath]
Why are we stopping now?
I thought we
couldn't afford to
waste time, right?!
Take a breath.
Until he catches up,
we really should strategize.
"Strategize" now?!
We are about to be
chopped into
little pieces!
Shinichi, I know
what you're feeling.
Anyone would fear
being killed.
I'm afraid, too.
But this...
this is our
moment of truth.
Ah...
Now remember, you have
a strength that other
humans don't possess.
And you can be calm,
no matter what the
circumstances are.
Now, put your hand
on your chest
and breathe deeply,
like always.
[Deep breaths]
Good.
Well done.
[MIGI]
Listen.
Yes, Goto's abilities outclass
ours in every possible way.
Simple logic says
we have almost
no chance of winning...
In which case,
I say we shift
our line of thought.
If it's not possible
for us to win even if
we work together...
then maybe we ought
to give working
separately a try.
Do what?
Sometimes sheer strength
can be beaten...
by pure chance.
"Chance," huh?
I took a lighter
from that car,
and I put it inside
your left pocket.
Well now...
They've used the branches
to spread out in all
four directions.
How uninspired.
[Migi voiceover]
This will be a race
against time.
The human body is our
lifeline, but it's also
our greatest weakness.
The cells within you
that were once part of me
have since been altered..
and are now
completely integrated.
Therefore, Goto won't
be able to detect you.
He'll come straight toward me
without ever noticing
you at all.
If this fight goes on too long,
I'll shrivel up and die.
It's indeed a reckless plan...
But that's exactly why Goto
is not likely to see it coming.
[GOTO]
What's this?
No counterattack at all?
Where is the human boy?
Once I've found and destroyed
the host, it's finished.
[Migi voiceover]
His body is protected by
an armor of semi‐hardened
parasitic cells...
but I doubt very much that
they cover the entire surface.
That said, there's no time
to search for the gaps
in his armor.
But I believe the area
least likely to be protected,
and therefore the most
optimal target...
would be... his head.
Controlling the multiple
parasites throughout
his torso and limbs
must require a tremendous
amount of energy.
So it must be very difficult
for the head already.
That means, if we can
remove the head,
he should lose control,
disabling enough protection
for us to be able to
destroy the body.
[SHINICHI]
Come on, Migi...
If we don't hurry up, then
you're not gonna make it...
[Migi voiceover]
We'll have just one chance.
Goto's speed and power
are far greater than mine,
so decapitating him
won't be easy.
[MIGI]
Uh oh. My consciousness is
already starting to fade.
I'll have to hurry.
But I still don't
have a good angle.
Come out! You cowards!
Am I really that terrible?!
Spreading out in all directions
is nothing but temporary
camouflage at best!
You should be using your brains
to fight, not run and hide!
[Migi imitating Shinichi]
Go now! Do it!
[SHINICHI]
Was that my voice?
There you are.
[Grunt]
[Stab]
Huh?
[Migi voiceover]
When exposed directly to fire,
Goto's surface cells will
reflexively break away
from his control...
And when that happens...
U‐ugh...
[MIGI]
Damn! Not deep enough!
That's not good.
[SHINICHI]
Migi!
[MIGI]
Stay back, Shinichi!
Are you okay?
We have failed.
Well, this is quite
a surprise...
Well done.
[MIGI]
Go, now! Hurry!
But you...
Just go!
Both of us don't
have to die!
But still... Migi...
Gah!
What are you doing?!
Get out of here now!
[Gasping]
[MIGI]
Goodbye, Shinichi.
This is our farewell...
I'm pleased I didn't take over
your brain when we first met...
Because of that, you and I
were actually able to
create many fond
memories together...
as friends.
[Groans]
[MIGI]
I'm... fading...
strangely... sleepy...
and I feel... so very...
alone.
Such... must be...
death...
[Frantic running]
Aahh!
[Catching his breath]
[Whimpering]
[Sobbing]
[Agonizing scream]
[Crying]
Who's there?!
Uh...
Uh... I'm sorry.
You a burglar
or somethin?!
I'm not!
But, yeah, I guess...
Well... Sorry.
Huh?
I sorta did try to
take a drink of
some of your water.
Ah, did ya now...
I guess that water
isn't even free anymore.
Uh, I'm sorry...
Well... Um...
I should be going...
I'm sorry for
all the trouble.
Okay, wait just
a second.
Yes, ma'am?
Looks like you've been
hurt, haven't you?
Uh... No, ma'am.
This is...
No... On your head...
Guessing ya lost that right arm
of yours a long time ago.
No, I'm all right...
And I think the bleeding's
already stopped.
Come inside and
let's take a look.
But, I...
Well come on...
I don't think any burglar
would be this polite.
Besides, you look like
you've been crying.
Ah...
[WOMAN]
Look kid,
I've been livin' on this
Earth for a long, long time.
And I can tell if a person's
worth a damn or not.
This isn't from a
fair fight is it?
Someone bullied you
good, didn't they?
Am I right?
Uh‐huh...
This cut's pretty deep actually.
Hmph... People out there
can do some awful things
to each other.
Uh... Oh...
[SHINICHI]
I never expected such
kindness from a stranger.
Thank you so much
for everything.
You should probably
stay here for the night.
Huh?
No, I couldn't possibly.
Where else are you plannin'
to go at this hour?
There aren't any
hotels around here.
Uh, Ma'am,
do you live out here in the
country all by yourself?
Nah, I don't have any
more family left.
Oh... I...
I'm sorry, Ma'am.
Oh, it's okay, son.
You call me, Mitsuyo.
It's nice to meet you...
My name is...
my name's Shinichi Izumi.
Shinichi?
It's nice to meet you, too.
[MITSUYO]
Thanks for this,
I'm sorry to have you
help with the shopping.
[SHINICHI]
Oh no, it's no problem.
It's the least I can do.
[MITSUYO]
We should probably tell
everybody that you're my nephew.
[SHINICHI]
Nephew?
A lot of strange things
have been going on lately.
People really don't like
outsiders around.
[SHINICHI]
"Strange things"?
[MITSUYO]
This is what I was
talking about.
Some company keeps
coming out here
and dumping these huge
truckloads of garbage...
One time,
it actually caught fire
and nearly burned up
the whole mountain.
The big cities are having
trouble finding room
for all their crap,
but this is ridiculous.
[SHINICHI]
Yeah...
Everybody around here's
been trying to keep watch,
but they still manage to
slip in here and dump more.
I don't know how
those assholes do it.
[SHINICHI]
Mitsuyo may be
a little nuts, but
she's got a kind heart.
Still, every time I try to
thank her and leave...
she stops me with another
barrage of conversation.
With Migi gone, I honestly
have no idea what to do next...
so a few hours have turned
into several days.
But I can't keep
imposing on her forever...
I really must go home and
tell Dad what's going on.
About how I lost my arm...
And how I had a friend...
named Migi...
About the day that Migi
first showed up...
and all the things
we did together...
And about...
about how great Migi was.
He fought for me.
Saved me...
He was intelligent,
courageous...
And better than
I could ever be.
Because Migi...
is a true hero!
[SHINICHI]
Where am I?
I feel like I've
been here before...
What is that?
Uh, who are you?
[MIGI]
What's wrong?
Did you lose something?
Have I lost...
Oh, that's right.
I'm looking for a friend.
Looking for your friend?
What do they look like?
Look like?
I can't really
remember that.
I'm afraid you're
on your own then.
Hey, wait!
I think he
looked like you.
That's right!
I remember now...
But... He...
He died.
What?
Your friend's dead?
Yeah.
No. No he's not.
He's still alive.
What?!
I can tell.
Actually, I know
his name, too.
His name...
His name...?
Migi!
[Panting]
[Gasp]
Ah... Migi!
Some of his cells
are still inside me!
Hey, there..!
It's me!
Don't you remember?!
[MITSUYO]
Keep it down a little bit...
You're talking in your sleep.
Oh!
It's no good.
There's still some
of him in there,
but not enough
to do anything.
Migi...
Migi!
[Terrified screams]
[Frantic running and screams]
[MITSUYO]
I see. Well, I guess
it is what it is.
And I suppose I just can't
keep you here forever.
I don't know how I'll ever
be able to repay you
for your kindness.
Hm...
[Knocking on door]
Hm?
What's your problem?
Don't you know
how early it is?
Okay boy, now talk to us!
You really expect us to
believe you're her nephew?
Hm?
Oh what the hell
difference does it make?
Besides, the kid was just
about to head out anyway.
Oh, I don't think so!
There's been way too much
going on around here lately.
All that illegal trash dumping
and then that crash between
two cars without any drivers...
Uh...
And now, we have a
murder on our hands.
Uh...
Haah?!
Nakano, you said the killer
was some outsider, right?
Well take a look at 'im.
I'm tellin' ya, that
thing I saw wasn't
just some "outsider"...
This kid has been with
me the whole time‐
It wasn't no human,
ya understand?!
I wasn't just
seein' things!
It was three meters tall!
A‐and... that thing it had
like four front legs!
And a whole bunch of eyes
all over the place!
I'm serious!
I'm not making this up!
That's Goto. It's gotta be.
Look, you guys can call me
crazy all you want...
But this blood, that's all
over my coat is from Kitayama!
And some horrible monster
killed and ate him,
he lives right down the road!
You gotta believe me!
[DETECTIVE]
So it was around
here somewhere?
[NAKANO]
Yessir...
that's right.
Oh! Uhh...
Ah, that is
just horrible.
Wait a second, this is just
like those stories that
were in the news.
Uhh...
The Mincemeat Murders...
Right.
Understood.
A bunch of local hunters are
getting together tomorrow,
and they ought to be able
to take this "monster"
of yours down for good.
Hunting rifles...
will not destroy him.
Huh...?
"Destroy him"?
You mean, you know about
this monster thing?
Yes, I do...
That's how I wound up here...
He's after me.
Huh?! Oh, quit talking
such nonsense.
So this whole thing
is my fault!
He followed me here...
And now more people
have been killed!
I'm gonna have to keep moving
or others will die too.
Come on, son.
All I wanted was to live...
No matter what it took...
Even though some
of my friends have
already died for me.
But I can't...
I can't keep running away
from this forever can I?!
Why can't you?
If it saves you then why not?
Just keep on running...
If it can save your life,
then you have to do it.
There's no shame
in that, son.
Mitsuyo, I can't.
There are things I've
avoided that now I must do!
I must sacrifice myself
and face that monster...
before any more people
out there get slaughtered!
Oh, shut up and
cut the crap!
Don't be a jackass!
What is this
"sacrifice myself" trash?
How can you talk
such bullshit?!
Who the hell do you
think you are anyway?!
Sacrifice yourself?
What a freakin joke!
What could a snot‐nosed brat
like you do about it anyway?!
Sigh...
Look, I might not know
your whole story...
but I think you need
to sit back
and just let the grownups
handle this situation.
[MITSUYO]
So, you're determined are ya?
Don't you have someone
special out there...
someone you care about?
Someone you know.
Someone you wish you knew.
Just someone out there
you can't leave behind...
You know...
S‐someone that
makes you...
human...
Look, I don't know what
your plan is or anything...
but you at least owe it
to yourself to give
some thought...
to something else...
anything else.
Because, son, once you've
thrown it all away,
then that's it.
I'm just sayin' don't
give up, no matter what,
and remember that
there's always an option.
Hold on...
Is there anything I can
give you that you can use?
A weapon or whatever?
Uh...
Ah...
I'll take this.
Really, you seriously
want that old thing?
Well I guess it's
better than nothing.
Hm.
[MITSUYO]
Please dear...
Keep that boy safe.
[SHINICHI]
If Goto has changed
his appearance...
then there'll be no way
to recognize him...
But I guess...
I'll just have to
deal with it...
whenever that time comes...
[SHINICHI]
Next time:
"Life and Vows"