Where is it?!
[Students chatter]
[STUDENT]
Didja fall asleep or something?
[SHINICHI]
Yuko!
[AKIHO]
What're you doing?
[TEACHER]
Mr. Izumi!
Just where do you
think you're going?!
Hey!
[Terrified quivering]
[SHIMADA]
Try not to move.
It will only hurt
more if you do.
Ah!
Ungh!
[Bottle clanks on the ground]
Huh?
[Terrified quivering]
Ah!
Eh‐uh... Ahhh!
Argh! Ahh!
Uhh...
[Grunt]
Huh? Hey, look...
Huh?
[Nervous sounds]
Ah!
Wha...
Huh?
Uh...
Ah!
Huh?
[Grunt]
Ah...
[Branches breaking]
[Thud]
[TEACHER]
Dear God! Are you alright?!
Can you hear me?
Speak up! Come on!
Are you okay?
Unhh...
[SHIMADA]
Gah! What's happening?!
Dammit! When I lost
control and morphed,
some of the chemicals
got inside me!
You saw that thing coming
out the window, right?
Yeah, man...
Let's go take a look.
[SHINICHI]
That sound just now.
I think it came
from the Art Room.
[MIGI]
He's on the move.
What? Where?!
Very strange...
I'm not sure it's Shimada.
Huh?
Its thoughts are disjointed...
Or rather...
completely incoherent.
Hmm...
[TEACHER]
Hey, you two.
What was that sound?
We think we saw something
in the Art Room, sir.
You saw "something".
Hmph...
All right then.
I'll find out
what's going on.
You guys can go
back to class.
Huh? Hold on!
Sir, wait a second!
[Shimada groans]
I have to...
I must restore my human form.
[Struggling sounds]
It's not working.
The surface won't respond!
This body is stuck
in attack mode,
and doesn't seem able
to restore itself.
It must be corrected...
The dead cells are preventing
intercommunication.
I have to unify my thoughts.
[Fly buzzing]
Uh!
What it this?
What am I doing?
[TEACHER]
Okay son, what's going on?
Get that that thing
off your head and
come with me.
[MIGI]
Oh.
What?
He just killed
three entities.
[STUDENT]
Ah... Ahh!
Huh?
Oh my God!
Over there! Over there!
That thing!
That thing's over there!
Huh? Do you know
what's going on?
OH!
AAAHH!
[MALE TEACHER]
Oh my God!
Call the police! Call 'em now!
[FEMALE TEACHER]
Okay, okay!
Migi, can you sense him,
where did he go?
Give me a minute.
Shimada's signal has become
exceedingly scattered.
He's quite fast...
Right now, he's headed
toward your classroom.
Ah! The classroom?!
Uh...
[Students chatter]
I can't get through here.
[MIGI]
Fighting in these conditions
would not be preferable.
For now, I recommend we
evacuate with the others.
[NAGAI]
I can't believe this
is happening again!
[FURUTANI]
You mean that
"Killer A" lunatic?
Who d'you think it is?
Well, I guess this time
it's just gotta be
"Killer B", huh?
[SASAKI]
What are you doing?!
Huh?
Hm?
You need to leave!
Everyone get out of here! Hurry!
It's not safe to be here!
I think Mr. Sasaki
peed his pants.
He seems more dangerous
than, like, any intruder.
[TEACHER]
Once you've confirmed that
everyone in your class
has made it out, you're to
leave campus immediately!
Seriously?
What about all our bags?
You can get them tomorrow!
Oh, Mr. Vice Principal!
Class 3‐3's students
aren't out here yet.
Uh?
That's Murano's class.
Where in God's name
are the police?
I don't know,
they're taking forever.
Migi, where's Shimada?
So we are going
to fight him?
Right now, I'm more
worried about what's
happening to Class 3‐3!
Shinichi!
[Screams]
Huh?
[Students screaming]
Huh? It's Murano's class!
I don't see her.
Where is she?!
Fine then...
I liked you
better before.
This can't be
how it ends...
I can't...
I cannot accept it!
Shimada's on
the third floor.
Uh!
Uh...
Uh‐ahh...
AAAAHHH!!!
Shinichi! Calm down!
[Catches his breath]
Urgh... Ahh...
Take it easy...
Slow your breathing.
What have I...
What the hell have
I been doing?!
I'm breaking.
My heart's tearing apart...
It's ripping in two...
You'll be okay.
Everything's going
to be just fine.
[Grunts]
I can't...
do this anymore!
But Shinichi.
You're different now.
It's like you're
made of steel.
Metal shell with nothing
left on the inside.
Hhmm...
Have you calmed yourself?
Yeah, I'm alright.
I will protect Murano.
And to do that,
I must take HIM down.
[Wet footsteps]
Hm‐oh...
Uh...
Sorry, I thought you
were someone else.
Migi, where's Shimada now?
About 60 meters from here,
on this floor.
[Students sobbing
and frightened]
Two, far away...
And three more close by...
And there's one beast.
That's very
impressive.
[SHINICHI]
It's coming from over there.
Huh...
[Students crying]
Uh...
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Huh... whah...
Murano...
[Sobbing]
I'm here...
It's alright.
You're okay.
How... how were you
able to get over here?
Can you stand?
Ugh...
You can do it.
Right. We're all
going together.
G‐go where?
Well, I came
from over there.
So we'll go back
that way.
[STUDENT]
Huh?! But...
but that's where...
I mean, we can't
go that way!
That's where they
all got cut down!
[Crying]
But it's safe now.
He's gone.
No! No chance!
Huh?
Wait! If you came that way...
Are you...
Oh God...
it was you...
Ah...
He's one of them!
No wait!
Aaah...go go go!
Come back!
Oh! Ahh!
[Slicing and screams]
Huh?
[Whimpering]
[SHINICHI]
He's right there.
[Growling]
He said they were looking
for ways to coexist...
but in the end, he murdered
them and ate them...
His directive.
[Footsteps]
He's here. Uh...
Wha... Ahhh!
It's okay!
[Grunt]
Alright, one more jump!
Whoa...
[Panting]
You should be safe
over here Murano.
But...
but how... Shinichi...
I know...
Something as crazy as this...
it's enough to rattle anyone.
[Sobbing]
Uh‐ahh...
[Police sirens]
[SHINICHI]
No. I'm fine...
Just take care of her.
But... don't go...
Look... You don't
have to worry.
Uhh...
Uh...
This is something...
I have to take care of.
I'm not sure if we
can get back in.
Do you still plan
to fight him?
We knew what Shimada was,
and we did nothing.
And that means
we're responsible.
Which in my book
means one thing...
It is up to us...
to end this.
[MIGI]
You're saying
strange things again.
Let the police handle this.
Under these circumstances,
they will prevail.
[POLICEMAN]
Police! Don't move!
Oh...
[Gasps]
Ahh...
[Moaning growls]
[Gunshots]
Ah!
You damned monster!
[Gunshots]
[MIGI]
Small‐arms fire won't be
enough to bring him down.
If they want to kill him,
they'll need to decapitate him
or destroy the heart.
[Slicing]
[MIGI]
Still, if he's injured
badly enough,
he will succumb eventually.
[Moaning]
[DETECTIVE]
He's headed where? The roof?
Understood. But approach him
with extreme caution.
[SHINICHI]
Migi, do you think Shimada
is really to blame?
[MIGI]
I think it's best to let the
humans use their rather...
arbitrary standards
to make that judgment.
No. This needs
to end now.
Yes... But how?
With this.
But we must keep a distance
of at least 300 meters.
Otherwise, Shimada
will be able to sense us.
I know.
[SHINICHI]
Shimada... This can't be
just about you...
There's also Ryoko Tamiya
and Mr. A...
Why the hell are you even here?
[Door opens]
[MIGI]
You're going to
need to merge
my strength with
your current power.
Right...
Migi, you know where to
aim this, don't you?
Of course.
[Grunt]
[Gasp]
[Crash]
[Gasping]
[SHIMADA]
Shinichi...
Uhh...
[Gasps]
[NEWS REPORTER]
A week has now passed
since the massacre
that resulted in the
deaths of 17 victims.
Several doubts remain
regarding the identity
of the presumed killer,
a drug addicted student,
who is now known to have
been using a false name.
I don't understand.
Why are they making such an
effort to hide the truth...
They should just show everyone
out there Shimada's body.
What happens if they put
Shimada's body on display...
and even openly announced that
they've identified a new type
of parasitic life form that's
feeding on human beings...
What's achieved?
"What's achieved"?
Public outrage...
And demands to capture
the damn things.
How would you capture them?
Huh?
Ah...
well we humans
can't do it alone...
You and I will have
to work together
with the police.
No way.
Migi...
I am an ally to myself,
and myself alone.
I am not an ally to
the human species.
Yeah, but still...
Even if they discover a parasite
disguised as a human being,
it can simply assume
another identity.
Humans would be unable
to apprehend them.
Okay then...!
So WE should hunt
them all down right?
And kill them?
Uh...
Shinichi. I don't have the
same sentimentality as humans.
Which means that even killing
my own kind has no affect
on me emotionally.
But try to imagine if
my position and yours
were reversed.
Ah...
Hm‐hmm...
[MIGI]
Talking about such
things distresses him.
A common condition
of the human race.
[COUNCILMAN]
Up till now,
we've kept their existence
secret to avoid mass panic.
But it's getting more and more
difficult to keep it hidden.
[COUNCILMAN 2]
An announcement of this
nature would most certainly
lead to chaos.
There are even rumors
that the Americans are
attempting to adapt these
parasites for military use.
[TAKIZAWA]
It's time to involve the public.
[Gasps]
And how do you
intend to make such
an announcement?
Let me clarify,
I'm not saying that we should
reveal the parasites' existence.
I mean we could subtly make
known a method that could be
used to distinguish humans
from the parasites.
But how would we
make that "known"?
And we can't even tell
each other apart...
Who out there's infected?
To explain this
matter further,
I'd like to hand it
over to Dr. Yui.
Mm.
Now then, I'd like to
start by expounding upon
what we've learned so far
about the parasites'
unique physiology.
These parasitic life forms
have the ability to act
as the human brain,
not only commanding
the entire body,
but even driving functions
beyond their normal limits.
Their cellular makeup closely
resembles that of neurons.
To put things more simply...
you could call it
"sentient muscle."
Ah, "sentient muscle"?
Very interesting.
There's more.
They have the ability to morph
their tissues in an instant,
to stretch out like rubber
or become as hard as steel.
So you might wonder, how could
such foreign cells as these
bind themselves to
the human body?
The answer is, a
near‐instantaneous
cellular fusion.
It's most likely a
substance much like how
polyethylene glycol
affects the cell
membranes‐
Please skip to how we
can identify them.
Huh? Ahh...
Ahem.
Now then...
As they are sentient muscle,
when enough of their
cells are gathered,
their intelligence level
is actually on par with
that of humans.
On the other hand,
what do you suppose happens
if enough of their cells
are not gathered together?
Hmm...
If deprived of blood flow
they shrivel up and die,
so they work together to fuse
with others of their kind.
So if a small enough
fragment becomes separated,
it struggles to survive,
but its small mass means it
lacks the intelligence
to rejoin the source.
Now if you were to pull out
the hair of a human,
nothing at all would happen...
But if you pull out a "hair"
from a camouflaged parasite...
I believe it would violently
writhe in pain for a few seconds
before the cells would
ultimately die.
In other words...
Pulling out a strand of hair
is one way to identify
whether or not someone
has been infected.
[Men chatter]
[COUNCILMAN]
Well done, Professor!
Good Lord, they could
just wear a wig!
What do you suggest
we do then?
A hair sample from
any part of the body
will create the
same reaction.
The main point is to isolate
a small enough mass of cells
away from the main body.
Well maybe...
I guess that makes sense.
Now then, I'm very sorry
for the imposition,
gentlemen,
but we ask that as you
leave this room,
you consent to pulling out
a strand of your hair.
Uh‐umm...
While the likelihood is low,
we cannot say for sure that
we don't have one of them
here among us.
[SHINICHI]
It didn't take as long
as you'd expect...
for school to be reopened.
Uh...
Murano.
Uh... Shinichi.
Are you...
are you doing okay?
Mm...
Sorry...
Sorry I didn't
text you back.
That's fine.
Are ya ready?
Mm‐hm...
How's Yuko doin'?
Oh, she's much
better now.
She'll be at
school today.
That's good.
She really... she really
went through a lot y'know.
Yeah, she did...
But she's always been
a pretty strong person.
Mm.
I've been
thinking about
how much I need
to thank you.
Oh?
Because well...
if you hadn't
been there...
Look that's all behind us...
Let's just try to think of
happier things now.
Shinichi...
You know, we jumped from
pretty high up there.
And somehow you
didn't even get hurt.
Yeah right, I think I
must've been all pumped
full of adrenaline...
I mean, I was as
surprised as you were.
Yeah, uh‐huh...
Well I do really mean it...
Thanks, Shinichi.
Mm...
Huh?
Good morning!
Oh!
Ah... Hehehe...
[SHINICHI]
The government never did
publicly announce
the existence of
the parasites...
However...
a little "fad" started.
People started greeting
each other differently.
Like... a new handshake.
[SHINICHI]
Next time:
"The Blue Bird"