[WOMAN]
You. You in the gray coat.
What do you think you're doing?
[PASSENGERS] (hmm?)
I think you need to keep
your hands to yourself.
That is disgusting.
Ew, that guy's a pervert!
N‐no, no! That's not true!
What the hell is your problem!
What're you trying to do?
I didn't touch anybody!
You're crazy!
Why would you say that?
[MAN] (gaahhh!)
(ungh...)
This year's Kayama Fantasy
Literature Award,
the winner is, uh...
It's Dai Yoshimi.
"Seventh Transformation," right?
Uh‐huh. You read it?
It's about a guy that
somehow gains the ability
to communicate with reptiles.
It's completely ridiculous.
Hmm... Huh?
Not this again...
That brings the total to 84.
More Mincemeat Murders?
I hate to say it, but it doesn't
even surprise me anymore.
Dinner was great. Thanks.
[MOM] But, honey,
you didn't even eat half of it!
[SHINICHI] Yeah, sorry.
I may be the only person
in the entire world
who actually knows the truth
behind all these horrible
killings.
I just don't know
what to do about it.
[SATOMI] Shinichi!
[SHINICHI] (huh?)
[SATOMI] Morning.
Morning.
You know, Shinichi,
you've changed recently.
Huh? I have?
Yeah.
Really?
What're you talking about?
[MIGI] (muffled) Shinichi...
Huh?
I swear I just heard a voice.
[MIGI] Look down here.
Migi? That feels
really weird, ya know.
What's wrong Shinichi?
Uh, nothing. I'm fine.
[MIGI] One of my kind is near.
Huh? Again?
[MIGI] It's approaching rapidly.
[SHINICHI] But there haven't
been any Mincemeat Murders
around here.
[MIGI] Perhaps the bodies
simply haven't been found yet.
It's currently about 70 meters
away from us.
Sixty meters...
(soft gasp) Not here...
[MIGI] It's inside the building.
Inside the school...
(general chatter)
[SHINICHI] Where is it?
WHO is it?
Is it a guy?
Or a girl?!
[MIGI] It's in here.
Approximately 30 meters away.
Thirty...?
[MIGI] Don't make eye contact.
It will find us.
It's looking for us as well,
but it seems unable to pinpoint
our location in the crowd.
Welcome, good morning, students.
I'd like to introduce our new
math teacher, substituting
for Mr. Matsuyama.
HE had to be hospitalized
after the unfortunate
traffic accident two days ago.
Now then, I present to you Ms.
Tamiya.
I'm Ryoko Tamiya.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
[MIGI] It's her.
[SHINICHI] What?!
And, as of today, Mr. Yamamoto
will be the new homeroom teacher
for Class 3‐3.
Oh, my God, Murano's class!
[PRINCIPAL]
Therefore, Ms. Tamiya will act
as assistant homeroom teacher.
[MIGI] No eye contact, Shinichi!
She just looked at me!
D'you see that?!
Just look at her...
the guys are gonna freak out.
[YUKO] Mm‐hm!
She found us...
[PE TEACHER]
All right, listen up!
Once you do your five laps
around the field,
be sure to stretch again
to loosen up.
Then split into two groups
and set up a match.
[MIGI] This surprises me.
[PE TEACHER]
You've read up on all the rules.
[MIGI]
After taking over the host,
[PE TEACHER] I don't wanna
see any crap out there.
she has managed to
successfully maintain
their position in society.
Plus, she functions as
a teacher of humans.
She appears to be quite gifted.
What are you praising her for?
We have to do something.
[MIGI] What do you mean?
Well, what if we don't?
She's gonna eat everybody!
[MIGI] No, I highly doubt that.
She wishes to blend in
with human society.
I do not believe that
she would use anyone
in her immediate social circle
as a food supply.
Therefore,
I believe they should be safe.
You don't know that.
[MIGI] We should just
observe her for now.
With everything that's
going on right now,
how can Migi go to sleep?
I mean, what if she
suddenly tries to...
[RYOKO] All right, class.
I want you to use this formula
to solve problems
six through twelve.
[RYOKO] Mr. Izumi...
[SHINICHI] Oh, my God!
Is there a problem?
You don't appear
to have made any progress.
Huh?! Uh... No, ma'am.
Sorry.
(students laughing)
(bell tolling)
Mr. Izumi, would you
please visit me in the
counselor's office later?
Thank you.
Whoa... what'd you do?
[SHINICHI] Uh...
Dude, how did you do that?
Jesus, what do I have to do to
get myself called to the
teacher's office?!
Hellooo? What's wrong with
what's sitting right here...
Shinichi knows!
[FURUTANI] Whatever.
You can't teach me all the
things sweet, mature hottie
Ms. Tamiya can.
But I don't understand it...
What's she wanna with
squirrely ass Shinichi?
Doesn't really make sense.
What's that sposta mean?!
Why you gotta be
such a jerk, huh?
Oh, whatever, Shinichi... You
don't know what you're missing.
[MIGI] Shinichi...
She's approximately ten meters
away right now.
[SHINICHI] Oh, so you're awake?
Excuse me.
Please, come on in.
Well then, Mr. Izumi...
You are aware of what I am, yes?
[SHINICHI] Yeah.
"Yeah"? That's no way to speak
to your teacher now, is it?
Oh, there's no need
for you to be so anxious.
You should know that I have
absolutely no intentions
of killing you right now.
Your right hand
should know that.
Besides, if we fought
in such close quarters,
we'd both end up
being mortally wounded.
I'd like the opportunity to
speak with you a bit more.
You think you have time to meet
with me after school today?
Okay.
[SHINICHI] Huh?!
But what if it's
some kind of trap?!
I am totally against this!
How predictable.
Why must humans always
be so irrational?
What's that?!
If I wanted to kill you,
I already would have.
[SHINICHI] (uhhh...)
I am... curious however.
Because I've never seen a case
anything like yours before.
I wish to collect more data.
I'd like to exchange
information with you...
and discuss our future.
"Future"?
[RYOKO]
Well, that's all for now.
(sliding door)
[SASAKI] Hey, Ms. Tamiya!
[RYOKO] Yes?
Uh... do you have
any plans this afternoon?
[RYOKO] I do. I have some
student counseling sessions.
Oh, okay.
[RYOKO] If you'll excuse me.
Hey I'm going to the bookstore,
do you wanna come with me?
[SATOMI] Uh‐huh.
Huh? Is that...
[MIGI] Shinichi, you should
roll up your sleeves.
Why should I do that? We're not
getting into a fight, are we?
[MIGI]
Perhaps, something's coming.
[SHINICHI] Huh?!
Actually,
two of my kind are coming.
(gasp) So it really was a trap?
[MIGI] There's no way to
know that for sure yet.
[MIGI] Shinichi, it would be
really helpful right now
if you could slow down
your heart rate a little bit.
It's making me feel anxious.
I can't do that!
[RYOKO] Sorry for the wait.
I'll keep this short...
Meet Mr. A.
Just "A"?
Yes, he has no name.
What is this creature?
Can we even call him
one of our kind?
That's enough. There's no
merit in killing one another
in a place as public as this.
Interesting... So at this point,
you've only encountered
those two types so far.
Yeah.
Now, I'd like to know...
In your opinion,
what exactly do you think
we are, Mr. Izumi?
Well from everything
I've seen...
You're monsters here to
feed on the human race.
But you see...
Mr. A and I have experimented,
and had sex with each other.
[SHINICHI] (gasps)
(breaking glass)
Oh, I'm so sorry!
Please excuse me.
(softly) Oh, my God...
And the result might
surprise you.
I am now pregnant Mr. Izumi.
[SHINICHI] (gulp)
So then, here's a question...
This "thing" that I currently
have growing inside my body...
What do you think it might be?
Oh... well, uh...
[MIGI] A human, a normal one.
Good answer. Yes...
The child I am carrying
is human, an ordinary
human baby.
In which case, what do you
think that makes us?
I've no idea.
Nor do I really want
to find out.
What I DO know is
that you eat humans
in order to keep
your human host alive.
And that's what we call
cannibalism.
Why would you do
something like that?
Have you ever...
tried asking your little friend
that question?
[MIGI]
I receive nutrients directly
through Shinichi's blood,
so I do not experience hunger.
Therefore, I am also at a loss
to understand our own kind's
alleged necessity for
cannibalism.
Our species cannot reproduce,
and we engage in a sort of
pseudo‐cannibalism.
I'm not really sure
what to call us.
[MIGI]
I've given it some thought,
and I consider it
strange as well.
[SHINICHI] Are you actually
even life forms? Or what?
Either way, I don't think
you're from this planet.
I am leaving now.
Whether or not I find out
exactly what I am,
isn't going to change
anything for me.
I eat when I feel hungry,
and I get rid of
anyone in my way.
And that is it.
[A] That one is dangerous.
He must be eliminated.
We didn't merge with
our host the same way.
Now...
Humans do sometimes
act illogically,
so I will give you a warning.
If you think of me
as an enemy,
and decide to make some
kind of a scene,
the disadvantage is yours.
You can't change your face.
I've decided it's in my interest
to protect my current
human identity,
so I will not behave
irrationally.
But if I were provoked,
an entire classroom...
(aahhhh...)
Would all be dead
in mere seconds.
I believe you have friends
in that class, do you not?
(whimpers)
[MOM] Shinichi! Is that you?
She's something else.
She was capable
of making you suffer an
intense amount of fear.
Shinichi... That's cold.
Huh?
So, uh, yesterday...
you took the bus somewhere.
Where did you go?
Murano was worried about you.
Oh... Nowhere.
(snap)
[MIGI]
Shinichi, we are under attack.
I sense nothing but
pure killing intent.
[SHINICHI] Huh?
[AKIHO]
Ms. Tamiya? Are you okay?
Idiot.
[AKIHO] (gasps)
[TEACHER]
(whimpering) Somebody help!
Oh, my goodness!
Are you all right?
(unh) There's an intruder.
He went that way.
Okay! Get a hold of the police!
And we must evacuate
the students at once!
Time for study hall, class.
(confused murmurs)
Who do you think would
try to attack us?
[MIGI]
Probably the one from yesterday.
[SASAKI]
Excuse me, sir. You are not
allowed to be on school property
without a badge from the office!
You need to come with me!
Sir, I... (ungh!)
[TEACHERS] (gasps)
[TEACHERS]
(whimpering) (ungh!)
[MIGI] He just neutralized
three obstacles.
Are you saying that he
killed some people?!
[MIGI] I'm not sure.
But he's very forceful.
Dear God! This is terrible!
We need to get the students as
far away from here as possible!
[PA]
Attention students and faculty!
This is an emergency!
There is currently
an intruder on campus!
[NAGAI] What?
What do you think they want?
[PA]
Students are to follow their
teachers' instructions
Was there supposed
to be a drill today?
[PA] and evacuate the school
[PA] in groups according to
class. I repeat: There is
an intruder on campus!
Damn! He's doing this
in broad daylight.
[PA] Follow your
teachers' instructions.
[MIGI] He has no concern for the
consequences of his actions.
[PA] Emergency protocols
are now in place.
He doesn't have the same
reasoning as Ryoko Tamiya.
[PA] Please remain calm and
be aware of your surroundings.
Guess not.
Where is she right now anyway?
[PA] There is a confirmed
intruder on school grounds.
She is approximately one‐hundred
fifty meters from here.
[PA] Everyone is ordered to
avoid Wing A completely.
It would seem that she intends
to observe our fight
[PA] Students are to follow
their teachers' instructions
from a safe distance.
[PA] and evacuate the school
in groups according to class.
That's better than fighting
both of them.
[PA] Make your way to
the stairs near Wing C.
Do not approach Wing A
under any circumstances.
Ms. Tamiya! She's gone?
Okay, come with me kids!
Don't push. Don't push!
I need everybody to stay in line
and keep moving.
Just follow me down
to the courtyard.
[MIGI] We will have to
fight him, Shinichi.
Fight him? But why?
It's daytime
in a crowded school.
He walked in here with
absolutely no regard
for being seen.
If we run,
he's sure to follow us.
It's better to finish him
here and now.
Plus, right now,
we have the advantage.
And we also have a plan.
Huh, a plan?
Hey, who the heck
have you been talking to?
Huh?! I'm just
thinking out loud.
Hey, isn't that him there?
That's gotta be him.
Huh? He's where?
Over there, that old guy.
[AKIHO] Oh, God!
What do you think he wants?
[SASAKI] Please, stay in line!
Keep moving!
[MIGI]
He's trying to pinpoint your...
No, he's trying to pinpoint
MY location.
However, the size of this crowd
is preventing him from
doing that.
[SHINICHI] And then what?
What's gonna happen?
What if he does find us?
[MIGI] Without a doubt,
he's going to attack us.
He will come full force,
affecting all those
who are around us.
Fortunately, that will
give us an opportunity.
Opportunity?
[MIGI] Yes.
[MIGI] While he's busy attacking
all the people around you,
I will be able to move in
swiftly and surprise him.
It's simple, and it has
a high probability of success.
All those people?
That's your plan?
[MIGI] Yes, that's the plan.
Mr. A will be encumbered by a
rather inconvenient obstacle:
a crowd of confused students.
A wall of flesh will protect us.
A "wall of flesh"?
I almost forgot
what a sicko you are!
Murano!
[SATOMI] Shinichi?
Get outta here!
Did you forget something?
I'll come wi‐
I said to go!
Get away from me!
(gasps)
Uh, I'm really sorry!
Just hurry up and
get out of here!
[SHINICHI] (panting)
[MIGI] What's wrong, Shinichi?
Do you not like my strategy
to fight Mr. A?
Of course I don't...!
How many need to die to do it?!
[MIGI] Does it matter?
It's for the sake of
self preservation.
Sacrificing others in order
to protect oneself...
That's simply the way that
all life forms maintain
their existence.
You know, you learned how
to speak like us.
But you don't understand
who we are at all, do you?
I just remembered...
Humans are very unique animals
that sometimes commit suicide.
It's not like anyone
WANTS to die.
[MIGI] What is it you're doing?
I have a better option
than a "wall of flesh".
C'mon, Class 3‐2,
you need to stay in line!
[SHINICHI] Are you angry, Migi?
[MIGI] Angry?
No, of course I'm not.
I have no time
for such things.
Shinichi, how do you think
we are different from Mr. A?
[SHINICHI] "Different"?
Well, he's a murderer.
And I'm a decent human being.
He can be someone else.
And I can't.
There's one of him.
And there's two of us.
[MIGI] Is that so?
[SHINICHI] (hmm?)
[MIGI] Do you think Mr. A sees
us as two separate entities?
I don't understand.
Here, this will be your weapon.
[SHINICHI] My weapon?
That's right. Mr. A and I are
equally matched in combat.
That leaves one obvious factor.
You are going to have to
join the fight.
If you allow yourself to become
flustered during the battle,
it will only hold me back,
and we will lose.
But if you are able to fight
effectively, we win.
Got it?
Fight "effectively"?
What's that mean?
[MIGI] In other words Shinichi,
we delegate our roles.
[SHINICHI] Do you think that's
really going to work?
[MIGI] It's our best option.
All that's left for you to do
now is conceal your weapon.
[SHINICHI]
The truth of the matter is,
Migi is way more skilled
at combat than I am.
I mean, he's even killed
two of his own kind.
I guess my only choice
is to trust him.
[MIGI] He's here, Shinichi.
Mr. A is within
three meters of us.
Three meters?!
Huh? But that's impossible!
He'd be right here!
[MIGI] Directly below us.
(gasps)
[A] Was that meant as
some sort of barricade?
The only thing you've
accomplished is to
block off your escape.
[SHINICHI]
Next time:
"Tangled Hair"