(running footsteps)
[SHINICHI] You're dead!
(gasps)
What the...
Uh...
(ah!)
It's not the one
I'm looking for...
But this one IS
one of those parasites.
Ah! Hey, wait a second!
[SHINICHI] What's wrong? Migi?!
[GUY] (ah... ah...)
[MIGI] I've determined that
his human brain is still intact.
It is?!
[GUY] (nervous laugh)
[PARASYTE] Whoa! That is crazy!
Just the hand?
[SHINICHI] (urk!)
How does THAT guy
have a human brain?!
No, he's telling the truth!
I really do have a human bra‐
[PARASYTE]
It's totally for real!
Can you believe this crap?
(crazy laughter)
[GUY] (umphf)
[MIGI] Yes, Shinichi, the
brain is indeed still intact.
From the lower half of his face
to the base of his neck,
perhaps down to his chest,
is the parasite.
Yep, that's right.
So, hey guys, that means
we're like practically the same!
[GUY] It was only a year
after we got married,
my wife ran off and left me.
She never really said anything
about what was wrong.
But my guess was
she just got tired of me.
I've never been the most...
exciting guy.
In fact, I'm so pathetic...
(waahhh... sobs)
I didn't even have the guts to
go through with killing myself.
It's really beautiful...
(thump)
[GUY] (waaah!) What is that?!
Go away! Shoo! Shoo, shoo!
(huh)
(urk)
(WAAAAHHHH!!)
And then, after all that, I‐
Oh, my God, he tells
the worst stories!
Now, your right hand should be
able to remember some of
this stuff.
So, y'see, my very first
and only thought
was to take over the brain
of a host, right?
So I start zippin' straight
for this guy's noggin.
But something's wrong...
[PARASYTE] What's happening?
It's not breathing.
If that doesn't change,
the body will die.
There's no time
to take the brain.
Neither one of us will make it.
So since he was about to eat it,
I had to just go for it and get
to merging as fast as I could.
(deep breath)
[MIGI] I see, very interesting.
Ya see, that's how
we wound up like this.
[GUY] (mmm...) (deep breath)
So, the problem is,
whenever I hand over the
talky part to this guy,
he just blathers and yaps and
puts everybody to sleep!
Quiet!
Anyway, I sure was
surprised to see you!
When this guy suddenly tells me
that one of my kind
is coming closer,
I was pretty nervous about
what sort of monster we
were gonna run into.
But when you showed up,
man, was I relieved.
I mean, wow! There are actually
other people out there
who're like me!
So, I am dying to know...
Tell me your story.
How'd you get like this?
[PARASYTE]
Yeah, yeah, totally! Tell us!
Sure, but before I do that,
do you think maybe we could go
somewhere else, please?
[PARASYTE] (hmm...)
My name's Shinichi Izumi.
And this is Migi.
The thing is, we need to stay
close to a certain place.
Ah, well, I'm Mamoru Uda.
And this guy, you can just
call him "Parasite."
That' s right, you can just
call me "Parasite".
Wait, where the heck did he go?
It's like he just disappeared.
[UDA] (sobbing)
That's awful!
It's just completely awful!
That's why you've stayed
so close to the hospital
this whole time?
It must be so hard.
I couldn't do it!
[SHINICHI] Yeah...
[PARASITE] I swear ta God, he
cries all the freakin' time.
I don't understand how
these humans operate at all.
[MIGI] I feel the
same way sometimes.
I can't help but notice.
Your Migi speaks quite well.
Huh? Oh, yeah...
Well, that's probably because
he reads whenever he
gets the chance.
Well, I learned how to talk
from watchin' a whole lotta TV.
I mean, all this guy does
is sit on the couch,
and watch old re‐runs and cry.
How about your host? Does he
spend all his time crying?
Hey, look, that is
just about enough!
Okay, I work at the hotel that's
just in the next town over.
And once he tells me one of
those things is around,
I will let you know.
[SHINICHI] Uh...
Please let us help you out!
I mean...
(beginning to sob)
You're the first person
I've met like me and‐
(sobbing)
[SHINICHI]
This guy really is a crybaby.
But I'm glad I met him.
It feels good to know that
I'm not the only one
out there like this.
[MIGI] Shinichi...
Shinichi!
It's really late, Migi.
What... what do you want?
This is very important.
I wanted to talk to you
earlier today,
but in meeting Uda and his
parasite, I missed my chance.
Did you notice, Shinichi?
First, you ran at the speed
of a seasoned athlete,
and then you jumped more than
three meters high.
What about it?
That doesn't seem odd to you?
Then I'll have to elaborate.
But first, about my own body...
See? Doing this kind of thing
takes practice, you know.
If I divide into
two parts like this,
each of the halves is still
fully capable of thought
and speech.
Wow...
But if I start dividing into
parts that are too small,
our intelligence will diminish
to where we're incapable
of thought,
much less rejoining together,
and those parts would be
unable to survive.
[SHINICHI] Huh... okay...
That's why,
whenever I do divide,
a consensus is
reached beforehand.
And it acts as a mantra,
an instinct to come
back together as one.
Uh, all right then,
I think I get it.
Then again, there are places
where even my smallest
fragments‐
They are still able to survive.
For example, a place where
there is a constant flow
of fresh blood.
In other words, they can
survive inside your body.
In my body?
Are you serious?!
[MIGI] Yes, that's right.
In fact, the Migi that's
talking to you right now
is actually only about seventy
percent of the original.
[SHINICHI] (gasps)
[MIGI] When I closed
the wound in your heart,
I instructed all my parts
to return to your right arm
via your bloodstream.
However, once it was restored,
your heart was much stronger
than I had expected,
so quite a lot of me was
dispersed throughout your body.
(hyperventilating)
[MIGI] They've become so small
that I can no longer
communicate with them.
Unbelievable...
Just when I thought you couldn't
tell me anything else that
could surprise me.
[MIGI] If there had been no
physiological changes,
I was going to
keep quiet about it.
Migi...
[MIGI] What is it?
You said throughout my body...
Does that mean even in my brain?
[MIGI] I don't know. But it's
not like those tiny fragments
have any consciousness.
I seriously doubt they would try
to enter the capillaries.
Is something bothering you?
[SHINICHI]
No, I'm sure it's nothing.
I'm probably just
over‐thinking things.
Before, I felt like my heart
was going to explode from
everything I was feeling,
but I still couldn't cry.
It was the
same thing today, too.
I mean, Uda started
bawling his eyes out
when he met someone like him
for the first time.
But not me...
How about your host?
Does he spend all
of his time crying?
A hole in my heart...
Hey, Maki...
Aww, how'd you know I was here?
Tell me somethin'.
Do I seem like
a normal person to you?
Huh? Of course you do.
What do you mean?
(sighs)
Oh, come on, what's going on?
You gotta give me
something here!
You... You haven't really
said anything to me.
Huh?
Back on the boat,
and even now, too...
It's like you just sit there
with this terrible look
on your face!
It's like...
You're crying inside,
but you're holding it all in!
It... it makes me worry.
[SHINICHI] Sorry.
Just... just forget it, okay?
(phone buzzes)
Oh, it's Uda.
[UDA] It's here now!
A parasite!
And I'm pretty sure it's
the one you're looking for!
[SHINICHI] (gasps)
[SHINICHI]
So, is it headed this way?
[UDA] No, it seems to have
noticed me and is coming closer.
I'm gonna try to stall it
somehow until you can
get over here.
[SHINICHI] No! That's crazy!
If that thing realizes that you
still have a human brain,
it's gonna try to kill you!
[UDA] (ah!)
[PARASITE]
'Bout another 100 meters!
Get outta there!
You need to run away right now!
[UDA] Uh, o‐okay I got it!
I'll make my way around the cape
and be there as soon as I can!
(running)
[MIGI] Shinichi,
I'm detecting one parasite.
[SHINICHI] One? It must be Uda.
[UDA] (panting)
Come on, it's gonna catch up!
Look, this is the
best I can do, okay?!
Well, it looks like that one's
learned to hone its host
and maximize its
physical potential.
There's no way we can beat it.
We've gotta get outta here!
No, we can't!
Shinichi and Migi
will be here soon.
We have to work together
to have a chance!
Then you gotta go that way.
It's the only hope we have
of not getting destroyed.
[MIGI] Shinichi...
[SHINICHI] Migi, can you
sense the other one yet?
[MIGI] No, I'm tired.
Huh?! No, no, not now!
I need sleep...
[SHINICHI] Come on, Migi!
You can't just let Uda and
his parasite die!
[MIGI] Shinichi,
You have to listen to me.
Hey!
[MIGI]
If possible, you should run.
Choose your own surviv... al...
Everything will be fine.
I just need to find Uda
before it's too late.
(panting)
[UDA] Oh, crap!
(heavy breathing)
What do we do?
There's nowhere else to go!
This is really bad!
Even if we get cornered here,
you and Shinichi can
still combine attacks.
(bushes rustling)
[UDA] (gasps)
(aahhh...)
You are the second
like this I've met.
The second one whose human
brain has remained intact.
As far as I am concerned,
you are nothing more than
an unfortunate mistake.
And you must be removed.
(waahhh!)
Whoa! That's what we're
supposed to really look like?
That's freakin' awesome!
Where could they be? Where?
(loud swish)
[UDA] (waahh!)
[UDA] (screams)
(umphf)
(ungh)
[UDA] I'm gonna die!
(umph!)
(muffled whimpers)
[NOBUKO]
You are clearly outmatched.
I am completely fused
with my host.
Your base remains human
which causes you to be
much less responsive.
[PARASITE] She's right.
You are totally slowing me down.
I can feel the effects of
your crappy conditioning.
But y'know, her attacks
are kinda repeating.
It's just like she's targeting
the same spot over and over.
She may be strong,
but she's not very creative.
This battle is all but done.
It is time for you to die now.
(muffled whimpers)
(ungh!)
In cases when it's difficult
to determine where
the parasite ends,
destroying the heart is
the best approach to
eradicating one's opponent.
[PARASITE] Yes, of course...
the heart...
(gasps) Another one of us?
Strange...
The signal is much too weak.
It's as if...
the parasite is asleep.
You're alive. My attack
should have terminated you.
Could it be that
my targeting was off?
No, that's not possible.
You were punctured through the
heart, yet somehow did not die.
Obviously, I should have
cut off your head as well.
Dammit...
Even the voice
is still the same.
I am gonna kill you now,
and it's gonna be quick.
(grr...)
Yeah, that's it, come on!
Like the disgusting
monster that you are!
You are going to die, too.
Like your friend.
(gasps) "My friend"?
What have you done to Uda?!
[NOBUKO] The signal from his
right hand is very weak.
It's almost as if
it's hibernating.
This human is all alone.
(swooshing)
What? Impossible!
How could normal human agility
be able to evade my attacks?
(swoosh!)
How is this happening?
[SHINICHI] I can see it...
I can see every move it makes!
It's completely different
from when I fought Mr. A!
There it is.
The tentacles move while
morphing at the same time!
[NOBUKO] Unbelievable.
(gasps) Uda!
(grr...)
He was the only one...
The one person in the world
who could understand what
I've gone through!
(gyah!)
[NOBUKO] I don't understand.
How is he able to
move like this?
The neck...
Aim for the neck up!
I cannot let it live.
(kyah!)
I will kill it!
I will kill this
goddamn monster!
(swoosh)
[NOBUKO] What is this?
He can't be human.
[SHINICHI] Don't worry, Mom...
I'm gonna hack that demon
right out of you!
(swoosh)
[SHINICHI] (ungh)
[NOBUKO] You fared
surprisingly well for a human,
but now it is time...
to die.
(gasps)
(splash)
(ungh)
Uda!
[UDA]
That... that thing wasn't...
really your mom, of course.
Even so...
I didn't feel like you should be
the one to have to do it.
[PARASYTE] But how?
How can you still be alive?
I could see right through
your attack pattern.
You aimed in the exact same
place, every single time.
So, I just moved the heart
and all the other vital stuff
out of the way,
and then let you think
you had taken me out.
(ungh...)
(waves crashing)
[SHINICHI] Mom...
It's over.
It's all over, Mom.
[SHINICHI] Thank you,
for everything. Take care.
[MAKIKO] Ah! I'll walk with you.
So, then...
you're all done here?
Uh... Yeah, I am.
Well, next time you come,
we should do some sightseeing.
No, I won't be
coming back here again.
You won't?!
Well, maybe someday...
Maybe someday you'll
change your mind.
[MAKIKO] Goodbye...
[DAD]
I wish I could say this better.
How can I put this?
I want you to understand this
one important thing, Son.
Right up until the very end...
No, even now, your mother
loves you very, very much.
And I love you and
your mom, too.
[SHINICHI] Dad...
I wanna ask you something
'bout what you saw.
Um...
The night everything happened...
did... did Mom...
Did... she...
Dad, did she suffer at all,
do you think?
No...
No, it all happened
way too fast.
Oh... okay.
(thump)
Shinichi?
(gasps)
It's him! He's here.
[SATOMI] Shinichi?
He's here! He's back!
Shinichi, hey!
Hey.
[SHINICHI]
Next time:
"Freezing Point"