[KUSANO]
Okay... as for the
detective himself...
[HIKAWA]
I'll deal with him...
What about the human
with the parasite arm?
Of course... Miki is
heading that way tomorrow.
[Firetruck sirens]
Hm?
Ah! Yoko! Yumi!
Oh!
[Shocked]
[Crying]
[MIKI]
Given your
situation...
I would imagine that
your combat style must
be truly unique.
Must be how you've dealt with
my kind so easily up until now.
But what I can't understand
is how having a human brain
still intact
could actually make
you stronger.
Judging by the condition
of the body left in
our dining area,
it would seem to indicate
your victory did not
happen instantly.
Hahaha...
What's wrong? Was that not an
appropriate moment to laugh?
So, how do you manage to do it?
I'd love to get a
demonstration of your
special fighting techniques.
Man... What's with this guy?
He's creepy as hell
and won't shut up.
[MIGI]
Stay alert...
He's only attempting to
figure us out right now.
And no matter how expressive
he may seem to you,
never forget that it's something
completely different
from actual human emotions.
Ohh... So you talk to each other
while you're fighting.
And that's an effective system?
Ah...
You certainly have impressive
speed and motion detection...
which means that bringing
you back in one piece
could prove to be
a rather difficult task.
[Shinichi grunting]
[MIGI]
There are too many blades!
So? Make more!
I'm afraid it doesn't
work that way.
There's a certain minimum
size requirement.
Ugh!
Hehehe...
[Panting]
That guy sure is pretty slow.
[MIGI]
True, you are faster
than he is...
but it's not as if you have
all that much stamina.
[Panting]
Yeah. I've been
running all day!
I'm really tired!
I agree. I am, too.
That fight was short
but very intense.
I guess we're pretty
pathetic aren't we?
[Labored breathing]
Okay, I think we've put
some distance between us.
[MIGI]
He's a new type of enemy.
Three‐in‐one this time.
So what about his legs?
His legs?
Well it's like you
told me in our
last fight...
that the human part
is the weakness.
If we can attack
his legs somehow...
Aah...
What's wrong?
We can't do it?
I'm worried...
I can't seem to get
a feel for how his
parasites are distributed.
But you said there
are three of them,
didn't you?
So they have
to be the head
and arms, right?
Logically, yes,
but something is wrong...
[Truck approching[
Uh...
[MIGI]
He's here. He caught up to us.
Ah!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! Oh!
[SHINICHI]
Here we go again.
[MIGI]
"Again"?
[MIKI]
Ugh!
I swear.
You sure do like to run.
And it's getting kind of old.
I guess I'll have to forget
about leaving your body intact.
Okay, it's time to gamble...
Let's aim for the legs,
just like you said.
Hm.
[MIGI]
I'll block the next
attacks that come
toward your right side.
You'll need to hold your
ground while dodging
attacks on the left side.
And how am I
supposed to do that?
[MIKI]
Huh?
[MIGI]
Peculiar.
Haha... Shall we finish?!
Ah!
What the‐?
[SHINICHI]
What was that?!
That was a
mid‐air collision,
and between his own
tentacles, no less.
Huh?!
I see his true nature
clearer now.
"True nature"?
Indeed... Seeing this new type
was quite a shock at first,
but he might turn out
to be mostly show.
I sure hope so.
As for the three parasites...
they're distributed through
more than his head and arms.
For instance, that leg
I was able to cut
earlier wasn't human.
It wasn't?!
Either way, I'm certain
that the head is,
in fact, the control center.
And I don't sense independent
thought in his arms' movements.
Look out.
I'll run as many
times as it takes!
I've found a good location.
Go into the woods right here.
[MIGI]
His control center
isn't that competent.
There's no cohesion to
his bodily movements,
which is why he falls down
and runs into himself.
Most importantly, his head
should be parasitic,
so why doesn't it morph
and join in the attack?
Good question!
I think the head has
a hard enough time
just governing the arms
and other parasite areas.
Meaning, the head has to
stay intact or the entire
system falls apart.
So, it's actually not
at all that difficult.
In the end,
he's just a single enemy.
Right... We'll fight here...
Stop running.
Rather than the legs or torso,
let's aim for the neck...
Severing the head is the
surest way to victory.
Y'think we can get to it?
We can! Whenever I give
you the signal,
I want you to run
directly toward him...
And at full speed.
What?!
You'll just have to trust me.
[MIKI]
Sigh! I'm really
getting tired of this.
Now don't you move!
[MIGI]
Use the trees as a shield
and maintain your distance.
Dodge his attacks by
moving in all directions.
If you avoid him by just
using a linear pattern,
he'll be able to learn our
movements and predict
our next move...
Until suddenly...
Now!
[MIKI]
Huh?
[MIGI]
From his perspective,
a prey that has done
nothing but run away
now is suddenly
coming at him.
Parallel becomes perpendicular,
horizontal becomes vertical...
For someone struggling just
to control his tentacles,
he won't be able to
track our trajectory.
Haa!
Yeah!
[MIGI]
Gasp!
What's wrong?
I didn't know...
that was possible!
[GOTO]
Now it's my turn.
Uh...
Get over here, Miki.
[MIKI]
Yeah, sorry 'bout that.
[GOTO]
Irrelevant. As I suspected,
you're better suited to
remain a subordinate.
[MIGI]
So there weren't really
three of them.
What?!
Look. He is now
completely one being.
In an instant, he took control
of the entire body and
became a single life form.
But just before that happened,
his consciousness split into
five separate pieces.
In other words, there are a
total of five parasites
in that one body!
Ah‐no way!
When the first one was
acting as the head,
I felt that there were three
because he wasn't capable
of unifying all of them
at the same time.
Yes, that's correct.
Only Miki and I can act
as the controller.
And only I am able to unify
all of us together.
Wow...
[MIGI]
Yes.
But now is not the
time to be impressed.
It seems we must've come
quite some distance
while I was asleep.
We've met before.... Yes?
It's that guy!
He moves different
from before!
Gah! Ah!
[MIGI]
Not even apes can
move like that!
Being in the woods is now
a disadvantage for us!
Ugh! Ah!
[GOTO]
He's quite fast...
For a human.
[Truck approching]
Excuse me!
Uh?! No!
Let's go.
Ah!
[Panting]
Well...
What?!
[MIGI]
Very impressive.
Ah!
[Blades clashing]
Hm? What in the...?
Aaa... holy...
son of ah..!
Uh... What do we do?
[Scared wimpering]
WAAAAHHHH!
Hmm?
[Tires screech]
[Driver]
I don't know
what's going on...
But I'm getting'
the hell outta here!
[Engine starting]
I can't believe that
bastard just drove off!
What the hell?!
Hey, are you
okay there pal?
[Grunt]
My body is feeling weary from
the loss of so much blood...
I will need some more.
Blood?
Uh... Ah!
Ah!
A‐ah! Ugh!
[KUBO]
I understand your pain
all too well. But, sir‐
Is there a detective
here named Hirama?
Hirama?
Yes, Chief?
You can go on now.
[Walking out, door closes]
Kuramori...
I'm going to put aside
for the time being
how it is you've even
come to know...
Inspector Hirama.
Because I think you know
something more important.
About the parasites.
[Gulp]
[Sobbing]
[Scream]
Sigh...
[MIGI]
Shinichi, you need
some new clothes.
We stand out too much.
And we need to eat.
I would. But I don't
have any money.
Uh...
Ah! Migi where did
you get that?
From that truck
driver earlier.
Before you say it,
I am not human,
and I don't want
to hear any lectures
about your human
laws and morals.
You're my hand, y'know?
I did this out of necessity
to preserve my own life.
Listen, even though you
and I are completely
different life forms...
we have developed
an alliance...
and we must respect
one another.
With that in mind,
what do you think is the
common purpose that unites us?
To survive.
[SHINICHI]
Yeah, but it's still stealing.
[MIGI]
Indeed.
[TV]
Police have now revealed
more information about the
grisly slayings of
Mr. Kuramori's wife
and daughter,
Hm? What tha? "Kuramori"?
saying that a bladed weapon
was used in the attack.
Furthermore, Kuramori's office,
which handled private
investigations,
burned to the ground the same
night in what is believed to
have been an act of arson.
Police have said that they plan
to question Kuramori
about any possible connection
between the two incidents.
[MIGI]
They must have decided he's
too dangerous to be kept alive.
His family was probably
just collateral damage.
Most likely their primary
target, the detective, escaped.
I have to get ahold of my Dad!
[Phone ringing]
[IZUMI]
Shinichi...?
It's late, where are you?
Everything okay?
[SHINICHI]
Dad, listen to me.
You need to get out of
the house... Right now!
Tell me what's
going on, Shinichi.
[SHINICHI]
A lot of things...
I can't come home
for a while.
Why not?! Talk to me,
tell me what's going on!
But Dad...
There's no way I can tell
him everything I know!
I have to hurry.
I gotta get him outta there!
[Deep breath]
Okay. Look, Dad...
Haven't I... Haven't I been
a good kid and followed
the rules and anything?
And y'know, ever since
Mom's been gone I've tried
really hard to help out,
and be someone
you can trust...
Dad, I promise, this isn't
some kind of stupid prank.
So, Dad, please!
You have to get out of
the house right now!
A monster is coming!
And it's the same one
that killed Mom alright!
Huh?
Sigh...
Shinichi please tell me
that you're safe.
Yes, Dad. I am.
All right then...
I'll leave here
for now, son...
Your father believes
in you okay.
That's good...
Thanks, Dad.
[HIRAMA]
My name is Hirama.
My sincere condolences
for the loss of your
wife and child.
Currently, they're still
being examined for
forensic evidence,
but what I've already seen
has confirmed my beliefs.
Right now, I'd like
to hear what your
thoughts are.
You need justice!
Hm...?
Justice, huh?
That's right.
[Quivering]
Sigh...
Since I was a boy...
I've always admired
the great detectives...
Heh... You know, like...
like Sherlock Holmes...
but things don't always
go as planned,
I managed to become
a PI at least...
[Crazy giggles]
Okay now listen here‐
You could be...
a great detective.
Can we...
can we avenge their deaths?
Of course we can!
I... I have some
information.
Mm‐hm.
But I'm afraid
I'm a little
messed up right now.
Can I have something
to write with...
and go somewhere
I can calm down first.
Absolutely.
[MIGI]
No, this isn't telepathy.
[SHINICHI]
How many times
is this now?
It's our sixteenth time
to meet in your dreams...
Though I'm sure you'll
just forget again.
Yeah but, you don't
look anything at all
like the Migi I know
in the real world.
You say the same thing
every time we do this.
But then, you don't
look like the Shinichi
that I know
in reality, either.
What, you're
already going?
I've now determined that
there's simply no way
for me to communicate with
the thirty percent of my cells
that still remain scattered
throughout your body.
So there's no point
in meeting in your
dreams anymore..
More importantly, our current
situation in the real world
is such that there's
no time to lose on
such trivial matters.
I should go.
Is that so...?
You'll remember
when you wake up.
Migi!
Huh?
What was I...?
It's cold...
You mean both of them were
failures? Unbelievable.
The real failure was on my part
in allowing the two of you
to deal with the investigator.
Killing the family without
getting rid of him first
shows your complete ignorance
regarding human nature.
The room was dark
when we got there...
At any rate, it will
be simple enough just
to kill him next, correct?
[TAMURA]
You underestimate the
humans a little too much.
True, individually,
they seem like
incapable creatures...
But that is not the case.
You need to recognize
something that's
very important...
The human race
is actually a
single life form
comprised of billions
of separate parts.
In addition to their
individual brains,
they possess a single,
collective "consciousness."
And when we oppose that...
we are truly defeated.
[KUSANO]
"Defeated"?
Is she truly one of us?
Something's different...
Something's not right.
[SATOMI]
Shinichi wasn't at
school again today...
And yesterday, he was
acting like something
was going on again...
[YUKO]
Murano.
Huh?
[YUKO]
Got something for ya...
Here... Shinichi forgot it
and left it behind.
You should totally go
take it back to him.
Wha...? But I...
It'll be a chance for you
two to patch things up.
If you won't take it
back to him, then I will!
Mm!
[Knocking on door]
[MITA]
Mr. Kuramori?
He duped us.
It's not like
he's a suspect,
so why do you think
he'd run off?
Huh?
A list of partners...
Reiko Tamura!
[KURAMORI]
Yoko, Yumi...
I will avenge you
with my own hands!
Reiko Tamura, you're dead.
[KUSANO]
Reiko Tamura...
No. She is not one of us.
She's dangerous...
She's a threat...
a threat to our kind.
[TAMURA]
You are such a mystery...
In a world of
so much confusion.
Why was I...
No. Why were we born?
[Doorbell]
[SATOMI]
I didn't think so...
Where are you...?
And are you safe, Shinichi?
[KURAMORI]
It was you.
YOU are the one who
dragged me into this hell!
[TAMURA]
Three of them.
And their intent seems
less than peaceful.
[KURAMORI]
Where's she going?
All right...
While I still
have the chance...
Good evening, Tamura.
We can try to hide them,
but they can't be
suppressed, can they?
The strongest signals
that we emit
are those which
harbor animosity...
I know of your intentions.
Get on with it.
[SHINICHI]
Next time:
"The Adventure of
the Dying Detective"