[school bell chiming]
[YUKO] Hey, Shinichi.
Huh?
Did you hear what happened?
You know, about the girl
who got killed in the next town
over? She, um...
Yeah, I heard about that!
There's like a ton of
rumors going around!
And I heard the body was found
by none other than you,
Shinichi!
Good grief, Akiho!
[STUDENTS] (surprised chatter)
[YUKO] (grr...)
(hmm?)
You okay?
Mm‐hm, what about you?
All right, I guess.
So, um...
[SATOMI] (hmm?)
The other day...
we were supposed to
go see a movie.
But uh...
Yeah, well everything happened.
It's just awful.
[SHINICHI] Yeah...
[HIROKAWA]
In spite of all the many
feeding locations we prepared,
he chose to feed
outside the
designated areas,
and was therefore
killed.
It's an unfortunate incident.
[KUSANO] Not only did he allow
himself to give in to the
immediacy of hunger,
he fought against his own kind,
which is very selfish.
He acted as though
he were an animal.
We're better off he's dead.
[GOTO]
If only it were that simple.
We have now provided the humans
with another sample for
them to examine.
And of course, the perpetrator
has yet to be revealed.
Do you think this could've been
done by a human?
Yes...
and we know exactly who it was.
[KUSANO] The boy who found
the dead human female.
[TAMURA] Shinichi Izumi.
He was probably enraged
when he saw that his friend
had been killed.
He was "enraged"?
His "friend"?
Are you saying that this boy's
brain is entirely human?
Yes, his brain remains intact.
And he's coexisting
with his parasite.
He's quite a valuable specimen.
[KUSANO] "Valuable specimen"?
He could also be viewed
as a threat.
Right now, I am making an effort
to ensure a more secure future
for all of us.
I'd like you to consider my
research on him as part of that.
Very well, I'll leave the matter
of this boy in your hands
for now then.
Oh yes, and by the way...
How is your child, Tamura?
Just like a normal human child.
(baby crying)
[TAMURA] Though I am rearing it
with human assistance.
Oh, goodness.
(baby crying)
Oh, what's the matter?
What can I do for you?
I already changed your diaper.
Whatcha' need?
(door closing)
Mommy's home.
[KEIKO]
Well, hello, welcome back.
(baby crying)
Be quiet.
(baby stops crying)
(gasps)
[TAMURA] I've trained it well,
haven't I?
Huh?!
Thanks for your help.
Please do come back again
tomorrow.
O‐of course!
If you'll excuse me!
(terrified gasp)
(door opening &amp; closing)
For me to conduct
the proper experiments,
it will need to grow a little
more first.
(phone ringing)
[KURAMORI] I've followed
him around for a week,
but so far I've found nothing
much out of the ordinary.
It's intriguing that his
mother's gone missing,
and that he was also
recently a witness
in that high‐school girl's
mysterious grisly murder.
Otherwise, he seems like
a completely average
high‐school student.
Yes, yes, that's correct.
[TAMURA] I understand.
Please continue
your investigation.
An average high‐school student?
Human observational skills
are less than impressive.
However, there are some things
that only humans can do.
I couldn't test him using
Hideo Shimada, but...
Perhaps...
I can arrange something.
(uh?)
You're Shinichi Izumi, right?
[THUG] (low chuckle)
(sounds of fighting)
[SHINIICHI] All right,
who put you up to this?
Uh, it was...
it was a woman.
[SHINICHI]
A woman? What's her name?
[THUG] I don't know.
She just came up to us today.
I'd never seen her before.
[KAMIJO] Yo!
Kamijo...
Why're ya looking so miserable
first thing in the mornin',
little man?
C'mon, I don't look that bad,
do I?
Are things going good
with your girlfriend?
Y'mean good like how?
Don't play dumb with me.
Have ya done it yet or what?
[SHINICHI] What? No, cut it out.
It's nothing like that.
[KAMIJO] Aww, whatever...
Hey!
This is a tough subject for me
to bring up with you, but...
there are some rumors
about... Shinichi.
[SATOMI] Huh?
I've heard that HE found the
body in the latest murder,
and that the dead girl was
actually a friend of his.
Yes, I knew that.
So, what else about it?
Has your brother
found out anything?
No, nothing so far.
Don't you think it's weird,
after something like that
happened,
Shinichi is so calm?
He's kinda acting
a little too normal.
[GIRLS] (uh!)
[SHINICHI] Morning.
Uh, see you later, Murano.
So, what's with her?
Oh, it's nothing.
Even back when...
when he saved my life,
he seemed so calm and strong.
It was almost like...
he was someone else.
But still...
was there really nothing
between him and Kana?
No, that's not the point.
Even if nothing WAS going on,
he's still kind of... cold.
Are you‐
Oh, sorry! I have to...
to run some errands.
[SHINICHI] Oh... Huh? Uh...
[KURAMORI]
Okay, I might have something.
This kid has some
incredibly fast moves.
It's amazing.
I mean look at this!
Okay then, did you happen
to notice anything else
about him?
Huh, well, whaddya mean?
Well, like...
something unnatural...
For example, did the movements
of his right hand seem
peculiar in any way?
Ah, well, I dunno.
I don't really remember
anything like that.
If that's the case,
some unique variation
must have occurred.
(dog barking)
[SHINICHI] I wonder
what's wrong with Murano?
Maybe...
maybe she's just worried,
because of everything
that happened to Kana.
(ah!)
Hang on... Of course!
She's supposed to be worried.
With all the stuff that's
been going on lately,
I'm the one being weird for
acting so calm about it.
That's exactly what's it is!
[MIGI]
What are you talking about?
You make an excellent
human being.
You can separate yourself
from needless emotions.
Migi, you're not helping.
You're making me lose
even more confidence.
[MIGI] In any case, you can
sometimes be overheard
when speaking to me.
Whenever you grow more agitated,
your voice becomes loud enough
for your father
to find it strange.
(knock at door)
[SHINICHI] Dad?
[DAD] Hm?
I'm going out for a bit.
All right,
don't stay out too late.
[SHINICHI] Right.
(typing on keyboard)
[KURAMORI] A bit late
to be going out, kid.
This is the same town where
that girl was murdered.
So you find the body
of your friend,
and now you're going back to
the scene of the crime?
Something's going on.
The way he was moving earlier,
and now whatever this is...
What're you up to Shinichi?
What're you hiding?
[MIGI] Shinichi...
What are we doing here?
I can't explain it, but...
The way I am now...
It's like, more and more,
I just forget about anything
that's painful or sad.
It simply disappears.
[MIGI] And is that wrong?
I was never like this before.
I used to obsess over the
smallest things.
I worried all the time.
[MIGI] That, of course,
is a waste of energy.
[SHINICHI] That's not the point!
Who're you talking to?
Yourself?
[SHINICHI] I think Kana
was out looking for ME
and ended up following
that monster instead.
And it got her killed.
It was because of me!
[MIGI] You really
shouldn't think like that.
No, for her,
I need to try to...
This might sound kinda strange,
but I want to be able
to mourn Kana's death.
I don't want to forget
what sadness feels like.
I'm a human being.
Uh‐huh...
[KURAMORI] (uh!)
(huh?!)
[MIGI] (baah!)
[KURAMORI] (waah!)
Ah, Jesus Christ!
(uhn) Migi,
what the hell're you doing?!
[MIGI] What do you think?
I'm going to kill him.
[KURAMORI] (waah!)
[SHINICHI] Wait! Stop it!
(waah!)
Run for it! Hurry!
[KURAMORI] (uhhh...)
Shinichi, don't interfere!
[SHINICHI]
What are you doing?! Run!
[KURAMORI] (waah!)
[KURAMORI] (ungh!)
[SHINICHI] (AHHH!)
[KURAMORI] (WAAH!) (ungh)
I don't have the body mass
to cut him in half.
[KURAMORI] (waah!)
Not good.
He's getting farther away.
[KURAMORI] Someone, help me!
[MIGI] Tch!
[SHINICHI] Migi...
Look, do you seriously
not understand
the position you're in now?!
We've just been seen up close
by some complete stranger!
And he had a camera!
Let's go!
Follow him...
[SHINICHI] (ahhh!)
and kill him!
No way! We can't kill him!
(ungh...)
Migi... stop it!
[MIGI]
Shinichi, I don't understand,
you've seen a great number
of humans die already.
So, what's the difference
if one more dies right now?
Besides, it's for
our own protection!
[SHINICHI] (umphf!)
There's no reason to hesitate!
Just forget it! I won't!
That's going too far!
I'm tired...
[SHINICHI] Killing humans
is out of the question.
We can't do that.
I don't care
what the reason is.
[MIGI] He's gone.
It would be too late to
catch him now anyway.
[DAD] You sure took your time.
Did something happen to ya?
No, Dad.
Everything's okay.
Get some sleep.
(birds twittering)
[MIGI] That male appears to have
been targeting you specifically
in his investigations.
Which means that, even though
he knows a lot about us,
we do not know
anything about him.
[MIGI] If that man turns out
to be a police officer or
someone in the media,
or a member of
some government agency,
then I'm afraid
we're already done for.
And if that's the case, we'll be
made into lab rats for sure.
[SHINICHI] Lab rats...
Shinichi?
Oh‐
(sighs)
You're a damn monster!
Have you really
been eating people?!
You... You stay away from me!
[STUDENTS] (angry muttering)
[YUKO] Leave me alone, Shinichi!
[GUY] Who do you think you are?!
[YUKO] I don't know you anymore!
[GUY] Get out of here!
[STUDENTS] (angry muttering)
[TEACHER] Mr. Izumi?
[TEACHER] Mr. Izumi?!
[TEACHER] Hey!
[SHINICHI] (gasps)
Pull your head out and wake up.
It's your turn to read
the next section.
If you're not going to make an
effort, then just leave!
[TEACHER]
Uh... What are you doing?!
Holy crap, he totally just left.
Shinichi...
(door closing)
(clock ticking loudly)
They'll come for us.
I know it.
They're going to come get me
and turn me into an experiment.
But before that happens,
it's possible that one of
my kind could eliminate us.
Either way, there will
certainly be consequences.
You can count on that.
[SHINIHCI] Whaddya I do?
What the hell should I do?!
Maybe I should just
cut my arm off right now.
While Migi's still asleep!
No, I can't.
Who was that guy?
Who's after me?
After us?
I bet... I bet he's still
watching, right this minute!
[LITTLE GIRL] (distorted)
Mommy! Over here!
[MOTHER] Saki, please wait!
(dog barking)
[REPORTER] Next up, for the
traffic report with
Mr. Fukada from Metro.
(whacking)
(doorbell)
Package for a Mr. Bulat.
[KURAMORI] (ragged panting)
[SHINICHI] (gasps)
(waah!)
[SHINICHI] Hey! Don't go!
Listen to me!
Please just hear me out! Please!
(door closing)
Why is this...
Why is this happening to me?
It's not fair...
I don't deserve this!
(ungh...)
I seem to be able
to calm down in seconds.
That's just how
my body works now.
I guess there's
no turning back.
In which case...
it's time.
What's up?
[SHINICHI] (huh?)
What did you want to
meet with me about?
[SHINICHI]
Uh, well... It's, uh...
I wanted to ask about Yuko.
[SATOMI] Huh?
[SHINICHI] I mean, um...
She's back to her regular,
cheerful self again.
She didn't even get
a scar or anything.
Did you seriously call me
out here just to tell me that?
Ah! No, uh... not really.
I just wanted...
to talk while we still could.
Come on!
That makes it sound like
you won't ever see me again.
[SHINICHI] Uh, that's not it.
Shinichi,
you seem kind of depressed.
The truth is,
I'm a little off myself.
Hey, is it okay if I go first?
Uh... Sure.
[SATOMI] I've been trying
not to let it get to me,
but I just can't help myself.
It's about... Kana.
You canceled our date that day
so you could meet up with her,
right?
It was for something important,
wasn't it?
At least,
something more important
than going to see
a movie with me?
I... I've wanted to tell you
about so many things!
[SATOMI] So tell me!
Just say something!
Shinichi,
you can tell me anything!
(sighs) You've been preoccupied
with something for a while now,
haven't you?
And not about what
happened to Kana.
What is it?
[SHINICHI] Nothing.
[SATOMI] You're lying!
You look miserable.
And whatever it is,
it's so big that
even someone dying
isn't enough to really
shock you anymore!
Come on, Shinichi! What is it?!
That's not...
That's not how it is, okay?
Shinichi, you're so strong.
I really think you are.
But even so, there are times
when I simply can't bear
to look at you.
I can see you trying so
desperately to hold
something back.
Please, what happened to you?
Don't do this by yourself;
talk to me.
I wish...
(gasps)
No, no!
Nothing's going on, really.
(whimpers)
How can you possibly expect me
to believe nothing's wrong?!
Forget it!
I can't even talk
to you anymore!
No, please don't say that.
I need you... I need you...
I need you more than anything!
I'll tell you!
Yeah! I'll tell you!
Murano,
something happened to me.
I have a... I have a...
There's nothing going on.
(gasps) (whimpers)
[SATOMI]
It's like you don't trust me.
Look, if you won't believe me,
then what can I do?
Shinichi, your eyes...
your eyes have no... tears.
[SHINICHI]
Next time,
"The Selfish Gene"