[SHINICHI] That look on
her face...
I hate her.
I hate everything about her!
She doesn't deserve to...
[MIGI]
Shinichi, calm down.
We'd be in trouble
if we had to fight
while your breathing
was this irregular.
I know.
[TAMURA]
There's so much I'd hoped to
discuss with the two of you,
but I can feel a strong
sense of imminent threat...
so I'll have to make this a
bit shorter than I'd planned.
I've killed at least
38 people so far.
Uh...
Most of which
were for food...
But to tell you the truth,
I'd say that figure is
quite low among my kind.
I was able to sustain
myself with the same food
humans normally eat.
What I've found is that
consuming humans is
completely unnecessary
in order for my kind
to survive.
I've done a fair amount
of study on your species...
Searching to find exactly what
we parasites are to you...
and, in turn, what you
are you to us.
The conclusion I reached is
that we are two halves...
of the same whole...
Parasites and humanity
are of one family...
We are the
children of mankind.
Huh? What was that?!
What kind of bullshit
are you talking about?
Of course, given your
human emotions,
I'm sure this is hard
to grasp...
But...
We are actually quite frail.
We're nothing more than
a life form that isn't
able to survive on its own.
So, please...
Don't be too hard on us.
You've got to be
kidding me.
Go to Hell.
[MIGI]
Hmm...
Hm?
Interesting...
[TAMURA]
You two are extremely
rare beings...
and that's exactly why
I wanted the chance
to share my thoughts
with you...
And also to give you an
important word of advice.
It's in regards to Goto,
the man who's been
pursuing you as of late.
You should avoid doing
battle with him.
If you had started facing
off against Goto first
rather than Miki,
I'm quite certain
you'd be dead already.
[MIGI]
Probably so.
Huh?
[TAMURA]
He is one of the most
"frail" among us ‐
a being I created through
experimentation...
But he's invincible.
You do know you
just contradicted
yourself, right?
Hehe...
Hahaha...
She's laughing.
[Footsteps]
And then there's
the Mayor, Hirokawa...
[HIRAMA]
Shinichi Izumi?
[SHINICHI]
I'm pretty sure that's
Detective Hirama...
That means, all these guys...
must be cops.
[HIRAMA]
At first glance it all
looks so normal ‐
a mother holding a baby...
and a young high school
kid in the park.
But one is a known parasite.
And the other found the
body of his own friend
murdered by a parasite.
And here they are, together.
Right after another murder.
What is this?
What in the hell
are you two up to?
Shinichi Izumi...
There's a lot more to you
than you're letting on.
[KURAMORI]
And there's some blood...
my blood got on
the baby's clothes.
Stay back! Hold on.
Hold your position!
Now then.
You're Reiko Tamura?
Correct?
Excuse me?
And you just killed a man.
His name was Kuramori!
Oh! Uh...
What is this?
Then I'll have to ask
the other one.
Ikeda!
Hm?
What the hell are
you doing here?
You and I have met before.
You do remember me,
don't you?
So if you're the same
person that I met,
then you should be able
to say my name.
So tell me, who am I, Ikeda?
Well I uh...
It sounds like you forgot
my name, Mr. Hirama.
Hehe...
Okay that one would
seem to be human.
Well. You appear to
be quite calm and
collected, Ms. Tamura.
I do believe you've mistaken
me for someone else.
From this short of a distance...
I feel quite confident
that I would not miss.
[Tamura acting scared]
Is this some sort
of sick joke?!
You people are crazy!
Leave me alone!
I'd be deeply sorry
if I were wrong...
but I'm afraid I'm
out of options now...
and I can't risk
getting any closer.
Now you listen to me!
I am accountable for
whatever happens here...
It's on me!
Don't do this!
I don't know what
your talking about!
[Others gasp]
Hirama wait.
[Gunshot]
[Birds fly off]
Uh? Huh?
[Normal voice]
Well done, you were right...
[Spits]
Fire! Fire!
Stop it!
The baby's human!
[Continuous shooting]
[HIRAMA]
Shinichi Izumi! Get back!
[MIGI]
Shinichi! Stay here!
But Migi...
[Continuous shooting]
[Distant shots]
[SATOMI]
This can't
be happening...
There's no way, right?
You're not involved in this,
are you, Shinichi?
No. You wouldn't be
caught in this...
No! You can't be!
Shinichi please!
Uh...
[Shooting continues]
[Continuous shooting]
[Migi]
Curious...
Why won't she fight back?
She's coming toward us...
She must have something
up her sleeve.
Fall back now, Shinichi. Run!
[TAMURA]
Shinichi...
Uh...
Wait, Shinichi. Wait.
You can't leave me just yet.
I need to speak to you...
I need to speak to
your humanity?
Oh...
[TAMURA / NOBUKO]
Shinichi.
Mother...
[MIGI]
Don't let her fool you!
It's a trap. Remember the
hole in your heart!
[Shooting continues]
Please don't.
Whoa. Stop! Hold your fire!
Stop! Don't shoot or
you'll hit the boy.
Something's wrong here.
I've been thinking...
for a long time...
About why...
Why was I even brought to
this world in the first place?
As soon as I would
resolve one question...
another one would
inevitably take its place.
I've sought the beginning...
And I've sought the end.
I've walked alone for so long...
always thinking...
wondering...
Perhaps nothing will change
no matter how far I go.
So even if I stop,
it will still
remain the same.
And if someone were to
tell me it was all over,
I wouldn't be fazed.
But today...
today I finally
found the answer...
to one of my questions.
Shinichi...
In the end...
I never did anything
to harm this child.
This perfectly normal,
beautiful child.
Please make sure it's
raised in a normal way...
by human hands.
Yes of course. I will.
Hm. Thank you so much.
[MIGI]
Uh... "Thank you"?
You know Shinichi...
I recently tried to...
to laugh like a human
in front of a mirror.
And I believe...
It felt rather pleasant.
Ahh...
[Gasp]
[SHINICHI]
She's dead...
[MIGI]
I don't understand.
I'm sure she could have
fought well if she'd wanted to.
Or at least run away.
[Baby crying]
Huh?
[SHINICHI]
I'm so sorry
little guy.
I know. I know.
Your mom is gone now,
isn't she?
She's gone...
Your mom is...
Mom...
[NOBUKO]
Shinichi.
[Splash]
Are you okay, Shinichi?
Did you get any on you?!
Are you hurt?
You have to meet once again
with whomever
created this hole...
It's dead.
Its heart stopped.
[Gasp]
It was just so embarrassing...
I could never tell...
anyone...
[SHINICHI]
They're dead...
All of them...
they're dead... they're dead...
[SHINICHI]
Life...
Life will be absorbed
by this tree.
Shinichi!
You... you will...
come back, right?
...come back, right?
Uhh...
[Door opens]
Oh!
We're back home.
I'm so glad.
Hm...
Hmm...
[NOBUKO]
What's wrong, Shinichi?
I just had a...
a really sad...
a really sad dream...
[Baby crying]
Uh...
Mm... Uh?
[SATOMI]
Shinichi?
Shinichi, you're here!
You did come back.
Huh...
Yeah, I did...
[Somber music plays]
[Camera clicks]
[YUKO]
Murano.
Huh?
How's Shinichi?
He's fine, and it looks like
he'll be coming back to
school pretty soon.
Well that's good.
So, like what happened?
He just left all of a sudden,
and never said
where he was going!
Uh‐uhh...
Mm...
I'm sure she doesn't
want to talk about that.
Let's go.
Hmm...
[SATOMI]
What happened in
the park that day...
didn't even make the news.
But still...
Shinichi's back.
He came back.
[SATO]
So, you'll be having
lunch in here.
Make yourself
comfortable.
So how'd it go?
Man, I'm worn‐out.
Well, he looks just a
little bit too calm
for someone his age,
don'tcha think?
[MIYAKE]
True, he does seem to be
surprisingly level‐headed,
but well, there are people out
there with an easy temperament.
Although, I'm not sure
he really has this ability
the detectives are
looking for.
Not anywhere in the
same league as the
other guy, anyway.
Oh, good grief...
So he's really the
only candidate?
Yeah, unfortunately so.
[URAGAMI]
Dogs and cats...
And monkeys and
birds and bears...
it's all such
a waste of time.
I never told anyone that
I could talk to animals.
You guys do get that, right?
Just shut up
and move it.
So, which little critters
will it be today?
[URAGAMI]
Humans.
Hm... Humans?
Hahaha...
Aah, that's just
great! Haha!
It means that the true
test is finally at hand.
Oh, is that so?
After all this time, now you
wanna hear what I have to say?
Please, sir...
I'm innocent, Mr. Detective!
Believe me.
Hahaha!
Nothing?
Come on that was good.
Shut your damn mouth.
[HIRAMA]
Get his cuffs.
[Knock on door]
[IZUMI]
Yeah?
[Door opens]
Um, Shinichi Izumi...
I need you to come
with me, please.
[SHINICHI]
Okay.
No matter what
they ask me,
I have to keep Migi's
existence a secret...
I should calm myself down,
one last time...
[Deep breathing]
This'll be the
last thing, 'kay.
Oh, alright.
[Hirama over headset]
Okay, Uragami.
This is your chance to
prove your ability
to us once and for all.
Alright, please go ahead
and have a seat here
and wait to receive
your instructions.
Sure.
[Hirama over headset]
You're going to be
meeting five people...
I want you to find which
one of them is like you...
A human that has
your same ability...
You did say you could recognize
it if you met one, right?
[URAGAMI]
Yeah yeah, that's right,
I can tell.
[Blow]
I think I can...
[HIRAMA]
And, let us know if
they've been infected.
Wait, what?!
So you're bringing one of those
monsters in here with me?!
What the hell are you thinking?
Hey, goddammit!
This glass isn't gonna
be able to keep me safe!
You can't just leave me in here
and let me get eaten by
one of those things!
It's all right. Stop worrying.
That is thick,
bullet‐proof glass.
And it's also
soundproof.
[Miyake over speaker]
Right, let's begin. Mr. Fukami?
Hmm?
Please come in.
Okay.
Tch!
[HIRAMA]
Hey, Uragami.
Knock it off
and look at him!
Yeah, yeah.
What are your thoughts?
Hmm...
Well, I can tell that...
this guy's not a parasite.
There is only a minimal
response to my telepathy.
He's keeping his thoughts
very tightly guarded...
so it's rather difficult
for me to determine if he
has the same ability I do.
Well I guess what he's
saying at least sounds
plausible, doesn't it?
Hehe... I really should
mention this up front...
All of the self‐proclaimed
"psychics" in that room...
are most likely full of crap.
But if any of them
actually had such powers ‐
or, rather,
finely honed abilities ‐
It'd be this guy
who has the best chance.
Okay? Whatcha think?
Chubs over there
is a total hack...
I want you to
tell him something.
"Lying's the first step down
the path of wickedness."
Well you'd know!
Yeah, great advice coming
from a serial killer...
[MIYAKE]
Okay, next candidate, please.
Huh?
[HIRAMA]
What's the
matter, Uragami?
You are screwed up,
Detective...
You know what bein' in
prison's like, right?
If you put a hottie like this
in front of me, then...
Mmph!
Huh?
Ooohh...
[Uragami groaning]
Is he... godammit!
Arhh...
So‐uh shouldn't we maybe
stop him, Inspector..?
This is probably affecting
his concentration.
Hehehaha...
[SATO] Oh dear God!
Ah! He's one! He's one of
the parasites for sure!
Eww... Disgusting...
Where ya goin?
Aw don't leave,
I'm not done yet! Baby?
Well this has been
a waste of time.
Hmmm.
[MIYAKE]
Mr. Izumi, sorry for the wait.
You may go in now.
Right.
You aren't able to
hear each other,
so there's no need
to hold back, okay?
[HIRAMA]
Now tell me, what do you
think of this man?
Well, I... I don't know.
[HIRAMA]
For some reason, you tend to
encounter parasites quite often.
Most recently, you were
approached by the parasite
known as Reiko Tamura.
Maybe there's something about
you that attracts them...
Or perhaps...
You somehow have a way
of telling them apart
from the rest us.
[SHINICHI]
Stay calm.
If I can just be calm,
It'll be fine.
No, sir.
[HIRAMA]
I can't help but think...
this is the partner Kuramori
was trying to tell me about...
just before his death...
But mentioning his name...
seems to have no effect on him.
But it's hard to believe
a kid could bluff
his way through this
without ever cracking.
I think that piece
a shit is asleep!
What the hell?!
[HIRAMA]
Dammit, Uragami!
Wake your ass up!
Uh... Hehe...
That chick really
wore me out...
Heh, heh. Huh?
We're still doing this?
You got a cute face there, boy.
I bet if you put on
a skirt or somethin'
I could rub out another one.
Hehehe...
Hm...
[URAGAMI]
Well, well, well,
Mr. Detective.
Huh?
I need you to tell this guy
to look me straight in the eye.
[HIRAMA]
Shinichi.
Yes?
Uh!
[SHINICHI]
Next time:
"In Cold Blood"