[SHINICHI]
What the heck's with this guy?
Don't tell me...
he's a parasite!
No, he's definitely human.
I can tell that much, somehow.
C'mon, Migi!
Wake up!
[KATSUMATA] What's with him?
He's changed.
He's different now.
Something's going on.
[HIRAMA]
This is who he really is.
[SHINICHI] Wait...
Is he human? Is he really?!
[URAGAMI] It's not like I really
think that I'm all that
special or anything.
How am I able to tell humans
and monsters apart?
Huh, let's see...
Maybe because I've had my share
of "fun" with humans.
(schnick!)
Put simply...
I know more about the "quality"
of these beings
than anyone else does.
It's just a shame...
they break so easily.
Oh, yeah...
I've had my fun.
(creepy laugh)
Still, most animals have the
same ability, don't they?
It's just an innate capacity
to tell your own kind apart
from others.
I was shocked the first time I
found one of them, of course.
I mean, it was a...
creature in humans' clothes,
walkin' around in the crowd.
If I watched everyone pass by,
there'd be one or two of them
every hour, if I was lucky.
It was kinda weird that no one
else seemed to notice them.
But as for
the creatures themselves,
they looked like they
really didn't care.
I pretty much kept my distance.
Honestly, I felt like
these guys were BAD news.
In fact, I guess you could
call that an "innate
animal instinct" as well.
(disturbing laughter)
Yet, part of me eagerly
looked forward
to seeing how some "mysterious"
monster would do things.
But it was really no big deal.
Honestly, it wasn't so
different from stuff
I had done.
[URAGAMI]
Well now, you made quite a mess.
I mean, ya gotta clean up
after yourself when you're
done playing.
[POLICEMAN] Don't move!
[URAGAMI] (uh!)
[BOTH] (nervous sounds)
[URAGAMI]
Wait, no! I... I didn't do this!
I know it looks bad,
but it wasn't me!
[KATSUMATA]
He's taking his sweet time.
[MIYAKE] Mr. Hirama,
I'm afraid we can't wait.
Shinichi Izumi's expression
never changed once during
questioning,
but he certainly seems to be
afraid right now, doesn't he?
[HIRAMA] (on headset) Uragami?
It's a wash.
[HIRAMA] (on headset) What?
What's that supposed to mean?
[URAGAMI] Well,
this guy might have potential...
but something else
has got my attention.
There's something different
about THIS guy.
Things got a little confusing
there at first.
[HIRAMA] (on headset)
"Confusing"? In what way?
[URAGAMI] I guess maybe I
could've imagined it but...
but just for a second,
I thought I saw something
inhuman deep in his eyes.
[HIRAMA] (on headset) WHAT?!
[URAGAMI] (urk!)
Jesus Christ, man, don't yell
in my ears, all right?
Anyway, I think it
must've been nothin'.
When I took another
good look at him,
I didn't see
whatever I saw before.
[HIRAMA] So, the two of you
will be staying at the hotel
for a few more days.
We'll have an officer escort you
if you need to visit your house,
so just be sure
to let us know in advance.
No thanks, that's not necessary.
Yeah, well, I insist.
[SHINICHI] Um, Mr. Hirama?
[HIRAMA] (hmm?)
I have a question
about the baby, sir.
I assume you're talking about
the one with Reiko Tamura.
Well, we need to do more tests.
After all, the poor little thing
was being raised by a parasite.
[SHINICHI] So, what happens if
you confirm the baby's normal?
If that's the case, the child
will then be raised in an
appropriate facility.
So, um...
Why would you be
worried about that?
Uh, no... It's just I...
[HIRAMA] If you were to come
forward and say that you are
related to Reiko Tamura,
then I'd have YOU look after it.
[SHINICHI] Huh? What?!
[HIRAMA] I was just joking.
Oh... (weak chuckle)
"Deep in his eyes," huh?
What the hell did he see?
[DAD] Shinichi, need the bath?
Nah, you go ahead.
[DAD] Okay, will do.
(door opening &amp; closing)
Ah man, who was that guy?
Just thinking about him
gives me the chills.
I've seen all sorts of
man‐eating monsters,
but that guy...
Shinichi, it would seem
that you're exhausted,
and not just physically,
but also mentally as well.
I met someone really messed up
while you were asleep earlier.
Human?
[SHINICHI] Yeah...
But this guy...
He must've been...
a killer.
[SHINICHI] I just...
I don't know what's
what anymore.
I mean, that guy was really off,
and just terrifying.
And yet, Reiko Tamura,
a parasite that ate people,
actually saved me...
And healed the hole in my heart.
[MIGI] I still find it
impossible to comprehend
Tamura's behavior.
We are two halves
of the same whole.
Parasites and humanity
are of one family.
[TAKIZAWA] Therefore,
in regards to the
"Legal Interpretation of
Emergency Measures and
Response to
Indiscriminate Killings
by Parasites"...
The government has indeed given
its approval for this operation.
But I'd like you to keep in mind
that there are still many,
many gray areas.
(uh‐hmm)
[YAMAGISHI] (chuckles)
[YAMAGISHI]
Well, yes there are.
Good to see you, Inspector.
Assistant Inspector.
Well, ASSISTANT Inspector,
there's talk you'll make
superintendent by the day
of this operation.
You're a really funny guy.
In fact, he'll be commanding
the front‐line forces
during the upcoming
tactical operation.
The name's Yamagishi.
[TAKIZAWA]
As you've already been informed,
[HIRAMA] (hmm?)
[TAKIZAWA] Mr. Hirama will be in
charge of overseeing the support
functions of this operation.
Meanwhile, Mr. Yamagishi,
has his own set of objectives.
Identifying and
eliminating the enemy.
Um, Director...
I feel that Uragami,
the man I mentioned to you,
could be a very powerful asset
if we use him correctly.
I think we need to reassess
our proposed operations
and incorporate him
into the core strategy.
[YAMAGISHI] Yeah, of course I
appreciate the input, but...
As for this "psychic power"
of his, I dunno.
I can't really trust
a convicted killer.
Using a rogue element
like that guy?
It could hamper how our
tactical forces operate,
especially when it matters most.
Now, he wouldn't be there
as an operative.
We'd only be using him
as an extra pair of eyes.
A "pair of eyes"?
But we already have
a detection system
that'll be set up
to handle that.
It's not like you're facing
some flock of sheep
that can just be
herded up by dogs.
You are clearly
attributing these creatures
with far too much humanity.
We're not out to
conduct a manhunt here,
Assistant Inspector.
This is pest extermination.
We haven't been able to
get in touch with
Reiko Tamura for days.
The same goes for Kusano,
Hikawa, and Maesawa.
Three dismembered corpses were
recently discovered in a
municipal construction site,
and the following day,
a female who was believed
to be a parasite
was shot dead in a park.
[HIROKAWA] However, all four
bodies were retrieved by
a special agency,
and none of their identities
have as yet been revealed.
We both know that Kusano never
cared for Reiko Tamura
or her methods.
I'd say he conspired to
kill her without our consent,
but instead ended up
being the victim himself.
[HIROKAWA]
So you think the woman
who was shot dead in the park
was Tamura, yes?
Most likely.
Now that a special anti‐parasite
agency has been created,
I am no longer receiving
confidential information.
That means the government
is finally starting to
take this seriously.
That would seem to be the case.
[SATOMI] Shinichi!
[SHINICHI] (huh?)
[SHINICHI] Murano!
I sure have been good
at making you worry.
(mm‐mm)
Oh, here!
These are all the notes I took
while you were gone.
Oh, thank you.
I'll make some copies of them.
[YUKO] Hey, it's been a while!
[SATOMI] (giggles)
[YUKO] Hey, Murano! (giggles)
You done with your
little vacation?
[YUKO] (hmm?)
Uh... uh...
[PE TEACHER]
All right, listen up!
This will be your last timed
trial in high school!
Give it everything ya got, guys.
Don't leave anything out there!
Oh, eat it.
[FURUTANI] I don't think I like
the idea of Coach holding a gun.
'Kay, Izumi, I've always
wanted to say this,
you have never taken
any of this seriously.
So just ONCE, for me, you gotta
run like you gotta pair!
Yeah, I couldn't really go
all out before, could I?
The last one, huh?
[PE TEACHER] Get set!
(starting gun)
[SHINICHI] (breathing hard)
(stop watch clicks)
(wha...)
Jesus! Ten point five seconds?
No freakin' way.
Whatever.
I could've done it in nine.
[NAGAI] What's the matter?
You too embarrassed to
change with the rest of us?
Uh...
[FURUTANI] (juvenile chuckle)
We're all dudes here,
so don't go gettin' all shy!
[FURUTANI] (uh...)
Sorry, man.
(sighs)
Nah, don't worry about it.
It's nothing.
(urk) (huh?)
Dumb‐ass!
[SATOMI] Hy‐aa!
(huh?)
(soft chuckle)
[SATOMI] We'll be
graduating in three months.
[SHINICHI] Yeah...
[SATOMI] So much has happened.
It's kinda unreal.
Way too much, if you ask me.
Yeah, but there were
good things, too.
Guess now I've gotta
do some studying.
Huh?! You're taking
the entrance exams?
[SHINICHI] Yeah. of course!
Hey, ya know what?
When I get to college, I‐
(gasps)
Let's go.
We can do it, y'know?
[HIRAMA]
In fact, I am certain of it.
And yet, I can't help but
feel as though we're
missing something.
I don't know what it is,
but it's definitely something.
I'd very much like
to hear your thoughts.
[SATOMI] Why's it always...
have to be Shinichi?
It shouldn't be JUST him.
Everyone at this school...
We're all trying
our best to move on.
We all just want things
to be normal again...
go back to how they were.
Instead,
we have to live on edge,
afraid of what'll happen next!
[YAMAGISHI] He looks like
just a regular high school kid.
[HIRAMA]
He's the witness I mentioned.
Ah, so you're the guy?
I heard that you got the chance
to see Hirama and his men
put one of them down recently.
That's right.
I know that you're
a civilian and everything,
but do you have any ideas
about any type of weapons
that would be
effective against them?
A flamethrower would be
an excellent choice.
But they can move so fast.
Of course,
fire alone will not be enough.
But I do think
it'll be effective.
To put it simply,
it will startle them.
At least the
surface part, anyway.
[SHINICHI] (ohh...)
Now,
we're as intelligent as humans,
and we parasites don't have
an irrational fear of fire.
But...
if we did
encounter it suddenly,
we'd suffer an
internal disconnect.
In short, we would be startled.
Uh‐huh...
We know Goto's body contains
several parasitic sections,
but each of those beings are
controlled by a single
consciousness.
So if that consciousness
is startled,
it should effectively
unbalance him significantly.
Makes sense, I guess.
So we should use flamethrowers?
(snide chuckle)
Huh?
[YAMAGISHI] Ah, I'm sorry.
Okay,
I'm sure that'd probably work.
But still, no matter how many
parasites there are
in one body,
there's just one heart.
[SHINICHI] (gasps)
[SHINICHI] The day has come...
[WOMAN] What's going on?
[MAN] I have no idea.
It looks like the riot police.
But why?
So, this is it.
(keyboard clacking)
(high pitched equipment hum)
Sensors ready...
and standing by.
Let's do this.
[MIZUSHIMA] (on PA)
Attention! This is
an emergency announcement!
Everyone within the building,
please listen to the following
instructions very carefully.
I'm Detective Mizushima with
the Higashi‐Fukuyama
Police Department.
A male assailant armed with
a hunting rifle has entered
the building
and is now hiding
somewhere on the roof.
(continues in background)
[YAMAGISHI] (on radio)
Mutsuki and Kisaragi Squads will
rendezvous in the main hall.
Yayoi Squad will
cover the annex.
Uzuki Squad, take the second
floor and seal all exits.
Satsuki Squad,
protect the detection system.
Minazuki Squad,
neutralize the chameleons.
Let's move men; make it count.
[MIZUSHIMA] (on PA) ...please
proceed to the main hall on
the first floor at this time.
(bing!)
[HIROKAWA]
They say they're police?
But I'm sure NONE of them
are peace officers.
You're really doing this,
you disgusting humans?
This is where the fun begins.
We will strip these bastards
of their masks and lead
them to the slaughter.
The suspect is currently
on the north side of the roof!
Now, we'll be able to evacuate
everyone so he can't see you,
but he may take notice if the
entire building leaves at once.
Therefore, we will be leaving
in groups of seven.
[URAGAMI]
I'm tellin' ya, I don't know.
I hafta see 'em in person.
A monitor's useless.
Still, this is
pretty impressive though!
It looks like some
kinda war zone.
I'm not so sure you even
really need me around.
(door opens)
[URAGAMI] (huh?)
[URAGAMI] Oh, it's you.
[SHINICHI] (huh?)
So bringing in the
armed forces wasn't enough.
You had to recruit a killer
and some damn teenager, too?
Man, you guys are up the creek.
[KATSUMATA] That's enough!
Shut the hell up!
(urk!)
[HIRAMA] You see any?
Well, do you?
I don't know, sir.
Most of all, we would like
to find the deviant with
the multiple parasites
that you were telling us
about earlier.
The "deviant"?
And then, of course,
there's the other one:
there is Mayor Hirokawa.
That's right...
Hirokawa's the key!
But what... what was she
trying to say about him?
They said we're supposed to
evacuate in groups of seven.
You should go first, Mr. Mayor.
No, I couldn't.
Please give the children
and elderly first priority.
And then the women.
Please ensure that
all city workers
are shifted toward
the end of the line.
(uh...)
[SOLDIER]
Here come the first seven.
[YAMAGISHI] HQ to all squads.
If shots are fired
and the chameleons make any
attempt to escape or retaliate,
initiate safeguards at once.
[RADIO] Roger.
[ODA] I will now remove all
matter from the sensor image
that does not
contain human DNA.
(sighs) Nothing in this group.
All right, let's send out
the next seven.
[ODA]
There's nothing here, either.
[SHINICHI] (wishpering)
Migi, you have any idea how
many of them are in there?
[MIGI] We're pretty far away,
so I can't say for sure.
But there are several present.
[ODA] There!
It's that one!
So the first one is a woman.
[SHINICHI]
Next time:
"Crime and Punishment"