(owl hooting softly)
[SHINICHI]
Out here in the trees,
I don't think I can pinpoint
Goto by the sound of
his breath.
I have no chance
of defeating him,
but I feel no fear.
I'm numb to it all. (gasps)
(owl screeches)
The will to live,
anger, grief...
I don't feel any of those
emotions right now.
And yet,
(owl hooting)
it's like I'm being driven.
I'm being pulled
straight to him.
It isn't...
it isn't courage,
and it's not some sense of
duty to fight as a 'hero'
of the human race.
It's just that,
if I do nothing,
then I will be forced to
witness more deaths
at the hands of the monster
that followed me here.
If anything, it's a miracle
I've survived this long
as it is.
It's up to me to finish this.
Death could very well be
waiting at the end,
but I don't care.
I'm just...
so tired of it.
It's like it's
not even real anymore.
But for some reason, I feel...
positive.
It doesn't make sense.
I feel like this thing
might work out somehow
if I just go.
Even though,
I know what my chances are.
And they're not good.
It's strange...
My senses are honed and sharp.
Like they're heightened
or something.
And then...
I found him.
(wind blowing)
[SHINICHI] He's sleeping.
I guess even they have to rest.
Migi slept a lot, too.
I guess I...
should've gone after him
when he was asleep.
It's only because
I'm not a parasite,
and that I'm no longer
joined with Migi,
that I'm able to get
this close to him.
Maybe this is why I've been
feeling like things are going
to work out somehow.
Well,
maybe there's another reason.
Migi...
Could you still be alive
somewhere in his body?
If I called out
to you right now,
would you answer me?
Migi!
(gasps)
I should've known it
wouldn't be that easy.
[SHINICHI] (ah!) (kyah!)
(thwack!)
(uh!) (ah!)
Dammit!
[GOTO] (roars)
Where are you?
Show yourself!
[GOTO] (growling)
(snap!)
[GOTO] Some lowly little human
is daring to challenge ME?
That's right...
Yeah, I'm not afraid of you!
I know I can't win,
but at least I can
do some damage.
I will make you suffer!
You have more speed and power,
but I have much keener senses.
I can fight you!
As long as I have a plan,
But what should I do?
How can I possibly find a way
to put a dent on
something so strong?
Migi,
please tell me what to do!
You at least owe it to yourself
to give some thought
to something else,
anything else.
I'm just sayin',
don't give up no matter what,
and remember that
there's always an option.
That's right, don't give up!
Think!
(growling)
The back of his neck... Yes!
When he's controlling
the entire body,
THAT should be his weak spot.
Even if I can't win,
I can hurt him.
I must cut as deep as possible.
(uh!)
(growling)
[SHINICHI]
His most vital organs are
located in his torso.
I won't know where the gaps
in his armor are if I
strike from the side,
but from above...
There's a hole on
the back of his neck
that leads to the esophagus
and his internal organs.
If I put all my weight
behind it...
Behind this...
The angle has to be just right.
Now!
The cleaver's still
stuck in there?!
It's in the way!
(ungh!)
(ah!) (ungh!)
[SHINICHI] (gasping)
[GOTO]
Silly boy, the last time we met,
you skittered away
like a little cockroach.
[SHINICHI] (grrr...)
[GOTO] It was a wise choice.
Why would you ever come back?
What can a helpless little
creature like you hope to do?
I see you took off
your disguise.
Now I can at least see you
for the disgusting monster
that you really are!
[GOTO]
It's not necessary for me
to pretend to be
human right now.
The air is clean,
and refreshing.
It seemed the perfect
place to revive,
but you have ruined the mood.
Now, of course,
I always welcome a battle,
even if there's to be
only one opponent.
(grrr...)
Hey! Migi!
Are you in there?!
[GOTO] Are you talking
to your little friend?
Unfortunately for you,
he's no longer with us.
You son of a bitch! Damn you!
How dare you kill Migi?! (kyah!)
(ungh...)
[GOTO] I don't understand
your approach to fighting.
I mean, take this little
trinket, for instance.
(thwack)
Humans fight each other
using a variety of tactics.
But something like this
against me is...
ridiculous.
[SHINICHI] (ah!) (ungh!)
(oofff!) (gasping)
(coughing &amp; gagging)
(gasps)
(whimpers)
What is this place?!
It's the trash pile
from the other day.
(gasps)
I'm really gonna die?
Here?
With the garbage?
[GOTO] How disappointing.
I wouldn't even
call this a fight.
A battle with my creator
Reiko Tamura would have been
interesting,
but it's too late for that now,
isn't it?
Would you know
anything about that?
[SHINICHI] Reiko Tamura?
[TAMURA] He's one of
the most "frail" among us,
a being I created
through experimentation.
But he's invincible.
[SHINICHI] "Frail"?
How can he be "frail"
if he's "invincible"?
[GOTO] Well, no matter.
It's time for you to become one
with the refuse that
surrounds you.
[MITSUYO]
...give some thought to
something else, anything else.
[SHINICHI]
There's no more time to think!
[MITSUYO] I'm just sayin',
don't give up no matter what,
and remember that there's
always an option.
[SHINICHI] I'm going to die.
Then again,
I should be dead already.
He let me go.
[GOTO] But this fight must wait.
There are too many others,
and I'm feeling
a bit tired today anyway.
We can make it.
(gasps!)
[SHINICHI] Blood...
That was blood!
Could that have been
the gap in his armor?
(huh?)
(ah!)
Can I get through it with this?
Well, I guess it's all I got.
Can I even be fast enough?
As soon as I try to get up,
he'll just attack and
rip me to shreds.
I'm not sure I have a chance.
(gasps)
But if I don't try something,
I KNOW how this'll end.
(aaahhh!)
[GOTO] (growls)
[SHINICHI] (kyah!)
[SHINICHI] It went in!
[GOTO] (roars)
(ungh!) (kyah!)
[SHINICHI] (ungh!)
[GOTO] (growls) Goddamn human!
(ungh!) You are going
to shriek in agony!
(gasping for breath)
(bushes rustling)
[SHINICHI] (gasps)
He's here!
But this is all I got.
I can't run anymore.
I did some good though, right?
I may not have caused a whole
lot of damage in the end,
but at least I was able
to hurt him, slow him down.
(gasps)
(waaahhh!)
(ungh...)
(growls)
(huh?!)
[GOTO] How did you know where to
find the gap in my defenses?
I saw you get shot there before.
I saw you bleed!
[GOTO] (hmph!) Are you serious?
Do you mean to tell me you
risked everything on that?
Very well then, not bad.
But I cannot abide being injured
by a lowly, scrounging,
unworthy species.
IT'S OVER!
[SHINICHI] This is it.
This time it really is the end.
(huh?)
[GOTO] Who is that?
Miki? Stop resisting me!
Stay out of my way!
(ah!)
What are you doing?
If you're gonna kill me,
then hurry up and do it already.
Just finish me and
be done with it.
[SHINICHI] The strike will
enter my right shoulder
and exit my left side.
I should die instantly.
[MIGI] (mmph!)
(clang!) (explosion)
[GOTO] (hmm?)
[SHINICHI] Migi!
(waaahhh!) (ungh!)
[SHINICHI] (AAHHH!)
Hey!
(ah!) Migi!
(growls)
[GOTO] What's happening!
Why do you defy me?
What are you doing you cowards?!
Shinichi...
Migi! (sobs)
That's quite a
powerful struggle.
[SHINICHI] (huh?)
[GOTO] (pained growls)
I'll kill you.
I'll kill both of you,
right now!
No, you won't.
As it happens, I shredded
several of your vital organs
when I was making
my way back out.
You'll have to repair them
before you can fight again.
(arrrggghhh...)
So what do you think's
happening to him?
It's a revolt.
The parasitic cells that
don't belong to the leader
have instinctively sensed danger
and are trying to escape.
He's now in the middle of
a tremendous upheaval
between the "head" and
all the other parasites.
But why? Why'd it start now?
[MIGI] (hmm?) It was you.
You were able to inject poisons
deep into Goto's body.
Poison?
[GOTO] (arrggghhh!)
[PARASYTES] (voices clamoring)
[GOTO] Silence!
You will pay for this.
I promise you that!
I'll tear you both apart!
He is quite full of rage now.
(arrggghhh!)
[SHINICHI] (ah!)
[MIGI] Anger is an emotion
I have not experienced,
because I never took
control of a brain.
But the source of his anger
stems from his desire to
devour the human species.
[GOTO] (roars)
[SHINICHI] (ah!)
[MIGI] Those feelings grew
and accumulated,
resulting in an insatiable
appetite for war and bloodshed.
But his time has now come.
[large explosion]
[MIGI] A single cut to the rope
that was already pulled taught
was enough to make
his entire body explode.
Up until the point the poisons
were driven into his body,
he was still
one complete organism.
The head held absolute control,
allowing him to put the other
parasites to sleep at any moment
and take full command of them.
So were you one of his slaves,
too, Migi?
[MIGI] To be honest,
it actually felt quite nice.
It was as if, though asleep,
there was a constant flow
of information streaming
through my mind.
It felt rather wonderful.
I got the feeling
I wouldn't mind
remaining a part of this
invincible "Goto" life‐form
forever.
Well, I'm glad you're back.
You have no idea how sad I was
when I thought you were dead.
[MIGI] Interesting.
[MIGI] This is where you
found the implement you
used against Goto, correct?
[SHINICHI] Yeah, but what's
this "poison" you mentioned?
[MIGI] Hmm? Burnt waste...
I can't actually say for sure,
but it might've contained
hydrogen cyanide
from the combustion of
acrylic compounds.
I take it that's poisonous?
[MIGI] Lethally so.
[SHINICHI] (ah!)
And it's from
some shady company.
They just dumped it all here!
[MIGI] Well,
it did help you out, right?
[SHINICHI] (uh!)
[MIGI] It just goes to show you,
humans are very unpredictable.
(sighs)
[MIGI] Shinichi, we must go
back to our previous location.
[SHINICHI] (huh?!)
[MIGI] This is surprising,
but Goto is trying to
revive himself.
He's doing what?!
[MIGI] Look! Being blown apart
earlier has expelled the
toxins from his body.
The head is trying desperately
to reunite with the other
elements.
(slithering sounds)
But since they were scattered
in such small fragments,
reaction time is slow.
Possibility of regeneration
is around 50 percent.
And if he does somehow
manage to pull it off?
[MIGI] It won't change anything.
He could be slightly
less powerful,
but as long as he's alive, he
will still have the same desire.
He'll come after us.
Then, we have to kill him.
[MIGI] That's correct.
Migi?
[MIGI] Never mind.
[SHINICHI] (huh?!)
[MIGI] From my perspective,
he's one of my own.
In fact, one with whom I've
even shared the same host.
And if I were to kill him,
(slithering sounds)
it would amount to what
you refer to as "murder."
So, I'll let you handle it.
If you use that cleaver to
destroy his exposed organs,
he won't survive.
So, then you mean
you want me to do it?
[MIGI] Do as you like.
If you don't want to do it,
you could always run away.
[SHINICHI]
But more people would die.
And he'd just find
me again anyway.
[MIGI] That's right.
(slithering sounds)
[SHINICHI] In that case, there's
nothing for me to think about.
(piano playing softly)
Honestly,
it's kind of pitiful, huh?
[TAMURA]
We're actually quite frail.
We're nothing more than a
life‐form that isn't able
to survive on its own.
So, please...
Don't be too hard on us.
Yeah, well, that may be true.
But still...
Why were they really born?
To kill humans, because there
are now too many of us?
To decrease our numbers because
we've polluted the Earth?
It's true...
The toxins we're producing
are driving other species
to extinction.
(piano continues playing)
And this is evidence of that.
Goto was so immensely powerful,
but not against what
humanity's left behind.
[TAMURA] We are two halves
of the same whole.
Parasites and humanity
are of one family.
[SHINICHI] So when it comes
to the life of Earth,
are humans the poison
and the parasites the cure?
Who decides that?
Who decides the value
of life on Earth?
What deserves to live?
(piano continues playing)
[MIGI]
You must make your decision.
There's no time for delay.
[SHINICHI]
I don't wanna kill him;
to end a life that's so
desperate to survive.
I mean, that's it, right?
I don't want to kill.
And that sentiment to treasure
life is a lasting trait
of humanity.
[MIGI] What is it?
(piano continues playing)
I can't do it.
You might find it strange
given all we've gone through
to fight him,
but if his chances of
survival are fifty‐fifty...
I'd rather let fate
decide than me.
He's not a human being;
he's different.
So imposing my will
on him is wrong.
[MIGI] I see.
If that's your decision,
then it's fine by me.
Well, let's go.
(piano continues playing)
[SHINICHI] It's entirely
possible that I could be
committing a grave mistake here
as a human being,
but I'm not sure
it's my place to decide
that an organism has
no right to live,
even if it's harmful.
Or even if it just
doesn't benefit humanity.
It's not...
it's not my decision to make.
[MIGI] Shinichi?
Do you believe the Earth
to be beautiful?
[SHINICHI] I don't know.
[MIGI] I cannot understand those
humans who proudly proclaim
that they're doing something
"for the Earth."
After all, the Earth can
neither appreciate nor
even accept such an action.
It feels nothing.
And the life it spawned was born
into a boiling pool
of hydrogen sulfide.
(piano concludes)
[SHINICHI]
Okay, so I'll leave it to fate.
Right?
(slithering noises)
[SHINICHI] I'm nothing more
than a lowly human being.
And all I can really do
is protect those close to me.
(groans)
I'm sorry.
This is not your fault.
But still...
It's your fate.
(thwack!)
What's wrong?
What's goin' on?!
[NAITO] The monster!
They found the monster's corpse!
They found what? Its corpse?!
Did you really do it, Shinichi?
[SHINICHI] Let's go home.
[SHINICHI] Next time:
"Parasitic Beasts"