[SHINICHI]
In the end...
what were they really?
They're still being
talked about online...
but no public agency has
issued any formal statement.
After the bloody battle
at City Hall,
there haven't been
any parasite‐like
activities around town...
or anywhere else in the world,
for that matter.
Nothing at all.
Why did they suddenly go quiet?
One theory, of course,
was that losing that fight
taught them all a lesson.
Another suggestion however...
is that they've just become
much better at blending in
with human society.
Like Reiko Tamura, they've
learned to alter their diets,
gradually eating less
and less human flesh and,
in turn, becoming more
human themselves.
And then...
there's Migi.
[Sleeping]
[MIGI]
Shinichi.
[Shinichi voiceover]
Migi, you never change, do you?
Nothing seems to faze you.
But ya know, I'm really glad
you're still alive, Migi.
[MIGI]
How do I look to you
now, Shinichi?
[SHINICHI]
I don't know. A little
different again I guess.
But kinda the same.
Maybe...
I don't know...
Don't trouble yourself.
I actually came today
to tell you goodbye.
Huh?
What do you mean?
I think I'm going
to go to sleep.
Go to sleep?
But you always sleep, right?
This is different.
It will be a bit
longer this time.
Possibly forever.
Put simply,
just think of this as you
regaining your right hand.
Huh? Why would you do this?
I don't understand!
My internal structure
has changed once again.
In particular, my time
spent inside Goto's body,
dreaming and yet awake...
being alone and
yet not alone...
that experience has been
a major factor for me.
But, Migi...
Not only did I suddenly
receive a wealth of information,
I became able to pursue multiple
lines of thought at once.
I'd like to shut out all
other information
and just work with what
I have for a while.
I've decided to cease
all outward activities.
But Migi.
You can't be serious!
You've always been
so curious...
What happened to that?
There's still a lot out
there you don't know.
That's very true...
So I guess I'll
put it like this.
I'm going to head in
another direction...
One slightly different from the
waking world which you occupy.
I don't understand!
Migi, please...
Shinichi...
I want you to think of me as
nothing more than a dream.
It's the reason why,
in the end, I'm choosing to
say goodbye to you in one.
What are you
talking about?!
The time we've spent together,
everything we've done...
That wasn't a dream!
It was real!
Indeed...
The terrible things
that happened to you...
all those deaths...
those things were real, too.
Ah!
Mom!
Why is my mom here?!
This is an image you
manifest when you
think about people dying.
Ohh...
So this is the form your mother
takes inside your mind...
Uh, what?
What do you mean?
Migi...
What is all this?
It's all so different from how
I saw them in my mind's eye.
Show me myself.
Really...?
What do you mean, "Really"?
Well, it is what it is.
Ultimately, we can only
understand each other
on certain points.
You humans share the same
physical makeup,
yet if you were able to exchange
consciousness with one another,
you'd be able to
see entire worlds,
and hear things beyond
your imagination.
Well, it's time to go.
I'll be moving on now.
Wait!
What if more
parasites show up?
How can I fight them
all alone?!
I'm sure you'll be fine.
Just be careful on the road,
okay, Shinichi?
Wait!
So, I won't ever be able
to talk to you again?
Not ever?!
I don't know.
Neither of us should be
dying anytime soon.
Besides, a human who
talks to his own hand
is just peculiar...
Fundamentally speaking.
How can you do this to me?
Without any warning?
Once you wake up,
I'm sure you'll have forgotten
all about this dream...
like always.
And...
When that happens,
I'd also like you to
forget about me as well...
You can do it...
I'm certain you can.
And just think...
When morning comes...
you'll have an
ordinary right hand...
Just like you did before.
Migi...
Thank you for
everything, Shinichi...
[Birds chirping]
Mm‐hmm...
[Deep breath]
How in the hell could I ever
forget you, you idiot?!
Migi...
Ugh...
Nagai's been like
a total pain lately,
he won't
leave me alone.
[YUKO]
Akiho, I swear...
[AKIHO]
Ah! Look who's here...
Hey, Shinichi!
It's been a long time.
I'm late...
sorry about that.
Mm‐mm... Yuko and Akiho
happened to be passing by.
Mm‐hm.
Yeah, the two of us are going
out to see an art exhibit.
And I could not care less,
art is so stupid.
Hehe...
We'll see you two
love birds later!
Be good now, bye!
Yeah! See ya!
Bye! Woo!
Oh my God, you are
so embarrassing.
They seem to be doing well.
Mm‐hm...
I guess those two
are really enjoying
the whole
college‐life thing.
Sigh... I've totally been
left behind haven't I...
Uh...
Then you'll have to hurry
and catch up!
We're waiting for you.
Hehe...
[SHINICHI]
After everything
that's happened,
having to wait to take
the entrance exam again
is like torture.
A wonderful summer of
basking‐in‐the‐sun torture.
[Kids laughing]
Nothing at all has been
happening recently...
And there hasn't been a
single sign of parasites
around anywhere.
In fact, one time,
I even called Uda...
and we talked about what we
thought might have happened...
and how we got to where we are.
I decided not to
tell him about Migi.
His "disappearance" is unique,
even among his kind.
Migi...
I could never
understand you ‐
and it looks like maybe
I'm not the only one.
But that fits. In fact,
I'm sure right now,
you're walking some
path all your own.
The battles we
fought together...
They weren't really for
the sake of the Earth...
They were for humanity...
Or, to be honest...
sometimes just for me.
I could never see things from
the parasites' point of view...
let alone Migi's.
Of course not...
That was impossible
right from the start.
We're two different species.
Sometimes we'd use each other,
and sometimes we'd
kill each other...
But we may never truly
comprehend each other.
Because, you can never
possibly understand someone
when you've judged them
by your own standards.
I believe it's arrogance that
makes humans think
we can sympathize how
other life forms feel.
It's obvious that among all
the creatures out there,
mankind doesn't really
have many friends.
But, even if we can't
relate to them,
they're still our "neighbors,"
and they deserve our respect.
We humans protect other species
because we feel alone.
We protect the
environment because we
don't want to go extinct.
Look inside the human heart,
and all you'll find is
self‐preservation...
I think that's all
there is to it.
We don't know anything else.
And I doubt it'll ever end.
I mean it seems to have
worked so far. Right?
Well that's what I think..
And so...
In the end,
it's a contradiction
for us to love the Earth
without loving ourselves.
Mm?
Are you okay?
Uh...
Oh, no I'm fine...
I'm actually trying to say
it's more peaceful lately.
Yeah? But I'm pretty sure
I heard that crime has
been on the rise.
Wait... that's it!
Huh?
[SHINICHI]
That's why they're
not standing out.
Or maybe...
they never stood out that
much in the first place...
Even murder can sometimes amount
to nothing more than a wild
animal feeding itself.
In a narrow sense,
they're our enemies...
but in a broader sense...
they're just like us.
I mean, we were all born
on this planet, weren't we?
And all of us...
all of us survive
off each other.
Uh? Hehe...
Hmm...
[SHINICHI]
Time has really flown by...
Can you believe how long
we've been going out?
Wait, have we been
dating all this time?
Huh?
Hehe...
I'm kidding.
Ah... hehe...
Y'know what...
Hm?
U‐uh...
You are so mean
to me sometimes.
Hehe...
What?
Oh...
What's the matter now?
I must be
imagining things.
He looked like that guy.
I just thought I saw
someone I knew.
So you wanna get
something to eat?
Oh! Uh!
No! It is him!
What is it?
Hold this...
Wait for me here okay.
Huh?
I'll be right back!
He went through here.
What are you doing Shinichi?
[URAGAMI]
Looking for me.
[SATOMI]
Uh... Aahh!
Uh!
Ah!
Huh?
[URAGAMI]
Yoo‐hoo...
[Satomi whimpering]
Murano!
Hey! You let her go!
Er.. Argh!
This cannot be happening!
I should've just acted
like I didn't see him!
[Door opens]
Ah!
Huh?
[Whimpering]
Let's get outta here.
Yeah.
[Whimpering]
Uh... Hmm?
Uh! Hey!
Hey, what do you think‐
[Gasping]
Huh?
AAAAHH!
Someone, help!
Ah!
Ugh!
[Stabbing]
Uh...
I'll get to you a little later.
I gotta talk to your
boyfriend first.
[Whimpering]
[Panting]
Murano!
Excuse me...
Gah!
[URAGAMI]
You got up here pretty fast.
Murano!
Shini‐chi...
Aw, isn't that just
the cutest thing ever..?
She's so scared,
she can barely even talk.
Stop it!
What'd you do to her?!
Nothing yet...
This blood's from
that minx over there.
Huh?
Hey. Come on now...
Settle down and just let
her go, so we can talk.
Huh?! You can't be serious!
What is it you want?
I'll do anything. Look just...
please don't hurt her.
Uh‐huh...
Is there something
that you want?
If there is,
just tell me.
Hmm...
Something I want?
The cops aren't
completely stupid.
I know it's only a matter
of time before they
catch up to me again.
So I'm glad I got to run
into you two kids first...
I would like to
get an answer
that I can't get
from any human being.
Gasp...
Huh?
[URAGAMI]
When those monsters
kill humans,
it makes total sense, right?
They're just feeding...
But what do you think I am?
Now, I'm sure you already
know the answer to that...
I am true human nature.
I do wonder how all
the people out there
are able to be so patient.
I mean, humans have
always naturally had the
itch to kill one another.
Yet they make
such a fuss over it,
when we're all
thirsty for blood.
And these people who don't
even know what they are,
try to demonize me?
I can tell the monsters from the
humans just by looking at 'em...
I know how unnatural
the world has become.
So there is no need for
any of these monsters!
We're already here.
Humans will naturally
feed on one another!
It's been that way
for thousands of years!
It's only because we tried
to stop all of a sudden
that there are now seven
or eight billions of us!
We can't even sustain
ourselves anymore!
They lie to themselves.
But not us.
We're different.
So you can be honest with me.
I don't follow you.
What do you mean?
Don't you play dumb with me...
You're a mix aren't you..?
You're part monster.
What?!
[Frightened]
I knew it the first time
that I saw you.
It's not in your
head, though.
It's somewhere else
in your body.
No...
Don't be ridiculous!
You're his girly‐friend, right?
You've seen him up
close and personal.
Tell me. Does he have some
kind of scar somewhere?
A hole where a little friend
might've dug inside him?
[whimper]
I'm begging you...
Please, just let her go.
Now, answer me!
I'M the normal human
here, aren't I?
I'm just doing my thing,
following my natural instincts!
I'm the one being
true to my nature,
while the rest of this
herd desperately keeps
looking the other way.
I'm asking you for a favor,
seeing as how you're
halfway between the humans
and the parasites.
[SATOMI]
Shinichi...
Halfway between
the humans and
the parasites, huh?
Someone said something
to me very similar
to that once before.
You know, you're not
really anything close
to the likes of Goto...
but then again,
I'm not very strong
anymore either.
So if words can settle this,
I'll say what you want...
Just please...
please let the girl go.
Hmm...?
Er! Okay, you're right!
It's like you said.
I'm a‐!
[SATOMI]
Shinichi!
Just go.
Call the police.
Huh?
Don't waste your time
with this guy.
How can you call yourself
a normal human being?!
You're even worse than
those damn monsters!
Oh, my...
For someone who was trembling
and couldn't even speak earlier,
you sure got spunky.
You can go to Hell,
I'm not scared of you!
I've seen things disgusting
garbage like you can't
possibly imagine!
Please... Murano...
Shinichi, you and
I both went through it.
That's right.
Shinichi,
you were incredible.
You carried me and protected me.
You did everything for me.
Sure, you might be
a bit different,
but you ARE a human!
Because real humans believe
that all life is precious!
You! YOU'RE the monster!
Enough, okay?
Shinichi, don't worry
about me, just go!
[URAGAMI]
Hahaha...
Yeah, yeah, go call 'em..
The two of us will just
hang here and wait.
I think we'll be able to keep
ourselves entertained...
I'll take my time slicing off
every tasty little morsel.
I mean, it'll probably be
the last fun I ever get
to have, right?
Breaking down the spunky ones
is always so satisfying.
Shi‐Shinichi!
Uh...
I was... I was always
trying to catch up to you.
But you were moving
so fast, and then...
you went to a place
I didn't understand.
I ended up being
left behind.
Ah...
And now, I've finally
caught up with you...
But I...
I may've gone a bit too far.
NO! DON'T!
I'll save her!
I can do it!
That's right, I'm fast!
I'm not your
normal human being!
I see him. He looks like
he's frozen in time!
Stop the knife with
my left arm...
and then go for the jaw!
Auughh!
Unngh!
Now, with my right...!
Uhh...
[URAGAMI]
Such a shame...
to break so easily...
[SHINICHI]
AAUUUHH!
Uh...
No... Murano...
God not you too...
Not again... no...
[SHINICHI]
I met an organism.
I got to know it...
And it suddenly dies.
And then, I get sad...
Why does that happen?
[MIGI]
Perhaps, that just
shows you,
humans have too much
time on their hands...
But still...
having those feelings is
also their greatest merit.
To live with such room
in their hearts...
It is indeed
a wonderful gift.
But anyway...
That's quite enough of
all this moping around.
I'm tired, you can do
the holding now.
Uhh...
Gasp!
Ah... Murano!
Uh...
I made it in time...!
Migi!
[Exertion]
Uh!
[Catches his breath]
Are you okay?
Sigh...
Thank you, Migi...
I'm so glad
you're still here!
Could Murano have seen Migi?
Oh, well... If it's her...
I guess I don't mind.
What a beautiful sky.
Hey, um... Do you remember
the little puppy that
died awhile back?
And I threw it in
the trash can.
I keep forgetting
to tell you this but...
but I thought about it
for a long time...
and I buried it
underneath a tree.
I know...
Huh?
I know. You did the right thing.
Because you're Shinichi Izumi.
Hm...
[Woman screams]
Oh my God!
Look! There's three more
bodies over there!
Did he say three bodies?
He's including us.
Hehe...
Hm.
[SHINICHI]
All of us are born
here together...
And we live our lives trying
to understand each other,
using little bits of reason
we accumulate along the way.
Striving to find
someone to relate to...
and when we finally do...
it's already over.