Hmm...
[Gunshot]
Huh?
[Gasp]
Ah!
[Gasping and groaning]
[MIGI]
One is dead.
Uh...
[ITO]
We got one!
[YAMAGISHI]
One down.
Retrieve the body...
Use a different route.
Yessir!
[YAMAGISHI]
Those things aren't
really alive...
They're just machines
driven by demons...
And all it takes to
stop a machine is to
destroy the engine.
To destroy the heart,
destructive spread is
more important than
mere penetrating power.
What we need are
shotguns loaded with
seven‐point‐six millimeter,
sixteen‐pellet number‐one
Buckshot shells.
[Man]
What was that?
Did you hear that?
[Man]
I heard gunshots.
[Woman]
Somebody's shooting.
[Man]
Hey! You know what's goin' on?
Everyone, please
remain calm...
The gunman's firing
warning shots.
He's only trying
to prove a point!
So for now, we're going to wait
for a just few minutes.
Then resume evacuations.
[PARASITE MAN]
Goddamn, humans.
You've fared better
than anticipated.
[PARASITE WOMAN]
Well now...
What is going on here?
[Kato]
Evacuations may now continue.
[ODA]
Nope. All clear...
None here, either.
What's going on?
This can't be right...
Are they onto us?
[ITO]
Captain.
Hm?
The late investigator's
notes mentioned
something interesting...
although rather vaguely...
Telepathy...?
Yeah yeah, I read about that.
[HIRAMA]
We need to take
every precaution.
I'm about to
send Uragami in.
Please, don't
hesitate to use him.
I don't trust this guy...
Hm?
Hold on for just a second...
Whatcha got?
I have an update
on Hirokawa.
So some people still
haven't made it down?
That's right.
It looks like a town
meeting was scheduled
in the second floor
conference room today.
And I doubt the people
who're up there
were able to hear
the announcement.
Don't worry we'll
take care of it.
We'll send some men
to check things out.
Yes, well I don't think
they're going to react well.
A group of men
coming in with guns...
It's likely to
cause more panic.
He's right.
We'll go up to
the second floor
and bring them
back down with us.
Looks like they're
making their move.
Don't let them leave...
Try and stall them.
Yessir!
Okay I'm back...
You can go ahead and
bring in your psycho killer
or whatever that nutcase is.
[URAGAMI]
C'mon man.
Ya gotta take
these cuffs off.
What'll I do if things
get ugly around here?
Look, I'm not gonna run.
I couldn't go anywhere
if I wanted to,
there's cops everywhere.
Fine...
But stay by me.
Hey Migi...
We should help out, too.
We can at least sense
who the enemy is.
[MIGI]
That's a bad idea.
Sorry sir...
Please just cooperate.
You can't threaten innocent
civilians, you hear me!
Hm.
Um, excuse me sir...
I would like to be
evacuated now please.
Uh? Uhhh...
I see...
So this is it.
Uh... Hold on!
[ODA]
They're all on top
of each other.
I can't tell who's who!
[SQUAD MEMBER]
Don't break formation.
Please walk
single file everyone.
What's wrong?
Ah! Ahh!
Oh God!
They're all over the place!
Ahh...
[URAGAMI]
One, two...
[SQUAD MEMBER]
Wait! Stop right there!
[Woman screams]
Ahh...
Not that guy...
That one's human.
[URAGAMI]
Oh, yeah nice shootin' boys!
Huh...
How could you?
How could you just
shoot him down?
Please stand back, sir.
Huh?
Oh...
Get back in line, now!
No...
please wait...
I... um...
Now there's one...
Kill it now!
Huh?
[Panicked reactions]
Aaugh!
Ah! Ugh!
[ODA]
Our equipment took some hits.
The detection system is down!
[Grunt]
[Gunshots]
[People screaming]
[KATO]
Please, everyone, don't panic.
Calm down! Please, calm down!
Waaaahh!
Ooof!
Aaah...
[SQUAD MEMBER]
Dammit!
No! Don't shoot!
[Gunshot]
Ugh!
[HELD MAN]
[Gibbering]
Argh!
Uhh...
[Gunshots]
[KATO]
Wait! Wait...
Where are you going?!
[Shooting continues]
[SQUAD MEMBER]
Hold it. Nobody leaves.
Forget it.
Let 'em go!
Err... Ah!
Unghh!
[People frightened]
[Gunshot]
[People screaming]
Aaaah...
[Screams]
Everybody down
on the ground now!
Put your hands
behind your heads.
You've five seconds...
Do it now!
Don't stand, no matter what!
If you stand up without
permission, you will be shot!
Urrh...
Who the hell are you?!
You can't just come
in here and tell us‐
[Gunshot]
Ugh!
[Screams]
[YAMAGISHI]
Hmph. Guess he was human.
Huh...
Uhh... Ooh...
Ah! Dear God!
[YAMAGISHI]
This building is crawling
with parasites...
And we are going to neutralize
every last one of them.
So listen very closely.
If you consider yourself
to be human...
then you need to do
exactly as we say!
[SHINICHI]
There's gotta be
something we can do....
Anything...
Let's expand our
hunting range.
Kisa‐ragi Squad
has this zone...
You see anyone suspicious,
shoot them.
Sir!
Mutsuki and Satsuki
Squad survivors...
You're reassigned to
my Shingetsu Squad...
And we'll clean up the
rest of the building.
[SQUAD MEMBER]
Yes, sir!
Hey. The lunatic's
coming with me.
What... me?
Don't go trying
anything stupid...
Or I'll make you
regret it.
I'm seeing monsters all over
the place out here... Haha...
Ah... This is all
just self‐defense...
Or uh... or, or is it...
we have to do our
public duty...
It's an emergency, right?..
It's special...
circumstances...
Huh..?
Whatcha babblin' about?
[Woman terrified]
[KATO]
Hands behind your head!
[MAN]
Ooh! No!
Aahh! Please!
[KATO]
No! Stop! Now!
[Gunshots]
[Terrified]
[Guns cocking]
So, why aren't you
trying to escape?
I think it would
be relatively
easy for you
to get through
the cordon, Mayor.
For you, as well.
Not just yet...
I want to watch
a little longer,
to learn more about the
enemy's battle tactics.
What are you
planning to do now?
I guess...
I feel that it's useless
to run away at this late
stage of the game.
[GOTO]
Oh? Very well.
Now I can do
whatever I wish.
Right, understood...
So then, where is
Hirokawa right now?
[Radio]
Uzuki Squad encountered his
group while en route to
the city council wing.
But unfortunately, we lost
contact with them in the
second‐floor hallway.
Tch!
We're gonna split up here...
Shingetsu Squad, main wing...
Mutsuki and Satsuki Squads, you
head over to the council wing.
[SQUAD MEMBER]
Yessir!
[YAMAGISHI]
Hey murderer...
Your assignment's changed,
you're going to be accompanying
the Mutsuki‐Satsuki joint team.
The name's Uragami, Captain.
And you're a murderer
too, are you not?
But sir... you won't be able
to identify the enemy.
Don't worry about me...
it's getting easier now...
I'm starting to get the hang
of spotting those things.
Uh?
[SQUAD MEMBER]
Uzuki Squad has been located.
It looks like they've
engaged Hirokawa's group
and were completely wiped out.
Heh... Just dreadful...
[Screams]
[Man]
Ah... Hey... I...
[Woman]
It's not what it looks like...
Hmm... Sorry guys...
Those're humans...
Fornicatin' humans.
[SQUAD MEMBER]
Jesus Christ.
Seriously?
At a time like this?
Get outta there!
Guess they
couldn't wait, huh?
But'cha know...
if I hadn't been here,
they'd both be dead now
wouldn't they.
[Gulp]
Hm.
Oh... thank goodness...
You've got to help me!
Fire.
Huh? Yes, but, sir.
Uh‐uh... Ooh...
[Gasping]
How could you tell?
He wasn't down on
the first floor hall.
Huh?
Listen to me...
just shoot everyone.
[HIRAMA]
The humans had the upper
hand right from the start...
But the assault force's
objective was never to
protect civilian lives...
It was strictly to
eliminate the enemy.
And by making that
their priority...
they successfully
prevented a panic.
And while it's true that
some human lives were
unfortunately sacrificed...
the parasites were
effectively wiped out.
[Distant gunshots]
[TAMURA]
We are actually
quite frail.
We're nothing more than a
lifeform that isn't able
to survive on its own.
So, please...
Don't be too hard on us.
Seriously, man.
I'm practically
right up in front here.
What's the point of
having you at the rear?
Stop right there!
Ah! Please don't shoot me!
I'm not one of them! I swear!
Shoot him.
Huh?
AAHH! No!
What is you damn problem?!
Shoot him now!
Aahh!
Tch! The hell were
you aiming?
Go! After him!
Urgh! Aah!
[Groans]
So, they're using large shotgun
rounds to destroy the body.
It appears to be a rather
effective technique.
[Footsteps]
Hmm...
What about him?
He sure
seems like one.
Sigh...
Yeah, yeah...
Fine, go ahead and
shoot 'im. Why not?
Just shoot everybody alright.
I don't care anymore.
H‐huh?
WAAAAAHHH!
Hey! What the hell?!
Where do you think
you're going?!
AAAHHH!
This way...
There's much more
room over here.
[Freaking out]
[KATSUMATA]
Dammit, Uragami!
Ah!
You son of a bitch!
This was your plan
all along wasn't it?!
You... You did see that guy
back there, didn't you,
are you blind?!
You had to see it, right?!
Are you telling me that freak
looked human to you?
What did you say?
[GOTO]
What's this?
There aren't more of you?
I'll let you have two minutes.
Fire!
[SQUAD MEMBERS]
Why doesn't he drop?
He‐he's not
even bleeding!
Uh...
[Metallic clicking sound]
D'you... do you hear that?
What is that?
It's coming from
inside him!
Ah...
Well, how kind of you to give me
so much to work with, gentlemen.
Ungh!
What in God's name...?
How in the hell?
Go for his arm!
Ahh!
Ugh!
[Pained groans]
Really now...
Some of them are
actually still alive.
I see...
They appear to be equipped
with body armor.
[Groans]
Uh?
A valiant effort...
Uh...
But I'm sure you're aware...
It was all for naught.
You'll be dead in
thirty seconds.
Hm?
What was that?
[RADIO]
It looks as though the
Mutsuki‐Satsuki team is gone.
They're all gone.
Roger...
Send Yayoi to the council wing.
[URAGAMI]
Hehehe...
[KATSUMATA]
Enough! Let's get
you back, Uragami.
Are you outta
your damn mind?
Ah...
I said that's enough.
Ah... Hello.
[SHINICHI]
Next time:
"Sex and Spirit"