[Slice]
[Footsteps]
[Sigh]
Oh!
[Birds tweet]
Again...
The same dream...
We have seen
several types
at this point...
Ryoko Tamiya
the teacher was
certainly a surprise,
but now there's
a politician...
He won't be able
to get elected
without having a solid
grasp of human psychology.
There's no way he'll
ever get elected...
He's gonna have
to show his true
colors soon enough.
Although, given which
town this guy's in...
It's possible that
Ryoko Tamiya
is somehow involved in
all this. Possibly...
He seems to be very
interested in this.
Could Hideo Shimada have
had something to do with
So... I guess you think
he's after something.
That could mean‐
Yes. I do.
The first possibility is
that by assuming a human
identity and studying mankind,
he has developed a real
interest in politics.
In which case, he would actually
make an excellent mayor.
That's ridiculous.
But there is also
a second possibility.
He wants to secure safe haven
and a food source for others.
Good point, but even if
they hide the bodies
after feeding on them,
people are still gonna
turn up missing.
And let's say they
killed somebody who was
famous or something...
they'd get
exposed for sure.
Being in a position offering
both access and control
of such information while
securing food would be ideal.
So that's his
goal then?
If they organize
this way,
they'll become more
and more dangerous.
And that'd put
HER at risk, too.
[HIROKAWA]
But it's right here,
in front of you...
[Speech continues in background]
Come on, let's go
over there.
Huh?
[SHINICHI]
That's not where we
agreed to meet, so...
what's going on?
Oh, y'know I just had this
feeling that you were there.
I thought I told you
to stay away,
even if that
happened again.
Yeah, but it was much
more than just you.
I could sense it in the crowd
that had gathered there...
I'd say, there were about
four or five of them.
Migi said that he could
sense eight of them,
so I guess the parasites
can sense their own kind
better than she can.
Either way, this makes things
way too risky for her.
Shinichi.
Gahh!
What are you
thinking about?
Uh... it's
nothing alright!
Look, I can still think
about whatever I want.
Well, I felt concerned
for some reason.
Hmm...
[MIGI]
Personally, I'd prefer
that you not get involved
further in this situation.
Even if we fought them,
we wouldn't win.
[SHINICHI]
Oh look. It's not like
I came here to fight.
I just want to see if
I can find out how many
of them are here.
[MIGI]
It's impossible to
calculate their numbers.
Even a guess
will be fine...
Honestly...
Don't you want to know
how the others of your
kind have evolved?
I suppose.
Well?
They don't show up
just because you go
looking for them...
Uhh...
Ah! You're here!
Hey there.
What's up?
There's something
kind of important
I wanted to
ask you about.
Oh yeah?
[SHINICHI]
About your special "ability"...
Have you ever gotten
that feeling from anyone
other than me?
Huh? Well. Yeah...
But not really that often.
And when I do see them,
they turn out to be normal,
some random guy or whatever.
Look for your own good...
you should really
stay away from anyone
you feel transmitting
that "signal."
But why, what's
wrong with them?
Are they those
parasite things
that everybody's
been talking about?
Wait a second, are you
one of these parasites, too?
That's not what I mean...
[MITSUO]
Kana.
Hm?
[KANA]
Mitsuo?
I need to talk to you, okay.
Right.
I'll see ya.
Uh...
Hey, hold on.
We'll talk soon...
There's something else
we need to talk about, too.
And what's that, huh?!
[SHINICHI]
I'll text you.
You don't have to
text me...
I'll be able to feel it
when you're nearby.
You'll "feel it"?
Kana, sometimes what
you feel is someone else.
"Sometimes what you
feel is someone else"?
Kana, what the
hell's going on?
Mitsuo! This has nothing
to do with you!
Unh...
[MIGI]
Shinichi. What is it that
you needed to talk about
with that female?
Tell me the truth,
was speaking to her
your actual objective in
going on today's outing?
So what if it was?
As you have surmised...
my species has indeed
evolved over time...
But still, we are not capable of
developing true human emotions.
We don't know "sympathy."
I know.
So I'm asking you
not to take any action
that would potentially
put me at risk...
If you were to reveal
too much to her, then I...
I get it okay.
I'm not so sure
you do Shinichi.
I can only assume that you
would not want your right hand
to suddenly slice someone
to shreds, would you?
So... You're threatening me?
Yes.
You literally have
no sympathy at all,
do you?!
I believe that's
what I just said.
[Grunt]
I wonder what he
wants to tell me...
[Gasp]
Again.
And it's so close.
I don't think it's him,
but I guess it's possible.
Over there...
...around the corner.
[Footsteps]
Huh?
Uhh... Ahh...
[Rapid breathing]
That's not him.
[Phone ringing]
Ah! Shinichi.
[SHINICHI]
In here?
[KANA]
You did say in your text
that a place with no one
around would be best.
[Thud]
Huh?!
Ugh‐ow, jeez!
Okay, he's asleep.
Huh?
And then... I told Kana
everything I knew...
everything about
the parasites.
...but the one that
bonded with me
messed up while trying to
take over my brain,
so it took over
my hand instead.
And he won't attack
anyone anymore.
So you understand, right?
[KANA]
Hmm...
I guess I was hoping for
something more interesting.
You kinda got my hopes up.
[SHINICHI]
Kana, I can't expect you
to believe all of this,
but everything I
told you is the truth.
Well if that's the case,
then why don't you
show me some proof?
Go ahead. Lemme see
your hand turn into
some monster.
I told you,
he's sleeping right now.
Why don't you just
come out and say it?
You don't want to see me
anymore because you
don't want that girl,
Murano or whatever,
to see you with me.
Are you kidding?
I wouldn't spin some
elaborate lie for some
bullcrap like that.
Some "bullcrap"?
Seriously, if you
hate me so much,
why don't you just
come out and say it?
Kana... You've got
this all wrong.
Hm... You know what...
The thing that I feel is
different for you than it
is for the rest of them.
Huh? Really?
Uh‐huh...
There's a very distinct
difference between them...
I can tell if it's you
or if it's one of
those weird monsters.
You really can?
So I won't go near anyone with
a "signal" that's not yours...
That should solve it, right?
Uh... Hm...
I guess so.
Okay, now as far
as I can tell...
I'm the only one in the
world who can do this...
You must admit, that's pretty
amazing stuff isn't it?
Yeah, you've got
something special.
So. Since I've told you
about my secret...
You're gonna have to
show me your secret
someday, too.
What secret?
Um your right hand...
Otherwise, how can I ever really
be able to believe your story.
Fair enough.
It's a promise, then.
Yeah, I promise.
Mm...
[SHINICHI]
Well. He won.
[MIGI]
That means the parasites
have now secured
a refuge as well as
a stable food supply.
They're as intelligent
as humans...
and they'll do anything
to protect themselves.
She said she's able to
tell me apart from
the rest of them,
but I'm not sure
that adds up.
Oh really?
Yeah.
It's supposed to be a
really great movie.
Oh...
Yuko and Akiho said they
cried their eyes out...
so I have to see it while
it's still in theaters...
Okay. So, tomorrow at
ten o'clock then?
Sure!
[KANA]
Why don't you notice me?
We're joined... by fate.
I'm the only one
who can sense you.
SHE doesn't feel you
like I do...
Look over here.
Feel me.
Please...
[Exhales]
[Gasp]
Mitsuo!
Don't scare me like that.
What're you doing?
What's it
matter to you?
This isn't like you...
It's like you're a stalker.
The way you're sneaking
around and following me,
that would be you...
You're the stalker.
Can't you see he
already has a
girlfriend?
That guy's not right
for you, Kana...
You know that.
Oh, yeah? And you're
saying that you are?!
I have had enough of this!
Always following me around
like a little puppy dog...
Please, you need to
get out of my life!
Uhh... Mm...
I don't know
what to say...
I can't believe you
hate me that much...
Mitsuo...
I'm sorry...
But, I just can't do this!
You need to give me
some space.
[MIGI]
I've decided to
tell you something.
Huh?
It'd be foolish
for me to make an
enemy out of you...
But then again,
I certainly don't want you
doing something rash
while I'm asleep, either.
Huh...?
It's about that
female, Kana.
Her power has grown stronger,
and she has now begun
to emit her own signal.
Signal?
It's the signal
parasites send out
that allows us to
sense one another.
I became aware of hers
while we were on our way
home from school yesterday.
What? No way!
If she sends out a signal...
then those things will
be able to find her...
She'll get herself killed!
Most likely, she can
only send her signal
when she has
full concentration,
however, her transmission
range is quite limited.
Why didn't you tell
me this before?!
No... Thank you for
telling me now.
Migi...
The other day...
While you were asleep,
I told Kana everything I knew
about the parasites, and I
told her about you, too.
But don't worry she
didn't believe me.
I thought as much.
Look, I know she wouldn't
turn against you. And so...
I was hoping...
that maybe you would agree
to show yourself to her.
I mean, it'll be fine!
Besides, if she does
ever tell anyone else,
I can always bluff
my way out of it.
As long as you
kept on pretending
to be my right hand...
she'd just sound
like a crazy person
talking nonsense.
Well?
All right.
[Sigh]
Okay, I'll give
her a call then.
We'll meet her tomorrow...
Ah! I have a date
with Murano.
Mm...
[Passing sirens]
[Marker squeaking]
Ah...
Mmm...
I guess we're a little early.
Hey. You remember, right?
What you promised
yesterday.
Yes.
But this is bad.
Two of my kind
are approaching.
Uhh...
[Phone ringing]
Hello?
I'm sorry...
I want to change
our meeting place...
For now, don't go
near the trains.
I'll call you later.
[Hangs up]
Huh?
[MIGI]
It's those two.
Let's go.
Wait. If we move, it'll
make them suspicious.
Pretend you're
making a call.
This time...
I'll show you what
my power can REALLY do.
I can sense you,
and you alone.
No one else,
not even that girl Murano,
has such feelings for you.
[Door opens and closes]
I want you...
I want you to sense me, too.
They acted as though we were
nothing out of the ordinary.
[Phone ringing]
C'mon why won't
she pick up?
There he is!
It's no good.
With all these people around,
there's no way I can
pinpoint Kana's breathing.
Migi. Aren't you able to
receive that signal of hers?
Impossible. Her signal
is weak in comparison,
and she may not
even be sending it
out right now.
[KANA]
I'll see him.
I will!
I'll see him soon...
Shinichi...
[MIGI]
There!
Uh! What?
You found her?
I didn't.
It's one of mine kind.
I'm not worried
about that now...
No... Wait...
If Kana senses
that guy's signal...
She's likely
to approach it.
Which way?!
[KANA]
Shinichi! I told you!
I am able to sense you
and only you!
Shinichi!
[Eating sounds]
Haha!
Ah...
Huh! Ohh!
It's a human...?
The signal was rather weak...
but this is...
unexpected.
Ah! Ahh!
AH! Uuh...
[Gasp]
[Kana panicked breathing]
I'll be okay...
He'll come to save me!
Hah...
Shinichi!
[Thwump]
[Thud]
Migi.
Handle the defense.
Defense?
[Grunts]
AAHHHH!
AHH!
[Crash]
Incredible.
[Deep breathing]
[MIGI]
It's no good.
She's lost too much blood.
No, no...
Ahh...
Kana.
Uhh...Shini...
Shinichi... I...
I knew that you were
going to come for me...
I could sense you.
Just hold on!
Uhh...
I saw this before.
It was in a dream...
Please, please try
not to talk.
It was just so
embarrassing...
I could... never tell...
anyone...
Ahh...
Kana...
[Sniffs]
Huh...
[Sobs softly]
[SANDA]
That's the boy who found her.
He seems pretty calm for
someone who just found
his friend murdered.
This is confidential
information,
but that kid's mother
was actually killed by
a parasite as well.
[SANDA]
Really?
Not too friendly, huh.
I'm sure he's pretty tired
of all the questioning
he's been through.
The kid's had
a rough go of it.
And we also had him give us
one of his hairs, just in case.
Oh, I'm sure he was
a fan of that.
Well we can't be
too careful...
The victim was
murdered by a parasite...
But we... we don't know
who killed that parasite.
Something tore through its
rib cage, gouged out its heart,
then slammed it with
enough force to destroy
the wall itself.
No human could do that.
Which means, there was at least
one other parasite at the scene.
So, the parasites
had a falling out?
Yeah well...
we have to consider that
as a possibility.
If I... had just gone to the
movies with Murano...
then none of this would ever
have happened to Kana.
[MIGI]
That's not true, Shinichi.
It was just a matter of time
for this to happen...
You don't need to
feel responsible.
How can you say that?
[MITSUO]
Stop right there.
Huh?
Kana...
Kana is dead!
AHH!
Why couldn't you
protect her,
you bastard?!
Ah!
Ugh!
How can you be
so freakin' calm
right now?!
[Punch]
Just one tear!
You can't shed just
one tear for her, huh?!
[MIGI]
Shinichi.
You aren't...
you aren't even human!
Ugh!
That's right!
Uuhh...
[Grunting in pain]
You don't know
who the hell I am!
Uh...
[Sobbing]
If we take this
any further...
I'm gonna rip
this guy to pieces.
"Not human"...?
He's right...
he's absolutely right.
And why am I
so calm right now?
Is it possible?
Have I just not
felt it happening?
Am I gradually being...
has my brain
been taken over?
I mean... Kana is dead...
but I...
but I can't cry.
[Thud]
[MIGI]
Stop it, Shinichi.
Huh...
At least my
blood's still red.
For now anyway.
[SHINICHI]
Next time:
"Hello Sadness"