It's over.
We have nowhere left to go.
This is it.
Our road ends here.
It was a foolish decision, doomed from the start.
This is the end.
We must turn back.
There is a way.
Have faith.
I know that we will find it.
But, Princess...
You mustn't give up!
Princess.
Princess Gale, this is as far as you go!
Now, halt.
Don't tell us, this storm is your doing!
Behind you, Princess! Look out!
Hah!
Give up, Princess!
Fall to your knees and bow before me.
I will never give up.
As long as I live, I will gather my
strength and forge a path for others to follow!
The princess!
Her Rainbow Chakra is ablaze!
My brothers, we must light the flames of our chakra, too!
Right!
Aaah!
Now!
All right!
Princess Gale, you rule!
Good sticks it to evil once again!
Hey!
What the heck do you think you're doing up there?
Hup, yike!
What's the big idea?
Don't play stupid with me.
You snuck in here without
paying, you lousy little freeloader!
Wait, you've got it all wrong! ere just getting
a little training in while we watch the movie!
Training for what?
We have tickets.
Are you ninja from the Leaf Village?
You bet we are!
You're looking at the next Hokage. A super ninja, pal.
Oh, yeah, Naruto Uzumaki, live and in the flesh!
Come, let's push on. Our fate lies beyond the rainbow!
Kakashi Sensei is late.
So what else is new?
Aw, man, that movie was so cool.
I don't think I've ever been so blown away in my life.
I don't want to hear it!
You made such a racket in there,
we didn't get to see the whole thing!
I wish we could've stayed a little longer.
I could have watched that handsome
Omiji who played Tsukekuro all day long.
Oh, of course, he doesn't compare to you, Sasuke.
Man, I don't know where you got your
taste in men, Sakura. But it stinks.
Come again!
I'm sorry.
What was the question?
Humph!
I wonder if there's anyone like her out there.
I mean, where's my Princess Gale, you know?
If I could fight for a girl
like that, I'd be on cloud nine.
Whatever.
It was just a movie.
It's funny.
I wonder why Kakashi Sensei told us we had to
go see this movie before he'd give us our mission.
No way!
Was that the princess?
Ugh!
Agh!
Why, you!
Ugh!
Huh?
Rrrarh!
Heyah!
Don't let her get away!
Not to worry, Princess Gale! I could protect you!
Aah!
Get her!
Ugh!
Stay on her! Don't move!
We got you now.
We've finally captured her.
Feisty one.
Ow!
Huh?
Who are you?
Ugh!
Where did the princess go?
Oh!
Oh, captain?
Aarh!
Oh, dear.
Huh?
Kakashi Sensei!
What are you guys doing?
Killing time.
Gee, huh, I'm really sorry about this.
Huh?
This is the gentleman who hired us for our mission today.
Are you hurt, Princess?
This is crazy!
So, like, you are the real Princess
Gale, aren't you? I don't believe this!
I just saw your movie, and it
totally blew me out of the water!
"I'll never give up."
It was so awesome. First, you
had me cheering. Then I was crying.
Aakk!
Ugh!
I mean, after seeing the movie, the
feeling just started to well up inside of me!
I'll never give up either!
I'm going to work my butt off.
And one day, I'll be the next Hokage.
Oh, right, you probably don't know.
The Hokage is the highest ranking ninja
in the Hidden Leaf Village where I come from.
Hey, lady, you really know how to handle a horse.
No wonder you're the Land of Fire's number 1 actress.
Ha!
And I know talent when I see it!
Ngeeh.
Hey, lady, aren't we going a little fast?
Look out!
Ugh!
Huh?
It's Princess Gale!
Oh, wow! It is her.
Princess Gale!
Oh, look, my name isn't Princess Gale, OK?
Yeah, that's right!
You're the actress Yukie Fujikaze. I'm your biggest fan!
Can I have your autograph?
Yeah, me, too!
Here, please!
Forget it, guys. I don't do autographs.
Please.
Come on.
Hey, what about me? Can I get one?
Please!
You're a movie star!
Aw, come on!
Sign autograph!
Enough, already!
I mean, come on!
What's so special about getting my autograph, huh?
You're just going to shove it in
some drawer and forget about it.
I it's good for is collecting dust.
They're just a waste of time!
They're useless!
What a joke!
Ugh, that was so rude.
Not like she is in the movies, is she?
Her success went right to her head.
Our mission is to guard Yukie Fujikaze, the
actress best known for her role as Princess Gale.
Guard?
Well, maybe not guard her so much as escort her.
The next Princess Gale movie is the
first one that we're shooting abroad.
And, uh, I don't need to tell you
our leading lady is a bit of a diva.
Sorry, uh, I do apologize.
I'll tell you, these Leaf Ninja are impressive.
Uh, they took care of those stuntmen
turned bodyguards we hired was child's play.
And those are some big fellows.
Oh, well, uh, thank you.
Oh, wow!
Look at those cliffs.
Uh, that's the Rainbow Glacier in the Land of Snow.
Hey, you played the part of Buriken!
That's where we're all going to shoot the
scenes for the film's big climactic ending.
You're Hidero!
You play Shishimaru!
Land of Snow?
Long way to go to shoot some scene for a movie.
Yukie Fujikaze's manager,
Sandayu, over here recommended it.
Apparently, he tells us this Rainbow Glacier
turns seven different colors during the springtime.
No, that's just an old legend.
The truth is, there isn't any spring in the Land of Snow.
What?
Not ever?
Does that mean it's winter all year long?
Mm hm.
You got it.
Kakashi, wasn't it?
From what I hear, this won't be your
first time in the Land of Snow. Is that true?
That was a long time ago.
They say that it's a very poor nation, too.
Huh!
You you, Tsukekuro, Omiji, you were great!
Actually, the story is their
former lord had a thing for gadgets.
The guy squandered everything the clan had
on mountains of useless doodads and gizmos.
Yeah, well, I just hope they've got central heating.
I'm not really all that cut out for the cold.
Maybe you should run for the hills, too.
Just like Yukie.
Oh, hey, come on, you guys. That's not even funny.
So does that mean, Yukie I mean, she not always like this,
is she?
Hm.
Kind of, yeah.
Poor Yukie, huh, she wouldn't even know the
meaning of words like "dreams" or "aspirations."
But she's never been one to neglect her work.
I don't know anything about her
personal life, and I don't need to.
As long as she's giving her all when the camera's rolling,
I won't have any complaints.
Say what you will, that woman is a born actress.
He's right.
And anyway, she only started running from the set
after she heard we were going to the Land of Snow.
Aah!
Ugh!
Oh, all right, already.
Awesome!
What's your name?
Naruto Uzumaki!
"Naruto Uzumaki," right?
Uh huh.
Gosh, lady, you sure do smell nice.
Ow!
What the heck was that?
Pepper spray for stalkers.
Ugh!
You freak.
I mean, you've got to be kidding.
Who would want to go to the Land of Snow?
Ugh!
I finally found you, Princess Gale!
I told you, kid.
I'm not the princess of anything, OK?
What?
You think I don't know that!
Do you really think you could trample
all over a kid's dreams like this?
I don't care how high and mighty an actress you are!
I'll never forgive you!
An actress?
High and mighty?
That's a riot.
I can't think of a worse job than being an actor.
Only the lowest of the low
would want in on this profession.
Huh?
We're handed lies put down on
paper and breathe life into them.
It's ridiculous.
Um, are you drunk?
Shut up!
Go bug someone else!
Ms. Yukie!
Our boat to the Land of Snow is about to sail.
Please, we don't have much time.
No, thank you.
Huh?
I'm bowing out as a princess.
Huh!
You, but
What on earth are you talking about?
Ah, don't worry.
It happens all the time, OK?
I mean, lead actresses change from sequel to sequel.
Come on, directors change every five minutes.
That's enough!
You listen to me!
There is nobody on this whole planet who
can play Princess Gale other than you nobody!
Besides, if you pull out this late in the
game, you'll never work in this business again.
Do you understand me?
So?
Who cares?
Ms. Yukie?
Well, guess there's no other choice.
Huh?
So she has the hex crystal.
Splendid.
This film actress Yukie, there's no
question she's really Koyuki Kazahana.
I can hardly wait.
It was worth the 10 years it took to find her.
Hah, taking care of one little
girl ought to be a piece of cake.
She's not alone.
She has Kakashi Hatake as a bodyguard.
Kakashi Hatake?
Well, this should be interesting.
In the end, it will be a clash of fate.
Father?
Where are you?
Koyuki, come here.
Good.
Now, stand there.
What do you see?
I see you and me.
If you look closely, you'll see the future.
Uh.
Ms. Yukie, are you awake?
Sandayu, could you get me some water?
My head won't stop spinning.
This is going to sound crazy, but
it feels like the room is swaying.
Actually, it's, uh, not all that crazy.
Huh?
Huh!
You have got to be kidding me!
I don't know. I don't think I can deal with this lady.
What are you talking about,
Naruto? You have to deal with it.
You've just sworn to protect her.
Come on, this is an important mission.
Mission?
Yes, an A rank one.
This is an A rank mission?
I don't really think our babysitting a little
pampered actress will be all that difficult.
That's not true, Sasuke.
Big celebrities are targeted all the time.
Besides, it's hard to predict who's after them.
Just be on your guard.
Light is set.
OK, we have speed!
Camera is rolling.
All right, folks!
I want to get this on the first take!
Right!
OK, scene 23, cut 6, take 1.
And action!
Oh.
Huh?
Shishimaru!
Stay with me!
Uhh, I'm sorry.
I failed you, Princess.
Forgive me, I beg you.
How can you say that?
Without you at our side, we never would have
found the courage we needed to make it this far.
I only wish I'd seen beyond
the rainbow with you, Princess.
Uhh.
Shishimaru!
Whoa.
She's amazing!
I don't even feel like I'm
looking at the same person anymore.
Oh, yes.
That's Yukie for you.
Huh?
When the camera starts to roll, she comes alive.
There isn't another actress on
earth who can match her brilliance.
Hold on a second, guys.
What's wrong?
Sandayu, bring me my drops so I can cry.
Right, right.
Oh, coming, coming.
I have the drops, the drops.
OK.
Now, let's see.
Uh, one there and
and now, the other one.
Ready?
Ugh, they're spilling over.
Come on, let's do this.
Ahh, for Pete's sake!
Start with the close up.
Right.
OK.
Scene 23, cut 6, take 2.
Action!
Shishimaru!
Mr. Makino, we've got a problem!
What is that?
When I woke up this morning, I found this waiting for me.
We can't get through!
What are we going to do?
This is it!
We're changing everything!
Ha aah?
You moron!
Look, we're standing on the perfect spot to shoot!
It's practically begging us to film here!
Uh, ha aah?
Cherish this moment.
The movie gods are smiling down on us!
Everyone, prepare to embark!
All right, yeah.
Clear this up.
Clear the area.
Let's try and get some last looks in, people.
All right, people, we're going to roll.
Stand by!
OK, scene 36, cut 22.
Action!
So, Princess, you've arrived!
Well done!
It's you, Mao!
Princess, please, stay back!
We'll take care of him for you.
Did you honestly believe these meager
fools would be a match for me, Princess?
Huh?
Is this in the scene?
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?
Everyone, get back!
Welcome, friends, to the Land of Snow.
You!
Greetings, Princess Koyuki.
I do hope you're still carrying around the hex crystal.
Princess Koyuki?
Huh!
You're as good as they say, Kakashi.
Unfortunately, it's not good enough.
Naruto, Sasuke, Sakura.
Huh?
You three protect Yukie.
Everyone, get back to the ship!
Wha
Huh?
Fubuki, Mizore, I'll leave the princess to you.
Very well, then.
It's been a long time, Kakashi.
I hope you're not planning to run like the last time.
Nadare Roga.
I don't know what's in the script, but
I've always wanted to be in the movies!
Don't you worry, Princess.
Naruto Uzumaki's here to save you!
Ice Style, Tsubame Blizzard!
Fire Style, Fireball Jutsu!
Huh!
Hurry!
Back to the ship, everyone!
Yukie!
Princess!
Sandayu, what are you
Ice Prison!
Aaah!
Naruto!
Water Style, Water Dragon Jutsu!
Keep that camera rolling even if it kills
you! Show the resolve of the cinematographer!
Sensei!
There's something strange about their armor!
Yeah, I know.
Just be careful. It's Chakra Armor
created by the ninja here in the Land of Snow.
Chakra Armor?
But it's definitely a lot stronger than it used to be.
So you remember.
The armor increases the chakra within the body,
strengthening a handful of the more useful juts...
A chakra barrier gathers around us as well,
able to deflect the chakra of our adversaries.
As a result, ninjutsu and genjutsu are rendered useless.
Ice Style, Dragon versus Tiger!
Water Style, Water Dragon!
Out of the way, little girl!
Ugh!
You little brat!
What is this chakra?
Ugh!
Yukie, hurry! Get to the ship already!
Princess!
Father!
What are you doing? Get out of here!
Princess, please, we must get to the ship.
No.
You've got to go now! Your life is...
I don't care if I die!
I won't I won't come back to the Land of Snow!
We don't have time for this, OK?
Ugh!
Aagh!
Sakura!
Princess!
Huh?
Don't be in such a hurry. We're not finished yet.
Ice Style, White Whale Jutsu!
OK, that was impressive.
Now, it's my turn. Naruto, get everyone out of here!
Ice Style, White Whale Jutsu!
Still copying my moves, huh?
You're not going to settle this by doing that.
Settle the fight?
That's not really what I was aiming for at the moment.
What?
And cut!
Man, I hope we got all of that.
10 years.
It's been a long time.
The ship pulled into dock a moment ago.
You've known all along, Sandayu, haven't you?
Yes.
Didn't you ever consider the risks of what
might happen if she came back to the Land of Snow?
You're right, of course.
But this was the only way I could
think to get the princess to return home.
Come on, Sandayu.
You don't have to keep calling her that. I
mean, she's only royalty on the big screen, right?
It's not like she's really a princess.
Actually, she is.
Huh?
Yukie Fujikaze is only an alias.
We're guarding Princess Koyuki Kazahana,
the rightful heir to the Land of Snow's throne.
I first met her a long time ago.
I was her aide when she was still just a little girl.
I don't blame her for not remembering.
It was years ago.
So does that mean you are also
from the Land of Snow, Sandayu?
That's right.
I served the princess's father, the former
leader of the clan, Lord Sosetsu Kazahana.
The Land of Snow is not a large nation,
but but served as a haven of peace.
Lord Sosetsu, he absolutely adored the princess.
Ahh, those were idyllic times.
But 10 years ago, on that
cursed day, Lord Sosetsu's younger
brother Doto hired a group of
Snow ninja and instigated a revolt.
It was a coup d'etat.
The magnificent Kazahana Castle burned to the ground.
And I feared the princess had perished as well.
Keep your face hidden.
They could still find us!
There was no way we could defeat them.
We had to keep running.
We had to get away.
Father!
The day that I discovered our beloved princess was
still alive, I was practically beside myself with joy.
She was she was alive after all those years.
I should have died back then.
Huh?
You mustn't say such things, Princess.
We feared the worst.
You can't imagine how frantic we all were.
We never stopped praying for your life.
I'm alive, but my heart is dead.
After that day, any tears I had left all dried up.
And that's how I came to be
the manager for Yukie Fujikaze.
I have bided my time waiting for the day
when I could escort her back to Land of Snow.
Uh!
So what are you saying then? That all
of this time you've just been using us?
Uh, I apologize for deceiving you.
But it was for the sake of the Land of Snow's people.
Princess Koyuki, confront Doto and assume
your rightful place as the leader of our land!
I will sacrifice my life without
hesitation in order to protect you.
I beg you!
Take up arms and lead your people!
I don't think so.
Huh?
You've got to be kidding.
But what about what your people?
I couldn't care less about them.
Just forget it!
But, Princess.
Will you give it up already?
Don't be dumb!
It doesn't matter what you do.
You will never get rid of Doto, OK?
So what? He should just give up? Quit being so heartless!
Can't you see this poor man has given his
entire life to the realization of this dream?
You keep insulting him like that,
and you'll be dealing with me, lady!
Naruto, I
Humph.
As long as there is hope, one may dream.
And with those dreams, the future comes.
I like it.
It's the perfect theme for our new Princess Gale movie.
Uh!
But, Mr. Makino, you're not really going to continue
filming with everything that's happened, are you?
I told you.
The movie is evolving.
Just think about it.
How often do you get the chance to
make a movie with a real princess?
We're looking at the chance of a lifetime here.
You're right.
Think of the buzz.
Even the "Making of" will be a hit!
We're sitting on a surefire blockbuster!
Hey!
Unfortunately, there's only one course of action.
Now that Doto is on her trail, running isn't an option.
We have to fight.
It's our only chance of getting through this.
Kakashi Sensei.
OK!
Time to continue the mission!
The princess returns to the Land of Snow
and shows that creep who is boss!
Stop joking around!
The movies aren't like real life.
There is no such thing as a happy ending in this world!
Of course, there is! If you're willing to fight for it!
Uh!
Normally, under these circumstances, I'd head
back to the village for a little bit of help.
But
It's a waste of time.
We're as fine as we can be. It's nothing we can't handle.
Oh, thank you all.
That's it then.
We're going ahead with this picture!
And you can bet this one will have a happy ending!
That's right!
Hm?
Our hideout is not far from here.
It's just beyond this cave.
Once we've finished our shooting here,
we'll pass through to the other side.
Then my people can rest easier.
They'll finally have their princess back.
Boy, I can't see the exit at all.
Once upon a time, a railroad ran through here.
Railroad?
It's covered over with pillars of ice by now.
But dig far enough down, and you'll
find the tracks laying there still.
Ahh.
All right, people, let's get this show on the road.
Ugh, Mr. Makino, we've got a bit of a problem.
What is it now?
Yukie has up and vanished again!
What?
Huh?
Forget it.
Absolutely not.
Fan out and look for her.
Radio in if she turns up.
Got it!
Ugh!
Aah!
If you look closely, you'll see the future.
I can't see anything.
Of course, you can.
When the spring comes, you will.
The spring?
You're a liar, Father.
There is no spring in this land.
Jeez, how many times are you
going to run away from your fate?
Come on, everyone's waiting.
Why?
Why do you always come looking for me?
Because it's my mission.
It doesn't matter how much you hate it,
I'll keep coming after you.
Just try to hide.
I'm going to find you.
You can drag me back if you like, but
all I'm going to do is act for the camera.
And that's it, you got me?
Hah!
Huh?
What is that?
It's chakra.
There's chakra running through the rails, melting the ice.
It must be him.
Everyone hurry!
You must get out of here!
You can't let them find you! 's not safe!
Sandayu?
Where are you going?
It's a train.
Train?
What do you mean a train?
Oh, that train!
It's gaining on us!
Not, if I can help it!
We'll never make it!
I'm not giving up, lady!
There's no way you can do this!
Will you just shut up already?
Ah!
Uh, this is going to be pointless! Just give up!
This isn't over!
I'll be dead before I'm going to give up, even if
you're ready to call it quits, I'm not giving up ever!
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on!
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on!!!
Ugh!
It's been a long time, Koyuki.
I knew it.
It's Doto.
It's been 10 years.
Come now, don't be shy.
Let's get a look at that face.
Hm.
There you have it, men!
Our beloved Princess Koyuki is here to watch over us!
With her at our side, victory is ours!
What the
Sandayu?
Hear me, Doto.
We've waited a long time for
this day of reckoning to come.
Sandayu Asama and 50 loyal warriors stand before
you to avenge our great fallen leader, Lord Sosetsu.
On this day, you will breathe no more!
Hm, I thought you destroyed the last of the insurgents.
My apologies.
We'll get rid of them immediately.
No.
With men such as these, there is little that
they can understand other than total annihilation.
Sandayu.
Huh?
Hold it, Sasuke!
Don't be hasty.
Awful.
That's what comes of never giving up.
If they hadn't stood up to Doto, then
none of this bloodshed would have happened.
My Princess, please forgive me, I I never
should have gotten you involved in all of this.
It's just that every single one of us here,
we are able to keep believing in spite of
everything because we knew you are alive.
When you were little, uhh, and even now,
you have always been
just as I, your loyal Sandayu, believed,
so, too, must you believe in yourself.
You have always been our purest hope, Princess.
Please do not waste your tears on me.
Ahh.
You are such a fool, Sandayu.
I can't cry.
You have my eye drops.
Are you all satisfied?
Let's go back.
If you stay here, your lives will be in jeopardy.
Let's go home already.
Go home to where?
I thought this was your home, wasn't it?
What the heck do you need to
go back to? Your place is here!
Now, face Doto and put your house in order!
You know absolutely nothing.
Spring doesn't come to this country.
Our tears have frozen over and
our hearts hardened with the cold.
But aren't you the only one with the power to change that?
I mean, at least at least, that's
what Sandayu believed anyway, wasn't it?
I've had enough of this nonsense.
Hey, hold on a minute!
Leave me alone already!
Huh?
Careful!
Sakura, where's Naruto?
Huh?
Oh, you're kidding me, he didn't!
Ugh, come on! You didn't think
I'd let you get away that easy?
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
You've grown quite beautiful, Koyuki.
Tell me, little princess, do
you have the hex crystal with you?
Yes.
Good.
It is the sole remaining link to the Kazahana Clan
and the key to opening its treasure.
The key to what?
When I wrested this land from your father's hands,
the Kazahana Clan's resources were all but gone.
I knew Sosetsu must have hidden his riches somewhere.
I searched for a long time, and finally, I found it.
It is hidden deep within the Rainbow Glacier.
There's a keyhole there which can
only be opened by the hex crystal.
Once I have possession over the Kazahana fortune,
our country can attain military
superiority over the five great nations!
Not going to happen!
You!
How on earth did you get in here?
Heh, never underestimate a ninja!
Ugh!
My apologies.
As you can see, the little runt was kind of a handful.
Well, he knows the Multi Shadow Clone juts...
I'll tell you, I don't know who this brat is,
but his level of chakra is nothing to sniff at.
What do you think?
Maybe we should try that contraption out on him?
Hm.
He would make for an interesting test subject.
Ugh!
Aargh!
Agh!
What is that?
We're cleansing him of his chakra.
That device will absorb any that's stored in
his body and bind it within a powerful barrier.
Once it's been activated, it
cannot be broken or destroyed,
no matter what.
My strength, it's starting to slip away.
Not looking like much of a ninja anymore, are you?
Just a little kid.
You dirty ugh.
Now then, I'll take the hex crystal, if you don't mind.
Oh.
Hm?
What is this?
Ugh!
This isn't a game!
Do you think I don't know this is a fake?
No, that's impossible!
Kakashi Hatake.
What?
Makes sense.
Kakashi's a shrewd one. I wouldn't put
it past him to pull a bait and switch.
Don't even worry about it. We'll
have him rounded up in no time.
That won't be necessary.
Huh?
Ugh!
Why even bother. The man will
show up on his own soon enough.
Until then, we just have to wait.
Ugh!
Uh!
Terrific.
I don't have any power.
Guess I should have spent a little
more time working on the Escape Jutsu.
These guys don't know who they're dealing with. A
real ninja finds a way, with or without his chakra.
Hm?
Serves you right.
Yeah?
You, too.
I know.
"No spring."
You said there was no spring.
What did you mean?
"You'll see when spring comes, Koyuki,"
my father used to say that.
Father, what is spring?
Oh, that's right.
You've never felt spring, have you, Koyuki?
Mm mm.
Koyuki, close your eyes.
Try to imagine yourself surround with flowers.
There now, isn't it beautiful?
Now, run through it as fast as you can.
Well?
It makes you feel all warm and happy, doesn't it?
Mm hm.
That is spring.
And if you never give up, if you believe
in the future, then spring is sure to come.
But this land has no spring.
My father died.
I fled from the Land of Snow.
And I stopped believing.
I was always running, always lying to people.
But mostly, I was just lying to myself.
My life has been one big charade.
Becoming an actress was about the only
thing I was cut out for in this world.
That's not going to change anything, you know?
Aah!
Told you.
In the end, all you can do is give up.
I bet it's a lot easier once you've given up.
No one ever cared about me before.
And I just try to blow it off, you know.
But it was still pretty rough.
I used to think there was no place in this world for me.
But aagh!
But I still found friends.
I kept at it and didn't give up.
And good things happened.
Aagh!
When you give up your dreams
and everything else, they're gone!
Rrrh!
Stop!
Your father and
Sandayu.
I'm going to show you that they weren't
wrong!
Rrrh!
Ugh!
Huh?
Naruto.
Aagh!
Uh!
Now, I'm just going to get you out.
Ugh.
We're under attack!
Hm, Kakashi.
So you're here at last and right on time.
Huh?
Hey, when did he
Uh!
Heh, told them not to underestimate a ninja.
Hm.
Rrh!
Hold it!
Hold it, Naruto!
It's me.
Kakashi Sensei!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
You look all right, Princess.
Yeah.
You switched my hex crystal for a
fake without telling me, didn't you?
Yeah.
I apologize for that.
But I figured this was what he was after.
All for this thing, huh?
This place is crawling with guards!
Sakura!
Sasuke!
This way.
Doto!
Well done, Koyuki.
Wha
Wait!
It can't be.
This shouldn't be a surprise to any of you.
I mean, really, I'm an actress, aren't I?
There you have it.
Another brilliant performance by the great Yukie Fujikaze.
Yes, it was all an act.
Ugh!
I told you, didn't I?
I'm an actress!
Uh!
You wretched
Aagh!
Princess!
Uhh, I always knew, Naruto, that if I ever
return to this country, I was going to die here.
At least, I could
Don't you do it!
Don't you stop fighting!
Naruto, it's only thanks to you that I
could stop running away here at the end.
No!
Because all you're doing is running away!
Don't throw away your life like this!
I'm sorry, Father, Sandayu.
Koyuki!
Aagh!
You really thought you could kill
me, did you with this little toy?
Humph.
That's right.
It's Chakra Armor, our latest prototype.
Uhh.
Don't you touch her with those filthy hands of yours!
Ugh!
Naruto!
You're wasting your time.
Every ounce of your chakra
has been completely sealed away.
Come, let us go, Koyuki, beyond the rainbow.
No!
Naruto!
Hm.
This ain't over.
I'm not going to go!
Do you hear me?
You could run, but you can't hide.
I'll follow you as long as I have to.
Rrrharrh!
Huh?
Hop on!
Huh.
This is it.
We've come here after all, I guess.
Sakura, how close are they?
Hold on a sec.
I've got it! 20 degrees left in 5 seconds, 30 meters out.
You want to aim for that branch!
Right!
Give it up. It's useless.
Come on, don't make me laugh.
Sakura Blizzard Jutsu!
Enjoy!
You're dealing with a ninja of the snow here.
It will take more than that to bring us down.
You're probably right.
Uh!
Lions Barrage!
Aagh!
Aargh!
What just happened?
Gosh, I'm not really sure.
Wait, you don't think that they
You really think you've got a shot?
Maybe you ought to turn tail and run, like the last time.
I don't have a choice, do I?
At least, I could show you one of my original techniques.
Lightning Blade!
Ice Style, Wolf Fang Avalanche!
How did you
Almost had me there.
What?
Even without ninjutsu and
genjutsu, a ninja always has taijutsu!
You rely too much on this armor!
I don't see it.
The treasure, where is it?
It's so warm.
What is this?
A heat generator?
This is the hidden treasure of the Kazahana Clan?
Koyuki!
Naruto!
Rrrh!
Ice Style Black Dragon Blizzard!
Huh!
Naruto!
What's the matter I hardly felt a thing there?
Naruto, that's enough!
If you don't stop, he's going to kill you!
Trust me.
If you just have a little faith in me, I promise you,
I won't lose!
How the... is it is it possible
that the chakra is leaking out somehow?
Hrrrh.
Rrrh!
Die!
Chidori!
Agh!
Hah!
Did you really think your pitiful
little jutsu would have an effect on me?
Naruto, his armor has been fractured.
The rest is up to you.
Naruto!
Come on, Nine Tailed Fox.
Where the heck are you when I really need you!
Show some guts, will you?
What is that?
Huh!
It's payback time!
With interest, pal!
Come on, you little halfwit, quit! Dragon Blizzard!
It's over.
This ridiculous little farce is over!
Huh?
Not yet, it's not!
I told you already!
It ain't over till justice prevails and evil is wiped out!
Every good story's got to have a happy ending.
Naruto!
I believe in you!
You are by far the strongest ninja I've ever known!
Yeah, I know.
I could have told you that!
Look, Rainbow Chakra!
It's just like in the movie!
Take this!
Rasengan!
Aaah!
Huh?
What the
Wait a minute. Could this be we're making this movie 3D!
Believe in the future.
If you do, the spring will surely come.
What will you do when it comes, Koyuki?
I'm going to become a princess.
Oh?
What sort of princess?
Um, let's see.
One who is strong and who is kind,
and most of all, one who fights for justice.
That's some dream.
Did I did I actually say those things?
Well, so long as you believe in your dream and
never give up, one day, you'll be that princess.
You can see it, can't you?
There's a beautiful princess
standing right there in front of you.
But I have sort of a problem.
There's something else I want to be.
Really?
What's that?
An actress.
What?
Oh, yeah.
Now, that's a happy ending.
Oh, whoa, oh, whoa, oh, oh.
Force of nature, unrelenting, can never fall!
And it's supersonic!
It will charge!
Invincible!
Here we go!
There's always something steering the path I lead.
There's always someone ticking and kicking inside of me.
I I will never give up!
Oh, whoa, oh, whoa, oh, oh.
Ever changing and evolving, life renewed.
From a fire, flies a phoenix born into.
Here we go!
The days of darkness, trawling the battlefields.
Remember your true friend,
call on and put your trust in me.
I I will never give up.
I I will never give up, will never give up, yeah.
Like a hurricane, like a hurricane.
Like jerks.
Hurricane, like a hurricane.
Lightning strikes.
In like a hurricane.
Oh, whoa, oh, whoa, oh, oh.
Oh, whoa, oh
That generator wasn't even fully developed in the end.
I guess it will be back to winter soon, huh?
Not really.
If we take what we know and continue researching,
before you know it, the Land of
Snow will be called the Land of Spring.
Yeah, but it's kind of a shame.
You're such a big star. Are you
really going to retire from acting?
Who said I was retiring?
Huh?
Ruling over the Land of Snow and acting?
I think I can handle both.
I mean, I'd have to be out of my mind to give it up now.
Uh, that's great.
Well, I'll be seeing you.
That's her!
There she is!
Princess, sign here!
Sure!
Can I have your autograph?
Would you please sign
That is great.
She's perfect.
Aaagh!
I'm so stupid. I should have gotten an autograph!
Don't worry, I took care of it.
Huh?
Whoa.
Aagh!
Oh, man, look at me.
Couldn't you, at least, have
used a better picture or something?
Haay.
And cut!
That's a wrap.
Good stuff people! Thanks a million.
Hey, let's do lunch, seriously.
Nice working with you, buddy.
Isn't that wonderful?