[theme music]
-[gasping]
-I understand.
I can't be your boyfriend,
but I can act like it.
-Thank you so much, I'll try
my hardest to make you love me.
I promise.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
I'll arrange for her
to meet L. She'll
tell me his name,
and then I eliminate
the entire task force.
And when that's done,
I'll kill her, too.
After all, she's
the only person who
knows Kira's true
identity-- the only one.
I can't let her
live much longer.
-So you'll just pretend?
All right.
I guess it's a good start.
Well, now that we
talked about that,
could you show me
your Shinigami?
I really want to see him.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): I
need her to trust me.
I guess I have to.
-Yeah, sure.
Could you please turn around?
MISA: All right.
LIGHT: You can turn back now.
MISA: OK.
-Hey there.
How's it going?
MISA: Oh, look at that.
You're a completely different
type of Shinigami than Rem,
aren't you?
I already know your name.
It's Ryuk, right?
Nice to meet you.
-Yeah.
Same here.
MISA: Oh, and by the
way, Light, darling,
do you know how to
kill a Shinigami?
-Hm?
Did you just call me darling?
-Fine.
Then do you mind if I
call you Knight instead?
'Cause you're like my knight
in shining armor, you know.
LIGHT: [sigh] Let's
just stick with Light.
MAN: So, were you
actually planning
to check all of the footage
we got from Aoyama on the 22nd
by yourself?
-That's right.
I think it's very likely
that Kira and the second Kira
make contact with each
other there on that day.
So I want to check all of
these tapes personally.
Also, Mr. Yagami?
-Uh, yes?
L: Please ask Mr. Mogi
to start following Light,
so we can keep tabs
on what he's doing.
YAGAMI: You want him followed?
-It's only a slim chance.
But if you Light is Kira, then
there's still a possibility
that the second Kira might
try to contact him somehow.
-Mm.
Very well
-I'm starting to wonder
if Ryuzaki is even human.
The guy never sleeps.
-I saw him sleeping in
that exact same position
the other day.
-Huh.
MAN: No, I'm serious.
LIGHT: So if a Shinigami has
feelings for a human and kills
someone else in order to
extend that human's life
beyond its natural end,
and Shinigami will die?
-That's right.
--[laughs] Good luck
trying to find a Shinigami
who'd volunteer to do that?
-[laugh] That's true.
I can't see you ever doing that.
By the way, where did you
send all those tapes from,
the ones that went
to the TV stations?
-Let's see.
Osaka the first time,
then Tokyo, this other one
from Nagano.
I took the bullet train every
time, so that way the police
couldn't pinpoint my location.
-All right.
One more thing.
Do you still have the
videotapes and envelopes
with your friends
fingerprints on them?
-Uh-huh.
-Well, you'll have to
dispose of everything
that was used to create
those videotapes.
Understand?
But before you do, I need
you to send one last video,
and make sure it's from a
place you haven't used yet.
It should say, "I've decided
to stop searching for Kira.
And I'd like to thank
the police department
for all of its advice.
However, I still plan to
help Kira in his mission,
and I hope that in time he
will come to see me an ally.
I will start by
punishing criminals
that Kira has yet to judge.
Also, I will share my power with
others who I feel are worthy.
And I will encourage
them to do the same.
Together, we'll make this
world a better place."
MISA: Share my power?
-We'll just add that part to
throw off their investigation.
They suspect that
there are already
two people with this power,
so it wouldn't be a stretch
to assume there could be others.
And if they believe the
numbers are growing,
then they'll start to panic.
Can you do this?
-No need to ask.
Just tell me what to
do, and I'll do it.
I don't care what it is,
'cause I'd do anything for you.
LIGHT: There's one more thing,
which is very important.
-What's that?
-If you get arrested
by the police,
or if you're ever brought
in for questioning,
you can never mention anything
about us or the Death Note.
As long as they don't get
a hold of that notebook,
there's no proof that
you did anything.
Can you promise to say nothing?
-I promise.
So this must mean
that we're officially
boyfriend and girlfriend
now, aren't we?
-Well sure.
I guess.
MISA: Then I'd like
to add one condition.
You have to go on a date
with me at least once week.
-[sigh]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Unbelievable.
She still doesn't get it.
-We can't.
-[gasp] But why?
-It looks like I'm going to
have to spell this out for you.
L already suspects
that I'm Kira.
Do you see what I'm saying here?
-No way.
L is amazing.
I mean, everyone's been saying
that he's getting nowhere
with the investigation
and that he's
a complete idiot and stuff.
But he already knows that much?
-Anyway.
It's all worked out well for
me, because thanks to that,
I've also been able
to get close to L.
-Huh?
You and L are in
contact with each other?
Then that's even more amazing.
This is getting so exciting!
-Even though he
suspects I'm Kira,
L figures he's safe as long
as I don't know his real name.
He came right out and told me
who we was, just to get to me.
However, he's only
focusing on me
because he has no
other suspects.
And he has no evidence.
At this moment, I'm working
with him on the case.
And little by little,
I'm winning his trust.
-Great.
So I'll you have
to do is take me
to where L is and I can
see his real name for you.
LIGHT: I'm afraid
it's not that simple.
-Hm?
LIGHT: Listen, it
was difficult enough
for me to get close to him.
Besides, if all of a
sudden someone I just met
gets too close, and
at the same time,
the police detect
changes in Kira
or the second Kira's
behavior, that person
will be suspected of
being in the second Kira.
And of course, that'll put me
under even greater suspicion.
We can't allow them to
make that connection, which
means we can't appear to
be too close to each other.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
-Well, I think I understand.
So is that why we
can't go on dates?
We can't be seen in
public, because it'll
look too suspicious?
-Look, we need to
take the time now
to come up with a
good plan, some way
that you can see L without
letting him know you exist.
-Yeah.
LIGHT: I can't
eliminate L without you,
so I'll call you and see you as
often as this situation allows?
-You will.
-But--
-Oh?
- --to make sure that our
meetings to stand out,
I have to make sure that I'm
seen with other girls, OK?
MISA: Huh?
What do you mean?
You're seriously gonna
date other girls?
-Yeah, more or less.
-I don't want you too!
-Huh?
-If I see you with another
girl, I'll kill her.
-Scary.
-Look, sweetie.
-Sweetie? [laughs]
-This is not a game.
Both of us are risking our lives
to change the world, aren't we?
-I know that.
But I love you more
than the world, Light.
-It sounds like you're confused.
Maybe it feels that way
to you, but you're here
because you admire Kira.
You don't even know me.
We just met.
-Don't you believe in
love at first sight?
-No.
-I admit that everything
you said was true.
I did want to meet Kira out
of gratitude and respect,
not love.
But from the moment I
first saw you, I knew.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): What
is wrong with this girl?
-Popular, as always.
-Well, you can show me
your love by obeying me.
I thought you said it
was OK if I used you.
A minute ago, you swore
you'd do anything I asked.
-Yeah, I did.
But I never said you
could date other girls.
I mean, those are two
totally different things.
-I think you're forgetting
I have both notebooks.
If you don't obey me,
I can easily kill you.
-I would never allow
that, Light Yagami.
If you do anything that
results in this girl's death,
the first thing I'll do is right
your name in my Death Note.
I will kill you.
I'm sure you realize that
I can see her life span.
If she happens to
die before that time,
I'll know it was
you who killed her.
LIGHT: But if you were to use
your Death Note to save her,
wouldn't that mean
you'd die, too?
-That's right.
If you tried to save
me, you would die, too.
-Yes, you are correct.
But I'm quite willing
to accept that outcome.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Is
this Shinigami serious?
This is crazy.
Then this means--
[knocking]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
--from now on--
LIGHT'S MOTHER: Light?
-Huh?
Yeah, what is it?
-It's almost 11:30, you know.
You really shouldn't have
a girl here this late.
-Oh, of course.
I guess we lost track of time.
MISA: Sorry, Mrs. Yagami.
I'm really sorry for coming
over so late at night.
See you later, Light.
-Yeah.
-Light, you should walk
her to the station.
-Uh.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): I can't risk
being seen with her in public.
-Oh, no, I'm all right.
Thanks.
Well, good night.
-Isn't she cute?
-Yeah, I know.
When she got here,
I wasn't so sure.
But you're right.
She's cute, Mom.
I like her.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
That Shinigami
is going to kill me if
I kill that girl, which
means I'm going to have her
hanging around me until she
dies.
Not only that, it
also means that I'll
be forced to protect
her from being caught
by the police for
the rest of her life.
-Thanks to you,
Rem, Light really
is gonna be my knight
in shining armor.
-I suppose.
-Hm.
But you can't
really kill him, OK?
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): For
a Shinigami to die,
they have to use
their Death Note
to save the life of
a human, a human who
they have fallen in love with.
Ideally, I could kill Rem first.
Someone I was controlling
would attack Misa,
forcing Rem to save her, but--
no, that would never work.
If Misa's life
was put in danger,
Rem would immediately
suspect me,
and I'd be the one
who'd get killed.
As things stand, she's a
bigger nuisance than L is.
Huh?
She-- she's famous?
Oh, I don't even
want to imagine what
would happen if someone
found out about us.
Damn it.
She's nothing but trouble.
What should I do?
No, more importantly,
I need to think
of how I can use Misa's
eyes to help me kill L.
If I can eliminate him--
SAYU: Good morning, Light.
-Good morning.
LIGHT: Mom, Sayu, could
you do me a big favor
and keep Misa a secret
from Dad for now?
-All right.
-Actually, it's not just Dad.
You can't tell anyone
else about her either.
You see, Misa's an
up-and-coming model,
so people can't know about us.
-What!
Is she really?
I thought she was pretty,
but I had no idea.
That's pretty impressive,
even for you, Light.
I'll keep it a secret for $50!
LIGHT'S MOTHER: Oh, stop it.
-[laughs]
-Ah, on page number 246--
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Misa's final
message should arrive today.
Although before it ever
gets to the TV station,
it'll be rerouted to
task force headquarters.
I have to go down
there are some point
so I can see L's
reaction first hand.
KIYOMI: Light.
Light?
-Hm?
-I thought you and I
were seeing each other.
That is, we're more than
just friends, aren't we?
-Yeah, we are.
-Exactly.
And that's the reason why I'm
sitting next to you in class,
wouldn't you agree?
-Sure.
KIYOMI: But you don't look
like you enjoy being with me.
I mean, you haven't
even looked at me once.
-That's not true at all.
I guess I was just thinking
about how everyone's
going to be talking
about us now.
To think that I'm
actually going out
with Ms. Takada, the
famous Ms. Todai.
I mean, you're the most
beautiful woman at this school.
-[laughs]
--[clears throat] Why do you
even care about stuff like that?
Besides, I hate being called
Ms. Todai or whatever.
It's embarrassing.
-Yeah, you're right.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
What do you know?
She actually likes
all the attention.
LIGHT: We should forget
about all that stuff,
and just go at our own pace.
KIYOMI: Yeah.
PROFESSOR: --increased
levels of dual-income housing
through the 1990s.
LIGHT: Hello.
-Oh, come in.
Your timing couldn't
be better, actually.
We just received a new video
message from the second Kira.
-Huh?
Wow, that didn't take long.
YAGAMI: Yes.
I believe it's the last one.
Well, take a look at this.
MAN (ON VIDEO): I've decided
to stop searching for Kira.
And I'd like to thank the police
department for their advice.
However, I still plan to
help Kira in his mission.
And I hope that, in time, you
will come to see me as an ally.
I will start by
punishing criminals
that Kira has yet to judge.
Also, I will share my power with
others who I feel are worthy.
And I will encourage
them to do the same.
Together, we'll make this
world a better place.
L: After watching
this, I can only
think that Kira
and the second Kira
have managed to make contact.
-What makes you say that?
-Oh, come on.
Didn't you sense it?
I was sure you'd come
to the same conclusion
after I did after watching
this once through.
First, consider how determined
he was to meet Kira.
So why the sudden
change of heart?
Now he wants to punish
criminals that Kira hasn't?
And all he wants out of it is
for Kira to see him as an ally?
Mm, it begs the
question, why didn't he
do this to begin with?
I'm guessing it's because he
never thought that far ahead.
He probably met
Kira and was told
which criminals he'd
be allowed to judge.
Mm, I suspect the
purpose of this message
is to hide the
fact that they met.
LIGHT: I see.
What I find really
strange is that it's
unlike Kira to be so careless.
-That's true.
[slurp] Mm.
But are we to believe that
Kira made a mistake this time?
Or is this his way
of letting us know
that they have made contact?
It would be an effective
means of provoking us.
The idea of their union
is very threatening.
However, this is
also one less reason
to suspect that Light is Kira.
-Ryuzaki, what do
you mean by that?
-If Light is Kira,
I don't think this
is the message he would have
had the second Kira send us.
It doesn't fit.
He would have made the second
Kira go through with his plan
to have me appear on TV,
then deny that they ever
made contact, letting
the second Kira shoulder
the blame for my death.
He'd make him say
something like, hm,
although I agreed not
to go through with this,
I have come to realize that it
was not Kira's true intention
that I stop.
I'm positive that the real
Kira would want L to die.
There's no way
he'd make me stop.
[slurp] Mm.
LIGHT: Ryuzaki?
-Yes, Light?
LIGHT: I think you're mistaken.
I would never do
that if I were Kira.
L: Why not?
-Well, if you're L
and I'm Kira, then I'd
already know your
personality pretty well.
L would never agree to
appear on TV, no matter
what threat he was facing.
And he wouldn't allow someone
else to die in his place.
The L I know would find some
way to escape the situation.
-So, you've figured it out?
-Look, Light.
You've got to stop that.
I don't like hearing
you say, "if I
were Kira," even hypothetically.
-Oh, I'm sorry Dad.
I just wanted to
let Ryuzaki know
exactly what I
thought of his plan.
-Hm.
LIGHT: I posed that
scenario because I
want to help solve this case.
It's the only chance I
have to clear my name.
Besides, the only reason I
feel comfortable saying things
like that is because
I'm not really Kira.
L: That's a good point.
You're not Kira.
That is, it would be a
problem if you were Kira,
because I feel you're the first
friend that I have ever had.
RYUK: Oh-ho.
L: Uh, yeah, I
know what you mean.
The two of us have
a lot in common.
-Thank you.
-And I have missed having
you around at school.
We should play
tennis again soon.
-Yes, we should.
-A friend?
He's your friend?
That's a good thing,
isn't it, Light?
-That damn Ryuzaki had no
problem figuring out Kira
and the second Kira had made
contact with each other.
I've got to eliminate
him right away.
-I see.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): The way
things are progressing,
I can't afford to
be seen with Misa.
MISA: Light!
-[grunt] Ah!
MISA: I'm sorry, but I just
couldn't wait for two weeks
like you said.
Actually, I was just
on my way to your house
when I spotted you. [giggle]
-[groan]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): This is
the first time in my life
that I've been provoked
to hit a woman.
-I-- I just wanted
to see you so badly.
-Well, you might
as well come over.
-Yay!
-Another girlfriend?
-Oh!
Great to see you, Misa.
I saw you in a whole
bunch of magazines.
-Please, come on in.
--[giggle] Sorry to
drop by like this.
-Could you make
us some tea, Mom?
Rem.
-Huh?
-You are Misa's
ally, aren't you?
-Yes.
I'd seen her many times
from the Shinigami realm.
And then certain events made
me develop feelings for her.
-Feelings?
But you're a Shinigami.
[laughs]
-You don't like
what I said before,
about how I'd kill you if you
even attempted to kill Misa.
-So, if Misa is
happy, does that mean
that you'll be happy as well?
-I suppose you could say that.
I definitely don't
want her to suffer.
LIGHT: As you know,
Misa loves me.
-Oh, Light.
-Misa.
-Yes?
-If I was happy, would
that make you happy, too?
MISA: Yes.
-[laughs]
LIGHT: Then could you
ask Rem to kill L?
-Huh?
-Rem said that your
happiness was important.
But what do you think would
happen if L caught one of us?
It means our happiness
would be ruined.
--[laughs] It's true that
Shinigami are forbidden to give
out a person's name to anyone.
But then again,
there's no rule that
prevents Rem from
killing anyone.
-That's right.
And if you agree to
kill L, it would only
make me love Misa
that much more.
Plus, I'd be grateful to you.
Most importantly, the two of
us will be happy together.
-Rem, I want Light to love me.
And I know we could
be happy together.
It's all I ever wanted.
-That's a shame.
REM: Fine.
-[gasp]
-As you wish, Light Yagami.
But I do not like you.
This will not kill
me, even if it ends up
lengthening your life.
I will kill L for you.
It really makes no difference.
He is just another human to me.
MISA: Hooray!
Oh, Rem, thank you so much.
I knew I could count on you.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): L will die.
That's all it took.
[theme music]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): That's right.
Ryuga revealed that he's
L. Therefore, he must die.
The game is over.
[laugh] Tomorrow will
be L's, or at least
Ryuga and Ryuzaki's,
last day alive.