[theme music]
-I'm going to announce
my engagement to Light
at the pop music festival.
I used to really like Kira
too, but I know for sure
that Light is gonna
catch him soon.
And as for you, you'll
probably be executed.
TAKADA: You are to
send me a fan latter
that I'll be able to
recognize as yours.
You will also enclose
something else in the envelope.
Five blank pages
from the notebook.
Carry on with your judgments
and killings as usual
until I received the
letter and the pages.
-And how after you receive them?
-Make a notebook that looks
as close to the original as
possible, and act as if
you're killing people
by using this decoy.
-I mean, wearing a short
skirt like that in the winter.
-Please, someone.
-Delete.
-He's getting off the train.
[screaming]
-A man who was on the same
train as Mikami just collapsed.
He was harrassing a young woman
and suddenly fell to the floor.
It all happened
about a half a minute
after he wrote something
in the notebook.
That's gotta be it.
-Well, now we know for sure.
-Yes.
Our next order of
business is to get
as close as possible to Mikami.
But before we rush
in blindly, there's
something we need
to be careful of,
and that is the being
known as the Shinigami.
The Shinigami will
be loyal to Mikami,
and it will warn him if it
discovers we're following him.
-But the Shinigami
can only be seen
by those people who have
touched the notebook.
It's going to be
pretty difficult to be
careful of something
we can't even see.
-We're going to try, no
matter how difficult.
-Right.
Understood, sir.
AIZAWA: Light's having another
one of his meetings with Takada
this evening.
Right after they started
having these encounters,
Takada got a phone
call from Kira,
and all the surveillance
cameras had to be removed.
The first thing
that came to my mind
was that they'd be able
to communicate secretly
by writing messages.
-Everything checks out in here.
I've gone over the entire room,
and there's nothing in it.
There's only the wiretap on me.
-Uh, right.
Then all that's left
is the bathroom.
Why does Light care
so much about checking
for cameras and wiretaps?
Never mind that, why is
Kira allowing these meetings
in the first place?
Something just doesn't add up.
If they really are writing
notes to each other,
there's only one
way to prove it.
-Light.
I thought you should know.
I had a private chat with
Ms. Misa Amane yesterday.
-About what?
-Whoa.
Oh boy, Light's in trouble now.
-Matsuda.
Is there some reason
you're so happy about this?
-She told me that she's planning
to announce her engagement
to you during her appearance
at the pop music festival.
-Whoa.
He's busted.
Light's in the dog house!
-Shut up, Matsuda!
-No.
She thinks we're together
because I haven't
been able to break
it to her yet,
but she means nothing to me.
Misa, you idiot.
Why pull a stunt like that?
No.
Takada.
you're just as bad.
Why are women like this?
-Nothing, you say?
Why should I believe you?
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
She was in charge
of killing before T. Somehow
she gained the same power as I
had and found out
that I was Kira.
In the end, I had no choice
but to take her as my partner.
It's the only
reason I would ever
choose such an impulsive girl.
KIYOMI (VOICEOVER): So, Misa
was doing Kira's killings.
But right now, I'm the
one doing it for him.
Light had no choice
with Misa, but he
chose me specially to help him.
-Believe me.
She's nothing.
You're the only one for me.
-You're the only one for me?
Is that supposed to be serious?
I expected better
from you, Light.
IDE: She does have a point.
I mean, that's a really cheesy
line, especially for Light.
MATSUDA: So which one
do you think he'll pick?
Amane or Takada?
IDE: Well, he could
keep two timing them.
MATSUDA: Are you serious?
You don't see any
problem with that?
-Hey, I'm not the one who--
-Will you two shut up?
-You're going to have to prove
yourself from now on, Light,
but I will trust you.
Of course, if I find
out that you're lying,
you'll pay dearly.
In fact, I'll tell
Kira about it.
-Kira, huh?
You know, I understand that
the world really needs Kira
right now, but I just
can't help but wonder.
Will the day ever come when
you and I can be together?
I can't help but hate Kira for
choosing you as a spokesperson,
because it keeps us apart.
I don't mind if he
kills criminals,
but we've done nothing wrong.
We have the right to lead
happy lives, don't we?
-Yes.
I want to be happy
together with you.
But that could only happen
if Kira wasn't around.
-You're right.
If only Kira wasn't around.
-Kira should be arrested.
It's true.
If you and I are ever going to
have a chance at being happy
together, Kira
needs to be caught.
-W-- Wait a minute, Kiyomi.
Do you seriously mean that?
-Yes.
LIGHT (ON RADIO): All right,
but if I'm going to arrest him,
I'll need your help.
You'll be putting
yourself in danger.
After all, I'll be
defying the police,
and you'll be going against Kira
and the entire world as well.
Are you sure that's OK?
-That's a long pause.
-All right.
If cooperating with you means
that we can be together,
then I'm prepared to make
that sacrifice, Light.
-What a turn around.
Just like you'd
expect from our guy!
He was able to move
the conversation
from cheating on Misa Misa
to getting Taki to help him.
-Mikami's talking to himself.
-What's going on?
-He was too far away for
me to pick up his voice,
but I recorded video
of his lips moving.
I'm sending you the
footage I was able to get.
It's of Mikami during
his lunch break.
This is it right here.
He's saying something.
RESTER: Show it to us one
more time in slow motion.
Is that you, Shinigami,
is what he said.
GIOVANNI: He seems to have
reacted to the scrap of paper
at his feet.
RESTER: He just
gave a small sigh.
GIOVANNI: At this point, he
talks to himself a little more.
I'm gonna zoom in on his lips.
RESTER: That Shinigami.
Ever since he handed me the
notebook, he hasn't reappeared.
That Shinigami.
Ever since he handed me the
notebook, he hasn't reappeared.
-Mikami was given the notebook
by one of the Shinigami,
but it seems that Shinigami
hasn't been following him.
So that's how it is.
-I guess that's all for today.
See you next time.
-Of course.
-It's finally over.
Man, things got pretty intense
today, don't you think?
It's tough to do this
for hours on end.
-Yeah.
You really look like
you're suffering.
-All right.
I'm gonna wrap things
up at the hotel.
-OK, thanks for
all your hard work.
You know, I feel kind
of bad that Aizawa
is stuck with booking the hotel
and checking out every time.
-It's gone.
The mark I left is gone.
I left four marks.
Two of them are gone.
The room's been
left just as it was.
Housekeeping hasn't come in yet.
Then how and why
would anyone switch
these two notepads for new ones?
That settles it.
They're writing notes.
[phone ringing]
-Yes?
What's that?
You want to meet and
talk with Near in person?
-Mr. Aizawa.
It's been a while.
And it's a pleasure to meet you.
-That's very nice
of you, but kind of
hard to accept while
I'm blindfolded.
-He doesn't have any
weapons or cameras on him.
-In that case, you're free
to take off your blindfold.
-Huh?
Near, I believe what
you said earlier.
L was been meeting Takada
almost every single night.
-I know.
-Well, then what about this?
They are passing
notes to each other.
I confirmed it.
-Mr. Aizawa, please don't
take any unnecessary actions
on your own.
-Unnecessary actions?
-Yes This is not the point
where we bring up evidence Kira
and openly confront him.
I must corner him in
a dead end with a plan
that would guarantee his defeat.
This is what it will take
to stop him for good.
Mr. Aizawa, I'm going
to be blunt with you.
You and the rest
of the task force
are already out of the picture.
However, if you still want to
help capture Kira, you can.
All I want you to do
is keep an eye on him,
as you've been doing.
-That's it?
Keep an eye on him?
-Yes.
Of course, there
certainly is a purpose
in watching over L. In
fact, I've already taken it
into account as part of my plan.
That's why I'm hoping you
can help me in that respect.
I want you to watch him, in
order to win against Kira.
And after that, I want you to
be a witness to the end of Kira.
TAKADA: This has been a
year of breathroughs for me,
and I'm sure for
many others as well.
And what better way to bring
this year to an exciting close
than with the East-West
Pop Music festival?
I'm your host for this
evening, Kiyomi Takada.
We hope you all enjoy the show.
-All right, the pop music
festival's about to begin!
-Matsuda, shouldn't
you be checking
over the reports
on Kira's killings?
-Yeah.
In a minute.
But after Misa Misa performs.
She's the opening act this year.
We got to cheer her on.
Yeah!
-Can we help you?
-Hm?
-Pardon me.
We're from the SPK.
We'll need you to come with us.
-Before we continue,
I'm afraid I
must apologize on behalf
of the staff of NHN.
It's very unfortunate, but it
seems that this year's opening
act, Ms. Misa Amane, has not
entered the concert hall yet.
-Huh?
-What?
-Of course, many
unexpected things can--
-What's going on?
Mogi didn't tell us
anything about this.
MISA: Take me back
to NHN right now!
What is this?
Are you trying to
ruin my reputation?
-Misa Misa, you've got
to try and stay calm.
-Motchi, why should I?
-We need to do this in
order to catch Kira.
MISA: But that has
nothing to do with me.
-You should know
that I was going
to take you at gunpoint
as a last resort.
But you didn't resist.
That was a great help.
Thank you, Mr. Mogi.
-I probably would
have resisted if I
hadn't listen to
what Aizawa told me.
But after hearing
about the notepads,
there's no doubt in my mind.
-(VOICEOVER) What's going on?
-Near.
NEAR: Yes?
What is it, L?
-We have a problem.
Mogi and Misa Amane
have gone missing.
NEAR: I'm already aware of that.
I was the one who took
them into custody.
-He what?
-For what reason?
-Oh, just in case.
-Near, kidnapping is a
blatant criminal act.
You have to stop this now.
NEAR: Actually, Mr. Mogi and
Amane both came here willingly.
You can even ask them yourself.
I'll put them on the line now.
Here they are.
LIGHT: Mogi.
Misa.
This is L speaking.
-(VOICEOVER) Light!
-I'm told that Near
is detaining you.
He said that you
both agreed to it.
Is that true?
-It is.
-Mogi.
-Actually, I was
against the whole thing.
But Motchi said it would be best
if I just went along quietly.
He told me we would have
both been killed if I didn't.
-All right.
It's fine, as long as you
both consented to this.
-So now I've removed
Misa Amane, the one who
might be the second
Kira from the equation.
Light Yagami, I'm sure the
significance of this move
isn't lost on you.
-Hey, no way!
You're planning to end this
without Misa Misa performing?
-God, what a ripoff!
-It looks like Lidner and
the others were successful.
It's past 9:00.
All right.
It's my turn.
Mikami leaves work at almost
the same time every day,
with only slight variations.
He leads a completely scheduled
life, for the most part.
-So, he always goes
to that particular gym
every Monday and
Thursday at around 9:00.
Is that correct?
-Yes.
He's kept that routine
for the past four years,
ever since he joined.
He didn't even skip
New Year's Day.
I became a member and made a few
inquiries to confirm it myself.
-Good.
So then we can assume that he'll
be there on Monday the 31st as
well?
-Yes.
If he's the type of man
who would go on holidays,
then he'll certainly
go on New Year's Eve.
-Giovanni, would it
be possible for you
to touch the notebook
on the 31st at the gym?
-Huh?
Yes.
I've already done a thorough
check of the hotel's security.
The locker room is
definitely free of any kind
of surveillance.
NEAR: Then I'll leave it to you.
-Sir, if there is a
Shinigami with him,
there's a distinct possibility
that I will die, isn't there?
NEAR: Yes.
Part of The reason you're doing
this is to test that theory.
Even if you don't see any
Shinigami after first touching
the notebook, I want you
to continue watching Mikami
for a while longer before
we conclude whether or not
he has one following him.
I can have Rester do it
if you're too scared.
-No.
I understand.
I'll do it.
Hm?
If there's a
Shinigami around-- no.
If there was one, I'd be dead.
It's too late to turn back now.
I have to touch it.
Sir, I've succeeded in
touching the notebook.
I can't confirm the existence
of any Shinigami at this time.
-Commander Rester,
please connect me
with Mr. Mogi for a moment.
-Hm?
-Mr. Mogi, according to your
investigation and the rules
of the notebook, how
long can a person be
controlled before their death?
-Based on the data we got
from Yotsuba's experiments,
it's 23 days.
NEAR: Are you sure?
-Yes.
I'd say that the
killings done by Yotsuba
were more than
enough to prove it.
-Thank you for your assistance.
We have to consider
the possibility
that Giovanni is already
being controlled.
In that case, they
could be making
him say that there
is no Shinigami.
That means I need to confront
L in exactly 24 days,
if Giovanni is still
alive until then.
-LIGHT: Kiyomi.
I saw you had some trouble
at the pop music festival.
-Yes.
I never imagined that
Ms. Amane would missing.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Give T an
order to contact you and let
you know as soon as he's
confirmed everything.
Once you hear from him, I want
you to send me a text message
or call me with the
following message.
I want to see you
as soon as possible.
GIOVANNI (VOICEOVER):
Photographs?
-Yes.
I want to see exactly what
he wrote in the notebook.
I want to see the pattern
in how Mikami writes,
if there are any habits, and
what kind of notebook it is.
I want to see it all.
Everything in detail
with my own eyes.
RESTER: What do you think, Near?
NEAR: Perfect.
Giovanni has done
an excellent job.
The handwriting matches
that of the records
Mikami keeps as prosecutor.
There's absolutely no doubt.
This is his handwriting.
-I agree.
-With this, we can do it.
[theme music]
LIGHT: The escort team
has been attacked.
Ms. Takada, are you all right?
Is this Near's work again?
No.
This isn't his style.
It's more like Mello!