[theme music]
[beep]
-Huh?
[sigh] Ah, OK, maybe the belt.
[beep]
Huh?
What now?
-Well, looks like
this system's going
to take some getting used to.
AIZAWA: Fine.
How's this?
Huh?
Good morning.
-Eh?
-What's wrong?
Did you get hurt?
-Oh, this?
Kind of.
[laugh] I had a little
fight with my wife,
and-- it's just that my
daughter's still young,
and I'm hardly ever
at home as it is, so--
-Ah, yes.
It's probably best
if you sleep at home.
-Well, you're going
to be missing out.
The rooms in this
place are amazing.
If I were you, I'd just move
the whole family in here.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's easy for you
to say as a bachelor.
Where are they?
-Oh, they're on a date.
Last we checked, all of them
were up in Misa-Misa's room.
-Hmm.
AIZAWA: Surveillance
cameras, huh?
Well, since we know
Misa has some connection
to the second Kira, I
guess it does make sense.
But for god's sake,
Matsuda, would you
stop with this Misa-Misa crap?
MATSUDA: Uh, yeah, sure.
-Man, this has gotta be the
lamest date I've ever been on.
-No, no, no, please, just
pretend I'm not even here, OK?
By the way, are you going
to eat that piece of cake?
MISA: Cake makes you fat.
I'm not gonna eat any.
-Actually, I find that you don't
gain any weight as long as you
burn calories by
using your brain.
-Hmph!
So now you're calling me stupid?
Fine, then.
I'll give you the
piece of cake as long
as you agree to leave
me and Light alone.
-Even if I leave
you two alone, I'm
still going to be watching
on surveillance cameras.
So it wouldn't make
any difference.
-You pervert!
Can't you stop it with
your creepy hobby?
-You can call me
whatever you like.
Last chance for cake.
-OK, then.
I'll just close the curtains
and turn off the lights.
L: We have infrared
cameras in here as well.
[grumbling]
-What's wrong with you?
I thought moving here was
supposed to help us catch Kira.
But since we've
been here, you don't
seem all that motivated to me.
L: Not motivated?
You're right.
Actually, I'm depressed.
-Depressed?
What for?
-Well, truthfully,
all this time, I
thought that you were
Kira, and my entire case
hinged on that fact.
I guess I just can't
get past the fact
that my deduction was wrong.
Although having said that,
I'm still suspicious of you.
That's why we're wearing these.
And we also know that Kira can
control people's actions, which
means it's highly likely
that Kira was controlling
your actions so that
I would suspect you.
If I assume both you and Misa
were being controlled by him,
then everything
we've observed so far
makes a lot more sense to me.
-If that's what you
think, Misa and I
were both Kira during
the time that we
were being controlled, right?
L: Yes.
I don't think I could have
been wrong about that.
The two of you are Kira.
-Hmm.
L: If what I'm
thinking is correct,
when your confinement
began, you were Kira.
I don't believe it's
coincidence that as soon
as you were imprisoned,
all the killings stopped.
Until then, everything
pointed to you being Kira.
But after two weeks, criminals
actually began dying again.
Based on that
evidence, I can only
conclude that Kira's power
passes between people.
-That's an interesting idea.
But if it's true, it'll
be nearly impossible
for us to catch Kira.
-Yes.
That's why I'm overwhelmed.
Even if we catch
someone under control,
they'll likely lose their powers
and any memory of their crimes.
So in the end, pursuing
them becomes futile.
-But at this point,
we have no way
of knowing if that's the case.
Cheer up, would you?
-Cheer up?
No, I'm sorry, I can't.
It's probably better if I
just stop trying so hard.
By chasing Kira so
desperately, we're
just putting our lives
at risk or nothing.
Yes, it's just a waste of time.
-Ryuzaki.
-Huh?
[shout]
[scream]
-Eh?
Eww.
-You know, that really hurt.
-That's enough.
You don't feel like
doing anything,
just because your genius
deduction was wrong,
and I'm not Kira?
-Fine.
Perhaps I phrased
that the wrong way.
I meant it would be pointless
for us to make a move,
so we shouldn't even bother.
-If we don't chase Kira,
he'll never be caught.
Is that what you want?
If you were just
going to give up,
then why did you involve
all those innocent people?
More importantly,
what was the point
of putting Misa
and me behind bars?
-I understand.
But still, whatever the reason--
an eye for an eye, my friend.
[shout]
It's not my deduction
that was wrong.
The fact is, I can say
that Light Yagami is Kira
and Misa Amane is
the second Kira,
but it won't be enough
to solve the case.
And that's why I'm
a little depressed.
Is that so unreasonable?
-Yes.
Yes, it is.
Besides, you should
hear yourself.
It's as if you won't be
satisfied unless I am Kira.
-I-- I won't be satisfied
unless you're Kira.
Well, there may be
some truth to that.
In fact, now that you
mention it, you're right.
I think I wanted you to be Kira.
[shout]
As I said before,
an eye for an eye.
I'm a lot stronger
than I look, you know.
-We've got to call the
room and stop them.
[phone ringing]
-Huh?
Yes?
MATSUDA (ON PHONE):
Ryuzaki, I've got good news.
Misa-Misa's number one
in "Eighteen" magazine's
reader popularity poll.
L (ON PHONE): Oh, I see.
MATSUDA (ON PHONE):
And get this,
she's going to get a lead
role in Ishinaka's next movie.
-What was that?
-Matsuda's acting stupid again.
LIGHT: Hmm.
Well, that is his specialty.
-I can hear you, you know.
-Ryuzaki, I know you're
not feeling up to it,
but come over here for a second.
Take a close look at this.
It can't be coincidence.
-Huh?
-All of the more prominent
Japanese businessmen,
CEOs whose companies are leaders
in their respective industries,
in just over a month, they
all died of heart attacks.
As expected, there's been a
general downturn in the market,
with the exception of Yotsuba.
In other words, their deaths
have worked in Yotsuba's favor.
Looking back, there have
been 13 similar deaths
in the past three months.
-Your thoughts?
-Based on this, I
can only conclude
that Kira is supporting Yotsuba.
-Hmm, could be.
But if what you're
saying is true,
we can assume that
punishing criminals is not
this Kira's real intent.
-Right.
Punishing criminals is
a diversion for him.
It obscures the fact that
he's actually killing people
for the benefit of his company.
Hmm.
Are you feeling a bit
more motivated now?
EXECUTIVE: It's funny.
This is starting
to feel too easy.
Look at all we've done, and
no one suspects a thing.
-Our stock continues
to increase,
but we've kept it
below the radar.
-Indeed, everything
appears to be
proceeding according to plan.
-That's true.
However, there is one thing
that has me concerned.
Those three we had killed
last week, why did all of them
die of heart attacks?
I thought we agreed one
would be accidental.
-You're quite right.
We did.
The problem was that we named
a specific location in Japan.
You see, he wasn't
even here when he died.
I hear he and his mistress
were in Italy at the time.
-Makes sense.
If our request is physically
impossible, then--
-Kira will kill that person
using his default method,
a heart attack.
-It's just like I was
saying last week, if you
want it to look believable,
request accidental death
or disease, and Kira will
always find the quickest way
to make it happen.
-Anyway, given Kira's
history, the police
are probably still focused
on the dying criminals.
Quite frankly, if
someone was able to trace
the deaths of these
people back to us,
then he'd have to be a god.
Besides, we've
taken precautions.
-Uh-- hey, chief.
Oh, you too, Mogi.
I've got some great news.
This is amazing.
I'm not even sure how
we figured it out,
but Light has a theory
that Kira is somehow
involved with the Yotsuba Group.
Can you believe it?
-Yotsuba?
-Uh, yes.
-That's probably it.
Good work.
-Huh?
-We just spoke
with the director,
and it seems Kira
has offered bribes
to a number of politicians.
-Kira made an offer.
As long as the NPA agrees
not to pursue him anymore,
he won't lay a hand
on any politicians.
-So that's that.
The police caved in to him.
-Huh?
-Mogi and I have already
made up our minds on this.
Aizawa, Matsuda, if you wish
to continue working this case,
you'll have to hand in
your letter of resignation
to the NPA, just as Mogi
and I are going to do.
[gasp]
Like it or not, you cannot
pursue Kira as a member
of the police force any more.
-Hold-- hold on a second, Chief.
-They made it quite clear.
If you continue to work
with L, you'll be fired.
That's all there is to it.
-So then, Chief, you're gonna--
-In a few hours, I'm no
longer going to be your chief.
However, we all
have our own lives.
So think it over carefully.
-That's true, Chief,
especially if you've
got a family to support.
L: If you want my opinion,
you'd be better off
as police officers.
I was alone when I
started this case.
And although I'm
grateful to all of you
for staying with me
as long as you have,
I know that I can
do this by myself.
I'll be sure to visit
you at the department
and bring you Kira's
head as a reward for all
that you've sacrificed.
-Ryuzaki, as long as I'm alive,
you won't be working alone.
You have my word on that.
L: Hmm, that's right.
I'll have Light working
with me until I catch Kira,
so I won't be alone after all.
But as I said, I
think the rest of you
should remain as
police officers.
-But when you
first contacted us,
you said that you would
need the help of the police
in order to solve this case.
-That's because the
police as an organization
were still hoping
to arrest Kira.
They weren't bowing to him.
Besides, with all
due respect, there's
a big difference between the
help of two or three civilians
and the police as
an organization.
As you said, the police have
made their position clear.
They don't want to catch Kira,
so let's just leave it at that.
-Well, I suppose what
you're saying makes sense.
If we're not police
officers anymore,
we won't be of much use to you.
However, we're all
personally involved in this.
All of us have risked
our lives to catch Kira.
Doesn't that give us the right
to decide whether we stay here
or return to the police force?
-Ah, good point.
Then by all means, please,
make your decision.
-But Chief, wait.
If you quit your job
with the police force,
you'll be unemployed.
Even if we do catch Kira, what
are you going to do after that?
-After that, I hadn't
really thought of it.
But I suppose after
we catch Kira,
I'll have to dust off my resume.
-Count me in!
I'm going to quit the police
and chase Kira too, Chief!
And I still have my job
as Misa-Misa's manager.
Besides, if I stayed
on as a police officer,
I'd feel like a total loser.
SOICHIRO YAGAMI: Think before
you open your mouth, Matsuda.
-Uh--
--[stammering] Is there any
way I could still keep my job
and help you in my spare time?
-There isn't.
If you remain a
police officer, then
please don't come back here.
-But you know I won't
leak any information.
-I won't be sharing
any of our information.
[gasp]
You're free to pursue Kira
on your own, if you want to.
But I don't think it's
fair to your families
to burden them by giving
up your livelihood just
to continue this.
I can't see how
that's a good idea.
-It's as Ryuzaki says.
No one here is going to
blame you for quitting.
-Yeah, right.
We all understand why
you've got to do this.
-But the chief has a family too.
-Our situations are
completely different.
-Damn it.
To leave now, after all
we've been through-- I
said I was prepared
to die if that's
what it took to catch
him, and I meant it.
What kind of friend would I
be to Ukita if I quit now?
I became a detective so I
could catch the bad guys,
not run away!
[beep]
WATARI (ON COMPUTER): Ryuzaki,
early on in the investigation,
you specifically told me that
if a task force member were
to lose their job under
any circumstances,
I should make preparations
to ensure that their family's
financial future was secure.
If you recall, a trust was set
aside for that very purpose.
I'm a little curious
as to why you're
withholding this information.
[gasp]
-This is not the time
or place, Watari.
WATARI (ON COMPUTER):
I am sorry.
-No way!
So all this time, we had
nothing to worry about?
I can't believe you did that.
There you go, Aizawa.
Isn't that great news?
Huh?
-Ryuzaki, I assume that
was some kind of test
to determine how committed
I was to this task force.
-It-- it's not
like that, Aizawa.
Ryuzaki's just not the type
to say things directly.
You should know that by now.
-Yeah, that's right.
L: No.
-Huh?
-I was testing you.
I wanted to see which
one you would choose.
-Ryuzaki.
-Fine, then.
If I wasn't sure
before, I am now.
-But Aizawa--
-Let's face it.
I wasn't able to decide
right away like you guys.
I was leaning towards
going back to the police.
-Come on, Aizawa.
Don't be so stubborn.
-No, I quit.
Now I know this for sure.
I've always hated Ryuzaki.
I hate him and his
way of doing things!
L: That's too bad, because
I like you, Aizawa.
-I also hate the
way you've always
gotta have the last word!
You insult me, now you
say something like that?
That's it.
I'm outta here.
-Thank you for everything.
-I just found another one,
a general manager of a bank,
Yotsuba's biggest competitor.
On September 7, he slipped
and fell on the front steps
of his house and died instantly.
SOICHIRO YAGAMI: September the
7th was a Friday, wasn't it?
-Hmm?
-After going over this
again, I noticed something.
All the deaths which are
beneficial to Yotsuba
are concentrated
around the weekends.
-Huh?
On the weekends?
-With the first few
victims, the time of death
appears to have been random.
More recently,
they all take place
between Friday night
and Saturday afternoon.
-I'm amazed that you
even noticed that, Chief.
-Matsuda, I thought I told
you to stop calling me chief.
-I'm sorry, but you'll
always be the chief to me.
-This is a really
important clue, Dad.
Nice work.
-Well, you know,
I can't let myself
fall behind you and Ryuzaki.
After all, the last thing I
want is to be dead weight.
-Ah?
Dead weight?
L: Is Kira someone from Yotsuba?
Or is Kira simply using Yotsuba?
I haven't figured that
out yet, but we'll
proceed under the assumption
that this is Kira's doing.
We will focus on Yotsuba.
-This is all of the
Yotsuba Group's employees.
Here.
-Thank you very much.
-That's 300,000 people.
How did you put this
together so quickly?
That's amazing, Mogi.
L: He's been incredibly
efficient from the start.
-Ryuzaki, please
tell me, is there
anything I can do to help
with the investigation,
besides the manager thing?
-So you really
want to be useful?
-Yes.
-Then could you get me
another cup of coffee?
-Uh--
-And for our guests
over there as well.
-Uh?
Who are they?
-Hold on a sec.
Who let them in?
-Those two are the newest
members of the task force.
-The name's Aiber.
I'm a con man.
How's it going?
-I'm Wedy.
And I'm a thief by trade.
-Oh, a con man and a thief.
-That's right.
Aiber is a lifelong con man.
His unparalleled social skills
allow him to befriend and gain
the trust of any target.
We'll use him for infiltration.
As for Wedy, she's a
thief who specializes
in cracking high-end
security systems.
As proof of how that, she was
able to enter the building
without setting
off a single alarm.
-You expect us to
work with criminals?
-Yes, that is correct.
However, these two have
never once been caught,
so it's unlikely they'll
be killed by Kira.
Think of them as professionals
of the underworld.
-I understand.
To investigate
Yotsuba, we're going
to need the help of
people like this.
Let's all do our part
and make this happen, OK?
-Yeah.
-(RELUCTANTLY) Uh, yeah.
[laughing]
-Huh?
Daddy?
-[laughing] Daddy!
-Yumi.
Eriko.
-What are you doing here?
Shouldn't you be
at work right now?
You need to tell me if you're
planning to be home for dinner.
I just went shopping, and I
only bought for me and Yumi.
-You can eat my dinner, and
I'll have dessert instead.
-Sorry.
It was sort of a
last minute decision,
but they just gave
me some time off.
-Huh?
Is a time off a vacation, Daddy?
-Yeah, that's right.
-Yippee!
-(VOICE CATCHING) From now on,
I can have a break every single
week.
Now I can go with
you to the park.
Maybe we can go to the zoo
together or the amusement park.
[crying]
-Oh?
What's wrong, Dad?
Mommy, why is Daddy crying?
[theme music]
MATSUDA (VOICEOVER):
Confidential meetings?
And from the sound of it, they
have one every Friday night.
This is it!
I'm on a roll today.