[music playing]
[music - nightmare,"the world"]
SOICHIRO: What?
[strangled cry]
SOICHIRO: I don't believe this.
Another 23 victims yesterday?
Are these confirmed?
L: As soon as we
began to suspect
that Kira might be a student,
the pacing of the killings
changed, as if to
contradict that theory.
This can only mean that Kira has
access to police information.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): When L
discovers that I'm somehow
getting confidential
information,
he'll be obligated to start
investigating the police
to find the source of the leak.
-You're being followed
by another human.
He's watching you right now.
LIGHT: That's a problem.
I'll have to get rid of
him as soon as possible.
-Because through a
Shinigami's eyes,
a human's name can be
seen above their head.
Not only that-- we see
their lifespan as well.
However, if a Shinigami
drops his Death Note
and a human picks it up,
he can grant that human
the eyes of a Shinigami.
The price for having
a Shinigami's eyes
is half of that person's
remaining lifespan.
That's all it is.
So what'll it be, Light?
Is it a deal?
-Has anyone seen
Ryuk around lately?
-Maybe he was serious about
losing his Death Note.
SHINIGAMI: It was probably
picked up by some human
before he could get to it.
-No way.
Then he'd be stuck there till
the end of that human's life
or until the Death
Note was destroyed.
That could take a while.
-Yeah.
I can't picture Ryuk
doing something so boring.
SHINIGAMI: But do you know what?
I actually heard he was
carrying two Death Notes.
SHINIGAMI: Seriously?
Why would he need two?
-Beats me.
I'll never understand that guy.
LIGHT: So the
price for receiving
the eyes of a Shinigami
is no more than half
of my remaining lifespan?
That's it, right?
RYUK: Yes.
Well then, do we
have a deal or not?
-Ryuk, this deal is
out of the question.
-Huh?
[dog barking in distance]
LIGHT: Let's get this straight.
My plan is to create
an ideal new world
free from evil
and all criminals,
and I intend to reign as a
god in that world for a very
long time.
I might consider the deal
if it lengthened my life,
but not if I'd die sooner.
I figured you of
all people should
know I wouldn't take this deal.
RYUK: Yeah.
I still felt I should tell
you that the deal existed,
just in case.
Anyway, I've done my part.
I don't need you complaining
I didn't tell you
this earlier on.
LIGHT: This is what you
call telling me early on?
Don't you think
you're a little late?
I don't see why you couldn't
have told me this when we met.
Or better yet, you could
have simply included it
in the instructions
for the Death Note.
-Uh, good point.
(VOICEOVER) He's not
the slightest bit
daunted by the fact
that I'm a Shinigami.
He doesn't suck up
to me and he seems
to have no problem
giving me a hard time.
LIGHT: Well?
You sure there's nothing else
you want to tell me ahead
of time, Shinigami?
-No.
Nothing else.
(VOICEOVER) Probably.
-Really?
That's too bad.
RYUK: What do you mean?
-You know, Ryuk, I might have
seriously considered the deal
if you'd offered me
wings instead of eyes.
Just the idea of flying
round freely in the sky
sounds very godlike.
After all, it's
been mankind's dream
since antiquity
to be able to fly.
-You'd stand out if you
sprouted wings and flew around.
Not to mention, the police would
have no trouble finding you.
-I was only joking.
Anyway, if I keep bargaining
for eyes and wings
and whatever else,
next thing you know,
I'm going to end up
becoming a real Shinigami.
Though who knows?
I bet that could be
pretty interesting.
-I wouldn't worry.
Even without the
eyes and the wings,
you're already a
worthy Shinigami.
The Shinigami Realm
is slowly rotting.
We lead meaningless
and empty lives.
And the only reason we
still take human lives
is because we're afraid
to die ourselves.
The truth of the matter
is that we no longer even
know why we exist.
In fact, I doubt
there's any reason
for our existence at all.
What I'm saying is
compared to that,
you're becoming a much
more impressive Shinigami.
-I don't know about that.
I mean, from what
you're telling me,
it sounds like I'm doing a
lot more work than they are.
But I don't want to be
compared to a Shinigami.
I'm a human using
this Death Note
to make the world a better
place for other humans.
But I wouldn't necessarily
say that the Shinigami Realm
is meaningless to
humans, either.
-Huh?
Why do you say that?
-Well, just think about it.
Whenever a Shinigami
like you comes
to the human world, once every
100-- no, more like every 1,000
years, the human world
changes dramatically.
The existence of the Shinigami
Realm is extremely significant.
-Really?
-You told me just now that
the Shinigami Realm is slowly
rotting, right?
Well, when you return
from this world,
why not use what
you've learned here
to try and change
it for the better?
-Well, Light, I'm not sure why
I never noticed this until now,
but you're quite the
positive thinker.
-[laughs] Yeah, of course I am.
That's why I'm using the Death
Note to create a better world.
You have to be a
positive thinker
to even attempt
something like this.
That's it.
I got it.
-Got what?
What's this about?
[buzz and hum]
-I think I just
figured out how find
the name the guy who
was following me today.
-How are you going to do that?
-I'm going to use the rules of
the Death Note to my advantage.
I already know that if I
write down a cause of death,
I've got six minutes
and 40 seconds
to record the conditions
and exact time of death.
First, I need to
know exactly how
far I can go in
terms of specifying
the details of death.
This should be interesting.
[phone ringing]
-Yeah, it's me.
Another six inmates were
found dead last night?
All were heart attacks?
It's him.
What?
Bizarre behavior
before they died?
Could you be more specific?
What do you mean?
So they didn't just
die from heart attacks.
No, what I'm saying is they
all died of heart attacks,
but it wasn't quite that simple.
Before one of them died,
he drew a pentagram
on the wall of this cell
using his own blood.
Another left a
letter, but it doesn't
seem to be a will or
anything meaningful.
And as for the third victim,
he escaped from his cell
and ran all the way to the
staff bathrooms before he died.
[beeping]
L: What is it, Watari?
-Three more heart
attack victims.
But the circumstances
of their deaths
are different from what
we've seen thus far.
-What do mean by different?
-I'm sending you a
copy of a letter,
as well as pictures
taken at the scene.
-OK.
L (VOICEOVER): It sounds
like he was afraid
that Kira would find him.
It's believable that our victim
might have been genuinely
afraid and wrote
this, but we know
Kira can control
the time of death.
What if he can also
determine the actions
in the moments
leading up to death?
In which case--
L (ON COMM): Chief.
-Hm?
L (ON COMM): We can't release
details of these men's deaths
to the media.
As far as they're concerned,
these are just heart attacks.
-Oh.
L (ON COMM): I have
reason to believe
that Kira was performing
some kind of test
using these criminals.
And if that's the
case, we'd only
be giving him the results
of this information if we
took it public.
SOICHIRO: Right.
I understand.
-So now he's experimenting
on his victims?
-Horrible.
-He's playing with
people's lives,
as if all this was just a game.
It's unforgivable.
L (VOICEOVER): If Kira
is really using criminals
as test subjects, what
is he trying to achieve?
It's
[clicking]
[beep]
-Look at this, Ryuk.
I think we're in luck.
The results of
yesterday's little test
have already been downloaded
onto my dad's computer.
And these results are
just as I expected.
The Death Note will work
for what I have in mind.
-What do you mean by that?
-One of them escaped and
ran into the bathroom
I had specified
in the Death Note.
Another one drew the same
symbol I had drawn in the Death
Note before he died.
And finally, a third
wrote the same letter
I had written in the
Death Note word for word.
All three did exactly what
I intended them to do.
For the other three
inmates, I purposely
wrote conditions that
were virtually impossible.
-Huh?
-With the first
one, I wrote that he
would die in front of the
Eiffel Tower in one hour.
However, everyone knows that
it's physically impossible
to go from a prison in Japan to
Paris, France in only one hour.
Since this couldn't happen, he
simply died of a heart attack
in prison.
The next was supposed to draw
an exact picture of L's face
on the prison wall.
This also didn't happen.
You can't draw someone
you've never seen, right?
RYUK: Makes sense.
LIGHT: With the
last one, I tried
something slightly different.
I specified that he
would write a note that
read, "I know that
L is suspicious
of the Japanese police."
To be honest, I actually
expected this one to work,
but it didn't end
up happening-- which
means it's impossible
to make someone write
what they don't already know.
Or at the very least, it
has to be the kind of thing
that they could come
up with on their own.
Basically, even the Death
Note can't do the impossible.
But as long as it's within
the realistic limits of what
that person might do,
I can control them
as much as I want
before they die.
-That's very clever.
But what's all this leading to?
What's the point?
-These latest
victims will no doubt
keep L and the police guessing.
Even as we speak
he's probably trying
to decipher all the clues
I left for him, especially
that little note.
That absolutely
meaningless dying message.
L (VOICEOVER): If Kira
used those criminals
to conduct an
experiment of some sort,
it means he's about
to start something.
If he moves now,
there's a good chance
that the FBI will notice
someone acting suspiciously.
But perhaps he has a different
goal in mind altogether.
Could the pentagram and this
letter be some kind of message?
[gasp]
L (VOICEOVER): Is this it?
LIGHT: All right, time
for the real thing.
-Real thing?
-Yesterday on the
news, they said
this drug addict tried to rob
a bank but was unsuccessful.
He attacked a few people and
then ran away empty-handed.
I'll use him.
It's kind of last minute, but
I'm sure I can find someone.
I got a few people in mind.
-A few people?
For what?
-You'll see.
Believe it or not, I'm actually
a rather popular guy, Ryuk.
[phone ringing]
[mumbles sleepily]
-Hello?
Uh-huh?
Light?
Oh, morning.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): He's
still following me.
Perfect.
This whole thing would
just be a waste of time
if he wasn't tailing me.
-Light!
-A date?
-Yeah.
It's a date no matter
how you look at it.
And I'm sure even my stalker
will see it that way.
-But this isn't
just a date, is it?
You said that you'd
figured out a way
to find your stalker's name.
So tell me, what do
you plan on doing?
-Huh?
Come on.
Didn't you see what I
wrote in the Death Note?
I explained it in great detail.
-No.
Doing that would take
all the fun out of it.
-In that case, just be patient
and watch what happens.
Sorry, did I keep you waiting?
-No, not at all.
Anyway, I haven't been to
Spaceland since junior high.
I'm so excited.
And the best part is I
have you all to myself.
-Uh, yeah.
RAYE (VOICEOVER):
During the week
he goes to school and
crams school at night.
Dates on his day off.
A normal kid, just a hardworking
senior in high school.
Chief Yagami's
son, Light Yagami.
No cause for suspicion.
[bus idling]
RAYE (VOICEOVER):
At any rate, I'll
be done with my surveillance
today, and that'll be it.
YURI: I don't get it, Light.
Didn't you say you
weren't going out
until entrance exams were over?
-That was before I scored number
one on the national practice
exams.
-Ooh, you're such
a nerd. [giggles]
[music playing]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): It's him.
He's here.
Seven passengers excluding him.
No one's in the way.
Everything should go smoothly.
[gun cocks]
-Aahh!
(SHOUTING) Stay in your
seats unless you want to die!
YURI: [whimpering]
RAYE (VOICEOVER): A bus-jacking?
You gotta be kidding me.
-Everybody shut up!
If anybody moves, I'm putting
a bullet in their head.
All right, driver,
you listen to me.
I know you've got the number
for Spaceland's office on you.
Call 'em!
-OK.
This-- this is Sasaki
calling from bus 174.
-Tell 'em what's going
on-- and no tricks, either.
-M-my bus has been hijacked and
he's holding a gun to my head.
HIJACKER: Give me that.
You heard what he said.
Now you listen up.
Have a female staff member
bring all of Spaceland's cash
from yesterday.
I know it's there.
Have her meet us two
bus stops from the park,
and don't make me wait.
If you mess with me at all or
try to get the police involved,
I swear I'll kill every
one of these passengers.
Hunnh!
[crunch]
-[whimpering]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Yuri, don't be scared.
As soon as he turns
around I'm going
to grab the gun out of his hand.
-Don't be stupid.
That's risky.
If it comes to that,
I'll take care of it.
It's OK.
We don't have to pass
notes back and forth.
As long as we keep
it down, he won't
be able to hear our voices
over the sound of the engine.
-Do you have any proof that
you're not his accomplice?
Why should we trust you?
-Accomplice?
-Yes, I've read
about this before.
The first hijacker comes
in like he's working alone.
Meanwhile, a second one pretends
to be a hostage and stays
in the very back, just in
case something goes wrong.
What's the matter?
-You-- you really
think he is one?
RAYE (VOICEOVER):
I-- I have no choice.
I'm sure Light
Yagami isn't Kira.
If he was, he could just kill
this guy with a heart attack.
-Here's my proof.
Take a look.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): FBI?
I see.
L needed an outsider so he got
the FBI to investigate anyone
connected to the
Japanese police.
His name is Raye Penber.
-I trust you.
And I guess for
the time being, I
won't bother asking
what an FBI agent is
doing on the bus
in the first place.
Do you have a gun?
RAYE: Yeah, I've got one.
-So if it comes down to it,
I can rely on you, right?
RAYE: Yes.
HIJACKER: (SHOUTING) Get
the hell up, you old hag!
You want me to
shoot you right now?
RAYE (VOICEOVER):
That's right, this guy.
His face was all over the
local news just a few days ago.
-(SHOUTING) Look at me
when I'm talking to you!
RAYE: Some junkie.
He tried to rob a
bank and ended up
killing three people
before he got away.
He's extremely dangerous.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): We're safe.
He won't shoot us.
In fact, he's not
going to do anything.
-Aaah!
-(SHOUTING) Don't
move, you little punk!
What the hell is that?
Ah, smart-ass.
You guys were planning something
back here, weren't you?
RAYE: Damn it.
If he sees that
note from before,
he'll find out that
Light was planning
to jump him and
take his gun away.
HIJACKER: [scoffs]
Plans for a date, huh?
Stupid kid.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Gotcha.
-Huh?
[gasps with fear] Who--
who the hell are you?
You in the very back, what
do you think you're doing?
D-- don't mess with me!
How long you been
hiding back there?
-What's this?
You're talking to me?
So you mean you can
actually see me right now?
-Ahhh!
Stay there, you!
You keep away from
me, you freak.
RAYE (VOICEOVER):
This isn't good.
He's hallucinating.
-(SHOUTING) Everyone get down!
[passengers cry out]
-Oh, I get it.
That little note that,
like, accidentally dropped
was actually torn from the
pages of the Death Note itself.
Since he tricked this guy
into touching the paper,
he's the only other one
in the bus who can see me.
That's so smart.
-(SHOUTING) Get away!
[gunshot]
-Aaaghh!
Aaaaaagh!
[gunshot]
-Sorry, pal.
I'm a Shinigami, so I'm
afraid your bullets aren't
gonna kill me.
[screams]
[frantic gunshots]
[passengers screaming]
[glass shatters]
HIJACKER: [screaming]
[click]
[click] [click]
RYUK: Anyone who touches
the Death Note can see me.
I have to stay till the
death Note is finished
or I see you die,
whichever comes first.
And the Shinigami can't
die from being shot.
I've said all these things
at one time or another.
Well, he is the top-ranked
student in the country.
Guess I shouldn't be surprised.
He even used this
hijacking as a way
to get the guy following him
to willingly give up his name.
-(PANTING) Stop the bus.
Let me off!
[brakes squealing]
[crunch]
[BRAKES SQUEALING AND TIRES
SCREECHING]
[wet thud]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
11:45 on the dot.
Everything went
just as I planned.
Kiichiro Osoreda.
Accidental death.
Boards the 11:31 Spaceland-bound
bus near the eastern entrance
to the park holding a loaded gun
and attempts to hijack the bus.
Sees a horrific
phantom and empties
his gun trying to kill it.
Terrified, he flees the bus.
Immediately
afterwards, at 11:45,
he dies when struck by a car.
The Death Note never failes.
You will be next, Raye Penber.
[music - nightmare, "alumina"]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
It's just as I thought.
He doesn't suspect me at all.
The remaining investigators
will all die of heart attacks.
Farewell, Raye Penber.