[theme music]
-Ryuzaki.
Please let me go
and make the arrest.
-I'd like to come with you,
Chief, if that's all right.
-I understand.
But remember, this is Kira.
Be sure to take every
precaution when you approach him
and don't allow him
to see your face.
Watari.
If Higuchi tries anything
or makes any sudden moves--
-Understood.
I will shoot to stop
him, not to kill.
-Aizawa, do you have
a helmet or something
to hide your face with?
-I do.
-Good.
Then cover me.
-Yes sir.
You can count on me, Chief.
-Higuchi.
Put your hands above your
head and get out of the car.
We've apprehended him.
-Mogi.
I want you to put a
headset on him as planned.
MOGI (ON RADIO): Roger.
L (ON RADIO): Higuchi.
How were you able
to kill people?
Tell me!
If you're not
going to talk, I'll
use whatever means necessary
to get it out of you.
-The notebook.
L (ON RADIO): Notebook?
-You probably won't
believe me, but I've
got a special notebook.
If I write someone's name
in it while thinking about
of their face, that person dies.
L (VOICEOVER): A notebook.
Mr. Yagami.
-Yeah, I found it.
It was in one of the
compartments of Higuchi's bag.
He has written a
lot of names in it,
but there doesn't seem to be
anything else unusual about it.
[screaming]
L (ON RADIO): What
is it, Mr. Yagami?
-It's a monster.
-Please calm down.
Don't panic.
Remember, you're not currently
armed to defend yourself.
-Oh.
All right.
Of course.
-Chief.
Hang in there.
Are you all right?
-Mogi, can't you see
that thing over there?
-Chief.
I think you must
be getting tired.
[screaming]
-Mogi.
What's wrong?
-It-- that thing.
It seems only people who have
touched the notebook can-- can
see this-- this monster.
L (ON RADIO): Please
bring the notebook over
to the helicopter.
-Uh, oh.
OK.
REM (VOICEOVER): What in the
world are you planning to do,
Light Yagami?
Once you take hold of
that notebook again,
all the memories
of the Death Note
and what you did while it was
yours will return at once.
However--
-Here it is, Ryuzaki.
-Hm.
It really is a Shinigami.
They really do exist.
Light Yagami--
[voices whispering]
-Ryuzaki, come on.
Let me see it.
L (VOICEOVER): Two books.
There have to be two notebooks.
Possibly more.
This isn't over yet.
[screaming]
[voices whispering]
-Uh, are you OK, Light?
I suppose seeing that monster
would surprise anyone.
LIGHT: Ryuzaki.
-What is it?
-I want to check this out.
I'm going to try comparing
the names written
in this notebook with
the names of the victims.
-Hm?
Oh, right.
Yeah, that sounds
like a good idea.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): I've won.
Exactly as planned.
I hereby forfeit ownership
of this notebook.
Now, that means ownership is
transferred back to you, right?
-Yes.
I already told you.
-Next, pass it on to Ryuk.
-Hm?
-Very well.
Here.
-Now that notebook's
ownership has
been transferred
from you to Ryuk.
OK, Ryuk.
Take the notebook and
drop it on the ground
so it's in the
human world again.
-Huh?
Well, OK.
-Now the ownership
goes back to me.
-Whoa, hang on.
It's just gone
around in a circle.
Nothing's changed, right?
-Maybe, at first glance.
But there will be a time
when I'll benefit from this.
Now, as for this notebook,
the one I first received,
I'm gonna give it
back to you, Ryuk.
Then you hand it over to Rem.
-Here.
-Rem, I want you to give
the notebook to someone
with status who lusts
for power and money.
They'll end up using the
notebook to satisfy that urge.
If you do that, I can
guarantee that Misa
will be released from
her confinement soon.
And if I'm wrong,
and if it looks
like she won't be released for
years, then you can kill me.
That sound fair to you?
-Light Yagami.
Just what are you thinking?
-Look.
This is all to save Misa.
You're gonna have
to trust me on this.
-All right.
If it means that Misa will
be saved, I'll do as you ask.
-After this, I'll go and demand
to be confined like Misa,
and have them put me under
24 hour surveillance as well.
While I'm locked
up, I'll relinquish
ownership of the
notebook to you.
That'll mean I'll lose all my
memories of the Death Note.
During this time, the killings
of criminals will start again.
Once that happens,
Ryuzaki will be
put in a position where
he has to release us.
And, after I've lost
all my memories,
chances are I'll want to
help catch Kira myself.
That's just the way I am.
-So then you'll try
and catch the guy who
Rem gives the notebook to and
steal it before L gets to it.
-Right.
Once that's done, I'll kill
the new owner of the notebook.
But there's still one
problem remaining.
-If you don't have
full ownership,
your memories will
only return for as long
as you're in contact
with the notebook.
As soon as you let go
of it, your memories
will disappear again.
LIGHT: That means I've
got to kill Higuchi
without letting go
of this notebook.
If I manage to do
that, ownership
will transfer back to me and
my memories won't disappear.
I just have to pull this four
times in less than a second.
Got it.
Just as I expected.
I'm wearing this watch.
Old habits die hard.
-Mr. Yagami.
Please take Higuchi to the car.
-Uh, right.
Of course.
-You know, about this notebook.
I wonder what we would
find if we put it
through a forensic analysis.
-That doesn't sound
like you, Light.
We both know this thing
is beyond science.
-Yeah, you're right.
Hm.
This has got to be the
longest 40 seconds of my life.
-Ryuzaki.
Hiroguchi is--
-What the hell?
What's happening?
CHIEF YAGAMI: Hey!
Higuchi!
-LIGHT: Dad, what are you doing?
We can't lose him!
If Higuchi dies on us now--
CHIEF YAGAMI: It's impossible.
I-- There's nothing I can do.
He's already--
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Yes.
He's already dead.
And you're next, Ryuzaki.
-Hm.
How to use it.
It says the human whose name
is written in this notebook
shall die.
This note will not take
effect unless the writer has
a person's face in their mind
when writing his or her name,
therefore people sharing the
same name will not be affected.
If the cause of death is written
within 40 seconds of writing
the person's name,
it will happen.
If the cause of death
is not specified,
the person will simply
die of a heart attack.
After writing the cause of
death, details of the death
should be written in the next
6 minutes and 40 seconds.
As well, the back cover
has some more instructions
on how to use it.
There are two more rules.
One of them is if you make this
note unusable by tearing it
up or burning it, all the humans
who have touched the note 'til
then will die.
-What?
Is that really true, Aizawa?
Aizwa: Yeah, that's
what it says.
-(VOICEOVER) That's right.
With a rule like that in
place, the notebook's safety
is guaranteed, which means my
memories of it will remain.
-Rem, there's no way the old
man back home will get mad at us
if we write fake rules
in here, is there?
-No.
There are no rules
against doing so.
-Fine, then, Light, I'll do it.
But you owe me an
apple for this.
[laughter]
-Oh, man.
Maybe I shouldn't
have let my curiosity
about seeing a Shinigami
get the better of me.
-Maybe.
But then you would be the only
one in the investigation who
didn't know what we
were dealing with.
Is that what you want?
-No.
Of course not.
I want to be on the same
page as everyone else
on the task force, Chief.
-And then there's
this last rule.
According to these instructions
at the back of the notebook,
if the person using the note
fails to consecutively write
names of people to be killed
within 13 days of each other,
then the user will die.
-Ah!
Wait a second.
If that's true, then
it means Light and Misa
Misa are completely
clear, doesn't it?
-Hm.
Yeah.
Now that you mention
it, that's right.
Light and Misa were detained
for more than 50 days,
and are still
under surveillance.
If either of them had
been Kira, there's
no way they would
still be alive by now.
-Wow, that's great news.
Isn't it, Chief?
-Yeah.
-Rem, was it?
That's your name, isn't it?
The white thing over there?
-Ryuzaki, isn't it
a bit rude to go
around calling
someone a white thing?
-What do you want?
-There's more than one
notebook in the human world,
isn't there?
REM: Who knows?
There may be, and
there may not be.
-If there are other notebooks,
either here or in your world,
would they all have the
same rules as this one?
-(VOICEOVER) You're
wasting your time, Ryuzaki.
You'll never get Rem to
admit these rules are fake.
-Yes, they are all the same.
There are many notebooks
in the Shinigami realm,
but they all have
the same rules.
Even the rules for when
humans obtain them.
-Ryuzaki.
Miss Amane and Light have both
been cleared of suspicion.
They shouldn't be under
surveillance any longer.
-That's right.
It's crystal clear.
-I suppose you're right.
I understand.
Please, accept my apologies
for all the trouble.
-Thank goodness.
-Yeah, but we still
can't say that we've
solved the case until we've
figured out everything.
Would it be all right if I
kept investigating with you?
Without the handcuffs on?
-Yes.
-(VOICEOVER) And just like that,
Misa and I are proven innocent.
A notebook of death filled with
rules written by a Shinigami.
He has no choice
but to believe it.
He just lost his edge, thanks
to the fake rules I created.
Listen, Ryuzaki, no matter what
the word, the god of that world
creates the rules.
In truth, you've
already been defeated
by the rules I created.
And as punishment for defying
the god of the new world,
you will die.
-Oh, Light!
Be sure to text
me every day, OK?
-After all this time, we're
saying goodbye to Misa Misa.
-Knock it off, Matsuda.
Let's leave them alone.
MATSUDA: Goodbye, Misa Misa!
AIZAWA: Enough!
LIGHT: Good.
There are surveillance
cameras, but they
won't be able to pick up my
face or mouth from this angle.
Misa, I'm going to tell
you about a special place.
I need you to go there
and dig something up,
but you have to make sure
that no one is watching.
-(VOICEOVER) Light!
Your memory must have returned.
Don't worry, I can do this.
I won't let you down.
[gasp]
-Light, I remember.
I remember everything
that happened
when I had this notebook.
You buried this one so I
could come here and regain
my memories.
Huh?
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Dear Misa, by
the time you read this letter,
you should have
remembered everything.
-Oh, a letter from Light!
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Do
you remember my friend
at To-Oh University?
He went by the
name Hideki Ryuga.
I want you to write his
real name in the notebook
and kill him.
Then burn this
letter right away.
Take a number of pages from
the notebook and re-bury
it where you found it.
The next time that
we see each other,
casually touch me with
a piece of the notebook.
If you do this for me, I
promise I will love you--
-For the rest of my life!
Yay!
Now I see.
This was all part
of Light's plan.
He wanted me to
get this notebook,
regain all my memories,
and then kill Hideki Ryuga.
Kill Ryuzaki.
One of Light's biggest
obstacles will be gone,
and I'll be helpful
to him at last!
-But Light, it's no good.
I don't remember
his name anymore.
I was seeing dozens-- no, no,
hundreds of names and lifespans
every day!
Oh!
I can't remember
it, no matter what!
Oh, I'm such an idiot!
Huh?
-I've finally returned
to the human world.
-Ryuk!
Oh, it's been so long!
Oh, I'm so glad to see you.
How are you doing?
-Sorry-- I'm a guy.
I get a little shy sometimes.
-Oh, yeah.
I almost forgot.
Here.
Light told me to
bring one for you.
Is it really that good?
-Oh, yeah.
Human apples are--
what's the word?
Juicy, I think.
They're great, anyway.
Why don't you try this?
-Huh?
-An apple from the
Shinigami world.
-Ew.
It doesn't look very good.
-Come on.
One bite won't kill ya.
-By the way, before
I forget, I want
you to make the
eye deal with me.
Ah!
It's sand!
Ugh.
-A deal, huh?
-Mm-hm.
-You understand what that means?
You already made the same
deal with Rem once before.
Are you sure you really want
me to cut your lifespan in half
for the second time?
-I know, but what
choice do I have?
You see, I've forgotten
a name that I absolutely
have to remember.
Light will be so mad at
me if I let him down.
-Well, it's fine with me.
[buzz]
-Hey, it's Misa Misa.
The poor girl.
As long as we're
stuck in here, we
can't turn our cell phones on.
So she has to come
all the way out
here just to hang
out with Light.
-Light, would you hurry
up and go see her?
Don't you know, you should
never keep a woman waiting?
-OK.
-Huh?
Ryuk?
Why is he attached to Misa?
Huh?
Misa's lifespan.
It's been halved again.
No!
Did she make the
eye deal with Ryuk?
-Hey, Light.
-It's been a while, Ryuk.
-Light, I'm so sorry.
I don't remember Hideki
Ryuga's real name.
I tried, but I totally forgot.
-Oh, I see.
Well, that's too bad.
-But I did the eye deal with
Ryuk so I can try again!
-So, everything's going
according to plan.
-You idiot!
If you do that, then
your life span will--
-No, it's all right.
I just wanna be of
use to you, Light.
-Misa.
All I want is to enjoy
a long life with you
in an ideal world.
That's just how I feel.
-Light, I'm so happy.
-Let's create a
new world together.
It'll be a place with no crime,
where only kind people live,
OK?
-Yeah.
[theme music]
LIGHT: Goodbye, L.