[theme music]
-The second L and
the person I think
is Kira can only be one man.
Light Yagami.
-This is Kiyomi
Takada from News 6.
I have an announcement that
comes directly from Kira.
His words are to become
the new law of the world.
-I just had an idea.
I think we can make
use of Kiyomi Takada.
-Please excuse me.
Kira!
-He's removing the bugs?
-We don't have a choice.
-Listen, Kiyomi.
I am the real Kira.
KIYOMI (VOICEOVER):
Light is Kira?
NEAR (VOICEOVER): All the
pieces have fallen into place.
Now that things
have come this far,
it's my turn to go to Japan.
Commander Rester.
-Yes.
-I'm afraid I need you to
return to New York immediately.
-Right now?
-Yes.
I'm intending to go to Japan.
-All right.
So you would like me to stay
in New York while you're gone?
-Not at all.
RESTER: Then what's the point
of me coming back there?
-Truth is, I've never
made travel arrangements
or boarded a flight
on my own before.
That's why I need
you to come back.
So you can escort me.
-Understood.
MAN: We got him.
Both Yoshida Productions and NHN
are practically begging us now.
The great Misa Misa comeback
plan is a huge success.
-These days, it's nearly
impossible for anyone
to get into NHN, but this
will get us full access.
-Yeah, that's right.
Mogi will be gaining
entry as Misa's manager.
It'll definitely
be to our advantage
to have someone who can
go in and out freely.
In the meantime, I'll
continue investigating Takada.
NEAR (ON SPEAKER): This is Near.
I want to speak to L.
-This is L. What is
you want from us?
I'm following through with
my goal to arrest Kira.
And that's why I'm Japan now.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
He's in Japan?
Why tell me?
He's up to something.
NEAR (ON SPEAKER): L. I presume
you've already contacted Takada
for the purposes of
your own investigation.
-That's right.
In fact, I'm investigating
her myself at the moment.
-I see.
For the time being,
it's a given that, if we
want to get any closer
to capturing Kira,
we'll have to keep an eye
on Kiyomi Takada and NHN
in general.
I want you to pass on a message.
Inform her that, as of
now, several SPK members
have entered Japan in order
to catch and arrest Kira.
-But why do that?
-To lure Kira out of hiding.
I also want you to mention
the following to her
so she'll relay it to Kira.
In total, there are only four
active members of the SPK.
That includes myself.
Kira won't be able to
resist such an opportunity.
Knowing him, he won't run.
Instead, he'll try to kill
us before we get too close.
That's where I'll beat
him at his own game.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Beat
me at my own game, huh?
All right, Near.
If that's how you want it,
I'll accept your challenge.
-I am in Japan as we speak.
-I am in Japan as well.
Then we'll be quite
close to each other.
Who knows?
We might even have the
chance to meet face to face.
-I hope so.
-Well, that'll be something
to look forward to.
-Yes.
-When that time comes, we'll
finish this Kira matter
once and for all.
-Definitely.
It's all becoming clear to me.
From the very
beginning, and even now,
it's been a one on
one fight against L.
And even though he's
dead, the battle's
just shifted to his heirs.
Very well, Near.
Fine.
I'll come out to
play if you will.
It's only fair, after all.
And when we meet, we'll find out
which of us is truly prepared
to win, and whose
wits will prevail.
When that happens, this
long battle will end
and I can finally begin
my reign at the top.
-First, let's review
what we know so far.
L is Light Yagami,
and he's also Kira.
For now, we'll call him L Kira.
There's also another one.
Someone who has the notebook
and is currently using it.
We'll call him X Kira.
Judging by the pattern
of X Kira's killings,
he has definitely made the
deal and acquired the Shinigami
eyes.
L Kira and X Kira can't
communicate directly.
They must be planning
to communicate
using Takada as a go between.
So, given the situation
as it now stands,
there are two ways
to win against Kira.
One, the simple way.
We arrange to kill
both L Kira and X Kira
and confiscate the notebook.
However, no matter
what might happen,
we will never resort to that.
-Why not?
NEAR: That's not the
way we work, Commander.
-We, sir?
-Yes, that's right.
We kill those two
and the murders stop.
Such ex post facto justification
will not be tolerated.
That's not the way
L and I do things,
because that would be an insult.
Don't forget, L
entrusted this case
to those who came after him.
LIGHT: So, Kiyomi.
I heard on the
news the other day
that you receive an enormous
amount of fan mail every day.
-Yes.
I'm told on average it's
about 200 letters a day.
LIGHT (ON RADIO): 200 letters?
Wow, I'm a little jealous.
-Man, this is kind of boring
listening to audio only
without any video feed.
-I think you should look through
them, even if they are just
letters from fans.
-You're right.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Keep calm as you
read this note and
the ones that follow.
Make sure not to let the people
listening to this conversation
hear your reactions.
The SPK has started
to make its move.
You have to start thinking
about your safety.
Instead of accepting
messages from Kira,
maybe you should consider making
a few demands of your own.
-Light's getting
down to business.
-You shouldn't only
be a spokesperson.
Your voice should
be heard as well.
Reach out to Kira.
Tell him what you
think he needs to know.
I have a different
job for T. In order
to create the perfect world
that Kira has envisioned,
I want you to begin judging
and punishing people as Kira.
-It's all right, Kiyomi.
I have faith in you.
It's going to be OK.
If you can do this,
I'm sure you'll
be able to send Kira
information that you
don't want the
SPK to know about.
-All right.
I'll do it.
-We nailed it.
-That's our Light for you.
-He's good.
-Delete.
Delete.
[phone ringing]
MIKAMI: Kiyomi Takada.
Hm.
Yes?
-I have an important
message for you.
You are to send me a
fan letter that I'll
be able to recognize as yours.
You will also enclose
something else in the envelope.
Five blank pages
from the notebook.
Carry on with your judgements
and killings as usual
until I receive the
letter and the pages.
-And how about after
you receive them?
-You have to stop using
the real notebook.
However, you must
continue entering names
in a fake notebook.
MIKAMI (ON PHONE): A fake?
-That's right.
Make a notebook that looks
as close to the original as
possible, and act as if
you're killing people
by using this decoy.
-I understand.
God.
What are you planning?
No.
It's not my place
to question God.
His will is absolute.
My job is to do what god wishes.
-Huh?
What's this?
-It's a replacement
for Kira's Kingdom.
-God, what's wrong
with these people?
MAN: Welcome to the show.
Today, Ms. Takada will introduce
her four new female bodyguards,
who were selected after a
rigorous screening process.
The first is the winner
of the 22nd World Karate
Championships,
Miss Tatsumi Oyama.
The second is a former CIA
agent, Ms. Halle Lidner.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
If there is an SPK
member among these
bodyguards, it
would have to be Halle Lidner.
Looks like Near's conducting
his own investigation of Takada.
MAN: A phantom
killer who stabbed
six people in Shinjuku's busy
quarters was apprehended--
NEAR (VOICEOVER): Who
I chose to be X Kira?
Out of all the
people in the world?
KIYOMI (ON TV):
--educating our children
about the existence of Kira and
the meaning of his teachings
must be made mandatory.
Above all, we must teach our
children that Kira is good.
-(VOICEOVER) Takada was
chosen because she's a strong
supporter of Kira.
So, that means X
Kira must be someone
who knew they Takada
was a Kira worshipper.
Someone who had a close,
intimate relationship with her
before her selection.
-Also, Kira will not forgive
any crime, no matter how small.
From this point
onwards, you should
assume that any person
alive is a viable target.
-I'd like to hear Kira's voice.
I want to hear his
thoughts once again.
We should follow his teachings,
exactly as Kira ordered.
To me, it's obviously
the quickest path
to lasting world peace.
Youth have a responsibility.
I think it is of
the most importance
that young people do all
they can to contribute.
It's our duty to
improve our society.
If there are no words
or orders from Kira,
then we have only one choice.
We need to think for ourselves.
We need to consider
what Kira has taught us,
determine what he wants most,
and make our own decisions
from there.
-L Kira is Light Yagami.
Could X Kira be Teru Mikami?
[whispers]
-Everything seems
to fit into place.
MISA: That's what
I've been asking.
So tell me why I'm
not the headliner.
You said I was supposed to be
the highlight of the East-West
Pop Music Festival.
-Well, it's true that
you're the highlight,
but when it comes
to the headliner,
it's a little harder
to secure that spot.
-Huh?
-That's why we should
be taking precautions.
-Kiyomi Takada.
What an idiot.
She doesn't even realize
that Light's just
using her for his investigation.
-Don't say that.
You might end up dead
if she hears you.
-Duh, I know that.
That's why I
whispered it quietly.
Hey!
She snickered at me!
I'm gonna go kick her!
-Hang on!
-What were you trying to do?
-What was I doing?
What about you?
Grr.
-Lidner, that young
lady is actually
a very good friend of mine.
Please, you shouldn't
be so rough with her.
-Hmph!
-Of course, Miss Takada.
Please, excuse me.
-Misa Misa, are you all right?
-That was so frustrating!
NEAR: L, this is Near.
I have a small request.
If Mr. Aizawa is there,
would it be possible
for me to speak to
him for a moment?
-Near, this is Aizawa.
What is it?
NEAR: I have a question
regarding surveillance for L
and Takada's meetings.
Are you recording both
audio and video feed
to their conversations?
-Uh, no.
Only an audio feed right now.
NEAR: I see.
Only wiretaps at the moment.
How interesting.
Thank you very much.
-If they're only using
wiretaps, then it's
safe to assume that L Kira
and X Kira have found a way
to contact each
other through Takada.
Seems like Lidner could be in
more danger than we realize.
-We knew the risks
getting into this.
To be blunt, what's
important is that L
starts focusing his attention
on Lidner and Takada.
In the meantime, we'll
use the opportunity
to investigate Mikami further.
-Hm.
How are things, Giovanni?
-Well, about Mikami.
It's strange.
It's ridiculously
easy to trail him.
He's not trying to
hide, or anything.
He's lived at the same
place the past four years.
There's nothing
unusual about him.
He also seems to be totally
dedicated to his career
as a prosecutor.
I'm beginning to think
he can't be X Kira.
-No.
There is a very high probability
that Mikami is X Kira.
Please be very careful.
Don't enter his room yet.
Just keep watch
over him for now.
-Gotcha.
MISA: Man, how many meetings
do I need to have with NHN,
for crying out loud?
-And seriously, how many
times do these people
have to tell me, be
careful about what you say?
What's with that?
-Yes.
Yes, of course.
I'll ask her right now.
Uh, listen.
Misa Misa, Takada would
like to have dinner
with you this evening.
Just the two of you.
-Huh?
(VOICEOVER) That Kiyomi.
What's she up to?
-Good idea.
The music festival's
MC should have
dinner with the main
performer at least once.
Tell her OK.
-Hm.
Hello?
-Miss Takada?
She's accepted.
-Great.
I'm looking forward to it.
Oh, and Lidner?
Please book a nice,
private room for us.
And also, I'd like you to
attend the dinner as well.
-Huh?
Yes.
TAKADA: Misa, I'm sorry
to have to invite you
to dinner so late at night.
I'm afraid it had to
wait until after the 9:00
news was finished
MISA: No problem.
I don't mind at all.
I'm a night owl, anyway.
Well, what is it?
-I'm not really sure how to
answer a question like that.
So, Light must be pretty busy.
How do you two manage?
(VOICEOVER) Why, you-- she knows
that I can't see him that much,
while she can be with
him all the time.
How dare she?
Things are great between us.
Light is way more
affectionate than he looks.
At least with me.
In fact, he starts
clinging to me
as soon as he gets in
the door every night.
-Ah.
I see.
It sounds like
you're doing well.
Thank goodness.
-Yes.
Actually, I should probably
tell you, since you are the MC.
I'm going to announce
my engagement to Light
at the Pop Music Festival.
-Does he know about this?
-Of course he does.
It's an engagement.
It's not as if I can
get engaged to myself.
He proposed to me
more than a month ago.
It was so romantic.
Don't you think it'd be
exciting to announce it
at the Pop Music
Festival, Miss MC?
-Why not?
If you're able to, that is.
-What do you mean,
if I'm able to?
What, are you not going
to let me announce it?
Or maybe it's something else.
Maybe you're going to
get Kira to kill me.
-Of course not.
Only Kira can decide who
he's going to punish.
I have nothing to do
with his decisions.
Besides, I've always thought
of you as a good friend, Misa.
You shouldn't say
such terrible things.
Anyway, I don't have any
intention of killing anyone,
no matter how horrible
they might be.
-Well, whatever.
I used to really like
Kira too, you know?
But I know for sure that
Light's going to catch him soon.
Oh, yeah.
Once he gets caught, it'll be
nothing but bad news for him.
And as for you, you'll
probably be executed.
[coughing]
-Miss Takada?
Are you all right?
-Huh?
[laughter]
-Listen, Kiyomi.
I am the real Kira.
Please, join me,
Kiyomi, and you will
be the goddess of the new world.
-Miss Amane?
-Yes?
-I find this unpleasant.
-Hmph!
Oh, yeah?
I feel the same!
-Obviously, this was a bad idea.
I should've waited until
you grew up and learned
a few minutes before I
invited you to dinner.
I suppose I'll know
better next time.
Goodbye.
-Oh?
I'm older than you, Kiyomi.
And anyways, you're
being childish
for storming out in
the middle of diner
over a silly little comment!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Hey, Motchi!
Thanks for waiting, Motchi!
How are you?
MOGI: A-A-- Are you OK?
MISA: Of course I am.
I won, after all.
MOGI: Won?
MISA: Yeah.
It was easy.
-About tonight's meeting
between Takada and Amane.
They just talked
about Light Yagami.
If you read between
the lines, they
were arguing over which
one was his lover.
-Your thoughts?
-All I can determine is this.
Light Yagami is popular
with the ladies,
and we know that Takada
and Amane both adore him.
-Near, please be
serious about this.
NEAR: It is serious if they're
both truly in love with him.
They will not easily betray him.
In fact, they'll likely
do whatever he asks.
WOMAN: Please stop.
-Aw, come on now, lady.
I mean, wearing a short skirt
like that in the winter?
It's an invitation.
-Please.
Someone!
-Hm?
Cell phone?
Mikami's just taken
out a notebook.
-Delete.
-He's writing something in it.
Could that be it?
He's getting off the train.
[screaming]
[theme music]
GIOVANNI: Mikami started
talking to himself.
He seems to have reacted to
the scrap of paper at his feet.
He's gone into the gym.
I've entered the locker room.
I'm opening the lock
on his briefcase.
I'm going to touch the notebook.