[theme music]
-The current Kira is
foolish and overconfident,
not to mention
unusually cooperative
with the task force.
In fact, I suspect he's
working hand in hand with them.
-You think so?
-That would make the
second L and Kira one
in the same person.
To the members of the
Japanese task force,
was there ever a point in the
investigation where the Second
L was suspected to be Kira,
even if the suspicions were
later dropped?
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Near.
I have to kill him.
-This is really bad.
Turn on the TV.
It's Demegawa!
-This is Demegawa live!
My comrades and I have
finally pinpointed the hideout
of the evil organization
bent on trying
to catch our beloved god Kira.
We now have the building
completely surrounded!
Hello, Kira supporters.
I urge you, do not rush
the building all at once.
The traitors may attempt
to blend in with the crowd
to escape.
I am Kira's loyal
servant and spokesman.
You must listen to me!
Find them, pull them
from the building,
and bring them in
front of the cameras.
They'll be a sacrifice for Kira!
-You can't hide from me.
I'll find you.
-Near.
You've got no choice.
You'd better evacuate.
-You've got some nerve
to say that, being Kira.
-What?
Are you still going on
about that nonsense?
-Think about it.
With all the anti-Kira
groups around,
why is it we're being
targeted, and right after I
start suspecting you?
Pretty convenient,
if you ask me.
-Near, with all due
respect, you're wrong.
You're jumping to conclusions.
-Members of the task
force, please listen to me.
Kira is likely amongst you.
Even as we speak,
he is in that room.
I'm simply asking you to
think about this carefully.
-(VOICEOVER) Light is Kira.
This is all sounding
way too familiar.
The original L also thought
that Light had to be Kira.
-The first wave of 20
people will break the door
and get inside.
Second wave, stand by!
-Wait!
We're the first wave!
-What?
Like hell.
We're going first!
-Near, we have to
evacuate immediately.
-Really, what pathetic people.
I'm not surprised that there
are ordinary people who
support what Kira's
trying to do.
I'm talking about
honest citizens who
believe in their hearts
that, by punishing evildoers,
Kira will actually make this
world a better place to live.
But, as for this
crowd outside, they're
a completely different breed.
They are truly
despicable and stupid.
This is just a
diversion for them.
They're all selfish.
-I-- I know that, but it still
leaves us with the immediate
problem.
We'll use L's legacy and the
anti-Kira protesters we hired.
-Yes, but we only have
one shot with that plan.
-I'm aware of that, but I can't
imagine a better time to do it.
Besides, it should
be interesting.
-What?
It's-- It's money!
-Money?
There's so much!
-What?
That's a lot.
Amazing!
Man, I wish I were
over there right now.
-Matsuda.
-Heh.
Humans are so interesting.
Of course, you can use
money to get apples,
so I can kind of understand.
-I got these first, you bastard!
-Out of the way!
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Dammit!
He's planning to use all this
chaos to escape into the crowd.
Even so, he can't escape
from Demegawa's cameras.
-Over there, pilot!
Go to the floor where all
the money's coming from!
-Geez!
What are you doing, Demegawa?
Don't you know that you can't
buy love and peace with money?
NEWSCASTER: A literal
downpour of money
is causing mayhem
in lower Manhattan.
NEWSCASTER: The
police have arrived.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Police?
NEWSCASTER: They're
a welcome sight
in the midst of what can only
be called a full scale riot.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): This is bad.
At this rate--
-Let's go.
This is our window
of opportunity.
We can leave via the front exit.
-It makes sense that
the police would
have to mobilize for
a riot like this.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Damn!
Near was prepared
for this situation.
He's planning to come out
along with the rest of them,
and if I tell Aizawa
and the others
to keep an eye on the
police, it will only
make me look that
much more suspicious.
NEWSCASTER: The police are
coming out of the building.
They've secured the area.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Where is he?
He's got to be in
there somewhere!
Where?
Dammit.
-How much money do
you think was there?
Bet it was a lot.
AIZAWA: Matsuda!
Knock it off.
-It bet it was around
$10 million or something.
-Ooh.
What's that in apples?
[beeping]
-Near.
Already?
NEAR (ON SPEAKERS):
This is Near.
We've reestablished
a secure connection,
so I thought I should give
you a call to let you know.
LIGHT (ON SPEAKERS):
You're safe.
That's a relief.
-To all of you on
the task force,
I'm sure that by now
some of you are starting
to suspect that Kira
may be one of you.
Given the timing of today's
attack on our headquarters,
I don't think anyone could
blame you for having doubts.
If you don't suspect the
second L of being Kira by now,
you're in the
wrong line of work.
The number I gave you the day
before has been reconnected.
Please feel free to
call any time you like.
Well then, I'll be
waiting for your call.
-Those were some strong words.
This guy's pretty
sure of himself.
-I've been thinking, and if you
want to cooperate with Near,
please go ahead.
I'm not particularly
satisfied with the way things
are going either.
Ideally, we should
cooperate with the SPK.
Maybe this will clear
the air a little.
Still, it kinda feels like
Near's against us, doesn't it?
AIZAWA: When I think about
Deputy Director Yagami--
I don't want to suspect Light
even a little bit, but--
-Dad?
Welcome back.
I didn't know you were
gonna be home tonight.
-Oh, yeah.
What are you still doing awake?
-I've a couple of
exams coming up.
-I see.
Well, don't push
yourself too hard, OK?
-Kay.
You too, dad.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): I wouldn't be
surprised if one of the others
contacted Near.
It's inevitable.
The problem is what
comes after that.
If I'm too late
to act, something
might happen that I won't
be able to take back.
I've got no choice but to do it.
[beeping]
-Oh!
An emergency order from Light!
Yay!
Hm.
File number three.
Huh?
No way.
[phone ringing]
NEAR: Yes?
This is Near.
AIZAWA: I'm with the
Japanese task force.
My name is Aizawa.
MISA: So, the time
has finally come.
If I do this my
safety is guaranteed,
and I can finally just
to be a normal wife.
This is what Light wants for me.
He wants me to be happy,
just as a woman should be.
Thank you, Light.
-NEAR: I see.
That's very interesting.
You're saying there were
two suspects in the Kira
investigation that the
previous L detained
for more than 50
days, and they were
cleared based on
the 13 day rule.
Correct?
AIZAWA: Yes.
But of course,
that alone doesn't
come prove they were Kira.
NEAR: And L was willing to
release them because of that?
-No.
L had Deputy Director
Yagami, the chief detective
at the time, put on an act.
He was instructed to tell the
suspects that they had both
been found guilty of being
Kira and the second Kira,
and that they were
going to be executed.
Then on the way,
the deputy director
pulled over and pointed
a gun at the suspects.
He said that he would first
kill Kira, then himself.
The idea was that
if he were Kira,
the suspect would have killed
the chief right then and there.
-(VOICEOVER) Kira
is quite impressive.
He must have used his detainment
to demonstrate his innocence.
Well done.
Out of curiosity,
did the suspect
volunteer to be detained as
part of the investigation?
-Hm.
Come to think of it, Light did
volunteer to be imprisoned.
NEAR: If he did, then I'd
say that settles the matter.
Wouldn't you?
So, who was it?
Who were those two suspects?
-I can't tell you that much.
I'm willing to
cooperate, but I'm still
a member of the Japanese
task force working under L.
NEAR: I understand.
Thank you very much.
you information's
been quite valuable, especially
the part about Shinigami's eyes
that enable you to see
other peoples' names.
It was very helpful.
Goodbye.
-Hm.
RESTER: Will that
be enough, Near?
Shouldn't you have pressed
for a little more information?
-I think that all
things considered,
his level of cooperation
is fine for now.
And besides, I discovered
something very important.
The person suspected
of being Kira
is Deputy Director Yagami's son.
It's the only
possible explanation.
Why else would the
deputy director
say he would kill
Kira, and then himself?
Therefore, tha
tmeans the second L,
and hte person I think is
Kira, can only be one man.
Light Yagami.
AIZAWA: Light.
-Yes?
-There's something
you should know.
I phoned Near and talked to him.
-Don't worry about it.
After all, I was the
one who recommended it.
So, what did the two of
you end up discussing?
No, on second thought, I
probably shouldn't ask.
I guess it's not
appropriate for me
to ask those kinds of
questions if I'm a suspect.
-Hm.
Don't get me wrong.
I want to believe
that you aren't Kira,
but I've got to be certain.
I'm sorry to have
to do this again,
but I want to put you
under surveillance
until we catch Kira.
I'm afraid that goes
for Misa Amane as well.
I'm going to search
your place right now.
There's a possibility that
Amane might have a notebook.
-Hang on a second, Aizawa!
-No.
Go right ahead.
Look at this way.
At least you can
prove to everyone
that I'm not sneaking around
and contacting Misa in private,
right?
-Huh?
Mogi?
-I'm coming with you.
I want to make sure, too.
-It would be best for
everyone if Light wasn't Kira.
But if Amane has any
evidence on her that
connects her with Kira, then--
[doorbell]
-Huh?
-Motchi, Monchichi, long
time no see, you two!
Light hasn't been
home at all lately,
so I've been super bored.
-Uh--
-Well, there's no way she's
got the notebook hidden
under a dress like that.
-We were just
investigating a tip
that there were explosives
planted in L's house.
We think it's a prank, but we'd
like to check the rooms, just
in case.
-What?
How about Light?
Is he OK?
I have to call him.
-No.
You can't call him right now.
-How come?
-Don't worry.
Light's safe, but he's
really busy right now.
He has some other
things he has to do,
so he's handed the investigation
over to us for the time being.
-Oh, I get it.
Light loves me like
crazy, so he doesn't
want me to call him,
'cause that'll only
make him worry about me.
-(VOICEOVER) Search as
much as you like, Aizawa.
You won't find the notebook.
[yawn]
-I wouldn't like
all the suspicion
to ruin the atmosphere
around here.
-This isn't a social club.
I think Aizawa and Mogi
should do as they see fit.
-It's time for Kira's Kingdom.
-Greetings to all my
fellow Kira worshippers.
I am Demegawa, the
voice of our god, Kira.
Behold!
This is the new
Kira's Kingdom, which
shares its name
with this program.
Its construction
is going smoothly,
but will depend on the generous
support of our loyal viewers.
Once it has been completed,
let us welcome our god here!
-Whoa.
Talk about bad taste.
-Hey, so is everything OK?
-Oh, yeah.
Seems like it was just a prank.
-Oh.
-But just in case, one of
us is going to stay and keep
watch over you for
the next few days.
-Really?
Oh, that would be great.
Mogi, why don't you go
back to headquarters?
I'll say on guard here.
-Huh?
I'm with Monchichi
instead of Motchi?
-What's wrong?
Don't you trust me?
-No.
You're just not Monchichi
without your old haircut.
You're not cute anymore.
[laughter]
-Mogi!
-Yes, sir. my apologies.
-All right.
You stay.
-We are now accepting donations,
starting at the million yen
mark towards the completion
of Kira's Kingdom.
So, if you truly--
-This sounds like a con.
-Yep.
Just another scam at this point.
-It doesn't even seem
like Kira's style.
-(VOICEOVER) Demegawa.
He's just acting on his own now.
If he keeps doing
this, he'll end up
pushing people away from Kira.
I don't need him anymore.
But I can't do
much at the moment.
-Hey.
Welcome back, Aizawa.
-We didn't find a notebook
in Light's or Misa's room.
But still--
-I understand.
You're more than welcome to
keep watch over Misa and I
until you're satisfied.
-Next on the program,
it's time for me
to introduce the new leaders I
have chosen for Kira's Kingdom.
The first gentleman is--
-Delete.
[gasping]
-We will unite with
Kira, and work with him.
-Delete!
Delete!
-Save me.
-And delete.
[groan]
-Wha-- What the hell is this?
Why would Kira kill
his own supporters?
-Do you think it's because
they're going overboard
with this?
-That might be a possibility.
But this is horrible.
-(VOICEOVER) What's going on?
There was no chance for
either Misa Amane or Light
to use the notebook
to kill Demegawa.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Mikami.
I can definitely use him.
It seems I was right
to choose him for this.
He understands Kira's
beliefs and ideals perfectly,
and he knows what Kira
wants and doesn't want.
Thanks to that, he takes action
without needing my orders.
I had Misa relinquish
ownership of the Death Note.
Before she lost all her
memories of the notebook,
she sent it to
someone else, along
with some special instructions.
Now she won't be able to
answer any questions about it.
She's just an ordinary woman.
The main problem was
selecting the next owner.
I saw him trying to speak to
Kira through the television
broadcasts.
It was clear he worshiped Kira
from the bottom of this heart.
He would understand that
he was chosen simply
by receiving and
accepting the notebook.
There was no mistake
in my selection.
Teru Mikami.
He's more than worthy of
becoming the hand of Kira.
-Shinigami.
Thank you for coming to me.
Now I'll be able to punish
evildoers with death.
[laughter] God.
[theme music]
LIGHT: You're a woman who the
entire world pays attention to.
It must be fate for us to
cross paths again like this.
Please, just listen to what I
have to say first, all right?
Let's meet somewhere.
Alone.