[theme music]
SOICHIRO YAGAMI (ON
PHONE): Light, Ryuzaki
has decided that he'd like you
to help with the investigation.
If you're still
interested, then you
need to come here right away.
LIGHT: OK, Dad.
(VOICEOVER) All along,
I've been trying
to find a way to get involved
in the investigation,
but I never thought they
would actually approach me.
Now I'll have access to
classified information
about the case, which
means I can learn more
about this other Kira.
I need to figure out what
this impostor is all about
before someone else on the
task force beats me to it.
L: Thank you, Light.
LIGHT: Not at all.
After all, I want to catch
Kira as much as you do, Ryuga.
-I'll have to ask that
you call me Ryuzaki here.
-Eh?
MATSUDA: I'm Matsui.
AIZAWA: I'm Aihara.
SOICHIRO YAGAMI: And I'm Asahi.
-Yes, of course.
Then perhaps I should
call myself Light Asahi?
L: Yes, please do.
To keep things simple from this
point on, I'll call you Light.
OK, let's get down to work.
You can start by looking over
all the information we've
collected.
I'd also like you to
examine these videos.
They were sent to the TV
station but were never aired.
For security reasons, you're
not permitted to take notes,
and all materials
must remain here.
-I understand.
L: We will begin now.
[beep]
SOICHIRO YAGAMI
(VOICEOVER): Light.
L: Well, then.
We need to ask Light
Yagami to assist us.
However, we cannot tell
him that we're considering
the possibility
of a second Kira.
-Are you serious?
But wouldn't that make working
together a bit difficult?
AIZAWA: He's right.
Why even bother asking
him to work with us?
L: Well, I didn't
mean indefinitely.
I'm curious to see what his
impression of these tapes
will be prior to knowing hours.
Light's deductive reasoning
is really quite incredible.
He may suspect that
these tapes are
the work of a second Kira, an
impostor or copycat imitating
the original.
-But the basis for
the second Kira theory
is that the victims of
these recent killings
were minor criminals who
don't fit the normal profile.
Without hearing our explanation,
how would Light ever know that?
L: Yes, but there's
more to it than that.
-Huh?
-The suspect that we've
been pursuing up until now
has needed both a need and
a face to kill his victims.
But there is something
different happening here.
Recall that Mr. Ukita
was killed the moment
he arrived at the station.
And this Kira demanded
only that I appear on TV
but made no request for my name.
This implies that
the second Kira only
needs to see a person's
face to kill them.
So I'll ask Light to look
over all of our information,
as well as our video evidence.
If he comes to the
conclusion that there
could be a second
suspect, then he'd
be almost completely cleared
of suspicion in this case.
SOICHIRO YAGAMI: But how
will that prove anything?
-Logically, if he's
really Kira, he'll
want me dead, seeing
as I'm the one leading
the investigation
against him right now.
And the way things
are going, if I
comply with this new
subject's demands
and appear on TV in
three days, there's
a very good chance I will die.
I can't see the real
Kira jeopardizing
such an easy opportunity
to get rid of me.
-OK.
But are you suggesting
that if my son does not
come to the same
conclusion, there's
an even greater chance
that he is guilty?
-No.
In that case, there will
still only be a 5% chance.
We'll inform him that
we are investigating
the possibility of
a copycat and have
him cooperate with
us as planned.
-Hmm.
DISTORTED VOICE (ON
RECORDING): Now that you've
seen proof of my
powers, you should
have no trouble
believing that I am Kira.
On the designated--
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): This
video is so mediocre.
It's making me
sick to my stomach.
I don't know, maybe it's
because I'm the real one,
but this is a complete disgrace
to everything Kira stands for.
Something's not right here.
It seems unusual
that no one bothered
to explain this video to me.
It's not like them.
Well, in any case, I'd be
stupid to comment on it.
It's probably best
thing if I say nothing.
If I just leave
it alone, L dies.
-So what do you
make of this, Light?
Have you come to
any conclusions?
-Hmm?
(VOICEOVER) Damn, it's a test.
It's hard to say for sure, but
there might be another person
out there with Kira's power.
-With Kira's power?
But what do you
mean by that, Light?
-At the very least, I'd
say this tape was not
created by the Kira
we're familiar with.
It's extremely out
of character for him
to use these kinds of
victims for his killings.
And since we've established
that he needs a name
and face to kill,
it makes you wonder
how he was able to kill
that detective and those two
officers right outside the
television station like that.
-I-- it's the same.
-That's almost exactly how
L-- I mean, Ryuzaki said it.
SOICHIRO YAGAMI (VOICEOVER):
That was incredible, Light.
Now any doubts about
you should be resolved.
-I think you're exactly
right about that.
We also believe that this is
the work of a second Kira.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): I knew it.
So you knew about this all
along, Ryuga-- sorry, Ryuzaki?
Which means this was just
another one of your tests?
-It wasn't my
intention to test you.
The truth is if I
was the only one who
thought there was a second Kira,
it wouldn't be too convincing.
But the fact that we both
came to the same conclusion
makes the theory that
much more believable.
As expected, you did
not disappoint us.
You've been a great help.
It's decided, then.
First, we must focus on
stopping this copycat.
From what we've seen, he
sympathizes with the real Kira
but clearly lacks
his sophistication.
I think he might even be
willing to obey the original.
If so, we could
lure him into a trap
by sending our own message
from the real Kira.
LIGHT: I guess I
shouldn't be surprised.
You literally took the
words right out of my mouth.
L: Oh, and Light,
I would like you
to play the part
of the real Kira.
-Huh?
Me as Kira?
L: Yes.
You're the only one
I can think of who'd
be able to pull
something like this off.
At any rate, we don't
have time to waste.
Do you think you could script
a message from Kira in time
for it to be aired on this
evening's national news?
[laughing]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Damn him.
He must have been planning
this from the beginning.
It's the only reason I'm here.
Ryuzaki, does this look OK?
I think I managed to
make it believable.
-Mm, I think you've done
an excellent job with this.
However, if we don't
omit the part that
says you're free to kill L,
then I'm going to end up dead.
-[laughing] Uh, sorry.
I guess I got carried
away playing the part.
I figured if I was
him, I'd probably
demand that you'd be killed.
I was improvising.
Feel free to change it
to whatever you like.
-That sounds good.
OK, Aihara.
The script is ready.
I'll leave it to you.
AIZAWA: All right.
-And now, a shocking
announcement.
In response to the
frightening Kira
video aired on Sakura
TV only a few days ago,
an anonymous individual
has contacted
us claiming to be the real Kira.
In short, he has demanded
of this network, as well as
several others, that we
air the message you are now
about to see.
I would also like to mention
that the NPA has granted us
permission to air this video.
Is this the real Kira?
No one knows for sure.
But we can only hope this
video will provide us
with some much needed answers.
DISTORTED VOICE
(ON TV): I am Kira.
-It worked!
I knew he'd answer me.
DISTORTED VOICE (ON
TV): The true Kira.
The one who was
broadcast on Sakura TV
several days ago is
a pretender, a fake.
The purpose of this message
is to communicate my will
to this impostor.
I have chosen to be lenient
with him for the time being
only because I believe
he wishes to cooperate
with me in the creation
of a new world.
But I want to make
it absolutely clear
that the taking of innocent
lives is against my will.
If this person
claiming to be me is
truly sympathetic to my cause
and wishes to be of some help,
I ask two things of him.
That he refrain from killing
aimlessly, and that he
agree to abide by
my basic principles.
-Yay!
Now where is that camcorder?
-What are you planning to do?
MISA: Uh, hello?
Do you really need to ask?
I'm going to reply
to him, of course.
[beep]
WATARI (ON COMPUTER):
Ryuzaki, we
have a reply from
the second Kira.
-What?
-Really?
WATARI (ON COMPUTER): I will
be bringing over the envelope
and tape that we received.
But in the meantime, I'm
streaming a copy of the video
so you can view it on your end.
DISTORTED VOICE (RECORDING):
Kira, thank you for your reply.
Please do not worry.
I will follow orders
and do as you say.
-Whoa.
-It worked.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): "I
will do as you say," huh?
This guy's going to
be no help at all.
If this fake had any
idea what my wishes were,
he'd insist that L appear on
TV and then kill him anyway.
How could you fall for
something like this?
Damn it.
DISTORTED VOICE (RECORDING):
I really want to meet you.
I don't think you have the eyes.
[gasp]
But you don't have to worry.
I would never try to kill you.
That's a promise.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
What the hell is he
thinking, talking
about Shinigami
eyes in a public
message like this?
AIZAWA: What's this "having
the eyes" supposed to mean?
Is it a code?
-Yeah.
DISTORTED VOICE
(RECORDING): Please tell me
how I can meet you without
the police knowing.
You'll think of something.
And when we meet, we can
confirm our identities
by showing our
Shinigami to each other.
[gasp]
-Shinigami?
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
He's a liability.
If I don't do something
about him quickly--
[shout]
-Ryuzaki!
You all right?
-Sh-- Shinigami?
Am I supposed to believe that,
that Shinigami actually exist?
Sh-- Shinigami?
Am I supposed to believe that,
that Shinigami actually exist?
MATSUDA: That's impossible.
AIZAWA: Obviously,
they don't exist.
-Yes, that's right, Ryuzaki.
Listen to yourself.
Of course Shinigami don't exist.
-Hmm.
You're probably
right, but I remember
that Kira had those prisoners
write something suggesting
the existence of Shinigami.
-So based on that
fact, perhaps we're
dealing with the same
person after all.
That would definitely
explain why
we're hearing the same words.
-I don't think so because
if this was the same person,
it's highly unlikely
he would have responded
to our video in the first place.
And why would he
agree to let L live
after going to all the trouble
of getting him to appear on TV?
The real Kira wants him dead.
So it doesn't make sense.
AIZAWA: Then maybe there's
some other connection
between the real one
and this new guy.
They could have
already met and decided
to use the word Shinigami
as a way to confuse us.
L: No, I'd say that's unlikely.
-Hmm?
-It's as Light says.
If the two Kiras
were connected, I
don't think the
impostor would be
so willing to give up
on his plan to kill me.
All of this suggests to me that
the copycat has his own agenda
and is acting
independently of the first.
I believe his actual motivation
is to meet the original.
-I think you're right.
He's acting out of
an interest in Kira.
The word Shinigami
could very well
be some reference to
their killing power.
Saying, "We can
confirm our identities
by showing our
Shinigami to each other"
probably means that they'd
confirm their identities
by somehow demonstrating
their ability to kill.
-Yes, that's it.
Based on their messages, we can
assume that the word Shinigami
must hold some other meaning
that only the real Kira
and the second
Kira are aware of.
Now, we just need to
convince this copycat
to tell us what that is.
LIGHT: So will you respond and
force him to be more specific?
We have to be careful
how we handle this.
We can't make it too
obvious that we're asking,
otherwise he'll
realize we're not Kira.
L: No, from now on, it's
best that we leave it up
to the two Kiras.
-Huh?
-What do you mean?
L: I imagine that the
second Kira is probably
quite satisfied with
the current situation
now that he's received
a televised response.
He sent a message to
get Kira's attention.
And as far as he
knows, he now has it.
Also, there's that word he used,
one that only the two of them
would understand.
We'll arrange to have
this reply broadcast today
on Sakura 6 o'clock news.
Naturally, this will
be of interest to Kira,
and he'll be following
this exchange
between the copycat and
the one we've invented.
Now, if I were Kira
himself, my priority
would be to prevent
this impostor
from coming into
contact with the police.
This is good for us because it
means that the real Kira may
feel pressure to
respond this time.
-OK.
But let's say that
he doesn't respond.
Then what do we do?
-Yes.
I've been thinking about
what the second Kira might
do if he gets no response.
For one, he might
reveal more information
that he knows Kira wants
kept secret, to pressure him
into a meeting.
Of course, that would
make Kira nervous.
It could be interesting.
And what would be
more interesting
is if Kira sends a
message of his own
to prevent this from happening.
Ideally, this could provide
us with the physical evidence
we'll need to build
a case against him.
In the meantime, let's
gather all the information
we can on this copycat.
PHOTOGRAPHER: Oh, that's good.
Yes.
Beautiful.
Just like that.
Perfect.
I'm telling you, these
are gonna knock them dead.
You'll look like a
little angel, Misa.
MISA: Ah, I'm so tired.
That shoot went on forever.
Modeling takes a lot of energy.
Hey, Rem.
-Huh?
-Can I ask you something?
-What is it?
-Each Shinigami has to have
one Death Note of their own.
For a Shinigami to give
a notebook to a human,
he needs to have two.
Ryuk could give a
Death Note to Kira
because he somehow
found a way to sneak
an extra one past
the Shinigami King?
-Right.
-What about you?
-The Shinigami King isn't
someone who's easily fooled.
It doesn't happen often.
-Oh, then how did I get mine?
-Let's just say it has a
lot to do with the fact
that I'm one of the few
in the Shinigami realm
who knows how to kill
another of my kind.
That's how I ended up with two.
-Oh.
I think I get it.
You killed a Shinigami, and then
you gave his notebook to me,
right?
-It's not like that.
I wasn't the one who killed him.
I just happened to be
around when he died.
It was coincidence, really.
-So how do you kill a Shinigami?
I have to know.
Well?
-Never repeat this to anyone.
I learned the only way
to kill a Shinigami is
to make them fall in
love with a human.
-What a beautiful way to kill.
-There once was
a Shinigami named
Gelus who spent all
of his time watching
over a certain human girl.
Gelus wanted nothing
more than to look at her
as she went about
her daily life.
It's today, isn't it?
Her last day alive.
-She looks so full of life.
I wonder why today?
It's-- it's just not fair.
REM (VOICEOVER): I
also wanted to find out
how she was going to die, so
I stayed and watched with him.
It was nighttime, and
she was walking alone.
No one else was around.
And then it happened.
A man suddenly appeared
and blocked her path.
He was clearly
infatuated with the girl.
-I love you more than
anyone else in the world!
I'm always watching you.
I want to protect you forever!
REM (VOICEOVER): She'd
never seen the man before
and, of course, turned him down.
[manic laughter]
-Then if I can't have you,
(SHOUTING) I'll kill us both!
[shouting]
-Wait!
Stop it!
What are you doing?
[crying]
REM (VOICEOVER):
Without even thinking,
Gelus did something that
we Shinigami must never do.
[heartbeat, screaming]
Gelus used his Death Note
to kill the man instantly
and therefore saved
the girl's life.
it was the wrong thing to do.
Shinigami exist only to
shorten and take human lives.
We aren't permitted to undo
that which has been fated.
[crying]
At that moment, Gelus
became something
which was neither sand nor
rust and disappeared forever.
He died.
The only reminder
of his existence
was his Death Note, left behind.
The rest of his life
span was added to hers.
So not only had
he saved her life,
he'd accidentally extended it
well beyond its natural end.
-So if he'd never fallen
in love with this girl,
he'd probably still be
alive today, wouldn't he?
REM: That's right.
-Hmm.
I had no idea.
All this time, I
thought it was luck.
But it was a Shinigami who
saved my life that day.
-Yes.
Gelus loved you
enough to die for you.
So that Death Note
is now yours to keep.
-Hmm.
I see.
For a Shinigami
to die, they have
to love a human
enough that they'd
prevent their death
from happening.
So what about you, Rem?
You're not in love
with me, are you?
Be honest.
-Just forget it.
You really think you
can kill me that easily?
-Oops.
You saw through that?
[laughing] I'm so glad.
At least now I have something
interesting to tell Kira.
But I wonder, does he know--
how to K-I-L-L a Shinigami?
I asked him on TV to find a
way for us to meet each other,
but he hasn't replied to me yet.
What's taking him so long?
Maybe I should just send
him another message.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
This isn't good.
I can't allow this second
Kira to act on his own
for much longer.
He's careless.
So it's only a matter of
time before he slips up.
And when he does, the
police will be waiting.
With him in custody, they could
find out about the Death Note.
-Something to start?
-Hmm.
A strawberry sundae, please.
-Of course.
Be right back.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
What should I do?
How can I contact
the second Kira
without L noticing anything?
-Here you go.
-Ah, mmm.
-Enjoy.
-Mm.
(VOICEOVER) I can't
wait to meet Kira!
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): I
wonder, what kind of person
are you, impostor?
MISA (VOICEOVER): I wonder, what
kind of person are you, Kira?
Mmm [giggle].
[theme music]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): May 22nd.
My friend and I showed off
our notebooks in Aoyama.
If this fake Kira slips
up and gets apprehended,
at the very least, I have to
get my hands on his notebook.
I may end up having to
kill everyone there.