[theme music]
[chanting]
[whooshing]
-[grunts]
-What?
A pair of sleeping skulls?
-[chuckles]
I win again.
No hard feelings, right?
Hey there, Ryuk, would
it kill you to join us?
You should come play
with us for a change.
-No, I'll pass.
TEACHER: Listen for the
voice of God, then follow it.
And know that in time, you
will find your salvation.
GIRL: I didn't do
anything wrong.
He just totally snapped at me.
GIRL 2: Really?
TEACHER: Yagami, are
you still with us?
Can you please translate
the following sentence
into English?
-[sighs]
"Follow the teachings of God
and receive his blessings.
And so it shall be that the
seas will again become bountiful
and the raging
storms will subside."
FEMALE REPORTER (ON TV):
Today, at approximately 11:00
AM, a 32-year-old
man was found stabbed
to death in his apartment in
the city of Yokohama Kanagawa
Prefecture.
Kanagawa police are treating
this case as homicide.
MALE REPORTER (ON
TV): In other news.
Today, suspected
murderer, Naoki Tokuji
was arrested in the
district of Shibuya, Tokyo.
He is being held in custody,
facing murder charges
for the brutal slaying of
his common-law partner,
who was only 25 at
the time of her death.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Day in and day out,
the same news on
permanent repeat.
RYUK (VOICEOVER): This
is all so ridiculous.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
This world is--
LIGHT AND RYUK
(VOICEOVER): --rotten.
TEACHER: Another
noticeable consequence
is the extinction of many
species on the planet.
-No way.
You paged--
TEACHER: Species are now
becoming extinct at a faster
rate than has ever occurred
in our record history.
[chatter]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): "Death Note"?
As in a notebook of death?
Hm.
"How to use it.
The human whose name is written
in this notebook shall die."
Hm.
It's pretty lame, not
to mention twisted.
It's really not that different
from one of those chain letter
you get.
"The human whose name is written
in this notebook shall die"?
Come on.
[train whistle]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): There must
be something wrong with me
to even consider it.
"This note will not take
effect unless the writer has
the person's face in their mind
when writing his or her name.
Therefore, people sharing the
same name will not be affected.
If the cause of death is written
within 40 seconds of writing
the person's name,
it will happen.
If the cause of death
is not specified,
the person will simply
die of a heart attack.
After writing the cause of
death, details of the death
should be written in the next
6 minutes and 40 seconds."
-Hm.
So depending on the
person you have in mind,
you can either kill them
easily or painfully, huh?
This is pretty detailed for
a prank, I'll give them that.
[sighs]
So I write a name
and that person dies.
Like anyone would believe that.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Wait, on the
off chance someone really dies,
would that make me a murderer?
Hm, yeah, right, it's
completely impossible.
MALE REPORTER (ON TV):
The same assailant
who attacked six people
at a busy shopping
district in Shinjuku
yesterday has struck again,
taking eight people hostage
at this daycare center.
His captives include both
children and teachers.
The police have now
identified the suspect
as 42-year-old Kurou Otoharada,
currently unemployed.
We expect negotiations
to begin immediately.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Hm, a
heart attack in 40 seconds,
we'll see.
MALE REPORTER (ON TV):
At the present time,
that's all the police
are telling us.
FEMALE REPORTER (ON
TV): You can't help
but feel concerned for the
safety of those hostages.
MALE REPORTER (ON TV):
You're absolutely right.
We'll continue to monitor
the situation from here.
-Thank you for that report.
What do you make of
this, Mr. Hashimoto?
HASHIMOTO (ON TV):
Well, one can only
hope for a quick resolution
to this situation.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Looks like
the notebook doesn't work.
Oh, well, I didn't
expect it to anyway.
FEMALE REPORTER (ON TV): Wait,
we're seeing something here.
Looks like movement
at the front entrance.
MALE REPORTER (ON TV): The
hostages are coming out.
And they all looked
to be unharmed.
The Special Forces
are taking action.
They're moving in.
We don't know if the
suspect's been arrested.
Huh?
Yes?
OK, we now have confirmation.
The suspect has been
found dead inside.
-[gasps]
MALE REPORTER (ON TV): I
repeat, the suspect is now dead.
-Dead?
MALE REPORTER (ON TV):
The Special Forces
are denying allegations
that they shot the suspect.
FEMALE REPORTER (ON
TV): So it's quite
possible he was feeling cornered
and decided to commit suicide?
MALE REPORTER (ON
TV): Well, according
to statements from the
hostages, the suspect
has suddenly collapsed.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
A heart attack?
No way.
It's coincidence.
This has to be a coincidence.
SACHIKO: Light!
-[gasps]
-It's already 6:30, you know?
Don't you have cram
school tonight?
-Yeah, I'll be
ready in just a sec.
Death Note.
It's unlikely, but if by
chance this thing is for real--
I have to test it one more time.
In which case, it should
probably be another criminal.
But if he's too well known,
that could be a problem.
If he dies, there's
a good possibility
that news of his death
will be covered up.
I need to see
results right away.
-Hey, Ryo, buddy.
-What is it, Sudo?
-Didn't you want to lend me $20?
-Hm, huh, again?
But I can't do that.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Sudo, maybe
I should try killing him.
No, I should definitely
avoid killing people I know.
And again, does it
even really matter?
I mean, would anyone
really care if a guy
like him was to
disappear one day?
-Sweet!
Looks like we'll be hanging
at the arcade after school.
-[snickers]
-We're having a speed
dating party tomorrow,
you want to come?
-Yeah, of course.
-Oh, there's no way
I'm missing that.
-Damn it!
Why is my mother so useless?
She's never here to
pick me up on time!
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Once you
actually start looking around,
it makes you wonder if you'd
be doing society a favor
by getting rid of
all these people.
-Hey, baby, where are you going?
Come have a little fun with us!
-That's our Takuo for you.
This guy could spot
a hottie a mile away.
-What's up, little lady?
The name is Takuo Shibuimaru.
What do you say?
Come hang out with
us, pretty lady!
-Please, I don't
want any trouble.
-You hear that?
She doesn't want trouble.
THUG: Whoo, isn't that cute?
Ha-ha!
-Ungh.
Agh.
No!
-Let's go, boys, strip
her down right here.
-Wha-- are you sure?
-Ha-ha-ha!
-No, stop!
Please!
Help me!
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Now, what will happen?
-No!
No!
-Hey, wait up!
-Takuo, look out!
[crash]
[woman screams]
RYUK (VOICEOVER): That,
uh, that settles it.
The Death Note, it's for real.
THUG: Oh, man, Takuo!
MAN: Stupid kid.
He just came out of nowhere.
Aargh!
RYUK (VOICEOVER): Now
then, I better get going.
It's been five days.
Now then, I better get going.
-Ah?
You headed somewhere, Ryuk?
-Hate to tell you, but our
whole world looks like this.
[chuckles]
-That's true.
But I've dropped my Death Note.
[laughter]
-You really messed
things up, didn't you?
-Hold on a sec.
Didn't you already trick the
Old Man to get a second book?
Don't tell me you
dropped both of them?
-You must have some idea
where you dropped the thing?
RYUK: Yeah, the human world.
SHINIGAMIS: What?
[whooshing]
SACHIKO: What a nice surprise!
I wasn't expecting
you home so early.
-Yeah.
Hi, Mom.
It's because, uh, huh?
Oh, the results of
the nationwide exams.
-I've been waiting all day.
-Here.
-Goodness!
Number 1 again!
These are the highest
scores you've had.
LIGHT: Yeah, I guess.
I'm going to study in my room.
So please don't
interrupt me, OK?
-As you wish.
Oh, Light, do you want
anything at all, dear?
You can ask for
whatever you like.
-No, I'm fine, Mom.
Thanks, though.
I've already got what I want.
[chuckles softly]
[maniacal laughter]
SPEAKER: You've taken
quite a liking to it.
[thunderclap]
-Aah!
[gasping]
-No reason to act surprised.
I am the Shinigami Ryuk.
That used to be my notebook.
Judging by your
laughter, you've already
figured out that what you
have is no ordinary notebook.
-Shinigami, a god of death, huh?
Well, I'm not surprised.
In fact, Ryuk, I've
been waiting for you.
-Oh?
-I've already figured
out that this Death
Note I found is real.
It didn't take me long.
And now that I've witnessed
the proof of its power,
I only feel more confident
in what I'm going to do.
-That's interesting.
I certainly wasn't
expecting this.
Several Death Notes
have made their way
into the human
world in the past,
but you're the first to have
written this many names.
Look at how many people you've
killed in only five days.
Most are reluctant
to write this much.
-I've already
prepared myself, Ryuk.
I used the notebook
even though I
knew it belonged to a Shinigami.
And now, that
Shinigami has come.
So what will happen to me?
You're here to take
my soul, right?
-Hm?
What do you mean?
Is that some fantasy
you humans came up with?
I'm not going to
do anything to you.
-Huh?
RYUK: The notebook becomes
part of the human realm
from the very moment
it touches the earth.
In other words, the
notebook is now yours.
-This is mine?
-If you don't want it, just
give it to someone else.
But if you give
it away, I'd have
no choice but to erase your
memories of the notebook.
-So then, you're saying I can
use to Death Note all I want,
and I won't be punished?
-Let's just say this.
You will feel the fear
and pain known only
to humans who have
used the notebook.
And when it's your
time to die, it
will fall on me to write
your name in my Death Note.
Be warned, any human
who's used the Death Note
can neither go to heaven
nor hell for eternity.
That's all.
[laughs]
Now, you have something to
look forward to after you die.
-[gasps]
SACHIKO: Light?
-It'll be all right.
Answer it.
-What is it?
-I thought you'd
like some apples.
The neighbors brought
them over for us.
Why on earth is it
so dark in your room?
You'll ruin your eyesight.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
What's going on?
Mom can't see him?
RYUK: That notebook you found
originally belonged to me.
And since you're
now using it, you
are the only one who
is able to see me.
And of course, my voice
can only be heard by you.
In other words, the
Death Note is the bond
between Light, the human,
and Ryuk, the Shinigami.
Mm, mm.
Yum.
-I just have one more
question I want to ask you.
Why was I chosen for this?
Hey, are you even listening?
-Apples in the human
world are worth the trip.
What's the best way
to describe these?
Juicy?
-Just answer my question.
-Hah, I didn't choose you.
Don't you see this is
all just an accident?
You actually thought
you were chosen
because you're so
smart or something?
Don't be so vain.
It just happened to
fall around here,
and you just happened
to pick it up.
And that's all there is to it.
That's why I wrote
the instructions
in English, the most popular
language in the human world.
-Then why did you drop
it in the first place?
You even wrote down
specific instructions!
So don't try to tell me
this was an accident.
-You're asking me why?
I did it because I was bored.
-You were bored?
RYUK: The truth is,
Shinigami haven't got much
to do these days.
Most of the time, we're either
taking naps or gambling.
If you take the time to write
names in your Death Note,
the others just laugh at
you for working so hard.
Even if you wrote the
name of another Shinigami,
it would be pointless
because they wouldn't I die.
Then since we live in
the Shinigami realm,
it brings us no amusement to
kill those in the human world
either.
So I figured I'd have more
fun if I get down here myself.
Anyway, I'm surprised at how
many names you've written.
But I want to know why you
only wrote the cause of death
for that guy who was
hit by the truck.
-If you don't write
down the cause of death,
the victim dies
of a heart attack.
And that's probably the best
thing about the Death Note,
Ryuk.
-Huh?
-You see, I've already
exhausted the list
of the world's major criminals.
And eventually, I'm going
to get rid of them all.
-What's the point of doing that?
-It's only a matter of time
before people figure out
that these criminals are
being eliminated by someone.
I want the world to
know of my existence,
that there's someone out there
passing righteous judgment
on the wicked.
-Why even bother?
What are you trying to achieve
by passing judgment on them?
I mean, why do you care?
-Because I've been bored, too.
I wasn't ready to believe it
at first, but it's obvious now.
There's something about
the Death Note itself
that makes humans want to
try it out at least once.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
I killed them both.
I real-- I'd killed two men.
Those were human lives.
It won't be overlooked.
Besides, who am I to
pass judgment on others?
Uhh, no, no, wait.
Maybe I'm wrong.
This is exactly what I've
been thinking about lately.
This world is rotting.
And those who are making
it rot deserve to die!
Someone has to do
it, so why not me?
Even if it means sacrificing
my own mind and soul,
it's worth it because the
world can't go on like this.
I wonder, what if someone else
had picked up this notebook?
Is there anyone out
there, other than me,
who'd be willing to eliminate
the vermin from the world?
If I don't do it, then who will?
That's just it.
There's no one.
I can do it.
In fact, I'm the
only one who can.
I'll do it.
Using the Death Note,
I'll change the world.
[groans]
-Ugh!
-Arrgh!
Ugh!
-Uhh.
-Ugh!
-Ugh! [groans]
-[gasping]
[yells]
-Arrgh!
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): At
first, I wrote the names
of the worst criminals
I could think
of, like I was cleaning up
the world, one name at a time
so that, eventually, no one will
ever do anything evil again.
And while the truly
guilty ones who
deserve to be punished for their
crimes die of heart attacks,
the people who are
less guilty but who
still make trouble
for others will slowly
be erased through disease
and accidental death.
Then and only then,
the world will
start moving in the
right direction.
It'll be a new world,
free of injustice
and populated by people who
I've judged to be honest,
kind, and hardworking.
-But if you did that,
it would make you
the only bad person left.
-Huh?
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
I'm a hardworking
honor student who's
considered to be one of
Japan's best and brightest.
And I-- I will become the
god of this new world.
-It's just as I thought.
Humans are so interesting.
[theme music]
-[snickers]
I'll show the world what happens
when you try to cross me.
The entire world
is watching now, L.