[music playing]
-I have to admit I
was surprised, Ryuga.
I never thought you'd
asked me to play tennis
as a way to get to
know each other.
-Is it a problem for you?
-Not at all.
But when you first
invited me to play,
did you know how good I was?
-Yes.
I'll be fine, though.
It's been a while,
but at one time
I was actually the
British junior champion.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): If I
ask him if he's British,
would he think I'm trying
to find out more about him
because I'm Kira?
Oh well, can't hurt to try.
-Ryuga, were you
raised in the UK?
-I lived in England for about
five years when I was younger,
but save your breath.
Nothing in that story would
reveal L's true identity,
I promise you.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Oh, is that so?
L: Well, since it's
out first match,
why don't we just
play a single set.
First one to six?
LIGHT: That's fine by me.
L (VOICEOVER): This is just
a friendly game of tennis,
nothing more.
In an of itself, it won't
determine if Light is Kira.
I'm But I know
Kira hates to lose.
L: 15-love.
-Woah, Ryuga.
You sure don't mess around.
-He who strikes first wins.
What do you mean you're
not at liberty to say?
-I'm very sorry, sir.
We're under orders from L not
to discuss the case with anyone,
including you.
-I'm not asking for details
here, just what you're doing
and where.
-I'm very sorry, sir.
-Hmm.
You know, Yagami, it's been
four months since this case came
to the public's attention,
and they want results.
People are saying that
the NPA is incompetent,
that L is incompetent.
-With all due respect, sir,
the rest of the department
runs away with their
tails between their legs
and we're incompetent?
Do you have any
idea how many people
are left at task force
headquarters these days?
If you're concerned
with public opinion,
then you'll want to
suppress the fact
that most of our
detectives would rather
let a serial killer roam
free than risk their lives.
Please excuse me.
-Yagami, what about
this L character.
Can he be trusted?
-In my opinion, he's a lot
more capable than we are.
Right now, even as we speak,
he's risking his life.
-Are these two really amateurs?
Who are they, anyway?
-I think their names are
Light Yagami and Hideki Ryuga.
These are the same two guys
who scored perfect on the exam.
L (VOICEOVER): Relax,
I'd While it's true
that Kira hates
losing, it's also true
that most people would
rather win than lose.
It's human nature.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Is he going to think
that I'm Kira if
I go for the win?
I suppose I could
just lose on purpose.
But if I do, it could
work against me.
Since he'd expect
Kira to want to win,
he might also expect me to throw
the match to avoid suspicion.
I don't see any way
that he can profile me
based on a tennis match.
So I have to assume he has
some other goal in mind.
Either way, I'm not
going to let him win.
L (VOICEOVER): Look at that.
He's going for the win.
-That's four games all.
Light Yagami to serve.
-And just like that, we've got
an umpire and a line judge.
-You won't believe this.
I thought I'd heard the name
Light Yagami somewhere before,
so I checked.
He was the '02-'03 junior
high tennis champion.
Apparently, during the
third year awards ceremony,
he announced that he was
hanging up his racket.
And I guess he hasn't
played competitively since.
-Hey, hey.
What about my Ryuga.
Don't tell me you haven't
noticed him holding his own
against this former
junior high champ.
L (VOICEOVER): I can see the
wheels turning, Light Yagami.
I'm already in your head.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
There's no way
this tennis match will
deepen our friendship.
This is a token gesture,
an elaborate act
we'll go through so we
can say we're closer.
L (VOICEOVER): Because I
wanted to play tennis with you,
you'll assume that I'm preparing
to take a step closer, laying
the groundwork to get
to know you better.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): And then
you're going to try and trap me
by getting me to say something
that only Kira would know.
L (VOICEOVER): However,
I'm sure you'll tell me
you need to know if
you can trust me first.
And of course, the only
way to win your trust
will be to share what
I know about Kira.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): If you want
me to discuss Kira with you,
it only makes sense that I'd
want to ask for proof that you
are in charge of
the investigation
and, more importantly,
that you are really L,
as you say you are.
L (VOICEOVER): So it
goes without saying
that the first thing you're
going to want from me is--
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Some
kind of confirmation
from a third party that you
really are L. Which means--
LIGHT AND L
(VOICEOVER): We'll have
to go to task
force headquarters.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
In all things,
one cannot win
with defense alone.
To win, you must attack!
-Game and set won
by Light Yagami!
Six games to four.
[applause]
-Just as I expected,
you beat me.
-It's been a while since
I had to play that hard.
I'm feeling kind
of thirsty, plus
there's something I
wanted to ask you about.
You want to go
somewhere for drink?
-You humored me
with a tennis match.
The least I can do is answer
some of your questions.
But before this conversation
goes any further,
there's something
I must tell you.
-What's that?
-I suspect that you, Light
Yagami, are in fact Kira.
Now, if you still want
to ask me something,
then please go ahead.
-You think I'm Kira?
-Well, when I say I suspect
you, it's only a 1% possibility.
But that aside, I don't mind
telling you that once I'm sure
you aren't Kira and I can verify
that your deductive skills are
as strong as I
think they are, I'd
like nothing more
than to have you
work with me on
this investigation.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): 1%, huh?
That was well worded
because no matter
how little he says
he suspects me,
it means he has
grounds to prevent me
from meeting anyone
on the task force.
It's quite the preemptive
move on his part.
He got me.
-This coffee shop is one of
my favorites in the area.
And if we sit here,
there's no chance
of anyone overhearing us.
-Thanks for showing
me this place.
I can see why you like it.
-Not to mention we're
so out of the way here,
no one's going to
give you a hard time
about the way you sit.
-I don't sit like this
because I want to.
I have to sit like this.
You see, if I were
to sit normally,
my deductive skills
would immediately
be reduced by roughly 40%.
So what was it you
wanted to ask me?
LIGHT: Right.
I'm sure that can
wait until you're
convinced that I'm not Kira.
So please, let's talk
about whatever you want to.
-You're under no
obligation to do this,
but would you mind
submitting yourself
to a test of your
deductive reasoning skills?
-Sure, why not?
Sounds like fun.
-All right, then.
We can begin by taking
a look at these.
Photographs of three notes
written by prison inmates
while under Kira's control
just prior to their deaths.
None of this information
has been made public.
You can take as long as
you want to look them over.
Please let me know
what you think.
-Very interesting.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Come
on, this is child's plays.
There's a print
number on the back
of each of these photographs.
If I ignore this fact and
was still able to come up
with the phrase, "L do you know
gods of death love apples?"
what would that mean?
Clearly, if I read it
the way Kira intended
on my first attempt, I'd
only look more suspicious.
But the fact that I'm able
to solve this silly code
isn't enough on its own
to prove that I'm Kira.
-It would be quite amazing to
learn that not only could Kira
kill others but could also
control his victim's actions.
I think Kira wrote
these, and it seems
he's encoded a message for
you, as well, almost as if he's
mocking you.
If you line these notes up
side-by-side and take a look
at the first letter of every
line, it reveals a message.
Rearranging it like
this gives you,
"L, do you know gods
of death love apples."
But there are
obvious print numbers
on the back of all
these photographs.
Arrange it in that
order, we get,
"L, do you know love
apples gods of death."
That doesn't sound right.
And based on that,
it's hard to believe
that Kira would have wanted
you to read it this way.
-That's incorrect.
-Huh?
-The thing is, there are
actually four photographs.
When we add this
one, it reads, "L,
do you know gods of death who
love apples have red hands."
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): It's a fake.
I never made any
criminal write the letter
in this fourth picture.
Is he stupid?
-But seeing as I only had
three photographs to work with,
my deduction was perfect.
-No, it wasn't.
The truth is there
were four of them.
If you'd figured that out,
it would've been perfect.
Even though you knew the
message was incomplete,
you decided that there
were only three notes.
You never even considered
that there might be a fourth.
What do you make of that?
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Damn him.
This wasn't just about gauging
my deductive reasoning skills.
He wanted to see what
my reaction would be.
If I keep falling
for his tricks,
I'll be playing
right into his hands.
-Hmm.
Well, you got me there.
I didn't think of that.
In any case, the likelihood this
message will lead you to Kira
is not very great.
Besides, we all know gods
of death don't exist.
-If you were me, faced with
someone who might be Kira,
how would you go about
establishing this person's
innocence or guilt?
You need to be absolutely sure.
-I would probably
try to get them
to say something
that was never made
public in any way, something
that only Kira could know.
Kind of like what you
were doing just now.
-Truly amazing.
What's incredible is that I've
asked countless detectives
that same question, and
it took most of them
minutes to even come
up with an answer.
But you?
You immediately
thought of a scenario
in which Kira is speaking
directly to the investigator.
I'm impressed.
You'll make a fine
detective, Light.
-But it's a bit of a
double-edged sword.
The more impressive my answers,
the more of a suspect I become.
L: Yes.
It's about 3% now.
However, it's made me
that much more determined
to work with you on
this investigation.
You see, I'm in a position
where even if you are Kira,
it would still be to
my benefit to have
you working alongside us.
Do you know why I'd say that?
-If I cooperate
with you, there's
a chance I can help the
investigation to move forward.
And if I'm Kira, I
might reveal myself.
In other words, whether
I'm Kira or not,
you stand to gain either way.
It's a very smart
move on your part.
But I think you might be
getting the wrong idea.
It's true that I do have an
interest in the Kira case.
And yes, detective work
is a hobby of mine.
But I know that I'm not Kira.
And I certainly don't
want to be killed by him.
Besides, what proof have
you been able to give me
that you yourself aren't Kira?
I mean, it hardly seems
fair for just one of us
to be investigated,
wouldn't you say?
At this point, neither of us
can prove that we're not Kira.
However, if you are
in fact L, I don't
imagine it would be that hard
for you to prove it to me.
I think I'd be convinced if,
say, my father or someone
else from the task
force headquarters
was able to confirm
your identity.
If you can't do
that, then I'm afraid
I just won't be
able to help you.
L (VOICEOVER): You sure
talk a lot, don't you Light?
Typical for someone
who hates losing.
We've got 7%.
Could it really be him?
-I don't remember saying
you couldn't meet anyone
from task force headquarters
to verify my identity.
I'm currently working alongside
your father, as well as
several other senior
detectives from the NPA.
Now, if I understand
you correctly
and I take you to task
force headquarters,
you'll help us with
the investigation.
Am I safe in making
this assumption?
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Does
this guy have a death wish?
I don't understand.
What's he thinking?
[phone ringing]
-Excuse me.
-Oh, there goes mine.
-Yes?
WATARI (ON PHONE): Ryuzaki
I have some bad news.
SACHIKO YAGAMI (ON PHONE):
Light, your father is--
-Light, it's your--
-My father!
He had a heart attack!
[sirens]
SACHIKO YAGAMI: OK,
see you tomorrow.
Have them call home if you
need me to bring anything.
Light?
You take care of him, OK?
LIGHT: Sure.
So the doctors think
stress was the only cause?
-Yeah.
To be honest, I thought it was
Kira when I first collapsed.
But I'll be all right.
It seems I've been pushing
myself a bit too hard lately.
-Indeed.
It must have added
to your stress
knowing that Light is a
suspect in this investigation.
-You actually told
my father that?
-Yes.
In fact, I've told
him everything.
It's true.
He even knows that I am L.
-That's correct.
This man is L. To protect his
identity, we on the task force
refer to him as Ryuzaki.
But make no mistake.
It's him.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
This guy is the real L.
My father wouldn't lie.
The very same man who's been
controlling the police up
to this point.
If I get rid of him and the rest
of the investigative team-- no.
No, let's face it.
It wouldn't be that simple.
There's no need to rush.
I have time to sit
back and watch.
But for now, I'm
the Light Yagami
who's worried for his father.
-So, Ryuzaki, now that
you've had the chance
to talk to my son, is
he cleared as a suspect?
-When I say I suspect him, you
should know it's very minor.
We've gone over this, but
I'll explain it again.
Not long ago, Kira
killed 12 FBI agents
who'd come to
Japan to assist us.
They were instructed
to follow people
connected to the
Japanese police.
One of these
agents, Raye Penber,
exhibited unusual
behavior before he died.
-I understand, and I was one
of the people Raye Penber was
investigating before he died.
It only makes sense
I'd be a suspect.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Nope.
To be more precise, there's
no one else you could suspect.
-I find Light's deductive
powers quite impressive.
He's always quick
and to the point.
-Ryuga, I'd like to help
with the investigation.
My father has
erased any doubts I
might have regarding
your true identity.
Also, I'd like nothing
more than to catch Kira
so I can prove once and
for all that I'm not him.
-No, Light.
This is a time in
your life when you
should be studying to
become a police officer.
It won't be to late to
join us once you are done.
-Come on, Dad, what
are you talking about?
Who knows how many
years that'll take.
Besides, don't you
remember my promise?
That if something
ever happened to you,
I would find Kira and make
sure he gets executed.
SOICHIRO YAGAMI
(VOICEOVER): I refuse
to believe that my son
could turn out to be Kira.
L (VOICEOVER): This doesn't
seem like an act to me.
Or if it is, it's too cheesy.
SOICHIRO YAGAMI:
Light, listen to me.
Kira is pure evil.
We can all agree on that.
But recently, I've
started thinking
of this whole situation
in a different way.
What is truly evil is
the power to kill people.
And any person who has come
to possess this kind of power
is cursed.
No matter how you use
it, no true happiness
can be obtained like that,
not by killing other people.
L: I think you're
absolutely right.
If Kira is just a normal
person who somehow obtained
this awful power, I would
say that he's cursed.
-Ryuzaki, I'm sorry
for all this trouble.
But I'll be back at work as
soon as the doctors let me out
of here.
-Excuse me, visiting hours
were over 10 minutes ago.
-Ryuga, what would
it take to get
you to believe
that I'm not Kira.
Please, isn't there something?
-If you aren't Kira,
it won't be necessary.
Let things run their course
and the truth will be revealed.
-I can't take this anymore!
Put yourself in my position.
How do you think it feels
to be accused of being Kira?
-It was one of the
worst feelings ever.
-What if you were to
lock me up for a month
in a place with no TV or
any other kind of access
to the outside world and keep
a constant watch over me?
L (VOICEOVER): Would
any normal person
be willing to go to such extreme
measures to clear their name?
-That's no good.
I can't do anything
that would deprive you
of basic human rights.
And furthermore, it is complete
nonsense for the investigator
to take suggestions
from the suspect.
-I understand.
L: Don't worry so much.
Be patient.
It'll become apparent to
us if you're not Kira.
And listening to that
conversation between you
and your father, I was almost
convinced you might not be him.
Light, please take good
care of Mr. Yagami.
-Oh, one more thing.
I know I agreed to help
with the investigation.
But I don't think
I'll be able to do
much until my father's
healthy again.
-Yes, of course.
Well, then.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Hideki Ryuga.
Ryuzaki.
He's the L I've been
fighting this whole time.
But what is his real name?
L (VOICEOVER): Light Yagami.
Are you not Kira?
-Ryuk.
-Huh?
-I never once felt cursed since
I picked up the death note.
In fact, the thought never
even crossed my mind.
I'm happier than I've ever
been, all thanks to this power.
I'm going to create
a perfect world.
RYUK: Honestly,
I could care less
whether you feel cursed or
happy to have a notebook.
I'll leave that sentimental
crap to you humans.
But normally, humans who come
into contact with the Shinigami
have nothing but misfortune.
[music playing]
-That's interesting.
But I have no intentions
of repeating that pattern.
-Well, I hope you're
right about that.
HITOSHI DEMEGAWA:
What is this crap?
Don't tell me this is
your idea of a proposal.
Listen, you people must think
that just mentioning Kira's
name is enough to get us
the ratings we need, huh?
Well, you're wrong.
Our program gets the ratings
because we cover the stories
that the other
stations won't touch.
If it bleeds, it leads.
What I need is a good
freaking story, not this crap.
Now get out there
and fine me a story.
-But the police won't talk, sir.
It's been impossible to get
details from them lately.
-Idiot!
I don't pay you to complain.
If they won't give you
anything, then get creative!
[knocking]
Huh?
-Mr. Demegawa, sir?
This is for you.
HITOSHI DEMEGAWA: What is it?
So who is this from?
Huh?
Now this is more like it.
This is what I call a story.
It's almost too good to be true.
A message to the
world from Kira--
"if you do not
broadcast these tapes,
I will kill your company's
board of directors one by one."
Who wouldn't air these?
If this is for real,
our ratings are
going to go through the roof.
Holy crap!
I'm so excited I feel like I'm
having a heart attack here!
[music playing]
LIGHT: If I just leave
things as they are,
I'm pretty sure that
L will be finished off
within the next four days.
It looks like I've even
got God on my side now.
I suppose it's actually a
god of death, a Shinigami.