[theme music]
OOI: Well, then, let's
begin tonight's meeting.
LIGHT: There's supposed
to be eight of them,
but only seven are present.
That must mean that--
L: They probably killed
one of their members.
-Hmm.
OOI: In order to further the
growth of the Yotsuba Group
and best serve its
financial interests,
who should we kill next?
[gasp]
-You see?
It's just like I
told you last week.
L: This is not good.
At this rate--
OOI: But before we
get to that, there
are several topics that
we need to discuss.
First, there is the
issue of Hatori's death.
NAMIKAWA: That was unavoidable.
To be honest, in
a certain sense,
I'm relieved that
Hatori is dead.
Kira has demonstrated
that we must
be committed to these meetings.
We now know what will
happen if we try to leave.
-Hmm.
I think we all understand
what Hatori's death means
for the rest of us.
Let's not take it lightly.
Now, moving on, our next
topic is Eraldo Coil's report.
[gasp]
-One of their members
just died, and that's
all they're going to say?
-So did we really pay $5
million for this report?
I mean, come on.
Look at this.
He hasn't found out
anything important about L,
like his name or his face.
Is this Coil guy seriously
going to be of any use to us?
-Hold on a second.
There is something
very interesting
in the last part of this report.
Coil's warning us
that we can't afford
to take L's existence
too lightly.
In particular, it
says, the concentration
of killings that are
beneficial to Yotsuba
will likely be
noticed by L if they
continue on Fridays
and Saturdays.
-Sounds like this
Eraldo Coil has
figured out what
we've been up to.
I admit, it's quite impressive.
At any rate, I
personally think we
should stop killing
every weekend.
MATSUDA: This is unbelievable.
It's like they're trying
to confess to everything.
-Hmm.
As long as we have
this video as evidence,
we could probably arrest
all seven of them.
-This is not good.
-Kira hasn't been flexible
up till now, has he?
It would be nice if
he could spread out
his killings over
the whole week.
-The fact that Coil noticed
what we've been up to
makes it too
dangerous to continue
killing at our usual pace.
From now on, we have
to be even more careful
and make sure that
nobody else happens
to notice a trend
in these deaths.
-Now, onto the main topic.
Who should we kill?
-Hmm.
-I think we should
focus on ELF Insurance.
If they expand into
the Japanese market,
Yotsuba and many other companies
will lose valuable clients
to them.
-Agreed.
-All right.
Any objections to killing
these people from ELF
with accidental deaths?
EXECUTIVES: No objections.
-Oh.
-Is this for real?
How can they do this so easily?
OOI: Another potential
candidate is Santero Zenzai,
a member of the Kugisawa Group.
He's been protesting Yotsuba's
resort development plans.
Zenzai's known to have
high blood pressure,
so we can designate
a time for him
to suffer a stroke,
resulting in natural death.
Any objections?
EXECUTIVES: No objections.
[gasp]
-Kira?
Deaths by accident, by disease?
Designated times of death?
It's all just as we suspected.
We were right.
-Now, unfortunately, we
can only be completely sure
after those people
they've named are dead.
-Ah.
-We will continue to
monitor these meetings
and take note of what
they say, how they act,
and, most importantly, whether
the people they choose actually
die.
If we can confirm the
connection between their plans
and the deaths, then
we'll definitely
be able to catch Kira.
-(YELLING IN UNISON) Ryuzaki!
-Ah, mm-- what is it?
There's no need
to yell in unison.
-I can't carry on knowing
these people will die.
That's just immoral.
-Right.
-Here it comes.
I know you're
planning to catch Kira
by letting these guys actually
carry out these murders,
but we can't let that happen.
-That's right.
It's obvious that these seven
men are behind the killings.
With Matsuda's testimony and
this footage we've recorded,
we have all the evidence.
L: You're making this difficult.
If we were to take action
now, everything we've done
will go to waste.
OOI: So what do you say we take
care of the ELF in three weeks.
And as for Zenzai, we'll ask
Kira to kill him this weekend.
EXECUTIVES: No objections.
-If that's what
they're going to do,
then there's not much time left.
Light, we already know the phone
numbers of these board members,
don't we?
-Yeah.
-I don't care who we call.
I need to reach one
of these men and have
them stop these murders.
L: Please, hold on.
That will cause suspicion.
It would mean the investigation
caught up to them three days
after they were
contacted by Aiber.
Also, it would make
it far more unlikely
that we would be
able to discover
who the real Kira might be.
We can't afford
such a huge setback,
seeing how far we've come.
In order to catch Kira, we are
going to need some solid proof.
LIGHT: Ryuzaki, if one of these
seven men is in fact Kira,
would it be safe to say that
if I try calling one of them,
the odds of that person
actually being Kira
is going to be one in seven?
-I'm thinking there could be
more than one Kira among them,
a probability of two
in seven at most.
-If we're prepared to let them
know that the investigation is
catching up to them, let's
place our bets on these odds.
Ryuzaki, I'm going to pose as L.
Judging from their conversation
so far, the one least
likely to be Kira
but with the most influence is--
-Ooi!
-(BOTH) Namikawa.
-Uh--
-If you're going to make a
call, please use this phone.
It's set up so it can't
be traced or tapped.
-You know, this would all
go a lot faster if we'd--
[phone buzzing]
--kill off the execs
of our rival companies
and be done with it.
-Hmm.
That would be going
a little too far.
EXECUTIVE: Why?
We can kill them and
split their holdings.
DISTORTED VOICE (ON PHONE):
Is this Reiji Namikawa, head
of the Yotsuba Group's
marketing department?
-Hmm.
Yes.
And who is this?
DISTORTED VOICE (ON
PHONE): Listen carefully,
but don't draw
attention to yourself.
I am L.
[gasp]
I've placed cameras and wiretaps
throughout that meeting room.
Even as I speak, I'm recording
footage of your entire meeting.
The first thing you
discussed was Hatori's death.
Now you're debating
who to kill next.
Am I correct?
NAMIKAWA (VOICEOVER): He's
been watching everything.
-If you're not Kira,
or if you are not
someone who can contact Kira
directly, let's make a deal.
-A deal?
DISTORTED VOICE
(ON PHONE): I need
you to delay the deaths of ELF's
president and Mr. Zenzai by one
month.
I doubt it will be difficult
for someone of your standing
to accomplish that.
-Yes.
Yes, I see.
Right.
Uh, go on.
-If you complete your end of
the deal and cooperate with
our requests from now on,
then your crimes-- no,
not just yours, but
everyone's crimes,
with the exception of
Kira's-- will be pardoned,
based on the premised
that Kira blackmailed you
into participating
in these meetings.
-I see.
OK.
(VOICEOVER) My only
option is to join L. No,
I'll be dead if Kira
manages to find out.
What should I do?
-If you tell the others about
this call, they will panic.
It would be of no
advantage to you.
Everyone would be
arrested immediately.
But that's not my intention.
I'm planning to go one
on one against Kira.
Listen.
If I win against Kira, you will
be acquitted of all charges.
If Kira wins, then you'll
be free to carry on
with your comfortable life.
Just play along
with both parties.
Staying on the
sidelines would be best.
You're not in a position to
lose anything, regardless
of who wins in the end.
You would only be at
a loss if I decided
to arrest you
right here and now.
NAMIKAWA (VOICEOVER): Damn it.
He already knew what
answer I would have given.
DISTORTED VOICE (ON
PHONE): That's all for now.
-Right.
I'll see you Monday then.
-What's going on, Namikawa?
Who was that?
-Oh, one of my men
screwed up again.
I'll have to fix it on Monday.
Anyway, sorry for
the interruption.
Let's get back on topic.
We were discussing when we
should kill Zenzai and the men
from ELF.
Here's what I'm thinking.
We'll give Coil one month
to reveal L's identity.
If he still hasn't
uncovered the information
we need, then we can go ahead
and kill the targets randomly.
Then we'll give
him another month
to investigate and
repeat the process.
Once we get rid
of L permanently,
we can go back to killing
two or three people a week.
In other words, our top priority
should be the elimination of L.
-I see.
Once we kill L, there won't be
anything standing in our way.
But until then, we
need to be careful.
-Right.
Sounds like a
reasonable plan to me.
-We need to be extremely careful
if we don't want to get caught.
OOI: Then we're in agreement.
We'll give Coil one month.
EXECUTIVES: Agreed.
NAMIKAWA (VOICEOVER): L, this
should satisfy you for now.
OOI: We will still be
meeting on a weekly basis.
That is all.
-That went well.
-Yeah.
-You really are
quite amazing, Light.
Not only did you manage
to delay the killings,
but you also set up Namikawa
as a potential mole for us.
It sounded exactly like the
sort of thing I would do,
and you thought of it
quicker than I did.
At this rate, if I
end up dying somehow,
it's quite possible
that you would
be capable of succeeding me.
-What?
Why are you being so morbid?
There isn't time for that.
We only have a month to
figure out Kira's identity
and gather evidence
against him to prove it.
This is only the beginning.
L: Yes, but you were the
one who first noticed
the connection between
Yotsuba and Kira.
You actually might be
more capable than I am.
I honestly believe you
could take this on.
[gasp]
L: Tell me, If I
should die, would you
take over for me as L?
[gasp]
If I should die, would
you take over for me as L?
(VOICEOVER) If he is Kira
and just playing innocent,
he's sure to say yes.
-What are you talking about?
As long as we're
joined by these,
we would die together anyway.
I see.
Ryuzaki, I'm sorry,
but I'm going
to have to tell everyone
what you're really
thinking right now.
He thinks that if
I am Kira, then
there are two possibilities.
Either I'm just pretending I'm
not him and putting on an act,
or Kira's power has passed
on from me to someone else,
and I have no memory that I was
ever Kira in the first place.
He's trying to determine
which, if either, is the truth.
The first theory-- if
I am putting on an act,
he will never remove
these handcuffs.
No, even if I wasn't
pretending to be innocent,
I'm sure he still
wouldn't take them off.
Ryuzaki still believes
that I'm Kira.
Even if that power had been
passed to someone else,
he thinks that I
would have planned
to have it return to my once
I'm safe from suspicion.
In other words, I wasn't
being controlled at all.
He thinks it was a plan--
to pass on the power
and arrange for it to come back
to me once I've been cleared.
L (VOICEOVER): Impressive.
He figured out exactly what I'd
been thinking all this time.
LIGHT: Ryuzaki's theory is
that once I steal L's title,
I will become Kira again.
-Correct.
LIGHT: Taking on
the identity of L,
having the power to control
the police in every country
while being Kira in
secret-- it's ideal.
And you're thinking
I could do it.
No, that I would do it.
That's what you're
saying, isn't it?
-Yes.
-But what about now?
I told you, I don't
want your title.
That should prove even to you
that I'm not putting on an act,
shouldn't it?
L: If this is all
an act, and you
are trying to steal
my identity, there's
no chance you would
be foolish enough
to reveal your plan
in front of everyone.
Wouldn't you agree?
-Hmm.
Ryuzaki.
-Huh?
-Do you think that I'm actually
capable of becoming a murderer?
Kira?
Even after I help you catch him?
Do I seem like that
kind of person to you?
L: Yes, you do.
I've always thought so.
[gasp]
-Hmm.
-Gah, not again.
-OK, break it up!
Once is enough.
It was a draw, so let's just
leave it as an even match, OK?
-Yeah, you're right.
Anyway, let's focus on catching
the Kira that's in front of us
right now.
As long as I have
the handcuffs on,
you shouldn't have
any complaints.
-I suppose so.
We only have a month, so there's
no time to get distracted.
[sigh]
-Ryuzaki.
-Yes?
-We have plenty of
footage from this meeting.
Can we use that as evidence
against those seven men
and prevent the murders
of other criminals?
L (VOICEOVER): Here we go again.
Unfortunately, no.
-But why?
-At the moment,
we're not certain
if Kira is among
those seven men.
If all they have is a
tenuous connection with him,
then Kira will kill them as
soon as they're arrested.
We have to be absolutely
sure that Kira is among them,
so there's no point
in detaining them now.
And even if it does turn
out to be one of them,
it will still be quite
difficult to determine
who the culprit is.
Mm, I believe it's still far too
early for us to make our move.
-Hold on.
At the same time, we can't
say that he's definitely not
among the seven.
That means there's a
chance the killings will
stop if we take this
opportunity to arrest them.
-I think Dad's right.
There is a chance.
We have to act on it.
L: Excuse me, but I
think from now on,
I should go after
Kira by myself.
-Huh?
L: You can use these
headquarters as you wish.
I'll also be here, but we
will be working independently.
You can conduct
your investigation
under your own direction.
Feel free to arrest
those men if you like.
I will be carrying on
my own investigation.
We'll only get into
arguments if we
don't split up and act
separately at this point.
This is for the best.
-Are you saying you're
going to figure out
who Kira is by any
means necessary?
-Yes.
This case will never be solved
unless we capture Kira himself.
Don't get me wrong.
I wouldn't say that preventing
more deaths is pointless.
But if we don't uncover the
entire truth once and for all,
Kira will only appear again,
and the number of victims
will continue to increase.
That's why I believe it's
more important to find out
who Kira really is.
As I've been saying, I'm opposed
to arresting those seven men.
If you want to do
so, then you will
have to take
responsibility for them.
I will pursue Kira on my own.
We only have one month.
I wonder who will succeed?
-R-- Ryuzaki.
Where are you going?
-To Amane's room.
Sorry, I know you're on your
father's side in all this,
but I can't remove
these handcuffs.
I'm afraid you're going to
have to come along with me.
[humming]
-Light!
I didn't know we were
supposed to have a date.
Oh, right, I should have known.
-Misa Amane--
[shout]
Tell me, do you love Light
from the bottom of your heart?
-Huh?
Uh, yeah.
Of course I do.
-But you also worship
Kira, don't you?
-Well, yeah.
-So then, if you had to
choose between Light and Kira,
who would you pick?
-What?
That's obvious.
Of course it's gonna be Light.
I'm really grateful to Kira
and want to meet him someday
in person, but
that's not true love.
I'd definitely choose Light.
-But your precious Light
is planning to catch Kira.
Isn't that right?
-Well, yes, of course I am.
[shout]
-He says he wants to catch Kira.
Now what will you do?
-Well, if that's
what Light says,
then I'm gonna support
him no matter what.
-I see.
So if you were given
the opportunity
to work with Light on
this investigation,
would you take the offer?
-What?
Ryuzaki--
-Yeah, of course I would.
I'd do anything I
could to help Light.
-Wait, hold on a second.
Where are you going with this?
L: I'm planning to have Aiber
pose as Eraldo Coil again.
He'll tell the Yotsuba members
that while he was investigating
L, he discovered that Misa
Amane might know who he is.
He'll also tell them
that L brought her
in for questioning on suspicion
that she was the second Kira.
MISA: That part is true.
-If the Yotsuba Group
believe that Misa
could be their
lead to finding L,
then they'll say that
they want to meet
her to discuss their
advertising campagin.
They'll use that
opportunity to question her.
Thanks to Matsuda's
screwup, they
may already be considering
Misa as their new spokesperson,
so this could work.
-Yeah, right.
-We can't do that.
-Why not?
-This plan is too risky.
Who knows what
could happen to you?
-Oh, wow!
Does that mean you're
worried about me?
Yay!
But don't worry.
I won't mind doing
something like this
if it's for you, Light.
-Listen, Misa.
If they suspect that you
might know who L really is,
we don't know how far
they'll be willing to go
to get that information.
-No problemo.
I promise I won't say anything,
even if they torture me.
-I can attest to that.
-But Kira can control
his victims' actions
before their death.
There's a good
chance he might try
to manipulate her into
revealing what she knows
and then kill her.
Also, if he does
manage to kill L,
he won't have any use for Misa.
He'd kill her to
keep her silent.
-Uh, I don't like
the sound of that.
L: Light.
-Hmm?
-You forget that if we win
against Kira, Misa won't die.
Besides, as long as we're
handcuffed together,
you and I share the same fate.
If I die, so will you.
If that happens, Misa is the one
who would grieve most of all.
Either we lose and
both die together,
or we successfully catch Kira.
Which is it?
-We catch Kira!
I would never dream about
living in a world without Light.
-Yes, that would be dark.
-Cut it out!
This is just crazy.
-We're running out of time, and
I'm starting to get desperate.
As for Misa Amane,
I've turned to her
because I know her bravery
and love for you is boundless.
-Do you really mean it?
Oh no, I think I've
totally misunderstood you
all this time.
I even called you a pervert.
But you actually do understand
how I feel, don't you?
-Yes.
Misa is indisputably the
most perfect and worthy woman
for Light.
-Uh--
-Yay!
You're such a sweetie.
Thank you, Ryuzaki.
-I could actually fall for you.
MISA: Let's not go that far.
But you could maybe
be a friend of mine.
Would that be OK?
-Yes.
So now I've gained
yet another friend.
-Yeah.
Of course, any friend is
a friend of mine as well.
[laughing] Let's all
be friends together.
-(DEADPAN) Yay, fun, huh.
-And of course, I
would never think
of betraying any of my friends.
With our powers combined,
we'll arrest Kira.
-Unfortunately, Light's taking
a different investigative
approach from us
and will be working
with his father and the others.
-Hmm?
L: I'm afraid it will
just be you and I.
-Huh?
What's up with that?
-Come on, L. Now you're
just playing dirty.
You're leaving me with no
other choice but to join your--
L: No, that's quite all right.
MISA: What are
you talking about?
Of course he'll be joining us.
-That's not it either.
I've been opposed to
this investigation
since the beginning.
It's too dangerous for her!
-Oh, Light.
You're so sweet.
Thank you for worrying about me.
But please let me do this.
I want to be useful
to you somehow.
If I can be useful, then maybe
you'll love me even more.
And besides, I would gladly
die if it were for you, Light.
-Figuring out the logistics
of arresting seven people
is going to be challenging.
I don't suppose you
two have any ideas.
Mogi?
Matsuda?
[theme music]
MISA (VOICEOVER):
Well, I am an actress.
Director Nishinaka, Light,
and the others, and now even
Shinigami.
They're all asking me to act.
This is a lot of work.
I might land a commercial gig,
too. [giggle] I'm so popular.