[theme music]
-So you're saying one of
those people is Kira, right?
-(MODIFIED VOICE) Yes.
I've got a lot of
evidence to prove it, too.
The man who died was Mr. H
-Kira--
L: If Higuchi can kill by
looking at someone's face
like the second Kira was
able to, Matsuda will die.
-It's-- It's him!
Don't screw with me!
Why the hell can't
you remember the names
of the people you hire?
That means I have two hours.
-I see Higuchi.
He's only carrying a single bag.
I'm in pursuit.
-I'll kill him.
I'll kill him no matter what.
I'm not giving up until
I have everything.
TV ANNOUNCER: Cosme Misa.
A devlish charm,
an angel's glitter.
Misa's new line of
lipstick just for you.
-Ryuzaki, the
commercial's almost over.
-Is that so?
-(MODIFIED VOICE)
Next thing you know,
I'm in a hotel room drinking
with all eight of them.
-Well, that's rather amusing.
-(MODIFIED VOICE) But if I
give you any more details,
I'm afraid the people who were
there that night would realize
which one of them is Kira, so
I think I'd better leave it
at that for now.
-Of course.
Please take your time to tell us
all the details of your ordeal
to find Kira.
-Light.
Please put Higuchi's car
on audio channel one,
and Sakura TV on channel two.
-As expected, Higuchi's
watching every minute of this
from his car.
INTERVIEWER: And so
according to you,
it was actually at that
party that you met Kira.
MATSUDA: (MODIFIED VOICE) Yes.
But of course, at
the time I had no way
of knowing he was actually Kira.
-So that means he saw your face?
This is incredible.
I think it's amazingly
courageous of you
to step forward and
appear on this program.
Are you sure you're OK with it?
-(MODIFIED VOICE) Yes.
After I started
investigating him,
I found out there are two
things Kira has to have in order
to kill someone.
There are rumors on TV and the
internet as to what those two
things might be, but
I know the truth.
HIGUCHI (VOICEOVER):
A name and a face.
-(MODIFIED VOICE) But Kira only
knows one of those two things
about me, so that
means I should be safe.
HIGUCHI (VOICEOVER):
So, he's saying
he feels safe enough
to step forward
just because I don't
know his real name.
Wait a minute.
Does that mean there's
nothing left that
can connect me to his name?
Maybe he's already destroyed
his file at Yoshida.
Am I wasting my time?
Rem.
What do you think?
-What do I think?
About what, may I ask?
-Rem?
Who's that?
There's no one else
in that car, right?
It's impossible for someone to
be hiding without us knowing.
He isn't using his cell phone.
Could it be a hidden radio?
-No.
There aren't any radios
or other devices.
Only the bugs,
cameras, and tracking
beacons that Wedy placed.
I have no doubt that
she did a thorough job.
-Do you think I'll get
to Yoshida Productions
only to find his
file isn't there?
-Is he talking to himself?
-Why ask my opinion?
I don't see how I'm supposed
to know something like that.
-If this guy was smart, he
would destroy everything
that connects him with his real
name before he appeared on TV.
And don't you think it's
a little too reckless
for Yoshida Productions
to just let me
into their offices unsupervised?
Maybe not.
If there was a robbery,
they'd figure out
right away who did it, since
I know where the key is.
-This is sounding very good.
-He'll still go there.
Don't you worry.
-Even if he does have
a file at Yoshida,
it could be just another alias.
Damn it!
I wouldn't put it past this
guy to do something like that.
No wonder he's confident.
REM (VOICEOVER): It must
be Light and Misa's plan
to have Higuchi go to
Yoshida Productions.
If that's the case--
That may be true,
but if he knows
that you are Kira,
he's going to announce
your name in public.
That's an inescapable fact.
INTERVIEWER: All right.
There's only one hour left
until the big announcement.
-Your only option is to go.
If the name on his file is
false, that'll be unfortunate.
But if it isn't, you
can kill him discretely
with the notebook.
-Yeah.
I already know that
much myself, but just
to be on the safe
side, I should also
kill the people I contacted
at Yoshida Productions.
That includes the president,
Misa, and that manager of hers.
-What?
No way.
He's gonna kill me?
-It's all right.
Don't worry.
He's talking about doing that
after he's killed Matsuda.
There'd be no point in
killing the rest of you
until he's gotten rid
of the main threat.
-That's true, but still.
-Don't be wreckless.
He's the only one
you have to kill.
If the people you
called end up dying too,
the phone records will
implicate you in their deaths.
-Oh yeah.
Rem, I didn't think
you were so smart.
Then I'll make them all
erase their call histories
before they die.
-But the telephone
company will still
have a record of the calls.
-There's no way he can
just be talking to himself.
But who's Rem?
Who is he talking to?
-If he's talking to
someone right now,
it could be a Shinigami.
Perhaps.
REM (VOICEOVER): I should
just go ahead and ask him.
How about giving up
ownership of the notebook
and returning it to me.
-No.
I'd end up being
ruined if I did that.
Even if I forgot the
notebook, this guy
says he has concrete
evidence to back him up.
If he points out Yotsuba's
recent growth on the air,
no one would ever
doubt his claims.
They'd believe whatever he said.
That means whoever he says is
Kira will be marked as Kira.
Even if he didn't have proof
and I got rid of the evidence
by returning the notebook,
my life would be over.
I wouldn't get promoted.
I wouldn't even be able
to stay with Yotsuba.
-Of course, Sakura
TV has broadcast
this show under the premise
that right now, as we speak,
Kira is watching this program.
-In that case, I'll take this
chance to call out to him.
Kira!
Please, turn yourself in!
-This guy's acting
like a complete idiot.
Still, he was smart enough
to fake his own death
to avoid being killed.
I have to kill him
as soon as possible.
-He's arrived at
Yoshida Productions.
-The show is about to begin.
HIGUCHI (VOICEOVER): To
the left as I come in.
In the desk at the very back.
Very bottom drawer.
-Now, Kira.
How do you kill?
Show me.
-We're in position and
ready to take him down.
We'll move on your command.
L (ON RADIO): Right.
-He's not doing it!
He just made a note of
his name before leaving.
So he's not gonna kill him here?
-Ryuzaki, do you want
us to apprehend him?
-Negative.
We still don't
know how he kills.
Perhaps he's planning
to do something
once he's back in the car.
Let's see camera one again.
-It's weird.
You'd think you'd be desperate
to kill Matsuda this very
second, but he's calm.
-It is strange.
If all he needed was
the name, then he
should've simply taken the
personnel file with him,
but he just put it back in his
drawer after taking a note.
HIGUCHI (VOICEOVER): 36,
37, 38, 39, 40 seconds.
MATSUDA: Kira is a
cold-blooded murderer.
I can't forgive him
for what he's done.
-Damn!
He didn't die!
-Wh-- What's he talking about?
He said he didn't die.
L: Did he already
try and kill Matsuda?
Was writing his name down
all he had to do, or was it--
-What do we do now?
Should we just continue
watching what he's doing?
What if he can cause a
death by just imagining it?
L (VOICEOVER): I don't
understand what's going on.
I still can't figure
out how he kills people.
But even if we restrain him now
and try to get him to confess.
INTERVIEWER: Only 50 minutes
to go until the big Kira
announcement--
-Damn!
I don't have any time!
-He's making a phone call.
It's probably Misa again.
[phone ringing]
-Yeah!
-Argh!
All right.
Calm down.
I already know his face.
If I go back to
company HQ, there
should be surveillance
videos from when he snuck in.
If I had the Shinigami eyes--
half my remaining lifespan,
huh?
That's a lot.
But if he makes
that announcement,
my life's as good
as over anyway.
Better to have a life
that's short and sweet.
Rem.
Let's make the deal.
-The deal?
Who is this Rem person
he keeps talking to?
Could it really be
that Kira's power
comes from another
world or some being?
-I really don't want to
think that's the case.
-Then what is this Rem?
-A Shinigami?
Whatever it is, we need
to keep watching him.
We'll learn nothing
if we take him now.
We may still be able to
find out how he kills.
HIGUCHI (VOICEOVER): With
these yes, I'm invincible.
I have more than
enough options now.
-We're heading after him.
[siren]
OFFICER: You in the red car!
Pull over to the
side of the road.
Now!
-This is bad.
Higuchi's been pulled
over by a traffic cop.
I'm gonna have to
pass him and leave
the pursuit to Aiber's team.
-You were speeding.
-License, please?
-Yeah.
No problem.
-Switch all screens
to Higuchi's car.
-Now, let's see.
Where did I put it?
This'll take care of him.
-Hey!
-Higuchi ditched the cop.
He's driving away!
-What a bastard.
This is Traffic Control Squad--
-That motorcycle cop just
rear ended that truck!
He's dead!
-He's dead?
By accident?
-This is very bad.
(VOICEOVER) All he did was
put his hand in his bag.
Could he have done
something at that moment?
More importantly, how
was he able to obtain
the name of the cop
who stopped him?
Does he only need a face,
like the second Kira?
-Rem.
A deal.
-No.
If he had the power to kill just
by looking at someone's face,
he would have already
killed Matsuda by now.
What's going on?
Unless-- Everyone!
It's too dangerous to allow
further action by Higuchi.
Let's bring him in.
I believe he has the same
powers as the second Kira.
He is able to kill just by
looking at someone's face.
Please keep this in mind when
you move in to arrest him.
[laughter]
-Watari, connect me to
the director of the NPA.
WATARI: Yes.
L: (MODIFIED VOICE) This
is L. We are now aware
of Kira's true identity.
He is currently
heading from Hibiya
to Shibuya along Highway
Route 1 in a red sports car.
Our group will be
handling the arrest.
In the meantime, please
instruct all officers
to refrain from
approaching his car.
-All right.
Dad, during the next
commercial, take measure seven.
-Understood.
Demegawa, during the
next commercial break,
swap Matsuda and the
MC with mannequins.
We'll make it seem as if
the broadcast is continuing
as normal using the voices
we've already prepared.
We'll leave the cameras
running and have
everyone evacuate the building.
-So then, Light, what say we
go and join the fun as well?
-Yeah.
-Hm?
-I'm sorry to do
this, Misa, but I'm
going to have to make sure
you're restrained for a while.
-What?
But that's-- stop joking around!
LIGHT: I didn't realize you
could pilot a helicopter.
That's incredible.
L: Well, you can figure
it out with intuition.
-Hm?
Higuchi isn't
going to Sakura TV.
He's headed the wrong way.
L: Based on his
route, I'd guess he's
going to the
Yotsuba main office.
INTERVIEWER: You've been
outstandingly brave.
-(MODIFIED VOICE) No.
I'm just doing what
anyone would do.
-(VOICEOVER) If I go to the main
office and find a surveillance
video with him on
it, I can kill him.
-Come in, Wedy.
Have you removed absolutely
everything relating to Matsuda
at the Yotsuba headquarters.
WEDY: Yeah.
Why?
Is he headed there now?
Isn't that convenient?
That should give me
mroe than enough time
to go ahead and meet up with
Mr. Yagami to set up the ambush.
HIGUCHI: What the hell?
I can't find him!
This is the right tape.
Someone must have erased it.
Did he come back and erase
them himself somehow?
Or has someone from
the group betrayed me
and started working with him?
No.
Doing that wouldn't absolve
them of their crimes.
Who cares?
I'm out of time.
I've got to hurry!
-We're quickly approaching
the time for the announcement.
How are you feeling?
-(MODIFIED VOICE) I
feel ready for this.
I really want to reveal it now.
INTERVIEWER: Yes, I understand.
But let's cut to a quick
commercial break first.
-(VOICEOVER) Damit!
I'll just have to go to
Sakura TV and kill him there.
LIGHT: Dad, Higuchi's
left Yotsuba.
He's on his way to Sakura TV.
He'll be there in
less than 15 minutes.
Are you ready?
CHIEF YAGAMI: I don't need
my son asking if I'm ready.
Of course I am.
INTERVIEWER: Is
there anything you'd
like to add before
the announcement?
MATSUDA: Well, I want
everyone to think hard
about Kira after he's caught.
People have to
realize that Kira is--
-You ready, Mr. Yagami?
It's almost time.
-I know.
-Here.
-Hm?
-Aiber hates using guns.
Right now I'm the
only one armed.
Take it.
-I can't take this.
I'm no longer a police officer.
Japanese law forbids
civilians from having guns.
That means you shouldn't
be using one, either.
-I guess you're as
stubborn as always, huh?
-I made it in time.
(VOICEOVER) Why
isn't anybody here?
is it just in case
the announcement
is true, and Kira
decides to retaliate?
Hm.
At least it makes my job easier.
MOGI: We've arrived
at Sakura TV.
We're moving into position.
Let's go, Aiber!
-OK, Mogi.
INTERVIEWER: Right now we're
being flooded with phone calls
and faxes showing support for
your courage and strength,
and demanding that
Kira's identity
be revealed right away.
-Huh?
Even the studio is deserted.
Still, I gotta be careful
of where the cameras are.
Can't let myself be seen.
INTERVIEWER: Due
to circumstances
beyond our control, we will
now end this broadcast.
-Huh?
What?
Dummies?
This can't be!
CHIEF YAGAMI: Higuchi.
Hold it right there.
-Don't move.
-Huh?
-I'd give up if I were you.
-You-- you must be making
some kind of mistake.
I'm only here to meet
with Mr. Demegawa
and discuss something with him.
(VOICEOVER) They're
wearing tinted helmets.
They must be taking
precautions against Kira.
In that case-- (OUT LOUD)
I'm with the Yotsuba Group,
from the Development Department.
Let me show you
my business card.
-No!
Chief!
-Aiber!
-Dammit.
I didn't want to have
to use one of these.
But--
-L, Higuchi has a gun on him.
The chief's been shot.
Higuchi's escaping!
-I'm all right.
Sorry, Ryuzaki.
If we pursue him right now,
we can still catch him.
Hurry!
-This is bad.
He's escaped from Sakura TV.
-This leaves us no choice.
We'll have to move
in and apprehend him.
Watari, are you ready?
-Yes.
-Light, I think you should hold
onto this for self defense.
This is Kira we're after.
-No thanks.
Firearms aren't
allowed in Japan.
-You know, I'm sure your father
would say the exact same thing.
[car horn]
-He's driving like a maniac.
-Don't lose sight of him.
-Yes, sir.
-What the hell was
all that about?
Had to be a trap.
WOMAN (ON TV): We now
end our current broadcast
and return you to
regular programming.
The evening news is next.
HIGUCHI (VOICEOVER):
The program's over?
It didn't end just
because I showed up?
What the hell is going on?
Ah!
What the--
[sirens wailing]
HIGUCHI (VOICEOVER):
Just like I thought.
It was a trap.
All these cars with
tinted windows.
So, all that stuff about the
cops not going after Kira
was a lie!
They've been preparing for this.
WATARI: What's happening?
I thought we told
the police not to get
involved with the arrest.
-The only one who
would do this is--
-Yes.
You must be right.
-Damn it!
That way.
-Stop right there.
-Stay back!
Stay back or I'll
shoot, I swear!
-It's over.
-Yes.
It's over.
[theme music]
LIGHT: A human whose name
is written in this notebook
shall die.
This note will not take
effect unless the writer has
the person's face in their mind
when writing his or her name.
Therefore, people sharing the
same name will not be affected.