[music playing]
[music - nightmare, "the world"]
[bus idling]
[crowd murmuring]
RAYE PENBER: You there.
-Yeah?
-Listen carefully.
I cam to Japan as part of
a secret investigation,
so the local police can't
find out that, um, that I--
-I understand.
I promise I won't tell
anyone that I met you,
and of course that
includes my father.
-Well, then please excuse me.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
It's just as I thought.
Anyway, I don't want
the police to know
that I've come into contact
with an FBI agent either.
If my father ever
found out, there's
no doubt he'd let L know.
It's obvious that he
doesn't suspect me.
And as for the police,
I'm sure they'll
treat this as just another
unfortunate accident.
[door opens]
-Hey, welcome back.
RAYE PENBER: [sighs] What a day.
-Raye, what's the matter?
Something happened, didn't it?
I've never heard
you sigh like that.
-Yeah.
The bus I was on got hijacked,
if you can believe it.
-A bus-jacking?
-Some junkie robbed
a bank two days ago
and I guess he wanted to
try taking on a bus today.
I didn't think this kind
of thing happened here.
-So you were already riding the
bus when the hijacker got on?
RAYE PENBER: Yeah.
And in the end, the guy freaked
out, jumped off the bus,
and got hit by a car.
-Did he die?
-Yeah, probably.
I couldn't really stick around
to see what happened to him.
-You know--
-Hm?
-It's a little hard
to believe that that
was all a coincidence,
don't you think?
-What do you mean?
-Think about it.
You got on that bus
because you were
investigating someone, right?
And now you're telling
me that this criminal
is most likely dead.
Doesn't that suggest that you--
RAYE PENBER: That's enough.
-Uh--
-Look, darling,
you and I know you
used to be one of the
best agents in the FBI.
But now you're my fiance now.
We talked about this.
You're not an agent anymore,
so just leave it alone.
-But--
-You wouldn't get involved
with the Kira case
and you wouldn't do
anything dangerous.
That's what you
promised when we decided
you'd come with me so I could
meet your parents in Japan.
You do remember that, don't you?
-Yeah, I guess you're right.
It's just force of habit.
Sorry about that.
-No, I should be sorry.
Let's forget about it.
Anyway, once we have a
few kids running around,
you'll probably
be so busy you'll
forget you were ever an agent.
Your mind'll be occupied
with better things, too.
More importantly, tell
me how I can convince
your dad I'm worthy
of his daughter.
Kira doesn't scare me
half as much as he does.
RYUK: Oh, let me guess.
You're about to write down the
name of that agent, aren't you?
The one from the bus.
-Not yet.
I'm going to wait one week
before writing his name.
If he dies right
after meeting me,
I'll only draw
attention to myself.
I'll write his name in
here once I've given them
time to investigate more
people with ties to the police.
It will be less
obvious that way.
In the meantime,
I think I'll use
some of those inmates
I've been keeping
alive to play around
with L a little more.
[beeping]
WATARI (ON COMM): L.
-Hm?
WATARI (ON COMM):
Another victim.
This one left what appears
to be a suicide note.
-Please, send it to me.
L (VOICEOVER): Gods of death.
L, do you know?
Gods of death.
Is he trying to tell us
that gods of death exist?
-Listen, Watari, tell the police
to monitor prison populations
closely for the next few days.
Kira may use other suicide
notes to communicate with us.
WATARI (ON COMM): Understood.
RYUK: This place is
crawling with humans.
Are you gonna do it here?
-Let's just say
you're about to see
the results of all the
research and experiments
I've been doing over
the last few days.
RYUK: Experiments?
-Yeah.
I've been using known criminals
who live in this part of town
to test out different
killing methods,
and I've learned a lot
about the Death note.
For example, if I
write a cause of death
and the circumstances
leading up to it,
I can add a name afterwards
and it'll still happen.
RYUK (VOICEOVER): Oooh.
Even I didn't know that one.
-He's here.
Right on time.
Mr. Raye Pember.
Turn around and you're dead.
I am Kira.
That's right.
Don't turn around or put
your hands in your pockets.
I won't hesitate
to kill you here.
RAYE (VOICEOVER):
It-- it couldn't be.
His voice, I've
heard it somewhere.
-But first I'm gonna prove
to you that I'm Kira.
Do you see the man working
over there at the coffee shop?
That's right, the one
sweeping the floor.
I'm gonna kill him just for you.
-But-- but how?
Don't do it.
[strangled cry]
[thud]
-I'm afraid I had no
choice but to kill him.
I figured if I didn't
kill at least one person,
you wouldn't believe him.
Although that man has
been repeatedly charged
with sexual assault, he's
managed to avoid conviction
every time due to
lack of evidence.
He was a menace to society.
He got what he deserved.
I can only assume that L has
already informed you of this.
I can't kill someone
who I haven't seen.
I have to know their face.
Which means, of course, I could
easily kill all these people
right now if I wanted to.
Go ahead and choose
someone if you want.
-D-don't do it.
I believe you.
You're Kira.
-But I'm sure you care
more about your loved ones
than any of these people here.
Imagine how you'd
feel if one of them
was killed just because
you refused to cooperate.
I think you should consider
them the real hostages
at the moment.
-How do you know about her?
-[laughs] You seem surprised.
I've been investigating you.
And if you don't do exactly
as I say, she will die,
and so will the rest of
your family, including you.
And that's a promise.
-I-- I understand.
Just tell me what
you need me to do.
-I see you've got
your laptop with you.
I want the files containing
the identities of all the FBI
agents who came to Japan.
RAYE PENBER: I do have
my laptop with me.
It's the one I use for work.
But I don't have the
files you're looking for.
LIGHT: All right, then
take this envelope.
-Huh?
-First, take the transceiver
out of the envelope.
Then put the earpiece in
and await my instructions.
RAYE (VOICEOVER):
The transceiver?
This thing looks like a toy.
But there'll be no record of
this transmission anywhere.
And it allows us to converse
from a close distance,
even underground.
He really thought this through.
LIGHT (OVER
TRANSCEIVER): All right,
now get on the Yamanote Line.
Inner or outer
route-- it doesn't
matter which direction you take.
I'll be close by
at all times, which
means I'll be watching
your every move.
When you get on the train,
pick a spot in front of you
and don't take your eyes off it.
If I see you looking
around, I will kill you.
Once you've boarded,
I want you to take
the seat closest to the door.
If it's occupied,
wait until it's free.
[horn blares]
[brakes squealing]
LIGHT (OVER TRANSCEIVER): Now
I'm going to ask you something.
If I have even the slightest
suspicion that you're not
being honest, your girlfriend
is as good as dead.
How many FBI agents
are currently in Japan?
Speak quietly into
the transceiver
and don't make it obvious.
-(QUIETLY) I believe it's four
teams, three agents per team,
for a total of 12.
LIGHT (OVER TRANSCEIVER): OK.
Now take the papers
out of the envelope.
-Huh?
What is this?
LIGHT (OVER TRANSCEIVER): Of
those 12 agents you mentioned,
I want you to write down
the name of your superior,
the one who's heading
up this investigation,
in the space at the
very top of the page.
RAYE (VOICEOVER): What
is the meaning of this?
What is he after?
Let's face it -- he hasn't
really left me any choice.
Besides, it's not
like he can kill
them using just their names.
LIGHT (OVER TRANSCEIVER):
Next take out your laptop
and turn it on.
Any minute now,
your boss is going
to send you a message
with a file attachment.
It contains the names
and photos of all the FBI
agents currently
active in Japan.
-But this-- this is--
LIGHT (OVER TRANSCEIVER):
Now one by one,
you're going to
look at each photo
and then write that agent's
name in the space provided.
You're going to do
this for each agent.
RAYE (VOICEOVER): It
doesn't make sense.
If he's got the names
already, why use me?
What's he planning
to do with them?
LIGHT (OVER TRANSCEIVER): Good.
Looks like you're done.
Now put the transceiver
and all the papers
back into the original envelope
and place them on the rack
directly above your head.
After that, you're going
to stay in your seat
and ride the train for at
least another 30 minutes.
When you are absolutely
certain that nobody will notice
you leaving without
the envelope,
you can get off the train.
RAYE (VOICEOVER):
I know that voice.
Why on Earth can't' I
remember who it belongs to?
[brakes squealing]
RAYE (VOICEOVER):
Kira, who are you?
[gasp]
[one heartbeat]
[strangled cry]
[breathing jaggedly]
[struggling to breathe]
RAYE (VOICEOVER): Light Yagami.
-Farewell, Raye Pember.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Raye Pember
wrote all of those names
on pages taken from
the Death Note.
Ironic.
Without even realizing
it, he was actually
signing a death warrant
for all of his colleagues.
As for Pember's boss, he
died of a heart attack
after sending all
his agents a file.
And the other 11 investigators?
[chuckles] They
all died of heart
attacks after receiving
the same file.
WATARI (ON COMM):
L, you have a call
from the director of the FBI.
STEVE MASON: It's me.
I've got a report in front
of me right now stating
that all of our agents
in Japan are dead.
All 12 died of heart attacks.
I can only assume that
Kira is behind this.
Look, I'm sorry, but
it's already decided.
We're calling off
our investigation.
[beeping]
WATARI (ON COMM): I have
Chief Yagami on the line.
SOICHIRO YAGAMI (ON
COMM): L, I just got off
the phone with the
director of the FBI.
According to him it seems
that you arranged for the FBI
to come to Japan and investigate
everyone here associated
with the task force.
L: Yes, I did.
SOICHIRO YAGAMI (ON COMM):
So how do you explain this?
Are we now suspects in
our own investigation?
L: I felt that it was necessary
to uncover Kira's identity.
-(ANGRILY) I cannot accept that!
I find it unbelievable
that you would
spy on us, the very people
working with you on this case.
-Hear that?
Well, I knew all along we
couldn't trust that guy.
-More importantly, Kira killed
those FBI agents, didn't he?
-It's obvious he'll kill
anyone who gets in his way,
whether they're
criminals or not.
So much for his
sense of justice.
He's a murderer.
[beeping]
WATARI (ON COMM): We
have another victim.
A note was found at the scene.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): L, do
you know gods of death?
-Hum?
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Love apples.
L (VOICEOVER): Damn you, Kira.
-(TEARFULLY) He's dead?
Raye's dead?
No, he was-- he was
murdered by Kira.
SAYU: Um, so what's with
the family meeting, Dad?
-I figured you're going to
find out sooner or later,
so I might as well tell you now.
I don't want you to be alarmed.
I'm sure you've heard of
this Kira investigation.
Well, I'm currently
in charge of it.
-What?
Are you serious?
That's totally awesome, Dad.
You're the best cop ever!
-That's not quite the
point I'm trying to make.
-Oh?
-You see, the truth is the
FBI sent 12 of their agents
to Japan to assist us in
finding Kira, and all of them
died yesterday.
-Does that mean they
were all killed by Kira?
-What?
-What I'm saying is there's a
chance that Kira will actually
try to kill anyone
who comes after him.
His crimes are ruthless and
more frightening than anything
we've seen.
Many detectives
have already quit.
-Dad, you should quit, too.
I don't want you to die.
What if he gets you?
-That's right.
Your life is so much more
important than some job.
-I can't.
I could never forgive myself
if I walked away from this.
I will not sit back
and let evil triumph.
-But Dad, you--
-Please, dear.
-I think it's
honorable of you, Dad.
I'm proud to be able
to call you my father.
And if anything should
ever happen to you,
I'm going to find Kira-- and
make sure he gets executed.
SOICHIRO YAGAMI: We now
know that Kira doesn't just
target criminals.
He'll kill anyone
who opposes him.
It's quite possible that we
may all be killed by Kira.
Think of your own lives, your
families and all the others
you'd be leaving behind.
If anyone wants to leave this
investigation, now is the time.
You won't be demoted if
you choose not to stay.
You have my word.
But if you're not absolutely
sure, then we don't need you.
You have to be willing
to fight against him,
even if that means making
the ultimate sacrifice.
That is all.
POLICEMAN: So what
are you gonna do?
POLICEMAN: I'm not sure.
BUS DRIVER: Oh, yeah,
that's him all right.
There's no doubt about it.
I remember him because
he told us to get down.
But I don't really remember
any of the other passengers.
NAOMI: I see.
Well, thanks for
talking with me anyway.
I appreciate it.
NAOMI (VOICEOVER): It's
a bit of a long shot,
but if what I'm
thinking is right,
Kira could have been one of the
passengers on the bus that day.
And if that is the
case, then I know
that he's close enough
to use this bus route.
-Five men, huh?
Well, six, including myself.
Still, I'm grateful to see
that there are as many as five
of you willing to risk
your lives to face evil.
L (OVER COMM): The
fact that you've
chosen to stay means you have
a strong sense of justice.
I trust all of you.
-Huh?
Uh, hold on a second.
L just said that he's
decided to trust us now.
But honestly, what reason
do we have to trust him?
HIDEKI IDE: Look,
L, all of us have
agreed to put our lives at
risk to bring Kira to justice,
so I hope you understand
what this means.
We're really sticking
our necks out here.
SHUICHI AIZAWA: But you never
have to show your face, do you?
You just give the orders.
I don't see how
you can expect us
to work alongside you
under those conditions.
-L, if all of us are
going to work together
on this investigation,
and if you truly
meant what you said about
trusting the six of us,
could you come here so we
can all meet in person?
L (OVER COMM): The thought
had already crossed my mind.
After all, I did say that
I trusted all of you.
-Huh?
HIDEKI IDE: Why is he
seeking our help now?
There's only six of us.
He solved all these difficult
cases by himself in the past,
so what makes this
one so different?
The way L's been
conducting things so far,
odds are he's going to
send a stand-in or a proxy
of some kind to meet us
instead of coming himself.
It's not like we'd ever know.
-A proxy, huh?
Well, it is possible.
-I believe L. I think
we can trust him.
And besides, I
don't really see how
we can solve this
case without his help.
SOICHIRO YAGAMI: I agree.
From the beginning he's been
very upfront about the fact
that he would need the help
of the police on this case.
Perhaps we should
think of it like he's
been waiting for this
to happen all along.
-Why would he do
something like that?
-There were a number of
people on the task force
who distrusted L before
this investigation began.
And once we got started,
we had detectives
resigning left and right.
Following that, classified
information was leaked,
so I'm not surprised
that he didn't trust us.
-In other words, he was
waiting for the task force
to get narrowed down to
only those investigators he
could trust.
And to do that, he
needed to weed out
anyone who wasn't
totally committed.
-Hm.
--[frustrated sigh] If
we're working with that guy
I'm leaving the task force.
You don't have to worry.
I won't try to follow you.
I'm not interested in finding L.
-Well, I think we
can trust L, so I'd
be willing to cooperate with
him on this investigation.
-Count me in.
L (OVER COMM): I'm staying
in a suite at the Teito Hotel
at the moment, but I'll be
switching hotels every few days
from this point on.
I want you to think
of these hotel rooms
as the de facto headquarters
of this investigation.
If this arrangement is
acceptable to all of you,
then split into two groups
and stagger your arrivals
so you come 30 minutes apart.
Please arrange it so you're
all here at midnight.
L (VOICEOVER): Kira.
It seems we're getting closer
to each other in equal steps.
It's only a matter of
time before we collide.
So be it.
I'm ready to show my face.
I'll make my first
public appearance
as L. If you ever
manage to find out
about these secret
meetings, I'm sure you'd
feel compelled to move in.
That's what I'm counting on.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
I've been quite active
over these last few days.
Think carefully.
Was there anything I missed?
And what comes next?
There are endless possibilities.
The real battle is
only just beginning, L.
[knock]
L: It's unlocked.
Please let yourselves in.
-Mm.
[music - nightmare, "alumina"]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): This woman,
If she had spoken to the police
before I met her--
but it seems there's
a god on my side after all,
and not just a god of death.