[theme music]
MELLO: What was that?
Roger?
What did you just say?
-I'm afraid L is dead.
-He's dead?
But-- But how?
Was it Kira?
Did Kira kill him?
Come on, Roger.
You've got to tell me!
-ROGER: Probably.
-But he promised me he'd
find Kira and execute him,
and now you're telling
me that he's been killed.
-Mello!
NEAR: If you can't win the game,
if you can't solve the puzzle,
then you're just a loser.
-So, which of us did L pick?
Me or Near?
-He hadn't chosen yet.
And now that he's gone, I'm
afraid he won't be able to.
Mello.
Listen.
You two Near.
Can't the two of
you work together?
-All right.
Sounds good.
MELLO: It'll never work, Roger.
We can't do this together.
You know I don't get
along with the Near.
We've always competed
against each other.
Always.
You know what?
It's fine.
Near should be the one to
succeed L. He's not like me.
He never gets emotional.
He just uses his head, like
it's a game or a puzzle.
And as for me, I'm
leaving this institution.
-Wait, Mello!
MELLO: Don't waste your breath.
I'm almost 15 years old.
It's time I started
living my own life.
NEAR: A police
officer who happened
to be nearby during
Higuchi's arrest overhead
him talking about a notebook.
If you write a person's name
in it with their face in mind,
that person will die.
-So that's what you're
saying this notebook of death
actually is.
-That's right.
At this point, the
Japanese police
should have it in
their possession.
Mr. President, the
current L is a fake.
He was created by
the Japanese police
to avoid confusion and
panic amongst the various
international police agencies.
The reak L is dead.
-Uh, Director Mason.
This boy, who is he?
-Sir.
Near is-- Well, in a
sense you could call him
the true successor to L.
MAN: But still, it's
impossible for us
to censor everything
on the internet.
And we haven't had any
new leads in a while.
-But posting names
and faces online?
I'm sorry, but if
you ask me, it's
the people doing that
who deserve to die.
But I guess that's
never gonna happen.
Kira gets a lot of his
information from the internet,
so he's not gonna
kill those people.
-Matsu, you silly.
You've got it all backwards.
-Still.
I can imagine how
some people must feel.
To them, the world's
become a good place
for people who don't
commit any crimes,
or rather, it's a good
place for innocent people
who lead good lives.
-Look who's talking.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
It's more than that.
Soon, everyone in the
world will think that way.
-Are you all still talking
about that Kira business?
Please, give it a rest
for one afternoon, dear.
Light, you too.
SAYU: I'm home.
-Hey, how's it going?
-We were just having tea.
-Oh Light, Misa.
Seems like it's been
forever, you two.
Missed you guys.
-Aw, we missed you too!
-And you must be
Mr. Matsuda, right?
-That's me.
-Wow, it's been a long time.
Thank you for always taking
such good care of my father.
-Gee, Sayu.
You're all grown up.
And pretty.
Last time I saw you,
you were this big.
-Matsu!
Your face is going bright red!
-It is?
I mean, no way!
-Well, you can forget it.
I'll never let Sayu marry a cop.
-Huh?
-Yes.
That's right.
I'd never want that
for my daughter.
-Really?
Aw man.
I never got the chance
to propose or even
tell her I like her.
You're too cruel
to me, mom and dad.
-Mom?
-Anyway.
I think you'd be a good
catch, Mr. Matsuda.
-What?
Y-- You really think so, Sayu?
-Yep!
In fact, I was thinking if
you were a little younger,
I might've considered going
out with you some time.
-Guess my little sister's
all grown up, isn't she?
MISA: No kidding.
She's already way more
mature than Matsu.
But of course, Light
hasn't changed one bit.
You're just as wonderful
and handsome as when I first
met you!
-You've already got a
career and everything.
Make it official.
You should stop living
together secretly
and just get married already.
-I think that's a great idea.
RYUK (VOICEOVER): A
heartwarming scene
from most unfortunate
family in the world.
[cell phone ringing]
-Hm?
Yes?
What is it, Aizawa?
Yes.
Right.
OK.
We have to go.
Matsuda, Light.
Come with me.
LIGHT: A kidnapping?
Involving who?
-They got Director
Takimura of the NPA.
I'm not sure who's behind it.
-Ah, damn it.
As if we don't have
enough on our plate
already with the Kira case.
CHIEF YAGAMI: Are
you sure about this?
-Unfortunately, yeah.
We got the call at 6:12.
That was about 45 minutes ago.
In the meantime, we
were able to confirm
that the call originated from
the director's cell phone.
-Did the kidnappers make any
demands in terms of ransom?
-They did.
They want a trade.
The director for the notebook.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Who's behind this?
And for what reason?
-Do you think it's Kira?
-Maybe not.
If the existence of the
notebook has been leaked,
there could be any
number of people
who'd want it for themselves.
-But hang on.
Dad, did you say anything to
the director about the notebook?
We all agreed to keep the
information between the six
of us.
So, he didn't know it, did he?
-I never told the
director, so he
couldn't tell the
kidnappers anything.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Someone
knows about the Death Note.
And beyond that, they know that
the Japanese police have it.
And now they've come to
claim it for themselves.
-Notify every bureau in
the police department,
but only about the
kidnapping itself.
-Got it.
[beeping]
-Has there been a call
from the suspects?
MAN (ON PHONE): No.
There's a visitor here who wants
to meet with Director Takimura.
-What?
-My name is John McEnroe.
I'm an agent with the FBI.
Of course, this
is just an alias.
As my assignment involves Kira,
it's a necessary precaution.
-Kira?
Due to unforseen circumstances,
the director is unavailable.
If it's acceptable, you
could speak with me instead.
-Very well.
That's fine.
Pardon me, I'll get
straight to the point.
The Japanese police have proven
themselves to be unreliable.
So in order to
solve the Kira case,
we want you to hand
over the notebook to us.
-So the FBI was behind it!
Where did you take the director?
-What are you talking about?
-Don't act like you don't know.
This is a serious
criminal offense.
MAN: What would the
FBI gain by capturing
the director of
the Japanese NPA?
CHIEF YAGAMI (ON
RADIO): Then how
do you know about the notebook?
-What the hell is going on?
-By the sound of
things, it seems
that the director of the
Japanese police force
has been kidnapped by someone.
Specifically, someone
who wants the notebook.
All right, Commander Rester.
Pass on this message
through our agent.
Suggest to the
Japanese police that
would like to assist them
in rescuing the director,
and apprehending the culprits.
We'll take the notebook once
we have the opportunity.
-Roger that.
Attention.
This is headquarters.
We have new orders for you.
[groan]
-Has he decided to
say anything yet?
-He told us the Japanese police
have begun to wimp out on Kira.
Looks like right
now, the only ones
who are officially working
for L are Suichiro Yagami,
Konzo Mogi, and Tota Matsuda.
Isn't that right?
-Yeah.
There was also Kida, but
he was killed by Kira.
-Right.
And as top cop,
somehow you didn't
know that this notebook even
existed, or that you had it.
[laughter]
-Japanese cops must be a joke.
-Of all the investigators
on the task force,
Deputy Director Yagami would
be the highest ranking, right?
-Yeah.
-My theory is that there
are two notebooks out there.
One of them is in
Kira's possession,
the other is with the NPA.
We're going to
take both of them.
-Huh?
-Don't worry.
As long as we do what Mello
says, there'll be no mistakes.
It's been a year and a
half since he joined us,
and in that entire
time, he's never
been wrong about everything.
-Yeah, but that's
what's so weird.
If he was able to bring us
the head of a mafia boss
that even Kira himself
couldn't kill, why the hell
would he even need the
notebook to begin with?
-It's not just the
nobebook I'm after.
I want to eliminate
my competition.
I will be the best.
I don't care what it takes.
I'll beat Near by
any means necessary.
-Boss!
-Shut up.
Can't you see that I'm busy?
-I'm sorry.
But Eddie and I were
talking for a minute,
and it looks like Takimura hung
himself with his tie somehow.
-What's wrong with you?
Just great.
What are we supposed to
do with a dead hostage?
-No.
This will be just fine.
-Huh?
-(VOICEOVER) If Kira is
responsible for this,
we know he can't touch us
since he doesn't know our names
or faces.
That's why he went
after Takimura instead.
That means Kira is someone who
knows about the kidnapping.
That should make things
rather interesting.
-So what are we gonna do, Mello?
-I'll tell you what
we're going to do.
We're going to kidnap Soichiro
Yagami's daughter, Sayu Yagami.
-We still haven't been
able to find any leads
on either Director
Takimura or the kidnappers.
-Things are getting
pretty weird.
I mean, they should
have contacted us by now
with further demands,
but still nothing.
-We know one thing.
I found out the real name of
the FBI agent, John McEnroe.
According to his
personnel file, he's
actually called Larry Connors.
-Well, that's good to know.
-He's also a genuine agent.
His background and
credentials check out.
On top of that, the
director of the FBI
has offered to help us
rescue Director Takimura.
I'm pretty sure we'll
be able to trust them.
LIGHT: (VOICEOVER) But the
director should already
be dead by now.
Why haven't the
kidnappers said anything?
Are they gonna
give up on the deal
just because they lost
their bargaining chip?
I didn't think our opponents
would be such pushovers.
Remember, Dad, and
the rest of you, too.
We're going to have to
be extremely careful.
The director might not have
known about the notebook,
but he does know
who was originally
working with L. It's
possible the kidnappers might
come after us.
-Hey, Light?
-Huh?
-I'll be a good girl and
go to bed by myself, OK?
-Uh--
LIGHT: Yeah.
Goodnight.
-Goodnight, everyone.
-Guess I'll hang
out around here.
-It just occurred to me, we're
not the only ones in danger
here.
Our families are at risk.
[phone ringing]
-A call from the
Director's cellphone.
It must be the kidnappers.
Quick, Aizawa.
Got it.
Tracing.
[phone ringing]
-This is Yagami.
MELLO (ON PHONE): Look.
About trading the director
in exchange for the notebook?
The deal's been canceled.
Takimura is dead.
CHIEF YAGAMI: You bastards!
What did you do?
MELLO (ON PHONE): It's
only canceled, though,
regarding the director.
The new deal is this.
The notebook for Sayu Yagami.
-Huh?
MELLO (ON PHONE):
Seeing as you're
the Deputy Director of
the Japanese police,
it would be stupid to ask
you not to call the cops.
But you had better handle this
on your own, without backup.
If I see the police
making any big movements
in the next little
while, I'll kill
your daughter That's right.
Just as easily as we
killed the director.
I'll send you a photo
of Takimura's corpse,
to prove I mean business.
Take a good look.
I'll contact you tomorrow.
-Huh?
Wait!
-(VOICEOVER) Damn, they got me.
They used the director's
death as an opportunity
to get to Sayu.
[laughter]
-Looks like things are
getting interesting again.
-Sir, I-- I can't believe
they'd go this far.
-Damn them.
[phone ringing]
MRS. YAGAMI: Yes, yes.
Coming.
Darling?
You usually never call
from your work phone.
Is something the matter?
Huh?
Sayu?
I don't know.
Now that you mention it,
she is late coming home.
-Sayu.
[buzzing]
-Dad-- are you OK?
I've just realized something.
I think it was Kira who
killed the director.
Not the kidnappers.
-Huh?
-He probably did it because
he doesn't want the notebook
to fall into the wrong hands.
Kira claims to be justice.
He wouldn't want the notebook
used by someone evil.
If he killed the
director, then it's
reasonable to assume he has
ways of obtaining information
from within the police force.
That means we should be the
ones who investigate this.
We leave the police
out of it Otherwise--
-Kira will find out about it,
and probably kill the hostage.
-Right.
And we can't take that chance.
[laughter]
-Near.
We've just received a
report that the director
of the Japanese Police
Agency has been killed.
-I see By whom?
-By whom?
-Uh, the kidnappers, of course.
Who else?
-It'd be interesting if
it turned out to be Kira.
-Hm?
NEAR: That's a very good point.
The police won't be
trading their notebook
if the hostage is dead, so
it protect Kira's interests.
And if it is in fact
Kira, that can narrow down
our list of suspects
significantly
-Hm?
-By the way, Commander
Rester, have you
been able to determine
his whereabouts yet?
-Not yet.
We were able to confirm that
he left the institution four
years ago, but
nothing beyond that.
-Very well That clinches it
-What?
-Mello, you never change.
You always overlook the
most important things
because you let your emotions
get the better of you.
Or perhaps you're not even
involved in this case.
How could you leave your
photo behind at the orphanage?
[phone ringing]
CHIEF YAGAMI: This is Yagami.
MELLO (ON PHONE): Your
daughter has finally arrived.
It's about time.
-What do you mean?
MELLO (ON PHONE): You already
have a pretty good idea
of where we are, don't you?
-Hm.
-We'll make the exchange here.
Come to LA, by
yourself, in two days.
And of course, bring
the notebook with you.
-I won't make the trade unless
I'm sure my daughter's safe.
I want to talk to her right now.
MELLO (ON PHONE):
How about this?
I'll send you another photo.
That should satisfy you.
[beeping]
[phone ringing]
-Sayu.
-Hey Chief, we've narrowed the
call down to 5th Street in LA.
-I just checked
out the show that
was playing in the
background, and it's
being broadcast right now
on a local LA station.
They must have shown us that
so we know the photo's recent.
-Thank goodness.
At least we know
she's still alive.
That's reassuring.
-I'm taking the
notebook to Los Angeles.
It's my decision, both as Deputy
Director of the Japanese Police
Force, and as Sayu
Yagami's father.
I'll take full responsibility
for the consequences.
That's my final word.
-Wait, Dad.
Before we do anything, we
have to come up with a plan.
-He's right, Chief.
We can't rush in.
-But I have to be
in LA in two days.
We don't have time.
-So what you're telling me is
that Kira killed Takimura, not
the kidnappers?
-I'm simply putting it
forward as a possibility.
If it does turn out
to be true, then it
means Kira must be
getting his information
from the Japanese police.
-Hm.
[phone ringing]
-Hm?
Yes?
LIGHT (VOICE
SCRAMBLED): This is L.
-Hm?
I don't believe it.
It's L.
-I've already heard what
investigator John McEnroe,
or rather, Larry Connors has
had to say to Deputy Director
Yagami in regards to the
notebook and the Kira case.
Will you help us with
the investigation
into NPA Director
Takimura's murder?
-I see.
Well--
-Pass me the phone.
-Huh?
-I'm pleased to meet you
at last, L number two.
-Number two?
What do you mean by that?
Who is this?
-There's really no point
in trying to hide it.
We are a new organization
known as the SPK,
or Special Provision for Kira.
It was established to
find and capture Kira
without the help of L.
(MODIFIED VOICE) Furthermore,
seven of our top members
already know of L's death.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): They do?
Where'd they hear that?
Who the hell told them?
-As for myself, I am at
the center of the SPK.
You can address me as N.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): N?
Who is this guy?
Is he joking?
But, this strange feeling.
What is it?
[theme music]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Damn.
What's going on?
I've already checked
today's flight crews.
No one on board was suspicious.
I can still make it.
But at this rate, is my
only option to kill Sayu?