[theme music]
[music playing]
REM (VOICEOVER):
You will continue
to kill criminals whose
names are broadcast.
Outside of that,
you're free to use
the Death Note however you wish.
That's the only condition.
If everything happens
as Light Yagami planned.
This should help save Misa.
Do as I say and you'll
get what you want.
In the end it works out
well for both of us.
I suppose for someone
in your position
you'd call this good business.
NARRATOR: Mister Yagami,
are you all right?
There's no reason for you to
keep doing this to yourself.
YAGAMI (VOICEOVER):
It's been over a month
since Kira started
killing criminals again.
And as far as I'm
concerned, that's
all the proof I need to be
sure that my son isn't Kira.
So then all that's left
is for you to be sure.
One way or another,
when I get out of here,
it will be with my son.
-Wow, the Chief can
be pretty stubborn.
-Light, how are you
feeling right now?
-I'm OK.
Ryuzaki, I know that in the
time I've been in prison,
no new criminals have died.
However that suggests
to me that Kira
must be someone who's intimately
familiar with my situation.
And if that's the case--
-No, Light.
The reason criminals
have stopped
dying is because you are Kira.
-No, I'm not Kira!
How many times do
I have to say it?
L (VOICEOVER): If
Light were Kira,
he'd know that I was bluffing,
so why is he getting so upset?
He honestly seems clueless.
-This is just cruel.
I don't care if he is a suspect.
Light still has a right
to know that criminals
are being killed again.
-Amane?
-Yes?
-Are you OK?
You seem tired.
-Is that supposed to be funny?
How were you
expecting me to look
after being tied up and
questioned for this many days.
-Hm.
That's true.
-Please just let me go.
I want to see Light.
Please?
Light?
Let me.
-I'm not sure how much more
of this the three of them
can take.
-Ryuzaki, you have no reason to
keep Light locked up anymore.
Do the right thing
and let him go.
Then we can get
the Chief out too.
Criminals are
still being killed,
even though Misa
and Light haven't
access to any of
that information.
We know that much already,
so what are you waiting for?
-Not true.
All we really know
at this point is
that Amane harbors an
unnaturally strong devotion
for Light Yagami.
-Ryuzaki, I'm sorry, but
with all due respect,
from where I'm
standing, it's starting
to look like you're only doing
this because you don't want
to admit that you were
wrong about Light.
-Yes, I figured you'd say that.
-OK, fine.
But we do know that Kira killed
Lind L. Tailor and those FBI
agents, right?
As Light said, if
Kira could kill while
under surveillance and
without access to information,
there would have been no need.
If they didn't pose
a threat to him,
then why would he
bother killing them?
Kira doesn't kill
without good reason,
I've heard you say so yourself
on more than one occasion.
-Oh, I see.
If he was able to kill
under these circumstances,
then he wouldn't have been
concerned about those FBI
agents in the first place.
-It's already been 50 days.
There's no point
to this anymore.
-Ryuzaki, it's time to start
looking for the real killer.
[music playing]
-Yes, I understand.
L (VOICEOVER): Mr. Yagami?
-Yes, what is it?
L (VOICEOVER): Would
you be willing to come
to headquarters, just once?
I'd like to discuss
my thoughts with you,
but it must be done in person.
However, above all else,
I need to talk to you
as Light's father.
-All right.
I'll come.
[music playing]
-Honestly, all this time
I never pictured you
as an old man, Mr. Stalker.
-I am not your stalker, I'm
a detective with the MPA.
-What?
Hey, wait.
I remember now.
You told me I was being
arrested for being arrested
for being the second Kira.
You mean that was for real?
No.
You're a stalker.
There's no way the police
would blindfold me and tie me
up all fetishy like that.
Anyways, it's kind of weird that
you have my hands and feet all
tied up, even though you're
planning to let me go.
-Please, just keep quiet.
[music playing]
-Light!
-Misa?
-Oh, I missed you
so much, Light.
-Dad, tell me.
What's all this about?
-He's your dad?
Oh my God, I totally
called your dad a stalker
and said he was old and all
kinds of other rude stuff.
Pleased to meet you.
My name's Misa Amane,
I'm Light's girlfriend
and I'd like to--
-They're all yours, Cheif.
-Let's go.
Get in the car.
-I was starting to think
I'd never get out there.
But it feels good to
finally be cleared.
-No.
I'm afraid you two are being
taken to your execution.
I wanted to be the one to escort
you to the execution site.
It was secretly built in
an underground facility
not far from here.
-What?
-Execution?
-Is this a joke?
-What the hell are
you talking about?
-We didn't do anything!
-L is convinced that
you are Kira, Light.
And that Misa Amane
is the second Kira.
Here he is convinced
that the only way
we can prevent the murders
is to execute the two of you.
-I don't understand.
The killings have
already stopped.
-No, they never stopped.
-They never-- That's
not what he told me.
So he was lying?
-L was trying to get a
confession out of you, Light.
He would have said anything.
But at this point,
that's not the problem.
It's political now.
You see, L's suggestion
that the killings would
stop if you two were
eliminated was unanimously
accepted by top officials in the
UN and the Japanese government.
They want Kira to disappear.
No trial, no publicity.
-But that's completely insane.
Please, dad.
I'm not Kira.
-That's right.
What kind of a father
are you, anyway?
This is your own son
you're talking about.
-L made this decision, not me.
And his word is absolute.
Over the years he's tackled
the most difficult cases,
solving all of them.
He's never been wrong.
-You trust L more than you
trust me, your own son?
-L went so far as to stake
his life on this theory.
If the killings don't stop,
then he, too, will be executed.
-L said that?
What could he be thinking?
I know that given
the material evidence
this might seem like the
only logical solution.
But he's making a mistake.
How could L come
to this conclusion?
Something's not right here.
It's just, it's
not like L at all.
The L I know would
rely on hard evidence.
He has to have the truth.
Is he really trying
to end it like this?
-All right, we're almost there.
[car engine]
-Where are we right now,
and why did you bring us out
to the middle of nowhere?
What is this?
-Wait a sec.
I bet he brought us
out here to let us go.
-This will do.
It looks like there's nobody
around to see us out here.
I decided it would be better
for us if I brought you here,
instead of the execution site.
Listen to me.
I'm going to kill you
here, and then kill myself.
-What?
What are you talking about, dad?
You can't, that's crazy!
-How can you say that?
You'd kill your only son for L?
If you want to die so bad,
why don't you kill yourself?
If you do this, you're
not different than Kira.
-I'm nothing like Kira.
I am bound by my
responsibilities as a parent,
and as Chief of the MPA.
-Dad, come on.
She's right.
Think about it.
If we die here, the truth
will never be revealed.
Please dad, you have
to let us escape.
-It's too late.
Either way, you
will be executed.
At least with this, I'll
be the one to do it.
-Please, stop dad!
I'm not Kira!
If I die here, Kira wins.
Can't you see?
-Amane, I'm going to
die here with my son.
But I have no
reason to kill you.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
It's only a matter of
time before the police
locate this car.
Then they'll transport
you to the original site,
and execute you there.
Light, my son.
From murderer to another,
I'll see you in hell.
-No, dad!
-No, stop it!
[gunshot]
-Light, my son.
From one murderer to another,
I'll see you in hell.
-No, dad!
[gunshot]
[gasping]
-You used a blank?
-Thank goodness.
-Thank goodness?
What's going on?
I don't understand.
-Please, forgive me, you two.
I know that was
hard on you, but it
was the only way I could
get you out of prison.
You must understand.
I only agreed to
do this because I
believe in your
innocence, Light.
Were you watching, Ryuzaki?
I did exactly as you said.
And as you can see,
I'm still alive.
L (VOICEOVER): Yes, it was
a convincing performance.
If Amane were the
second Kira, who
only need to see a
person's face to kill them,
there is no doubt you
would have killed you
before you had the chance
to fire your weapon.
Also, if Light was in
fact Kira, the Kira I know
wouldn't hesitate to kill even
his own father to save himself.
With Light in particular I
cannot rule out the possibility
that he may have seen through
our act at some point.
However, as we agreed, I
will end their confinement
immediately.
And as we discussed, Amane
will remain under surveillance
until Kira is apprehended.
Although she insists the
tapes we found were just
occult videos, the
physical evidence
we have, plus her confession,
suggest otherwise.
-Hey, no fair!
You still suspect me?
-If I were you, I
wouldn't complain.
You get to go back
to your normal life.
Organisms the surveillance
shouldn't be a threat to you.
Think of it as complimentary
police protection.
-Oh, I get it.
Since I'm not the
second Kira, it'll
be kind of like having my
very own private bodyguards.
L (VOICEOVER): As for your
part in this agreement, Light.
You and I will be together 24/7.
And that's how we'll remain
until we've brought Kira
to justice.
[music playing]
-Fine by me.
We'll catch Kira.
Together.
L (VOICEOVER): Yes, I look
forward to working with you.
-Are you sure this is
necessary, Ryuzaki?
-This is as difficult
for me as it is for you.
-So is this what you
meant by being together
24 hours a day with him?
Looking at you, I never
would have guessed.
Are you on that side
of the fence, Ryuzaki?
-I told you, I'm not doing
this because I want to, OK?
-But Light belongs to me.
I don't want to
share him with you.
If you're with
him 24/7, then how
are we supposed to
go on dates together?
-Oh, you can still go on dates.
But it will have to
be the three of us.
-No way.
Are you telling me we have
to kiss in front of you,
and stuff?
-I'm not telling
you to do anything.
But yes, I suppose
I would be watching.
-That's so gross.
You really are a
pervert, aren't you?
-Light, please make
Misa stop talking now.
-Listen, Misa, that's enough.
The police have
already established
that it was you who
sent those tapes,
so you're lucky to
even be here right now.
They have every right
to keep you in prison.
-Huh?
How could you even
say that, Light?
In case you forgot,
I'm your girlfriend.
Don't you trust
your own soul mate?
-What do you mean, soul mate?
You're the one who said
you fell in love with me
at first sight, Misa.
-Huh?
So why would you kiss me if you
didn't have feelings for me?
You took advantage of me?
Stupid!
-About this love
at first sight, it
happened in Oyama on
May 22nd, didn't it?
-So what?
-Why did you choose
that day to go to Oyama?
And do you remember
what you wore?
-It's like I told you.
I just happened to go there.
I don't know why, I don't
remember how I felt,
and I don't even know
what I was wearing.
Anyway, since when do I need
a reason to hang out in Oyama,
huh?
-And somehow, when you
came back from Oyama,
you knew you that you were
in love with some guy,
and that his name was Light.
-Yes.
-And yet you yourself
have no idea how
you came to know his name.
-Yeah, so what?
-Tell me, what if
light was Kira?
How would it make you feel?
-Huh?
How would I feel
if Light was Kira?
-That's right.
-That'd be wonderful.
I mean, I've always been
grateful to Kira for punishing
the men who murdered my
parents, so if I found out
that Light was actually Kira?
That would be like
a bonus for me.
If anything, it would make
me love him even more.
Even though it's like,
practically impossible
to love him more
than I already do.
-It's Kira, though.
You'd love him
even more for that?
I mean, wouldn't you be afraid?
What if he tried to kill you?
-You're talking about
Light being Kira?
He wouldn't be scary at all.
I'm a supporter of Kira, so if I
found out my Light was actually
him, I'd think of how
I could be helpful.
-That's very generous
of you, but I'm
pretty sure Kira
doesn't your help.
Well, Misa, based on
what you just told me,
there can be no mistake that
you are the second Kira.
But you've made it so painfully
obvious that I don't really
want to believe it.
-Whatever.
It's not believable, because
I'm not the second Kira, OK?
-Anyway, for the
time being, you'll
remain under surveillance.
When you do go out,
if needed, you'll
be able to contact us using
this room's extension.
For the most, your life
will return to normal.
But from now on, for all private
and work related affairs,
Mr. Matsuda will
be accompanying you
as your new manager, Matsui.
-Matsui here!
-Your agency's been
paid to keep quiet,
and the police don't know.
Don't blow his cover.
-This old guy's my manager?
Oh you can't be serious.
-Oh, come on!
What's wrong with me, Misa Misa?
Is it the tie?
Because I can get a--
-Would you cut it out with
all this dating, kissing,
and Misa Misa talk all ready?
This is the Kida investigation.
Stop messing around.
-Sorry about that, Ayuzawa.
-No, it's all right.
I just figured out
what the problem is.
Misa Amane, it's time for
you to go to your room.
-Why?
-Out you go!
-Don't, no!
Hey Light, let's go on a date,
even if it is the three of us.
-So Light, are you
serious about her?
-No way.
Like I told you earlier,
it's completely one-sided.
-Then could you at least
pretend to be serious,
for the sake of
the investigation?
There are two things I
know about Amane for sure.
One, that she's
involved in this.
Two, she's in love with you.
-You want me to become
intimate with her
to gather information
about the second Kira?
-Yes, I think you could
do it without arousing
her suspicions.
And Amane would definitely
be a valuable source
of information for us.
Not to mention this
is the main reason why
I agreed to release
the two of you.
-Ryuzaki, as much as I want
to help you, and as important
as the Kira cases
is to me, I can't
manipulate a woman's
feelings like that.
Please try to understand.
To me, exploiting other person's
feelings for personal gain
is unforgivable, and I won't
allow myself to stoop that low.
L (VOICEOVER): There's something
wrong with this picture.
It's as if he's a
different person now.
Is it possible this is an act?
If this is genuine,
it not only implies
that Amane was being controlled
by Kira, by Light Yagami, too.
-What's wrong, Ryuzaki?
-Nothing.
I suppose you're
right after all.
However, considering Misa
will have a lot of contact
with the public,
it would be helpful
if you could make sure she
doesn't leak information.
-By the way, do you
think we could come up
with some kind of alternative
to this system of moving
from hotel to hotel
every few days?
-Yes.
In fact, I had that very
same thought some time ago.
And so I arranged for
a facility to be built.
Construction started right
after my first meeting
with Mr. Yagami and the others.
It should be finished
in a few days.
Where is it?
Here it is.
23 floors above
ground, and 2 below.
Although it's impossible
to see it from the outside,
there are two helicopters
hidden on the roof.
-What?
That's amazing.
-Ideally I want all of
us to spend as much time
here as possible.
If the investigation
team grows, we
can accommodate up to 60 people.
Misa shouldn't have
any complaints.
And she'll have her own floor.
-This is truly impressive.
But to go to such lengths.
-Hold on a second.
Where did you find the
finances to build this thing?
-As you can see,
it is my intention
to solve this case, no
matter what it takes.
That's how it is.
-I'm sorry, but how
is that an answer?
-No, he's right.
The mass killings are
bad enough already.
But personally, I will never
forgive Kira for putting my dad
and I thought this.
I want to solve this,
no matter what it takes.
-If you're serious
about that, you
should try to get close
to Misa and find out
about the second book.
-I can't.
That goes against my principles.
-Right.
You said that.
And what a shame.
-Hm?
-Nothing.
I'm just feeling really
motivated right now, Chief.
Ryuzaki, Chief Yagami,
Light, let's get out of here
and bring Kira to justice.
-Excuse me, I couldn't help
but notice you missed my name.
[traffic sounds]
-Well.
This looks like all of us.
Let's get started, shall we?
We're all here to further the
growth of the of the Yotsuba
group by reducing competition.
So the question is,
who is going to die?
-I'm not thrilled that wee have
to do this every single week.
This may be irrelevant,
but I have to wonder,
what prompted Kira to start
killing business people,
in addition to the usual
criminals and such?
-Come on now, haven't
you figured this out yet,
Takahashi?
-Hm?
-This is the most advantageous
course of action for Kira.
-Advantageous?
He's basically started a
killing service, Higuchi.
-You have a lot to say,
considering how stupid you are.
I'd hate to see you get
killed because of it.
-Despite the fact that we're
all relatively young, all of us
are now front-runners to
become Yotsuba's next CEO.
Not to mention, our
salaries have virtually
eclipsed those of the other
employees in the company.
-It's unlikely he would choose
to back a particular company,
no matter how you look at it.
One of the people in
this room has to be Kira.
-So, back to business.
Does anyone have a proposal?
Who should we have Kira
eliminate this week, gentleman?
-Human beings are truly
disgusting creatures.
[theme music]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): It's no good.
It's obvious from
thee way you talk
that you won't be satisfied
until I'm convicted as Kira.
Stop this, Ryuzaki!