[theme music]
[music playing]
MALE SPEAKER: Near,
it's all taken care of.
I did exactly as you asked.
NEAR: Good.
-T, that is all I have
to tell you today.
We'll talk soon.
-Very well, I understand.
I also have a message for you.
FEMALE SPEAKER: Yes?
What is it?
-I've confirmed it.
[gasp]
[text alert]
-Hm?
-You got a text?
Oh, it says she
wants to see you.
Man, I'm so jealous.
Huh?
L (VOICEOVER) : I've done it.
That's the sign of
confirmation from Mikami.
Now all I have to do is
wait for Near to request
a meeting face to face.
Game over, Near.
I win.
I knew what your move would
be from the very beginning.
-(ON RADIO) Sir,
this is Giovanni.
I've been checking the Notebook
regularly as you ordered.
For the past three days,
he's continued filling out
one page every night, after
midnight, as he usually does.
The victims still
match up, and there's
been no change in Mikami's
behavior otherwise.
-I understand.
Well, then let's begin.
[clock ticking]
-Oh!
It's Near.
-She called.
NEAR (ON TELEPHONE): L?
-Yes, this is L.
What is it, Near?
NEAR (ON TELEPHONE):
I want to meet you.
-What?
NEAR (ON TELEPHONE):
There's something
I must show you pertaining
to the Kira case.
-But don't you suspect
me of being Kira?
Do you really think it's wise
to reveal your face to me?
NEAR (ON TELEPHONE):
That's true.
I cannot show you
unless I reveal my face.
Furthermore, the very
act of showing my face
will prove something.
And that will bring
this case to a close.
-All right, fine.
As far as I'm
concerned, the sooner
you realize you're wrong
about me, the better.
MALE SPEAKER
(VOICEOVER): The time
has finally come for Near
to prove that Light is Kira.
But on the other
hand, if that's true,
this will be a chance
for Light to kill Near.
It all comes down to this.
NEAR (ON TELEPHONE):
I'd like to lay out
some ground rules
for the meeting.
-We're willing to go along
with whatever you want.
-First, I want to have all the
investigators from both teams
be present.
In other words, everyone
who is chasing after Kira
should be gathered together
to take part in the meeting.
L (ON TELEPHONE): I understand.
That's not a problem.
NEAR: As I mentioned
before, there
are a total of four
members in the SPK.
That's including myself.
All of us will be there.
Besides our team,
we'll also bring
along Mr. Mogi, who is
currently staying with us.
As for Misa Amane, she will be
released right before we meet.
She'll not be told
where we're going.
You can come and
meet us once you
confirm that she's
been safely released.
Is that acceptable?
-What do we do?
-Hmm.
-OK, Near.
I understand.
I have a team of
five investigators,
including myself.
Of course, Mogi's with
you at the moment.
So aside from me, they'll
there'll be only three people.
-Very well, that's fine.
Now, as for our meeting
place-- Daikoku Wharf.
There's a warehouse on the
outskirts of the southeast side
that's been abandoned
for some time.
It's known as the Yellow Box.
I've already taken the
liberty of purchasing it.
If this arrangement is fine
with you, then we'll use it.
How about it, Light Yagami?
With a location
like this, you can
do what you're planning to do.
One more thing-- This meeting
cannot take place unless I have
your word that someone
will bring the Notebook.
-Wait.
Why the Notebook?
-It's quite simple.
If your entire team
leaves HQ to meet me,
there will be no one left
behind to guard the Notebook.
I can promise you this-- I will
make no attempts to steal it.
In fact, I won't
even try to touch it.
As long as Mr.
Aizawa can confirm
that it's the
genuine Notebook, I'm
willing to place my faith
in you and accept his word.
-Huh?
All right.
NEAR (ON TELEPHONE):
However, I do
insist that someone other
than L hold onto it.
My reasons for
making that request
should be fairly obvious to you.
-Right, I understand.
But I'll be the one who
decides who will hold onto it.
Does that sound fair?
NEAR (ON TELEPHONE):
Yes, of course.
Then all that's left to
arrange is the time and date.
-Right.
The question is.
What time?
-Mikami makes his
judgments after midnight.
He most likely receives
a notice in the morning
of which people to kill next.
If we take his movements
into consideration,
say, three days from
now on the 28th at 1 PM.
L (VOICEOVER): o'clock, huh?
That's the exact time
I expected him to pick.
Near is obviously aware
of Mikami's movements.
That's fine by me.
The time doesn't
really concern us.
-Well then, 1 o'clock,
three days from now.
L (ON TELEPHONE): Sure.
Near.
NEAR (VOICEOVER): Light Yagami.
BOTH (VOICEOVER): I know
exactly what your plan is,
and I am going to win.
-Kiyomi, I'm sorry, but I'm a
little busier than usual today.
-Oh, really?
Does that mean you can't
stay until morning?
-Yeah, I'm sorry.
Police are going to have their
hands for the next two or three
days.
-That's a shame.
Hm?
L (VOICEOVER): I've
already given orders
to both Mikami and
Takada about what to do.
This will be the final
order to kill Near.
[tires squealing]
[shouting]
FEMALE SPEAKER: Quick.
This way.
Are you all right?
FEMALE SPEAKER: Yes.
MALE SPEAKER:
They're getting away.
After them.
-We need to get inside NHN now.
-Don't do it--
take a look around.
It's not safe for her here.
Not even inside.
-Well--
-It's best if you get her
away from here right now.
Miss Takada, get on.
Now.
-It's OK, you'll
be safe with him.
Please, you have to go.
-Right.
-Team A and Team B,
stay on that bike's tail
and don't lose sight of them.
As for the rest of you, I need
you to find that assailant.
-All right, we've confirmed
Miss Takada's safety.
Let's get her into Car number 7.
-What the hell?
-No, he's taking her.
Damn it.
Stop, you idiot.
You can't do that.
What if it ends up hitting her?
-Wh-what are you doing?
-One of the attackers
was heavily armed.
As of this moment, both
Miss Takada's escort team
and the police are hot on
the tail of the suspects.
MALE SPEAKER: Oh, man.
This is really bad.
-Is it Near again?
L (VOICEOVER): Near.
You promised that we'd
meet in three days time.
What's the meaning of
making a move like this now?
It doesn't make sense.
No, this isn't Near's style.
It's more like--
MALE SPEAKER: It's Near.
[shouting]
-So those cars got
ahead of me, huh?
How many damn body guards
does one woman need, anyway?
Hey, come on, give me a break.
Since when were the
Japanese allowed
to carry around such big guns?
You got me.
I'm part of this whole
kidnapping incident.
That means you'll have a
lot of questions to ask.
You won't shoot.
-What an idiot.
He probably wouldn't have
told us anything, anyway.
And death is the only way to
pay for crimes against Kira.
FEMALE SPEAKER
(VOICEOVER): This man--
he's the person
that Light warned
me to be extra careful
of-- Mello Mihael Keehl.
[shivering]
-Take off everything
you're wearing
and put it all in that box.
Hurry up.
You can use this blanket.
NEAR (ON TELEPHONE): L, I am not
the one who kidnapped Takada.
-Is that so?
Then it has to be Mello.
-Yes, that's right.
And I have to be honest
with you on this--
we had one of our
members escorting Takada,
and they confirmed it-- Mello
was the one who abducted her.
I apologize for letting
this happen while one of us
was guarding her.
-Near, isn't there any way
for you to contact Mello?
NEAR (ON TELEPHONE):
No, I'm afraid that
would be impossible.
While I do have a method of
getting in touch with him,
there's no way he'd respond
in the current situation.
[sighs]
-B-before I take off
the rest, could I
please have the blanket so
I can wrap it around me?
-Whatever you want.
-Our latest report is
that the escort team
was forced to shoot one
of the perpetrators.
They are also still
making efforts
to track Miss
Takada's whereabouts.
-Were you able to
get a hold of her?
-Not yet.
Takada's phone has
been turned off.
Mello must have confiscated it.
Damn it.
I need to get in
touch with Takada.
With no way of getting a hold
of her, all I can do is wait.
-This is the only
thing that can be done.
If I don't do it--
MALE SPEAKER: As for the suspect
who was gunned down earlier,
we're still not able
to identify him.
The police are tracking
the remaining suspects
and are currently--
MALE SPEAKER: Matt.
I never thought you'd be killed.
I'm sorry.
[shivering]
[heavy breathing]
[telephone ringing]
-Light's cell phone.
-Could it be her?
-Quiet, everyone.
Hello?
TAKADA (ON TELEPHONE): Light?
I--
-Miss Takada?
Listen to me.
Are you all right?
The only reason she'd
be able to call me
like this without
getting caught is
if she had an opportunity
to get away from Mello.
Or--
TAKADA (ON TELEPHONE):
Light, Light, please save me.
-It's all right.
Calm down and answer
my questions, OK?
-Oh, OK.
LIGHT (ON TELEPHONE):
First, your location.
Do you know where you are?
TAKADA (ON TELEPHONE): N-no.
No, I don't know where I am.
I was put into a truck that
was locked from the outside.
But we were on
the freeway, and I
caught a glimpse
of the sign that
said we were heading to Nagano.
Right now, I think we're parked
inside of a building somewhere.
-Miss Takada, you are
Kira's spokesperson.
Do you remember
the conversation we
had when I told you that
there might be people who
would try to hurt
you because of that?
TAKADA (ON TELEPHONE):
Y-yes, I remember.
-We talked what you should
do if a situation like this
ever arose.
Do you remember that?
-Ah, I remember.
I did what you
told me to, Light.
I did it.
-Yes.
TAKADA (ON TELEPHONE):
I didn't struggle, even
when he stripped me naked.
I did exactly as you
said-- I made survival
my first priority,
and-- and, I did it.
Please, Light.
I did everything
that you told me to.
Come quickly.
Save me.
-Miss Takada, you remember what
I told you to do after that,
don't you?
-I have to do as many killings
as possible while I still can.
I-- I know, but-but Light--
-Can you do it?
[whimpering]
-I can do it.
[telephone disconnect]
[weeping]
-Aizawa, Ide, let's get going.
Matsuda, you stay here and
take care of headquarters.
-You got it.
[weeping]
TAKADA (ON TELEPHONE): It's me.
Send me as many names of
people to punish as you can.
Here's my email address.
-Yes, right.
I understand.
If Takada is calling
me like this,
it must mean that
she's been able to kill
her kidnappers, in which
case, the only certainty
is that she's in a situation
where she can't move.
Nakajima, I'm going to the scene
of the crime for this case.
-OK.
MALE SPEAKER: All right,
I got the location
by tracing the call.
Head to Karuizawa by freeway.
MALE SPEAKER: Karuizawa, huh?
Damn.
It'll take at least 30
minutes to get there.
MALE SPEAKER: Well, hurry.
This is Mello we're
talking about.
Who knows what he'll do?
-Got it.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
I don't believe
this-- Aizawa and Ide
are just too stupid.
They jumped the gun and
got in the front seats
without even thinking.
This is just too easy.
-Ah, no-- Mello.
-What the hell is this?
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Kiyomi Takada-- suicide.
January 26, 2013, 2:32 PM.
Burns to death by setting
fire to everything
around her-- including
everything she wrote on.
[theme music]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Looks like this
is the end-- no, more
like the beginning--
the perfect world of Kira.
And those who know of the
Notebook's existence--
all of them will die.