[theme music]
L: Greetings to all
of you at the ICPO.
I am L. Whether the guilty party
is an individual or a group,
there's a strong possibility
that they're Japanese.
LIND L. TAILOR (ON
TV): Kira, I've got
a pretty good idea what
your motivation might be,
and I can guess what
you hope to achieve.
However, what you're
doing right now is evil.
-You, you bastard.
L: Now, try to kill me.
-I am justice.
I protect the
innocent and those who
fear evil I'm the
one who will become
the god of a new world
that everyone desires.
L--
-Kira--
L AND LIGHT (IN UNISON):
I will hunt you down
wherever you're hiding,
and I will eliminate you.
-I am--
L AND LIGHT (IN
UNISON): Justice.
-All right.
Let's start with the
tip line reports.
-Yes, sir.
Up to this point, we've
received 3,029 responses
about the murders via
telephone and email.
Most of these have been curious
citizens and prank calls.
But there are 14 people who
claim to either know Kira,
or who have seen him.
All 14 accounts were followed
up on, and carefully documented.
However, nobody could
provide any information
that wasn't already
publicly available.
And lastly, this week, there
were an additional 21 people
who called in
claiming to be Kira.
We didn't want to
rule anything out,
so we followed
standard procedure,
and created files
for all 21 of them.
-Uh huh.
All right.
Onto the victim reports.
-Yes, sir.
Upon further
investigation, we have
confirmed that information
of the heart attack victims
was in fact publicly available
in Japan immediately prior
to their deaths.
Also, concerning L's
request that we investigate
the time of death
for each victim,
we found that all
of them occurred
between the hours of 4:00
PM and 2:00 AM on weekdays,
local time, with 68%
of them occurring
between 8:00 PM and 12:00 AM.
Weekends and holidays appear to
be the exception to this rule,
as the times of death vary much
more widely during the week.
L: That information is
extremely relevant for us.
It suggests that given
the times of death,
our suspect could very
well be a student.
-Hmm?
L: Based on the fact that Kira
is only killing criminals,
I think it's safe
to assume that he's
driven by very idealistic
notion of justice.
It's highly possible
he may even aspire
to be some sort of
god-like figure.
We're dealing with
an individual who
has a very childish
concept of right and wrong.
[whispering]
L: Of course, this is mere
speculation at this point.
But still, I recommend you
reexamine any assumptions
you've made as to whether or not
our suspect could be a student.
We must consider
every possibility.
I believe that is the shortest
route to defining and arresting
Kira.
Please, continue
with your report.
-Uh.
All right.
Does anyone else have
something they'd like to add?
-Uh, yes sir.
-What is it, Matsuda?
-Um, well I'm not saying
this to support Kira,
or to condone the murders,
but in the last few days
throughout the world, but
especially here in Japan,
we've observed a
dramatic decrease
in the number of violent
crimes committed.
Uh.
-Well, I suppose it makes sense.
We've suspected something
like that would happen.
Anything else?
-No.
-Well that about sums
up our report for today.
L?
L: Thank you, everyone.
I feel we're a one step
closer to finding Kira.
Before I go, I'm afraid I have
one additional request to make.
This is directed to
the teams investigating
the victims, TV
news, and internet.
I would like you to go
back and take a closer
look at the exact way in which
the victims' identities were
made public.
Be as thorough as possible.
In particular, I want to
know if photos of the victims
were made available to
the public in Japan.
I'll leave it to you.
-Chief.
-Mm?
-You look like you
could use one of these.
Sleepy much?
-Ah, thank you.
That'll do the trick.
I feel all these late nights
are starting to take their toll.
-About what I said
earlier at our meeting--
well, now that I think
about it, um, I'm
sure everyone already knew that.
I wanted to apologize.
-What on earth are
you talking about?
Nobody said it would be
easy to speak the truth,
but it has to be
done, especially when
it's something that
isn't easy to say.
-Huh?
-Having said that,
if you'd gone on
to say that we
should commend Kira
for doing such a great job
of reducing violent crime,
then yes, I might have had
a little problem with that.
-Oh no.
Uh, no, I wouldn't.
That would never happen.
-[laughing], I'm just kidding.
-I knew I could
count on you, Light.
-Hey.
So, do you think you're ready
to try a few on your own now?
-Huh?
Yeah.
I guess so.
[doorbell rings]
-Oh, sounds like Dad's home.
MOTHER: Welcome home, dear.
FATHER: Thank you.
-He's home really early today.
-Hey!
Why don't you at least try
the last problem by yourself?
-I will, but maybe after dinner.
-Yeah, right.
-Helping your sister
with her homework.
You sure are relaxed.
-Of course.
If the police try
to come after me,
I'm pretty confident
I've got something
that'll give me the advantage.
Hey, glad you could
join us for dinner.
You hungry, Dad?
-Yeah.
It's been a long day.
So, Light.
Tell me, how are
your studies going?
-Hmm?
Everything's OK, I guess.
-Whatever.
He's at the top of his class.
My big brother's a genius.
-That's my son.
We're all proud of you, Light.
-Is everything OK, Dad?
You look tired.
-Yeah.
I'm not able to say
too much about it,
but this case I'm working
now is really tough.
-I see.
Well, well.
Daddy's a police man.
And that must be the reason
why you're so confident?
-That's right.
It's easy for me to hack
into Dad's computer.
We're on a home
network, so I can
copy the files I need
without leaving a trace.
This way, I can keep track
of their investigation.
There we go.
Hmm.
Well, isn't that interesting?
Looks like the
police are already
beginning to suspect a student.
--[laughing] I guess that
means you're in trouble.
-Hmm.
If the cause of death is written
within 40 seconds of writing
the person's name,
it will happen.
If the cause of death
is not specified,
the person will simply
die of a heart attack.
After writing the cause of
death, details of the death
should be written in the next
six minutes and 40 seconds.
That sound right to you, Ryuk?
-So what's your point?
-In other words, if
I write heart attack
as the cause of
death, then I should
be able to write down all
the details, including time
of death afterward, shouldn't I?
Looks like I'll be
able to provide you
with more entertainment now.
[groaning]
-Huh?
Inmate 148, what's wrong?
Snap out of it.
-What?
I-- I don't believe this.
Another 23 victims yesterday?
Are these confirmed?
-Yes.
-The day before, there
were another 23 victims.
He's killing one off
every hour, on the hour.
-Considering that this
new pattern has been going
on for two weekdays--
-It does punch some
holes in the theory
that our suspect is a student.
-Maybe not.
Anybody can skip
two days of school.
L: You're missing the point.
[gasping]
L: It does appear less likely
now that Kira's a student.
But that's not the message
he's sending by doing this.
Ask yourselves, why every hour?
And why are all these
victims in prisons
where they are sure to be
discovered immediately?
Why not other
criminals like before?
I believe Kira is telling
us that not only can he
kill from a distance,
but he can also
determine the time of death.
[whispering]
L: But, something's not right.
As soon as we began to suspect
that Kira might be a student,
the pacing of the
killings changed,
as if to contradict that theory.
Coincidence?
No.
Too convenient.
This can only mean that Kira has
access to police information.
It's obvious now.
This is a direct
challenge to me.
-I'd say L is probably starting
to sweat a little by now.
What'll really make
his job difficult
is that I've deliberately
left about 50 criminals
alive for times like this.
-Oh?
-If L's as good as
they say, by now
he should be starting
to suspect someone
with connections to the police.
L (VOICEOVER): So Kira has found
a way to obtain information
from the task
force headquarters.
This is one fact that
cannot be ignored.
But what does he
get out of all this?
What is he hoping to
achieve in the end?
-There's one thing I don't get.
Showing them you have
connections to the police
makes it easier for
them to find you
than when they just
suspected you were a student.
-Well, my real agenda
is to get close to L,
so I can eliminate him.
-How are you going to do that?
-You still don't
understand human beings.
In this world, there
are very few people
who actually trust each other.
And it's no different
for the police, you know.
What's especially important is
that L and the investigators
don't trust each other at all.
Think about it.
Could you trust someone
whose name and face
you don't even know?
When L discovers
that I'm somehow
getting confidential
information,
he'll be obligated to start
investigating the police
to find the source of the leak.
When that happens, it'll
only be a matter of time
before the police start
resenting L. On the surface,
it will appear that L and
the investigation team
are working together
to try to catch me.
But in reality, L will
investigate the police,
and they will be
investigating L.
I'm not the one
who's going to find
L. I can let the
police do that for me.
And when they do, that's
when I'll eliminate him.
CHIEF: What's this about?
-With all due respect,
Chief, we're resigning.
We demand that you assign
us to a different case.
Otherwise, you can have our
badges right here and now.
-Why?
You're good cops.
-Isn't it clear?
It's because we
value our lives, sir.
-If what L says is true,
Kira has some ESP like power
that somehow allows him
to kill people indirectly,
from anywhere.
-Well, if I were Kira,
sir, I'd probably
want to try and get
rid of the people who
were trying to catch me.
-Let's face it.
He knows he'll be sentenced
to death if he's caught.
-We all sat here
and watched when
L decided to pull
that media stunt
and challenge Kira to kill him.
Well, it was all very
impressive at the time.
But then again, L never
had to show his face,
or reveal his name,
for that matter.
I'm sure you recall
L's last request.
He asked that we
take a closer look
at how these victims'
identities were
made public, and specifically
to determine whether photos
of the victims were
available to the public
prior to their deaths.
Well, it turns out he was right.
Every single one of those
victims' names and photos
were broadcast to the Japanese
public, and then they died.
Unlike someone we
know, we're out there
investigating this
case wearing police IDs
with our names and
photos on them.
Anybody with a computer
can find out who we are.
We don't hide our faces.
We're out in the open.
-Sir, the truth is, we could
be killed by Kira at any time.
-For these reasons, we refuse
to continue working this case.
Excuse us, Chief.
-Hey, stop.
All of you, hold it right there.
-Huh?
-In order to solve
this problem, we
must establish the
concept that x squared
equals large N.
Now pay attention,
because this is important.
Before we tackle more
complex quadratic equations,
we have to start thinking
of large x's value
as simply the multiple
of two integers.
Now, let's apply this
concept to our first problem.
-We brought the FBI to
Japan four days ago.
They're fully operational.
As requested, they're now
gathering intel on the police.
-And this is the complete list?
-Yes.
-There are 141 people
in the police force
who have access to classified
information regarding
the investigation.
I am sure that somewhere in
this list of police officers
and the people closest to
them, we will find our suspect.
-Light, you got a second?
-I already told you Ryuk, you
can't talk to me in public.
How many times do
I have to tell you?
-In that case, I'll talk.
You just listen.
If you don't want
to hear me, you
can plug your ears or something.
First of all, I don't
have anything against you.
I actually think the
notebook couldn't
have been picked up
by a better person.
I'm here 'cause I have
to stick around 'til
the death note is
finished, or I see you die,
whichever comes first.
But make no mistake, Light, I'm
not on your side or L's side.
-Yeah, well I knew
that much already.
-You'll never hear
me say anything about
whether what you're
doing is right or wrong.
I'm not here to support
you, or give you my opinion.
I'm just a spectator.
But as your roommate,
I might have
a few things to
say now and then.
-What's this about, Ryuk?
Why are you telling me all
this stuff now, anyway?
It's really not like you.
-It's just that I'm
no ally of yours,
or Kira's, if you prefer.
The only reason I'm
going to tell you this
is because personally, it's
starting to creep me out.
-Get to the point, already.
--[laughing] You're being
followed by another human.
He's watching you right now.
It's really starting
to get on my nerves.
I realize there's no
way he can see me.
But because I'm always following
behind you wherever you go,
I feel like I'm
constantly being watched.
-That's a problem.
I'll have to get rid of
him as soon as possible.
Who would be following me?
Does this mean L is already
starting to suspect the police?
If he's going to
investigate the police,
he'll need a lot of
resources and manpower.
Even if he has as many
as 50 people on the case,
I don't see how they could
ever figure out that I'm Kira.
I shouldn't look
like anything other
than your average
high school senior.
But the longer I let this
person keep following me,
the greater the
chance is they'll
figure out who I really am.
Above all, I need
my stalker's name.
Once I figure that out, I
can get rid of him for good.
-Light.
-Hmm?
-I'm going to let you
in on a little secret.
What makes a
shinigami and a human
who has a death note different?
Well, there are two things.
And why do shinigami
have to write
the names of humans
in their death notes?
You got any ideas?
-Of course not.
Why would I know that?
You know, you sure
are talkative today.
-It's because we
are able to take
human lifespans for ourselves.
-Huh?
Wait, what do you mean by that?
-Let's say you
have a human who is
due to live until the age
of 60, and a god of death
wrote that this person
would die at 40.
60 minus 40 equals 20.
Now, those 20 years taken from
someone in the human world
are added to that
god of death's life.
-Huh.
-So it means that as long
as we don't slack off,
even if someone was to
shoot us in the head,
or stab us in the
heart with a knife,
a god of death cannot die.
On the other hand, no
matter how many names
you write in your death
note, your lifespan
will not increase.
That is the first
difference between gods
of death and humans who
possess a death note.
-Huh.
That's something about shinigami
that I haven't heard before.
Pretty interesting stuff.
-The second
difference between us
will probably be of even
greater interest to you.
Though this has less to
do with lengthening life,
and more to do with
cutting it short.
-What do you mean
cutting it short?
-Shinigami can tell
what a person's name
is by just looking
at their face.
We know instantly.
And do you have any idea why?
Because through a
shinigami's eyes,
a human's name can be
seen about their head.
Not only that, we see
their lifespan as well.
-Their name and lifespan?
-That's right.
I'm able to see your name
and lifespan right now.
If I converted
that to human time,
I could tell you how many
years you've got left.
But there's no way I'd
ever tell you that.
I may have a big mouth, but
even I wouldn't go that far.
[laughing] Shinigami
never have to worry
that they won't be
able to a person
just because they
don't know their name.
And every time we
do take a life,
we always know exactly how many
years we're going to receive.
Our eyes just aren't
the same, and that
is the difference
between you and I.
However, if a shinigami
drops his death note,
and human picks it up, he
can grant that humanity
the eyes of a shinigami.
But only if a deal
is made, one that's
been with us since
ancient times.
-And what's the deal?
-The price for having
a shinigami's eyes
is half of that person's
remaining lifespan.
That's all it is.
-Half of my remaining lifespan.
-Yeah.
In other words, if
you were supposed
to live another 50
years, it'll be 25.
If it was one more
year, then six months.
-I see.
And since you've made it clear
you're not on anyone's side,
and won't help me
out, you wouldn't just
give me the names of
people I wanted to kill.
Basically, you're saying
that I can't simply
borrow your powers.
I'd have to pay for them.
-That's right.
It's a key part of the code
that all shinigami are bound by.
I'll say this once more.
Give me half your
remaining lifespan,
and I'll give you
the shinigami eyes.
-If I agree, I'll be able
to know everyone's name just
by looking at them.
If I had that power,
the death note
would only be easier to use.
-So, what'll it be, Light?
Is it a deal?
[theme music]
-Everything has
turned out exactly
as I wrote it in the death
note, to the last detail.
11:45, on the dot.
Everything is going
just as I planned.
The death note never fails.