[theme music]
-The human whose name is
written this notebook shall die.
[laughter]
-Help me!
-Now, what will happen?
The Death Note.
It's for real.
[screaming]
-Any human whose
used a Death Note
can either to go to heaven
or hell for eternity.
-I want the world to
know of my existence.
That there's someone out there
passing righteous judgment
on the wicked.
And I-- I will become the
god of this new world.
-He found himself
overwhelmed with happiness
and satisfaction--
-I have no idea what he was
thinking coming to my house--
but I am so through with him.
-Seriously?
So happened with
your dad after that?
TEACHER: All right then, Yagami?
-Mhm?
-Please recite this line for us.
-Sure.
"Having finally made
his dream a reality,
he was overwhelmed, both by the
magnitude of his achievement
and by the joy and happiness
that it brought him."
-That was very well done, but
I'm not surprised, of course.
Absolutely flawless.
Very good.
Well, then we'll leave
it that for today.
[dismissal bell]
-I thought it would never end.
How do you do this everyday?
It's so boring.
Hey, were are you going?
Hey, Light, are you
listening to me?
-Don't talk to me.
Unlike you, people can still
hear me when I talk out loud.
-Huh.
Well aren't you boring?
-Hey.
What's up, Light?
We were just get ahead down--
-Sorry, I'm a little busy today.
-You don't have anything to do.
Aren't you just going to go
home and hang out in your room,
as usual?
-What are you talking about?
Of course I have something to.
Yes.
Something very important.
-NEWSCASTER (ON TV): There was
more violence across the city
today.
Another stabbing, this
time at a restaurant
in the heart of the Kabukicho
District of Shinjuku.
-Hey, Light.
I'm talking to you.
-What is it?
-Why are you working so hard?
-I can't afford
to waste any time.
I have a very small window to
write names in this notebook.
I only have from when I get home
from school until I go to bed.
I still need to sleep, so
I can maintain my average
and stay at the top my class.
Obviously, I can't
be sleeping in class.
Plus, there's all the studying
at home and at cram school.
I can't let myself
get too tired.
It'll start to affect my health
and my mental performance.
If I'm serious about trying to
create an ideal world that's
free from evil, then I need
to make the most of my time.
SAYU: Huh?
Weird.
Hey, Light!
What's going on?
Why's your door locked?
-It's Sayu.
What is it?
SAYU: Can you help
me with my homework?
-Uh.
Yeah.
OK.
-We're doing quadratic
equations in math.
Sorry to interupt.
I know you're
studying right now.
But I'm, like, the
only person in my class
who doesn't get this stuff.
Thanks so much.
-No problem.
-I'd be careful
if I were to you.
If anyone else
touches that notebook
you've got hidden in
the drawer right now,
they'll be able to see me, too.
-Uh huh.
(VOICE OVER) He waits
till now to mention
that important detail?
Damn shinigami.
-What's wrong?
Are you all right?
-It's nothing.
So what exactly
don't you understand?
What are you stuck on?
SAYU: Um.
Well, I think all of it.
PANELIST 1: There have been
52 deaths that we're aware of.
And that's just
in the past week.
PANELIST 2: Every single one of
them involved a heart attack.
PANELIST 3: They
were all criminals
who were either
being held in prison
or who were wanted by police
for outstanding crimes.
And I think it's
safe to say, there
are other criminals whose
deaths are unaccounted for.
-In which case the death
toll could be well over 100.
[chatter]
-Uh.
Morning, Chief.
They started the
meeting without you.
-That's fine.
I had to take an urgent
call from headquarters.
-At any rate, these
were criminals
who would probably facing
execution sooner or later.
Perhaps we shouldn't wait--
-Why should it matter whether
it's a criminal or someone
innocent?
Last time I checked,
murder was still murder.
-It's still too early to
consider these a homicide.
-Then how did all
these people have
heart attacks at
the exact same time?
That's not coincidence!
It's murder!
-Do you think it's possible
to simultaneously kill
all these people in
different locations?
-We're treating this has an
elaborate murder plot that's
been carried out by
a large organization.
-If it is a large
organization, I'm
sure I'm not alone in
suspecting the FBI or CIA.
MALE SPEAKER: I dare
you to say that again.
-Now, now this is not the
time to be joking around.
We need to confirm that these
are, indeed, homicides and not
coincidences.
-How?
Autopsy results showed that
all of these cases the victims
died of a sudden heart attack.
-Investigating a series of
heart attacks is pointless.
I don't see what
else we can learn.
-Absolutely, if these people
had been shot or stabbed,
at least we'd have
something to go.
-If that's the case,
It looks as if we'll
have no choice
but to bring in L.
-I can't believe--
[inaudible]
-Uh, Chief, what's this
L they're talking about?
-Right.
I forgot that is your first
time at this conference.
We don't know L's real
name or whereabouts.
In fact, we still don't even
know what it looks like.
However, he's managed to solve
every case he's ever taken on.
And he's tackled
some of the greatest
mysteries this world
has ever known.
He hides in the shadows.
But he's the best of the best,
a last resort, our trump card.
-But I've hear this L
is extremely arrogant.
I understand he'll
only take on cases
that he's personally
interested in.
-That's exactly right.
Besides, we don't even
know how to contact him.
L's CONTACT: L is
already on the move.
Gentleman L has already
begun his investigation
into these incidents.
-What?
[inaudible]
-Huh?
Who's that?
That man's the only
known person who
can contact L. Nobody knows
his true identity either.
L's CONTACT: Please be silent.
L would like to
address the delegates.
-Greetings to all
of you at the ICPO.
I am L.
-What are we doing here anyway?
I don't understand why we're
thinking about this dump.
Tell me.
-Isn't it obvious?
You told me that anyone
touches the Death Note
will be able to see you.
I can afford to carry something
this dangerous with me anymore.
Up until now, I thought
that if my family ever
saw the notebook,
I could tell them
I was keeping records of
various criminals in preparation
for becoming a
detective one day.
But I'm walking a very
fine line right now.
I don't want to think about it.
But if I make one
mistake, I might end up
killing my own family.
-The difficulty
of this case lies
in it's unprecedented scope.
And make no mistake,
we're witnessing
an atrocious act of mass murder.
One that is unforgivable.
This case cannot be solved
without the full corporation
of the ICPO.
That is, all of the
police organizations
we represent
throughout the world.
You need to make the
decision to fully support
the investigation
at this meeting.
Also I require
additional corporation
from Japan's national
police agency.
-What?
Why Japan in particular?
-Whether the guilty party
as an individual or a group,
there's a strong possibility
that they're And even
if they're not, we can be
sure they're hiding in Japan.
-What is all this based on?
-Why Japan you ask?
I think I'll be able to
provide you proof of that
after I directly
confront the culprit.
-A direct confrontation?
-At any rate, I
would like to set up
the investigation
headquarters in Japan.
-That was easier to make
that I thought it'd be.
-Huh?
Does that mean you were
able to hide the notebook?
-Yeah.
I hid it right here
in this drawer.
-But it just seemed to be
particularly well hidden.
You left the key in the lock.
-And that's the whole point.
I intentionally left the key
in the most noticeable place
I could think of.
-Isn't that just
a regular diary?
-That's what it is.
I'm guessing that
once most people find
the diary inside
my desk, that'll
probably satisfy
their curiosity.
But the real key is this.
Just in every day
item that you'd
expect to find lying
around on my desk,
a regular ballpoint pen.
And all I need is this part.
RYUK: So that's the key?
-Yeah.
If you look closely,
you'll find there's
a small hole
underneath the drawer.
Then you just insert this.
-Ah!
A fake bottom.
The diary will
distract most people,
so I doubt anyone will find it.
-But that's not all.
Even if someone figures out
that there's a fake base,
I've set things
up so that there's
no way they could get their
hands on the notebook.
You see once the ink
reservoir is inserted in acts
as an insulator, preventing
the flow of electricity
around this circuit.
When the fake base of
the drawer is put back,
this piece of
rubber also prevents
the flow of electricity.
However if someone were
to try to and force
the bottom of the drawer open,
the circuit would connect
and that would ignite
the gasoline contained
in this thin plastic
casing, instantly
setting the notebook on fire.
The way I've got it set
up, all the evidence
would be completely destroyed.
If I'm ever
questioned, I'll just
say that I was
hiding the real diary
because I didn't
want anyone to see.
It sounds like a pretty
believable excuse.
I mean, it is my
diary after all.
-I've heard of humans finding
Death Notes in the past.
And typically the biggest
problem they have is
find a good place to hide it.
But you, Light, you're probably
the first to have giving it
this much thought, though
it's a pretty risky
set up from the look of it.
If you make even the
slightest mistake,
you could be badly burned.
-Risky.
You say the strangest
things sometimes, Ryuk.
This whole thing has been a
risk since the very beginning,
from the moment I
obtain the Death Note.
I'm sorry but compared to
that, this doesn't even
qualify as a risk to me.
In fact, it actually
protects me.
It all comes down to a choice.
Would I prefer to be executed or
deal with a little house fire?
REPORTER (ON TV): Last night
in the West Tokyo Penitentiary,
Nyoki Korishkiyama, originally
sentenced to 15 years
for armed robbery is reported
to have died of a sudden heart
attack at the age of 32.
This is just the
most recent death
in a steadily growing number of
cases involving inmates dying--
CROWD: This is unbelievable.
Criminals are dropping
like flies lately.
It's a little scary.
But at the same time,
it's kind of cool.
Just make sure you
don't do anything bad.
I wouldn't be surprised if
the police were behind this.
No way.
The police don't have
that kind of power.
Don't you know about him?
Huh?
About who?
Kira?
You know.
Kira.
I wonder who's going
to be killed next.
LIGHT: Ryuk, you
should check this out.
-Uh huh.
-Websites like this are
popping up everywhere lately.
RYUK: The Legend
of Kira the Savior.
Huh.
Sounds pretty cool.
It's this about you?
-Yeah.
I think they've taken the name,
Kira, from the English word
killer.
Can't say I'm too
happy about that.
But it looks like that's the
name they decided to give me.
When I searched
the word Kira, I'm
pulling up ton of sites
just like this one.
The media hasn't
picked up on it.
They're still calling
this a succession
of unexplained deaths
among the world's most
hardened criminals.
But the people of
the world can already
sense that there's
something happening.
They know there's
someone out there
passing righteous judgment.
-Oh?
LIGHT: Human beings
are like that, Ryuk.
-Oh.
-Although this would probably
never happen in school,
let's say that
students were asked
to discuss whether bad
people deserve to die.
Well, you can bet
that everyone would
give the politically
correct answer.
-It's just wrong to kill people.
LIGHT: That's what they're
bound the say, of course.
That's the correct
response to give, right?
Humans will always try
to maintain appearances
when they're in public.
That's just how we are.
But this is how
they really feel.
Most are too afraid
to support me
as they're worried about
what others will think.
Many would rather
deny my existence.
But on the internet, where
you can remain anonymous,
support for Kira is growing.
Maybe people are afraid
to say it out loud.
But they all understand
what's happening.
Someone's making the bad
guys disappear one by one.
Those who have done no wrong are
cheering for Kira in the hearts
because they have
nothing to fear.
While those who done
wrong are on the run.
They're forced to hide
from an unknown enemy.
This is how it should be.
It's perfect.
Everything's going
just like I planned.
-We'd like to apologize
for the eruption
as of now we're bringing you
a live worldwide broadcast
from Interpol's ICPO.
-Hm.
What's this?
[interposing voices]
ONLINE REPORTER: We now
take you live to the ICPO.
-I head up an international
police task force
which includes all
member nations.
I am Lind L. Tailor.
Otherwise known as L.
-What?
Who is this guy?
CHIEF: So this is
how it all begins.
-But sir, I don't get it.
He's never actually
shows face before, right?
Why we choose to do it now?
-It must mean L's
serious about this.
(VOICEOVER) L, we followed
every single one of your orders.
Now it's time for you to prove
what you said to the ICPO.
-Criminals around
the world are being
murdered by a serial killer.
I consider this crime
to be most atrocious act
of murder in history.
I will not rest until the
person or persons responsible
are brought to justice.
Kira, I will hunt you down.
I will find you.
-He seems certain
he'll catch you.
-Hm.
That fool.
He'll never find me.
He'll have to get this first.
And as long as the
police don't find it,
there won't be any
evidence to convict me.
Which means that catching me
will be absolutely impossible.
I anticipated that the
police would get involved
and that something
like this might happen.
-Kira, I've got a
pretty good idea
what your motivation might be.
And I can guess what
you hope to achieve.
However what you're
doing right now is evil.
-Uh.
You think I'm evil.
I am justice.
I protect the innocent
and those who fear evil.
I'm the one who become the god
of a new world that everyone
desires.
All those who would
oppose that god,
they are the ones
who are truly evil.
I guess you're just
too stupid L. Too bad.
This could have been
a lot more interesting
if you'd only be a bit smarter.
I'll show the world what
happens when you cross me.
The entire world is watching, L.
Five more seconds, four, three,
two, one.
What's wrong?
You got nothing else to say?
Huh?
-I had to test this just
in case but I-- I never
thought it would
actually happen.
Kira, it seems you
can kill people
without having to
be there in person.
I wouldn't have believed it
if I hadn't just witnesses it.
Listen to me, Kira.
If you did, indeed, kill Lind
L. Tailor, the man who you just
saw die on television,
I should tell you
that he was an inmate
whose execution was
scheduled for today.
That was not me.
-What?
-L: The police arrested
him in absolute secrecy.
So you wouldn't
have heard about him
on TV or through the internet.
It appears that not
even you have access
to information about
these types of criminals.
-Heh, heh.
He got you there.
-But I assure you, L is real.
I do exist.
Now try to kill me.
-You, you bastard.
L: What's wrong?
CHIEF: What the
hell is going on?
He's really taking this too far.
-Are you try to
kill yourself, a L?
CROWD: What going on?
Look it's Kira versus L.
Live broadcast killing?
This is freaky.
Amazing.
Do it Kira.
Someone stop this.
-L: Can't you do it?
Well, Kira, it seems that
you can't kill me after all.
-(LAUGHING)
-So there are some
people you can't kill.
You've given me a useful hint.
I'll tell you something that I
think you'll find interesting.
Although this was announced
as a worldwide broadcast,
the truth is we are
only broadcasting
in the Kanto region of Japan.
I had planned to broadcast
this message around the world
until we found you.
But it looks like that
won't be necessary.
I now know where you are.
-(LAUGHING) This L
guy is pretty good.
-The police treated
your first killing
as an unrelated incident.
But in actuality, the
first of your victims
was a suspect in Shinjuku.
Of all the criminals that
recently died of heart attacks,
this one's crime was by
far the least serious.
Furthermore, his crime was only
ever recorded inside Japan.
I used that information
to deduce this much.
You are in Japan.
And your first victim
was little more
than an experiment
which means that you
haven't been killing
for very long.
We decided to broadcast
in Kanto first because
of its large population.
And luckily, we found you.
To be completely
honest with you,
I never expected that
things would go this well.
But it won't be too
long now before I
am able to sentence
you to death.
-L has certainly lived
up to his reputation.
-Uh huh.
He proved that Kira exists,
that the deaths were murders,
and that he's here in Japan.
-Naturally, I'm very
interested to know
how you're able to commit these
murders without being present.
But I don't mind
waiting a little bit
longer you can answer all of
my questions when I catch you.
Let's meet again soon, Kira.
-Really?
He's going to
sentence me to death.
Sounds interesting.
I accept your challenge, L.
-Each of the has to
hunt down the other
without knowing the
other's name or face.
And the first on whose
identity is revealed will die.
Humans are so much fun.
-L.
-Kira.
-I will hunt you down
wherever you're hiding
and I will eliminate you.
-I am--
I am--
-justice.
[theme music]
-I'm not the one
who's going to find
L. I can let the
police do that for me.
And when they do, that's
when I'll eliminate him.
Looks like I may be
able to provide you
with more entertainment, Ryuk.