[theme music]
-How many seconds has it
been since you wrote down
the first name?
-35.
36.
37.
38.
39.
-Well, Near, look like I win.
-40.
-We're still alive.
-It's been over a minute
and we haven't died.
-Didn't I already tell you all
that no one was going to die?
-But-- but why?
Why won't they die?
God, I did everything
you told me.
-Rester, Gevanni, take him now.
[screaming]
-Gevanni, the notebook please.
If you didn't
believe me earlier,
then see for yourselves.
I can confirm that the first
four names are definitely
the real names of
the SPK members.
The second four are
the names of your team.
The only name that hasn't been
written down is Light Yagami.
If that weren't enough, Mikami
also addressed you as God,
and said he did what
you asked him to.
It's settled.
-It's a trap!
This whole thing is a set up!
This is all part of
Near's plan to frame me.
Isn't it a little
odd that no one
died after having their name
written in the notebook?
This proves it's a trap.
-I believe I already told
you that no one would
die because I
modified the notebook.
-No, you-- that-- that can't be.
This is a set up.
I don't know this guy.
-Light, it's too
late to deny it.
You know Near has won.
Just a moment ago, you were
saying, "it looks like I win."
How much more of a
confession do we need?
-Light.
Why?
-Stop it.
-Light Yagami.
L. Kira.
It's over.
You've lost the game.
Just a moment ago, you
proclaimed your victory,
expecting us all to die.
And to tell the truth, you
might have actually won,
and I would've lost.
We ended up doing exactly
what you expected us to,
and altered the fake notebook
in Mikuni's possession.
However, when I said before that
we had modified the notebook,
I was, in fact, referring to
the real notebook as well as
the fake.
We only switched part
of the fake notebook.
But as for the real one, we
replaced the entire thing.
This notebook here is
actually the real one.
-No.
Impossible!
-We used the same kind
of pen that Mikami
used, copied his handwriting
perfectly, and made
both the inside and
the outside of our fake
look exactly like the original.
Gevanni was able to do
it in a single night.
Of course, since I had
touched the real notebook
before coming, I've been able
to see the Shinigami as well.
It's a pleasure to meet
you, Mr. Shinigami.
I'm Near.
-Nice to meet you too.
My name is Ryuk.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
He can talk to Ryuk.
He can see him, so that
means it must be true.
-Some of the edges of this
notebook's pages are torn.
Tell me, if someone's name
was written on a ripped
off piece of paper,
would they still die?
-Oh yeah, of course they would.
-I thought so.
I bet you were able to use
that to your advantage.
I wonder how many times
you deceived us with this,
and how many people you killed.
Light Yagami, you are Kira.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Thi--
this has got to be a trick.
Or could it be that Mikami's
betrayed me somehow.
-You're mistaken.
This was all thanks to Mello.
I believe if I
explain this much,
you'll begin to understand.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): What?
Mello?
-Please take a look at
this page of the notebook.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Takada's
name is in the notebook.
I was the one who killed
her, but her death
was written there
just one minute later.
Did that mean Mikami did
the same thing I did?
-God, you told me you
couldn't move freely.
I had to make sure
Takada was taken care of.
Wasn't that my duty to you?
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): You idiot!
I gave you strict orders not to
make any unnecessary movements
until today.
-It's all true.
On the 26th, right after
Takada's kidnapping
was broadcast on the news,
Mikami went to the bank.
-I'd been trailing him.
I knew he went to the bank
every month on the 25th.
So it was odd for
someone so methodical
to go to the bank
twice in two days.
I followed Mikami to the bank as
he headed for the safe deposit
boxes.
It was only at this time
that he seemed concerned
whether someone was
following him or not.
I got into his safe deposit box.
Inside was the real notebook.
Sure enough, Takada's name had
already been written inside it.
-Do you understand
now, Light Yagami?
You didn't realize that
Mikami made a move on his own
and wrote Takada's
name in his notebook,
because you had
already killed her
using a notebook
clipping yourself.
This was the event
that made me consider
the possibility of
a fake notebook.
We were able to stop you thanks
to the efforts of one person--
it was Mello who did it all.
-Mello probably knew what was
going to happen all along.
MELLO (ON PHONE):
It can be resolved
by having a name
written in the notebook?
-That's right.
-Well then, if I don't do it--
-I bet Mello knew in his heart
that working by ourselves,
neither of us would be
able to attain our goal
and surpass our mentor L.
But together-- together,
we can stand with L.
Together, we can surpass L.
And now, acting as one, we
face the Kira who defeated L.
And with solid evidence,
beat him at his own game.
Let's see you try and talk
your way out of this one,
if you can.
[laughing]
-That's right.
I am Kira.
And what can you do?
Kill me right here?
Hear this.
I'm not only Kira, but I am
also God of the new world.
Kira has become law in
the world we now live.
He's the one who's
maintaining order.
I have become justice,
the only hope for mankind.
Kill me?
Is that really the
right thing to do?
Since Kira's appearance six
years ago, wars have stopped,
and global crime rates have
been reduced by over 70%.
But it's not enough.
This world is still rotten
with too many rotten people.
Somebody has to do this.
And when I first got that
notebook all those years ago,
I knew I had to do it.
No.
I was the only one who could.
I understood that killing
people was a crime.
There was no other way.
The world had to be fixed.
A purpose given to me.
Only I could do it.
Who else could have done
it and come this far?
Would they have kept going?
The only one who can
create a new world is me.
-No.
You're just a
murderer, Light Yagami.
And this notebook is
the deadliest weapon
of mass murder in the
history of mankind.
You yielded to the power of
the Shinigami and the notebook.
And you have confused
yourself with a god.
In the end, you're nothing more
than a crazy serial killer.
That's all you are.
Nothing more and nothing less.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Useless fools.
As if they could
ever understand.
-Near, here's some
food for thought.
That notebook you
have and the one
that Aizawa brought from
the Japanese task force
headquarters-- are
they both real?
NEAR (VOICEOVER):
What is he up to?
Is he bluffing?
-At the moment, only I know
where the real notebook is.
If you truly want
to defeat Kira,
as well as test the notebook
that Aizawa was carrying,
I guess you're going to have
to write down either my name
or Mikami's.
It's the only way to see
if it's real, or fake.
-He's hidden a piece
of the notebook.
[gunshot]
-Matsuda.
-Matsuda!
You idiot!
Who the hell do you
think you're shooting at?
Don't screw with me!
-What was it all for then?
What about your dad?
What the hell did he die for?
-My dad?
You mean Soichiro Yagami?
That's right, Matsuda, in this
world, all those earnest people
like him who fight for
justice-- they don't lose.
You want a world where people
like that are made to be fools?
I know you understand,
so kill the others.
Shoot them!
-You led your own
father to his death.
And now that he's gone,
you call him a fool?
-His blood!
-I'll kill him.
I'll kill him.
He has to die!
-Matsuda!
[whimpering]
-Damn you.
What the hell is this?
Mikami, what are
you waiting for?
Write down their names!
Write them down!
Kill them now!
-It's finally over,
isn't it, Near?
-Yes.
[gasping]
-Where are you, Misa?
Where's Takada?
Someone.
What do I do now?
[screaming]
-What the-- Mikami!
-Quick, stop the bleeding.
-It's already too late.
He'll be dead in a few seconds.
-Wait, Light!
-He's getting away.
Light!
-Mr. Aizawa.
It's unlikely he has anymore
pieces of the notebook.
And with those wounds,
he's not going to go far.
He'll stop running soon,
even if we leave him alone.
-Hmph.
Near, I'm not going
to follow your orders.
-Very well then.
I'll leave it up to you.
[panting]
RYUK (VOICEOVER): Well, Light,
it looks like you've lost.
Remember how, in the
beginning when we first met,
I told you that I'd
be the one writing
your name in my notebook.
That is part of the
agreement between a Shinigami
who brings a notebook to the
human world and the first human
who picks it up.
If they put you in prison,
who knows when you'd die.
And I don't want to
lie around waiting.
So it's all over.
You'll die here.
It was good while it lasted.
We eased each other's
boredom for quite a while.
Well, Light, it's
been interesting.
[theme music]