[LUCIFER] Oh. If it
isn't the great King Satan.
Oh right.
I s'pose I should call you
"Sadao Maou" from now on, yeah?
Heh. And the Hero Emilia, too.
[EMI] Lucifer?
[EMERALDA in Ente Isla]
[ALBERT in Ente Isla]
[barfing sounds]
[EMERALDA in Ente Isla]
[ALBERT in Ente Isla]
[barfing sounds]
[EMERALDA in Ente Isla]
No. It can't be.
I ran my sword right
through your chest.
I did the "you killed my father"
bit and everything!
[LUCIFER] And yet here I am.
Now, how could that be possible?
[MAOU] Does it
have something to do
with your new friend
hiding over there?
One of the six high
priests of the Church.
Why don't you stop
lurking in the background
and show your face already?
Olba Mayer.
Olba?
[MAOU] When Emi
came through the gate.
You were the one right
behind her, weren't you?
Soon as I heard that,
I put two and two together.
You and your "crew"
are a shady bunch,
but I'll give you credit,
you're the shadiest.
Congratulations,
you found me out.
And Emilia, you're
certainly looking lovely.
Olba.
[EMI] Why? How could
you work with Lucifer?
Hmph! You wanna know, huh?
I'll tell ya, but it'll be
the last thing you ever hea--
[MAOU] The Hero was really
throwing her weight around,
and you couldn't abide
that, so you figured,
"after she ousts the Demon
army, let's execute her."
Spot on, huh?
And you got Lucifer
here on your side
by promising him a golden
ticket back to Heaven town.
Damn! How'd you know that?
[MAOU] Please,
you're joking, right?
C'mon man, that's the
oldest trick in the book!
And who says "the last
thing you'll ever hear"?
I've seen B-Movies with better
scripting than that, baldy.
Get a wig!
[OLBA] B-Baldy?
And what is a "B Movie?"
Heh heh!
[ASHIYA] Sorry Sire,
but I'd be derelict
in my duty...
if I let that slide.
Am I to infer you've been
wasting our money
on movie tickets again?
First. I'm a little
busy right now.
And besides, it's my
allowance, isn't it?
So all this time,
I've been working
my fingers to the bone?
And cleaning up your messes
without so much
as a morning off?
No more allowance for you, Sire!
[MAOU] You're going there?
You're really gonna go there?
Knock it off already,
you morons!
Ashiya!
[LUCIFER] That was fun.
But I'm afraid the show is over.
I'monna have to close
the curtain early.
Just promise me, Sire.
When you see a movie,
go on the first of the
month; it's half off.
[MAOU] You're gonna be okay.
Also, don't tell me what to do.
Now, I suppose
it's Emilia's turn.
Or should the King be first?
Decisions, decisions.
Ah, I'll kill both at once!
[maniacal laughter]
Yeah, I know
you're not supposed
to play with your food,
but I just can't help it.
This whole feeding on despair
thing is just so much fun!
[OLBA] Lucifer!
[LUCIFER] Relax, Baldy.
It's not like they're
gonna be able to stop us.
Good plan, coward.
Running with your
tail between your legs!
Oh please!
Like you're in a
position to be critical!
His magic's so strong.
Way stronger than anything you
or I've been able
to achieve; how?
[MAOU] It's 'cause he's feeding
off negative human emotions!
Huh?
Those two are definitely the
ones behind all the trouble.
The robberies
and shootings, too.
[EMI] I don't get it,
why would they--?
To cause fear,
despair, and sadness.
The more negative
people's emotions become,
the more power they can absorb.
They want them in
a state of panic.
'Cause that equals fear,
and fear turns
into every negative
emotion you can think of,
which then
intensifies their magic
and makes them more powerful.
[LUCIFER] I'm impressed
you figured that out.
Well done.
You made it
easy, so thanks.
I realized it
when I was trapped
inside that café
after the quake.
I could feel the humans' fear
and despair flowing
directly into me.
That's what returned
me to my original form.
If that's the case,
why haven't you tried
to get more magic?
All you had to do was keep
stirring up their negativity.
Eventually you would've
been powerful enough
to find a way back home.
[MAOU] That's true,
but the thing is,
I don't wanna go back.
I like it here. Being
human isn't half bad.
This world's done a lot for me,
and I don't wanna
cause it any trouble.
[MAOU] If I were you,
I'd leave this realm alone.
How sweet.
You've gone soft on me,
haven't you Sire?
But you and I both know
there's no chance
that's gonna happen!
Cause I'm hungry!
What's on the menu?
Oh, look, a scared little girl
served medium rare.
[EMI] Let her go!
[MAOU] No! Don't do it!
Not your cup of tea, boss?
I think you're right, that
would be a lot of trouble,
so how about I just
eat her raw instead?
Go, now!
[LUCIFER] Wow!
Figured she wasn't a fan,
but from the vibe I'm gettin',
this girl's really
jealous of you, Emilia!
Son of a bitch that hurt!
Human bodies suck. So much ow!
Oh, stop whining, tough guy.
Some Demon King you are!
Maou!
[EMI] Olba!
Why are you using a gun?
Sorry about that, but I
need to save enough power
to control the Gate
on my journey home.
[LUCIFER] It's too bad.
He used to be such a big shot
and now look at him:
King Satan's all washed up.
[OLBA] Enough
with the chit-chat.
Kill them both now.
Two birds with one stone.
[MAOU] Emi.
Prepare yourself.
[EMI] Huh?
[LUCIFER] Rockin' a
little teleportation action.
Someone had more
juice than they let on.
[EMI] This is Koshu Kaido Road?
We're right
by Sasazuka Station!
Why bring us
somewhere so crowded?
Oh, I see, you
came here to catch
an ambulance,
didn't you, you big wimp?
Could ya cut
me some slack, please?
[LUCIFER] You can run
but'cha can't hide, "Sire."
The party's over.
[OLBA] Do it quickly.
There are far too
many witnesses already!
I think you need to relax, Olba.
[LUCIFER]
We can kill them, too.
But first things first.
[EMI] Maou?
Snap out of it, okay?
Get up.
[LUCIFER laughs]
Hate to break it to ya,
but he's not gonna bounce
back like he did in Shinjuku!
So, now that he's
out of the way,
I suppose I don't
need her anymore.
Knock yourself out.
[EMI] Chiho!
Olba! The show's almost over!
But first, it's time
for the big finale!
Help me kick up a tasty groove!
Stop it, Lucifer!
Don't do this! Please!
Thought she liked to party.
[LUCIFER] Whoa. I did that?
[LUCIFER] No way.
[MAOU] That's a B Movie
for ya. Predictable.
Guess I owe you one, Lucifer.
Thanks to you, I managed
to get my true form back.
He's alive!
You're okay!
[CHIHO] Is that Mister Maou?
Yeah, it sure is.
[thinking] I see.
He brought us to
the most populated area
he could think of,
so he could absorb the fear
and despair of the crowd.
As if Lucifer and
Olba weren't enough
to deal with on their own.
[MAOU] Snap out of it!
Uh, yeah!
Hey. What's happenin'?
[MAOU] This is no
time to be spacing out!
Get with the program!
[EMI] Huh?
Hurry up and take
those guys out right now!
This stuff is freakin'
heavy. Come on!
Can't hold it much longer.
You can see I'm slipping, right?
Emi!
[groans and grunts]
[MAOU] Please hurry!
[sighs]
Yer such a loser.
Seriously, like I have never
seen a Devil as lame as you.
[MAOU] Whatever!
Just do something already!
Help me!
What?
[MAOU] Oh, uh, sorry.
What I meant to say was:
Pretty please?
[EMI] You're on your own.
Didja forget I'm the Hero?
I would rather die
right here and now
than help you do anything!
What? You can't be serious?
I always am.
[EMI] Just hold on
a bit longer, okay?
And don't worry; I'll clean
up your mess for you.
But what about me?
It's all right,
you'll be safe in there.
It's weird, for some reason,
I've decided to let you
know the truth about us.
[EMI] Here we go.
Manifest now, my true power,
so I may vanquish all evil!
She can still do that?
I am a Hero born.
Though the world may change,
I swear, that fact never will!
[MAOU] Lame! Rewrite!
Oh, shut'cher trap!
After I finish with those two,
your butt's next
on my list to kick.
So you better watch yourself!
Just be quick about it, yeah?
Here. This should help.
[EMI] What did you do?
[MAOU] I put up
a magical barrier.
Now you're free to
unleash on these fools,
and won't have to
worry about civilians.
[EMI] Hmph!
Well, that's lame.
Don't you know taking
out innocent people
is what makes this fun?
[pained noises]
[EMI] Oops. My bad.
[MAOU] So not awesome.
[EMI] You won't get
away with this, Lucifer!
[LUCIFER] You gotta fess up:
how exactly did you plan
on taking me out
when you can't even
recover your celestial force?
[ASHIYA]
Now, what could be so funny?
[ASHIYA] It is
certainly not my wish
to do battle alongside a Hero.
But since I've sworn
allegiance to King Satan,
I have no choice.
[LUCIFER] Alciel!
So right now, that makes you
my sworn enemy, Lucifer!
[EMI] Well, well,
I thought you were dead.
On the contrary,
my king saved me.
He left me just enough magic
to escape death's
mighty clutches.
Yeah? If that's true,
what the heck
took you so long?
[ASHIYA] I had to go
back to the apartment
and pick up my General's cape!
I knew that was coming.
In the future, I'd prefer you
let me handle things on my own.
I'll let you thank me later.
Right now you and I
need to focus our energy
on taking these two out.
Dude, you're the worst!
Seriously, you've gotta be like
the worst partner
in the history of time.
You gonna do anything?
I do not have the means
to replenish my celestial force.
If I use it all now,
I can't go home!
[LUCIFER] What do you
think happens if we lose?
[MAOU] Is it just me,
or does my role
in all this seem a
little anticlimactic?
This is real.
It's actually happening.
[sighs]
Guess there's no way
to talk our way out
of this one, huh?
[EMI] Holy Flame Slice!
Lucifer!
Emilia. You're a fool.
How could you join
forces with a Demon?
[EMI] Are you
freaking kidding me?
[MAOU] Man, that was heavy!
I mean, like super heavy!
But still, way to go me!
Seriously, awesome
job there. Good work!
Damn you!
[MAOU] Whaddaya say
we wrap this thing up.
If we don't get a move on,
she and I're gonna be
late for work. Right, Chi?
I promised to teach you how
to fix the ice cream
machine today.
[MAOU] As for the rest of you,
you got some nerve
relegating a Demon King like me
to a menial task like
holdin' up a stupid bridge.
Time for a little payback.
No!
Suck on this!
[MAOU] So, Emi.
What do you think
I should do with this guy?
[EMI] Let's see.
I'd say a great place
to start would
be punishing him for
wrecking the neighborhood.
[MAOU] Good idea.
Oh, and Lucifer, if I'm late
to work today, it's your fault.
[LUCIFER]
Wh-What are you talking about?
[MAOU] If I lose my perfect
attendance bonus because of you,
you're gonna regret it.
[ASHIYA] Don't think
about that one too hard.
I don't understand it either.
[MAOU] You're a great
Demon General, aren't you?
Where did all of
this fear come from?
Face your doom like a man!
[CHIHO] So uh--It seems a
little late for me to ask this,
but uh-- What exactly
are you guys?
You know, just outta curiosity.
No offense or anything.
[MAOU] I'm all shy now that
you come right out and ask me.
But, truth is, back home,
I'm a Demon King.
You don't believe me, do you?
Uh! No, I do, for sure!
I saw you do all those
incredible things.
It was beyond amazing.
Well, you're sweet,
but it wasn't that big a deal.
Sire.
Modesty may be a virtue,
but at this moment,
braggadocio is the wiser course.
I'm not like him,
I'm just a person.
Well, guess I do
have half Angel blood.
[MAOU] Huh? Seriously?
You're half Angel?
[EMI] Don't act so surprised.
You're a Demon King!
[EMI] Why are you
laughing, Chiho?
[CHIHO] I'm sorry!
I don't mean to poke fun it's
just that-- Well, honestly,
when I picture an Angel
or a Demon in my head,
they don't look so ordinary.
No. I see your point.
Who'd think a Demon King would
work at MgRonalds, right?
Like you're one
to talk Little Miss
"Thanks for calling,
how can I help you?"
Hey!
[MAOU] Here's what
I wanna know, Angel Face,
if you have that
much power left,
why haven't you attacked me?
Because I'm not careless.
For all I know, you could've
been pretending not
to have any power
this whole time.
And besides, I had
to conserve enough
to make sure I could get back
through the gate, didn't I?
Don't you see,
we could never be
in a romantic
relationship together
'cause we hate each other's
stinkin' guts. So relax.
[CHIHO] Whatever you say!
Well, what are you
going to do now, huh?
I mean, now that you've
gotten your magic back,
are you gonna go back
to Ente Isla, or what?
[gasps]
[MAOU] No way.
I'm already scheduled for
tons of shifts this month.
You need to get your
priorities in order, Sire.
What matters more,
Ente Isla or a job at MgRonalds?
Uh. 'Scuse me?
What should I do now?
I've been meaning
to ask you something.
You were the one
who called me at work
and threatened me, weren't you?
[LUCIFER]
Yeah. Sorry 'bout that.
I knew it!
How did you find me?
Well, uh--
Man, get off my back!
[shriek]
[EMI] But this is my wallet.
[MAOU] Lucifer.
Did you really look
inside a lady's wallet
without asking permission?
[ASHIYA] Now that's low.
[EMI] Oh! I will destroy you!
[ALBERT in Ente Isla]
[EMERALDA in Ente Isla]
[EMERALDA] Emilia!
[EMI] Emeralda? And Albert!
Well, you missed
all the fun.
[EMERALDA and ALBERT
in Ente Isla]
[ALBERT in Ente Isla]
[EMERALDA in Ente Isla]
Yes, you are correct!
Tremble with fear, peasants!
[EMERALDA in Ente Isla]
[ALBERT in Ente Isla]
He said to head
back to the Devil's Castle
and that they had
everything under control.
[EMI] That's it.
Just up ahead there.
[EMERALDA in Ente Isla]
[EMI] Trust me, you're
preaching to the choir.
[MAOU] Okay, then.
[ASHIYA] Sire.
Are you completely sure
you won't regret this?
Yeah. Can't exactly leave
things the way they are, can we?
You're kiddin' me.
His Highness has spoken.
That means the
discussion is over.
Dude, what the
hell is that all about?
You just do whatever he says?
Yeah, pretty much.
The boss is responsible
for the mistakes of
his subordinates.
That principle's as
true at MgRonalds
as it is back in Ente Isla.
The supreme ruler's gotta
take on that responsibility!
[EMERALDA in Ente Isla]
[ALBERT in Ente Isla]
[CHIHO] Wait, your voice.
It's the one I was hearing
in my head all those times.
[ALBERT in Ente Isla]
What did you hear?
[EMERALDA in Ente Isla]
[door opening]
Hey guys, we're home!
[screams]
[EMERALDA]
Alrighty, we're all set!
[ALBERT] Good!
Can't be gone too long,
or the Church will be able to
get away with who knows what.
I guess you know this already,
but it'd be a big help if
you'd come home soon, too.
[EMI] Yeah.
You did well though.
No fatalities and the city's
basically back in one piece.
Apparently, no one remembers
much, so that's good.
I tell you, he's really
something, isn't he?
Are we positive this
kid's the real Demon King?
[MAOU] Thank you, come again!
[CHIHO] Thank you, come again!
[CHIHO] Mister Maou?
I was wondering.
Uh. Are you going back home?
Not planning on it.
More like I can't, I guess.
I used up most of the
power I had rebuilding
that neighborhood so I'm stuck.
But I do have a little
gas left in the tank.
You know, Chi.
It's enough to erase
your memories too.
I mean, if that's what you-- Ah!
You're a big jerk!
My bad.