[MAOU] What's this?
Vegetables, Sire.
I suppose this is her
way of saying thank you.
Allow me to ascertain
their safety for you.
Is it good?
Yes, Sire.
It's quite good.
[ASHIYA] That's unusual, why
is there a key on the floor?
[MAOU] I'm guessing she opened
the window on her way out,
and locked the door
from the outside,
then tossed the key back in.
Typical hero.
All exemplary in her conduct.
What would you have
done if you were her?
[ASHIYA] Isn't it obvious?
First, I would've
locked the door,
and then I would've
taken the key with me.
[MAOU] Typical Demon.
[ASHIYA] Would you have
me any other way, Sire?
[EMI] I feel so violated.
[MALE NEWSCASTER 3A] In other
news, multiple shots were fired
in the Shibuya area
before dawn this morning.
The area was littered
with numerous bullet holes.
An abandoned bicycle,
hit multiple times, was found
at the scene of the crime.
[EMI] Oh, unbelievable!
Those jerk wads.
Well, guess it's not my problem.
[MALE NEWSCASTER 3A]
Police are also investigating
possible links between this
incident and a recent string
of late-night muggings
and storefront robberies.
Although the exact nature of
the connection remains unclear.
[CHIHO'S MOTHER] That's a hop,
skip, and a jump from here.
Darling, isn't that really
close to where you work?
[CHIHO] I'm not joking
or imagining things!
I really think an
earthquake is coming!
So, if you don't mind,
could I ask your advice
about this in person?
[CHIHO] And "Send!"
[MAOU] Okay. Does
tomorrow evening work?
I've got the day off.
And you're not on
shift either, are you?
[CHIHO'S MOTHER] Chiho,
are you working today?
Uh. No. I'm not.
But I am real busy today--you
know, with lots of other stuff.
[CHIHO'S MOTHER]
You just be safe out there.
Why wouldn't
I be? Safe, heh.
That's my middle name!
[CHIHO'S MOTHER]
This neighborhood's not like
it used to be.
Yeah. I know, Mom.
[CHIHO'S MOTHER]
What is the matter with you?
Um. Nothing, I'm fine.
[CHIHO'S MOTHER] Chiho!
[RIKA] Emi. You heard
about the shooting, yeah?
Wasn't that pretty close
to where you live?
No, I'm like three
stops from there.
[RIKA] That's crazy.
Anyway, whatcha doin' for lunch?
Wanna hit that curry place
I told you about?
Yes, there'll be a line but
it is totes worth the wait.
Uhh.. Thanks, but I'm way too
busy to stand in line today.
Plus, I lost my wallet.
What? That sucks!
[EMI] Yeah, and
now I have to fill out
a bunch of forms on my break.
Thank you
for your call today.
I'm Emi Yusa,
how can I help you?
[MALE YOUTH] "Yusa"?
Sounds to me like you're fitting
in quite nicely,
Emilia the Hero.
[EMI] May I ask who is calling?
[MALE YOUTH] Someone who knows
'bout "the Hero and the Devil."
And that's not all.
I'm gonna do everything in my
power to destroy you both.
[EMI] Understood, sir.
I'll do whatever it takes to
keep that from happening.
[MALE YOUTH] I gotta admit,
I didn't expect you
two to join forces.
[EMI] That was not our
company's desired result either.
[MALE YOUTH] I guess not.
Either way, King Satan
will be taken out.
As will Emilia the Hero.
It's Ente Isla's will.
[EMI] Is that right?
I'm afraid we won't
have any specifics
'til we've had a chance to
investigate the situation.
[MALE YOUTH] The Devil
and the Hero running away
from a little gunfire?
That "situation"?
And how're you
gonna investigate?
[EMI thinking] A vile tone
that seems to echo
from the pits of darkness.
He's a Demon.
[EMI] Alciel is the
only reputable general
still walking among us.
So that would make you nothing.
If you think
you can scare me
with words like "Ente Isla's
will" you're dead wrong.
I don't listen to idle threats
from nobodies like you.
[MALE YOUTH] When this
is all said and done...
I guarantee you'll be
singing a different tune.
[EMI] Takes all kinds, huh?
[EMI] Hey, so how
'bout that curry place.
I remembered how busy
the bank is during lunch.
Yeah, hello?
[MALE COP 3A] Hello there.
I'm trying to get in touch
with a Miss Emi Yusa?
[EMI] Yes. That's me.
[MALE COP 3A] I'm calling
from the Yoyogi Police Station.
[EMI] Huh? The police?
[MAOU] Didn't think there
was a snowball's chance
at home they'd ID
us from that bike.
These cops are good.
Well, we were
definitely right
about one thing.
Regarding her age,
the Hero "fudged the truth."
If I remember correctly,
she's only about
seventeen or eighteen.
Yeah, I told you that.
But she must've registered
as being at least twenty;
no idea why though.
I thought women lied about
their age to appear younger.
I don't understand
why "fudge" means "lie."
[EMI] Who the
crap cares about that?
Why me?
I wanna know, 'cause
I'm a little confused.
I'm a Hero!
So please tell me why
I just had to post bail
for a couple asinine
good for nothing demons?
Dude. Wouldja
please calm down?
I'm sorry but we couldn't
think of anybody else.
We weren't
positively overjoyed
about asking for
your help either,
but we had no choice.
Well I for one never
thought I'd have
to use my seal and ID card
for something
that's just so dumb!
I suppose I could've asked
my manager at work
to help us out first.
We can't annoy your
boss with such trifles.
[EMI] So you annoy me, instead?
Well, duh, causing trouble
for heroes is the whole
point of being a devil.
You win. Can't argue
with that logic.
Don't be mad; we let
you stay at our place.
Emi, relax, heroes
aren't supposed
to have nervous breakdowns.
Yeah?
That's 'cause they
never met you! Jerks!
Your fridge was
completely empty.
Put a little more thought into
your grocery list next time!
You're a Demon General and you
don't even know how to shop!
[ASHIYA] I'm on a diet.
I'm watching my calories.
[EMI] Just so you know,
I got a threatening
phone call at work today
and it wasn't very pleasant.
They're after you, too, Maou.
Mister King Satan himself.
Thanks for the heads-up.
It was just a heads-up.
So don't get the wrong idea,
I'm still going to be
the one to take you down.
And don't you forget it!
Just a reminder:
we're in public so stop
acting like a psycho.
You suck.
Just make sure you don't get
murdered by some loser nobody
before I get the
chance to kill you first!
[MAOU] They're after
both of us, huh?
And they called her
at work of all things.
[ASHIYA] It's a diet
and workout plan...
Oh, get a grip! Really!
Nobody cares about your
stupid exercise routine!
[CHIHO] I'm home!
[ASHIYA] To clarify: What time
are you meeting Miss Sasaki,
where are you meeting her,
and when can I expect you back?
[MAOU] What are you, my mom now?
Five o'clock, Shinjuku station.
We do have a bit of
time to spare then.
In that case,
Sire, you and I must go.
Wait. Go where?
[ASHIYA] Oh yes. Quite fabulous.
Whatever, where
did you get the money
to pay for this stuff anyway?
Naturally I've set aside
a secret stash of savings
for just this sort of emergency.
[MAOU] "Emergency"?
I'm just gonna sit
there, hear her out,
and come home; I don't
think this is necessary.
Au contraire, Sire!
Do you not see?
A fragile teenage girl never
divulges her deepest fears
to anyone but her
closest confidants!
And that's you!
Did she or did she
not reveal it to you?
Surely you cannot be blind to
what such a disclosure means?
Yeah. Okay,
will ya just chill out?
N'besides.
There is no way I'll
allow you to go on a date
dressed like some
dowdy transient bum.
Ouch. Why so harsh?
I do not dress like
a "transient bum"
and you will take that back!
Got this!
[CHIHO] There you are!
Hey Chi.
Oh wow, is that a new haircut?
[CHIHO] Glad you noticed!
Yeah. It's short.
So what do you think?
[MAOU] Uh. Looks good.
[CHIHO thinking] Score!
[CHIHO] I like your outfit.
I don't think I've ever seen
you all cleaned up like this.
Huh?
[CHIHO] Uh, not to say
you looked bad before;
you always look good.
It's just now you
look better is all.
Um, I didn't mean better.
What I mean is--
You look so cool.
Yeah, my roommate
told me I needed
to dress a little
nicer for our date.
Wow. So are you saying you
think of this as a date?
[MAOU] Uh. I guess so. Yeah.
[CHIHO thinking] Score!
[MAOU] So, what now?
[CHIHO] There's a great café
not too far from here.
It's cheap and
pretty laid back, too.
[CHIHO] You'll love it!
And since you're giving me
advice, it'll be my treat!
Does that sound
like a good plan?
I can't let you do that.
I mean, thank you.
But I can't accept.
This lunch is on me.
[CHIHO] Uh, Mister Maou!
Hm?
You see. The thing is--
What's up?
Are you all right?
Yeah. I just wanted
to hold your hand.
[MAOU] Oh that's all?
Yeah, no problem.
You okay?
Huh? Yeah, I'm great.
Never better actually!
Thank you for asking, though.
[MAOU] This way, making
our way through the crowd,
we won't get separated.
You're right, that's true.
Better safe than
sorry, I suppose.
What sort of
"no good" are you up to?
Ahh! Eh... Em... Em... Eh...
Emilia, 'tis you!
[EMI] Don't use my real name!
You realize how creepy
and suspicious you're
acting right now, don't you?
What are you doing,
tailing somebody?
No! I mean, it's none
of your business!
I'm a Hero; so
it is my business
when I see you behaving like
some creepster weirdo, isn't it?
Yeah, I guess so.
Drop it, just this once, for me?
[EMI] You've gotta
be kidding me.
I knew you when
you were a demon,
or have you forgotten?
Curses.
I've really done it this
time, haven't I, Sire?
You scum bag! Ass face!
What are you planning to
do to that girl? Tell me!
You've got it wrong!
His Majesty's intentions
are nothing but pure,
I can assure you!
He's a Devil;
I seriously doubt he
knows what "pure" is!
I beg you!
Listen to what I have to say!
Well, that's unexpected.
[ASHIYA] So you
understand me now?
[EMI] If you mean,
do I understand that
"His Majesty's" as much
of a "you know what"
as ever, then yes.
But what I don't understand is
why they need to go on a date.
[ASHIYA] I wondered
the same thing initially.
But it's clear to me,
after observing her,
that this "Sasaki" girl is more
than just a little
fond of your old rival.
[EMI] It seems so.
Um. I'm sorry, that
doesn't bother you at all?
[EMI] You want it to?
Well-- No, I--I just
find it extremely unbearable
and highly insolent that
a mere human girl has
become so enamored of my King.
[EMI] Personally,
I'm surprised a girl
that cute would waste her time
with a no-good, very-bad
miscreant like "Your King."
You dare insult
His Majesty so?
[EMI] Of course I do. Anyway.
From a girl's point
of view at least,
it's pretty obvious
she's into him.
The trendy little
dress she just bought.
Brand new hairdo,
fresh from the salon.
[EMI] And those
boots are new, too.
[ASHIYA] Oh? How can you tell?
[EMI] Well, it's not so
apparent to a man, I guess.
Her dress is screaming,
"I'm young and available."
And the form-fitting
cut is there
to emphasize her--damn
those are huge.
[ASHIYA] What're huge?
Nothing, pervert!
I said nothing!
Besides, big ones
just get in your way
when you're
fighting in a battle.
Small ones mean small armor,
which saves money
and means you're less
constricted in your movements!
I think you've lost me.
[EMI] Just forget it!
Back to the matter at hand.
Do you think he can get
anything useful out of her?
[ASHIYA] Don't ask me.
I'm only trailing in the event
that any undesirables
decide to show up.
[EMI] You're here,
so you fail by default.
[EMI] Still, this whole
earthquake thing
is definitely a
cause for concern.
One thing I know for sure;
I'm not going to sit here
and find out the hard way.
Not really any point in
spying on 'em from out here.
Follow me in.
[ASHIYA] Follow you in where?
To get a table.
Now are you comin' or not?
Wait a second!
How could I expect His Majesty
to excuse such extreme audacity?
No! Stop right there!
[MAOU] Maybe you
could just go over
the details one
more time, please.
Yeah. Sure.
I told you how my tinnitus
got really bad, didn't I?
It happened right
around the time
I started working at MgRonalds.
At first, I thought
I was just tired
from doing a bunch of
work I wasn't used to.
But then, last night--
[MALE VOICE in Ente Islan]
Hmm...?
Someone there?
[MALE VOICE in Ente Islan]
Hello? Hm?
Hey. I can hear you.
[MALE VOICE in Ente Islan]
What the heck?
Wait, a "big one"?
[MALE VOICE in Ente Islan]
Uhhh...
Not only could I
hear what he said,
but I understood him.
So you can see why I'm confused.
[MAOU] Yeah.
And because of the
quakes we've had lately,
you assume they're
the disturbances
he was referring to?
Yeah.
[MAOU] The Idea Link.
A method of communication
where beings
in different worlds tune
their minds to each other
and share impressions
and concepts.
They're able to transfer
these ideas across time
and space by utilizing
sonar probe technology.
When the signal reaches
the desired target,
it causes a magical explosion
that creates various phenomena.
In this case, these
pulses could've easily
caused all the
recent earthquakes.
And if that's true,
given the number
of quakes we've had,
the only possible
explanation is that somebody
is dead set on tracking
down me and Emilia.
A big one
is coming soon indeed.
Things are happening
faster than I expecte--
[splutters]
[CHIHO] What's the
matter, Mister Maou?
Are you all right?
[MAOU thinking] Oh, come on!
What is Emi doing walking
in here with Ashiya?
What's wrong?
[MAOU] Nothing.
I haven't done anything wrong.
Huh?
So anyway. To wrap this up.
The tinnitus and weird voices
you've been hearing aren't
really a cause for concern,
so don't worry about that.
The real issue is whether or not
a big one is actually coming.
And assuming that it is,
I think simply being able to
warn the people around you
will make a big
difference, don't you?
I'm glad I built up the nerve
to actually ask you about this.
I feel a million
times better already.
[MAOU thinking] Hear that, Emi?
I'm doing a good thing here!
Anyone can see I'm just
trying to help this girl out!
Can't tell my parents about it.
Or school friends, either.
That's why-- Well,
I guess I knew you'd
be the only one
who'd believe me.
You're kind, and so gentle.
I love talking to you.
See. Thing is.
You're real nice and--uh.
I uhh--Well,
Mister Maou, I like-
That's enough!
I hope you know
you're conversing
with the worst
being in the world.
Please. Not now.
Trust me, little girl,
this one is not what he seems.
He's cruel, cunning, and stupid.
Hey now.
Don't pop up out of nowhere
and start saying
hateful things like that!
That's about as rude
as a person can be!
Who are you to him anyway?
I'm his archenemy. Look.
Take it from someone
who knows. He sucks.
Nothing good will
come from knowing him.
[MAOU] Emi, cut it out.
Never tell me what to do!
You need to calm down too, Chi!
No, Mister Maou,
I won't calm down!
I remember you.
You came into our restaurant
a couple days ago, right?
Yeah, so what?
[CHIHO] What's the deal?
Are you his ex or something?
[EMI] Where'd you get that idea?
I was dead on,
you totally are!
In that case, what I do
with him is none of
your business, got it?
And if you know
what's good for you,
you'll stay out of my way!
You don't even know what
you're saying right now!
It's not like that with us,
so why don't you just relax?
Oh yeah?
If that's true, tell me
why you're always
around him like a stalker!
[EMI] You need to stop yakking,
little girl, and listen:
There is nothing between us!
If anybody here needs
to stop "yakking"
it's you, sister!
You better take that back! Now!
You think I'm afraid
of you? Please!
[MAOU] Can we please take
it down a notch or three?
[rumbling]
[loud crashing]
[MALE CUSTOMER 3A] Earthquake!
[MALE CUSTOMER 3B] A big one!
Mister Maou!
[CHIHO] Wha-- What happened?
[EMI] Oh, good.
I'm glad you woke up.
[CHIHO] Where are we?
[EMI] Well, we're trapped.
This used to be the café.
[CHIHO] Where's Mister Maou?
[EMI] Not with us, I can
tell you that much for sure.
[CHIHO] Yeah, but do
you think he's okay?
[EMI] Oh. You're worried
he got crushed
by the rubble, are you?
Well, it's true he'd
make a lot of people happy
if he kicked off, me included.
But I guarantee he's alive.
[EMI thinking] I'll be
the one to defeat him.
He's not allowed to
die here. No way, no how.
[CHIHO] Yeah, right.
I'm sure he'll be fine.
[EMI] Oh, he will.
Trust me on that.
Emi Yusa, by the way.
In case you're still wondering,
there really is nothing
between Maou and me, I swear.
[CHIHO] Chiho Sasaki.
And I guess I'll pretend
to believe you for now.
[EMI] So, what made
you fall for him anyway?
[CHIHO] What are
you talking about?
I haven't fallen for him!
[EMI] Then you picked a fight
with me in a public restaurant
because you don't like him?
[CHIHO] No, I do! I mean, I--!
Not like... Nnnnn...
I guess I really
am super obvious.
[EMI] Don't worry,
your secret is safe with me.
[CHIHO] That might
be more comforting
if you told me how you really
feel about Mister Maou.
[EMI] How I feel?
[CHIHO] For someone
who claims to be his enemy,
you sure do seem chummy
with him whenever
you're together.
[EMI] Like the Godfather says,
friends close and
enemies closer.
[CHIHO] Huh?
[EMI] I've known
him for a long time,
Chiho, almost my entire life.
[EMI] Just 'cause I'm friendly
with him doesn't mean what
I said to you is any less true.
Loving Maou will get you hurt.
[CHIHO] I guess I don't quite
understand what you mean.
[EMI] You'll get it.
But, in reality, maybe
it's better if you don't.
For now. Rest up.
You could use a little sleep.
[EMI] I hear you breathing.
She's asleep; you can come out!
[rocks tumbling]
[DEEP VOICE]
Stay outta my business!
[EMI] Maou? What
happened to your body?
[MAOU] Don't know.
It just changed on me.
[EMI thinking]
His magic. It's back.
[MAOU] Man. This is the worst.
How'm I supposed
to explain this?
[EMI thinking] This is it.
Now's my chance.
If I focus all of the
celestial force I have left.
I can still make a
Sacred Sword strong enough
to defeat him!
[MAOU] Take care of Chi.
These people need me.
Hopefully there
aren't many casualties.
But we don't have time to
wait for the rescue squad.
I'll figure something out.
[EMI thinking] Is he serious?
[MAOU] Alright. It's time to go.
[EMI thinking] What? Why?
Why would the
Devil rescue humans?