Oh, for shame; I am a
complete and utter failure.
I dare not even
think about how much
just this single IV will cost.
Even if I do
manage to get better,
I can never again look
His Majesty in the eye.
Ah!
Well, well.
Look who's back
among the living.
Yes--well.
Kind Miss.
I just want to be clear
about one minor detail.
I'm correct in assuming you take
public health insurance, yes?
Oh, don't worry
about that.
For now.
We need to give you
a little more medicine.
No, thank you!
[ASHIYA] What's this?
Excuse me.
Are you all right, sir?
A policeman?
What is going on here?
[ASHIYA groans]
[ASHIYA] Olba!
Mister Ashiya!
[NURSE A]
Didn't I say you weren't ready
to get out of bed yet?
That's it,
I'm adding another bag.
You're getting two now!
[ASHIYA] I can't believe it!
[NURSE A]
And I can't believe you!
How do you feel?
[OLBA]
"Villa Rosa Sasazuka."
[NURSE A]
...You most certainly are not!
Hold on, Chi.
I'm coming!
[EMI screams]
If you want the pain
to end, all you have to do
is stop resisting and
hand over Better Half.
[EMI] It's not materializing, so
what do you expect me to do?
If you wanna know what
I think, I'd say the sword
is rejecting you.
[SARUE] By all rights, the
Sacred Sword shouldn't be
in the hands of
a mere human being.
Therefore, we must take it
back once and for all;
this is Heaven's
collective will.
[EMI] Either way, Chiho's got
nothing to do with this.
Please, let her go.
Sorry, but I'm afraid
I can't do that.
She's a precious
specimen, this one.
A human who loves the
Devil--even after learning
the truth of who he really is.
She'll serve
as our lab rat,
and through her we will discover
what impact the Devil's power
has on the human ecosystem.
You're sick;
you know that?
You watch your
tongue, human.
None may speak in such a manner
to the Great Archangel Sariel!
[EMI screams]
[MAOU] Ah, son of a--!
Damn.
It's a barrier field!
You're very durable.
But you and I both know
your body can't withstand this
much longer, plus I hate
to cause a lady pain.
[EMI screams]
Although,
on second thought,
that horrific howl
isn't exactly ladylike.
You're far more attractive when
you aren't screaming, darling--
Ah.
Everyone, it seems we have
an uninvited guest tonight.
Maou... help.
Let's give our very
special friend
a very special welcome.
Say hello.
Satan's current power
level makes you quite able
to defeat him, Bel.
[EMI] So that's it then?
The Devil and I both
perish in another world.
And back in Ente Isla,
things continue on the same
as they did before
you came here.
That's it?
That's what you want?
[SARUE] Enough chit-chat.
As patron angel of the
Doctrinal Correction Council,
I hereby grant Crestia Bel
moral authority to end this.
Do your worst.
[CHIHO] Miss Suzuno.
Why?
Tell me why!
[SUZUNO] No.
I can't!
I don't want to
sacrifice anyone else!
Aw man, what a pain
in the butt.
[MAOU] Suck on this!
Woozy.
[MAOU yells]
What was that?!
[MAOU] Suzuno?
[MAOU] Suzuno!
You totally smashed my bike!
How could you do
something like that?
What the heck did Dullahan
ever do to you, huh?
Now you're gonna
owe me for the new bike,
the bike registration fee
and the over-sized
garbage disposal fee!
No, I am not even kidding!
[MAOU] Wait! Hey!
[SUZUNO] Shut up!
I don't want to hear
any more nonsense from you!
[MAOU] Stop!
Please, just gimme
a minute here, will ya?
[pants being unzipped]
You're embarrassing me.
Put your clothes
back on, please.
[MAOU] Right.
Now I'm ready!
[SUZUNO] What
is wrong with you?
[MAOU] Ha! You probably
won't understand,
since you've never had a job.
But try anyway.
MgRonald's uniforms are
given to employees on loan.
If I damage one in
a non-work situation,
then it'll come out
of my paycheck.
And the Devil's Castle is
running pretty low on treasure!
[SUZUNO] Give me a break!
[MAOU] Hey!
Stop taking your
clothes off in public,
you pervert!
[MAOU] That was your fault!
You got guts comin' here
alone and movin' in next door.
Plus you're a decent cook,
so I let some things slide!
But now you're in my way,
trying to hurt my crew?
Sorry, but as a Substitute
Manager, you shall not pass!
[SUZUNO] You knew
who I really was?
The whole time?
[MAOU] How could I not?
A sweet young girl moves next
door to an all-male household,
inveigles her way in, and starts
cooking and doting on them?
It just doesn't happen.
[URUSHIHARA] We still have
leftovers from Suzuno.
Seems a little
celestial force-y, but hey.
YOLO.
[MAOU] You sure did a number
on Ashiya though, didn't you?
It really is too bad.
I thought you showed
a lot of promise.
I mean, you even
got along with Emi.
But in the end, you're
no better than Olba.
You pretend to be good.
But you don't care what you
have to sacrifice to get power,
isn't that right?
Quiet!
If your M.O.
is doing whatever it takes
to get what you want,
how are you any different
from the demons you hunt?
[SUZUNO] Shut up!
You buddied up to Emi
and Chi and helped them
with the bazaar.
They were your friends and
you dragged them right down
into your mess.
You should be ashamed.
[SUZUNO] Just shut up!
[SUZUNO] You're insane.
Oww...
[SUZUNO]
Why didn't you...?
Didn't have a choice.
I used up my magic
destroying the barrier.
What's wrong?
You not gonna fight me?
Well, in that case,
I'm just gonna go.
Chi's waiting for me.
It's no use.
You can't defeat him.
Not the way you are right now.
[MAOU] Great, so you are working
with someone; who is it?
The archangel Sariel.
Lovely.
But thanks.
Emi couldn't take
him down either.
Ow.
The moon is his source.
The closer he gets to it,
the more powerful he is.
With no magic, you
don't have a chance.
It would be pointless
to even try.
[MAOU] So what,
you gonna run?
[SUZUNO] I don't
get why you won't.
'Cause it's my job.
Chi works under me; I've gotta
make sure she's looked after.
Plus, I don't abandon
my people and run;
I do have some dignity left.
And let's be real, you're
counting on me, too, right?
To do what?
To put the screws
to your pal Sariel.
That's why you didn't
stop Chi from calling me,
isn't it?
So that I'd
take him out?
No.
I mean, I only meant to--
Well, it's all
the same to me!
[SUZUNO] Why?
Why would a Demon
like him act this way?
He's supposed to
be the bad guy.
If caring for his
friends makes him evil--
Then so am I.
From now on I'm fighting
for my dignity, too.
[URUSHIHARA] What is Maou doing?
I bet he's gotten
himself mixed up
in some kind of trouble again.
So yeah, what else is new?
[doorbell]
'Zat Maou?
He didn't bail on Emilia
and leave her to deal?
[URUSHIHARA] Coming.
Was there a problem down at--?
Olba?
Good to see you, Lucifer.
How've you been?
You got out, huh?
You look like
you're doing well.
[OLBA] As do you.
Not a bad set-up you
have here, my friend.
[URUSHIHARA] I like it okay.
Tell me: how would you
like to go back to Heaven?
[OLBA] I know you
want to, Lucifer.
And I can make
that wish come true.
[SARUE] If the Sacred Sword
won't reveal itself after
you've endured
this much torture.
I suppose I have no
choice but to remove it
from your body directly.
What are you
talking about?
[EMI] Hey!
Wait!
What do you think you're doing?
[SARUE] Come now, you know
precisely what I'm doing.
I'm taking the heavenly
silver that forms Better Half
straight out of your flesh.
[CHIHO] You take your hands
off of her, you big pervert!
[SARUE] Well, look
who found her voice.
Trust me, little girl, I'm
not lusting over 'flat chest'
over here; she's
not my cup of tea.
Flat chest?
I'd take that
back if I were you!
[SARUE]...have more of the
attributes I'm interested in.
I'll have plenty of time
for a more thorough examination,
but my initial impression
is quite positive.
You're depraved beyond all
redemption, you bucket o' crap!
Perv!
Dirty old man!
Deviant freak!
Filthy peeping Tom!
Panty snatcher!
[SARUE] Now that
is just going too far!
I've had all the lip
I can take from you!
[EMI] You lay so much
as a finger on Chiho,
and you'll live just
long enough to regret it.
For someone
in your position,
you seem quite confident
in yourself, Hero!
You misunderstand.
It's not me; you hurt that
girl and you will literally
have the Devil to pay.
[SARUE] Is that a fact?
Does Emilia, the mighty Hero,
rely on the Devil
to save her skin?
[EMI] That's not
what I'm saying.
You ran a competing
restaurant across the street
from MgRonald's, and
you still don't get it?
What, that my place
was better?
[EMI] That girl is
a MgRonald's employee.
And the Devil is
her shift manager.
If one of their
people is in danger.
It is the duty and the
obligation of the manager
to protect her,
no matter what the cost.
Have you lost
your mind, Hero?
Are you honestly foolish enough
to believe that the Devil
is in any way bound by the
conventions of this world?
[MAOU, breathing heavily]
Damn it. This sucks.
Elevator out of order.
So tired.
[EMI] He's not bound
by them, you're right.
But he still chooses to follow
them of his own free will.
That's him.
The A-level staffer and
substitute manager of the
Hatagaya MgRonald's franchise:
the man called Sadao Maou.
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
Oh, this is hilarious!
The Devil and his Hero,
like two peas in a pod!
[MAOU] Yo.
Mister Maou!
I'm sorry I kept
you waiting, Chi.
[CHIHO] You're naked!
[MAOU] Glad to see
you're safe, Emi.
Stay away, jerk!
And don't look!
[MAOU] Oh, come on!
I can't believe you'd
show your face here.
[MAOU] And I can't believe
the little perfumed dwarf of
a Manager from SFC is
Mister Gaze from the Fall.
I'm not above going
undercover to get what I want.
The divine silver that forms
Better Half is Heaven's
most prized possession;
I'm taking it back.
After all, we can't let
the Hero hang onto it, can we?
[MAOU] Frankly, I couldn't care
less about Heaven's problems.
Trouble is, you decided to
mess with my co-workers,
that we have an issue, "buddy."
How dare you make
Chi go through such
a frightening experience?
He really does care!
[MAOU] Chi is a valued
employee of MgRonald's.
As the Devil and
as Shift Manager,
I protect those
under my charge.
It is my job!
He doesn't care.
What can you do with
that frail little body of yours?
Mister Maou!
With the pittance
of magic you have left,
you're no match for me!
[CHIHO] You're
hurting him!
[EMI] Maou!
[MAOU] Don't worry, Chi.
I'm fine.
I ain't losing this.
You're truly unbelievable.
How far is that false
courage going take you?
[MAOU] Damn it.
With no magic, I can't
do any real damage.
C'mon Maou, think!
Unlike you Demon King,
I get stronger the closer
I get to the moon!
I'd say you're
in a bit of a pickle.
What will you do?
[OLBA in Ente Islan]
Destroying this place
would cause a panic.
[URUSHIHARA] That's
putting it mildly.
[SUZUNO] Lucifer?
[URUSHIHARA] But we'd get
a whole lot of magic from
the fear and anger, right?
Forget about it,
it won't do you any good.
Too late.
Look.
[SUZUNO] What're they doing?
What in the
world is this?
What's happening?
[SARUE] Magnificent!
Look how close the moon is!
I'm brimming with power!
All right, if that's
how you wanna play it,
no more holding back!
[MAOU] Huh?
[MAOU] Let me go or
I'll kick your face in!
[SARUE laughs]
[SARUE] Can't you see
your resistance is futile?
With this much
power at hand,
no one will be able to stop me,
not even the Devil himself!
[cars honk]
[GIRL A] What's going on?
I am coming
to your aide, Sire.
Whoa, wait.
This was not part of the plan!
That's not Celestial Force,
it's magic.
Which means that--There must
be panic down in the streets.
That's it, Mister Maou.
[MAOU] Yes.
Thanks to you, my magic
is completely replenished.
[SUZUNO] You're all right now.
[SUZUNO] You simpleton!
Huh?!
[SUZUNO] If I were you, I'd
mind my powers, Good Sadao!
Or are you trying
to kill all of us?
[MAOU] Right. My bad!
[EMI] You're not really gonna
fight in those are you?
Never fear.
This underwear is made
from a special fabric.
It's extra durable!
[EMI] You're puttin' a lot
of faith in your panties!
[MAOU] Hey, Suzuno.
Watch after them, will you?
I will, of course.
[CHIHO] Wait.
I'm confused.
I'm so sorry.
I do hope you
can forgive me.
Please.
I'm back on
the right side.
Oh, Miss Suzuno.
[SARUE] You would
align with the Devil?
Have you lost your mind, Bel?
I'm afraid you're the one
who's lost it, Sariel.
You force a false
peace onto our people.
You create chaos
for another world.
And you betray those
you should be protecting.
Those who would do
anything for their faith,
even give up their lives!
As Head Investigator
of the Doctrinal
Correction Council,
I refuse to let your base,
self-serving brand of justice
go unchallenged!
[SARUE] Please.
Why don't you get off
your high horse?
The inquisition's bloodthirsty
God of Death has no right
to talk to me about justice!
Enough!
Of one thing I am certain, Sadao
Maou's life here is no trespass.
It is no thorn in
the side of justice!
[SARUE] Believe what you
will, but with the power
of this giant moon behind me.
No one can stave me off!
You're in for
a rude awakening.
Excellent, the great
Sariel will dispose
of the Devil for us.
One last thing.
I'm gonna need you to go ahead
and hand me Emilia's bag.
Hm?
Sure.
I have no idea why
you'd want it though.
Duh.
So I can give it
back to her.
What?
If I don't, she'll be
one pissed off Hero.
No. You tricked me!
You little weasel!
Lucifer!
[URUSHIHARA] Don't you know
Heaven is a place on earth,
specifically a one-room
second-floor apartment?
My job's done here!
You can take it
from here, Satan.
N' give 'em hell!
No.
Not the moon!
[MAOU] Hey. Sariel.
I'm a nice guy, so
I'll let you pick.
[SARUE] Pick what?
[MAOU] Run home with your
tail between your legs,
or get the living crap
beaten out of you.
What'll it be?
[SARUE] That's
an easy one.
Except I believe you're
mistaken about which of us
walks away from this!
A Devil who can only
get power by doping himself up
with human negativity is
nothing to be scared of!
[MAOU] Aw. Man!
I've had enough of this!
He's on a
freaking rampage!
You're coming
with me, little girl!
[CHIHO] No, I'm not!
Any permanent damage?
You're my hero, Satan.
--[MAOU] So, yes.
--[EMI] Eh.
I don't even care anymore.
That stupid perv bag
tormented me all day long.
Just put me down now.
[MAOU] Emi, listen to me.
What is it?
[MAOU] Your shirt's open.
I will kill that Devil!
Once I get my hands
on the Sacred Sword,
he's as good as dead!
I will take his head off!
[MAOU] Just give it
up, douchebag.
You may be invincible against
anyone with celestial force.
But you decided
to dance with the Devil.
[EMI] I said, put me down.
[MAOU] As I was saying
before I was interrupted,
you decided to dance
with the Devil.
So now I'm gonna mop
the floor with ya!
If you want
a Sacred Sword,
come and try to take mine.
Go on, you creepy
angel freak.
Beg for mercy and see
what good it does you!
Oh. Dear God.
Please forgive me for being
such a complete and total tool.
[MAOU] Yeesh.
That idiot sure did
a number on this place.
Man, I finally get my
magic back and now I have
to fix everything again!
Your fault for taking
so long to get here.
Uh.
When someone saves your butt,
most people just say thank you.
I don't recall asking
for your assistance.
[MAOU] Whatever, Tiny Tits!
Your tits are small!
More importantly,
Emilia--!
[EMI] Shut up!
'More importantly?'
This is very important!
[CHIHO] Please everyone
just calm down!
Stop fighting!
I am here, Sire!
Sincerest apologies
for being late,
I had to stop at
home for my cape.
Your cape?
Dude! Why even come?
The battle's already over!
[EMI] Who cares?
Just put on some clothes!
[ASHIYA] Again I
have failed you!
[MAOU] Aw crap, I left
my uniform downstairs.
And I missed work!
My perfect attendance record!
[ASHIYA] I brought
your cape, too!
[URUSHIHARA] Wonder
if it's all over.
[stomach grumbles]
[URUSHIHARA] Man, that
was a lotta work for me.
I need some fried fish.