[EMI] So, basically
you have no confidence.
If I lose, I don't think I'll
ever be able to recover.
[EMI] Okay, listen--
[CHIHO] Ignoring the
fact that she was half
a year early for New Year's,
the girl still put together
a really nice bento box!
I just don't trust her!
As far as we know,
this is all part
of her elaborate plan
to slowly poison them to death.
If she's a real assassin
from Ente Isla,
the job's already done.
Right.
Trying to make
everything about
all that angel-demon stuff
is just a lame excuse.
You gotta tackle
this thing head-on.
[CHIHO] Yeah. Good point.
[doorbell]
[SUZUNO] Yes, one moment please!
Greetings.
Good Sadao, you have visitors.
--[MAOU] 'Kay, hold on a sec.
--[CHIHO] S-S-S--
--Who is it? Tax collector?
--[EMI] What the what? Chiho?
--[CHIHO] S-S-S--
--[MAOU] Really?
--[CHIHO] S-S-Sadao?
[CHIHO] Oh!
You've been cooking
for Mister Ashiya
while he recovers
from heat stroke?
Now it all makes sense!
Wow.
That's incredible,
how do you manage
to chop the shiso
leaves so thin?
[SUZUNO] First you
slice them in half.
Then you gather them into
bunches before you julienne.
Yeah?
Well, how did you get
the lettuce so crispy?
That is the way
lettuce is;
you simply wash it
and shake the water off.
[CHIHO] Really? Color me
impressed, Miss Suzuno!
Jeez, it's getting
crowded in here.
Hope we have enough
bowls n' chopsticks.
Don't worry, Mr. Maou,
I brought mine with me.
[MAOU] Oh. 'Kay. Guess there's
nothing to worry about.
[ASHIYA] Miss Suzuno
is cooking in my stead.
I'm a disgrace.
[URUSHIHARA] Whoa.
Breakfast already?
Wait. Where the heck
am I supposed to sit?
Not cool, Bro.
Unacceptable!
You make room for Emi,
but not for me?
She's technically
our guest.
[URUSHIHARA] And
these are the bowls
from that stupid takeout place!
[MAOU] Bon appétit!
[ALL] Bon appétit.
[URUSHIHARA] Screw you!
[CHIHO] Dang. I hope
one day I can become
a great cook
like you, Miss Suzuno.
[SUZUNO] I am certain
you will learn quickly.
[CHIHO] You think so?
As long as
you remember,
even when serving others, a
chef has motives of her own.
In this case,
I'm forcing everyone
to help me get through
my abundance of noodles.
I bought in bulk
to save money
'til I can find a job,
but with this summer heat,
I don't know if I'll be able
to finish it before it spoils.
[EMI] Speaking of, what kinds
of jobs are you looking for?
I do not
reasonably expect
to find full-time work.
So long as my
expenses are covered,
I will indenture myself
wherever I am able.
[EMI] "Indenture"
herself? Who says that?
Well, you could always
come work at MgRonald's.
Yeah, Chi could
train you.
And I'd be there
to help out too,
so it wouldn't be
that stressful.
[URUSHIHARA] Yeah, the
learning-the-job part
is not what's
gonna be stressful.
We've been pretty
understaffed lately;
we could use another
set of hands.
[URUSHIHARA] Think about
how Lil Miss High School's
gonna take it.
Don't you think
she'd be a big help, Chi?
[CHIHO] Huh?
Uh. Right. Yeah. Sure.
[URUSHIHARA] And fail.
Well, hey, there's no need
to make a snap decision here.
Trust me, when it comes to
working with your friends,
there are just as many
minuses as there are pluses.
That's very kind,
Good Sadao.
I'll take your extremely
generous offer
under consideration
and let you know if I
require your help.
[MAOU] Cool. Sounds good.
[SUZUNO] Perhaps I will rely
on you as well, Good Chiho.
Um. Great.
Finding a job is indeed
of high importance,
but in the interim, your time
may be better served helping
the young lady acquire new
clothing and belongings.
It's true my wardrobe
is a bit barren;
I don't even own a decent pair
of shoes, much less a purse.
Hang on, all of
your clothing
is traditional
like that?
[SUZUNO] Indeed it is.
[SUZUNO] What? Is that unusual?
[ASHIYA] Well, I wouldn't
exactly classify it
as run of the mill.
[URUSHIHARA] You know where
to find this fashion stuff,
right Yusa?
Hey! No touch!
I don't want your slacker
germs all over my stuff!
Jeez, chill!
I've never met a person
who had less shame than
you, Mister Urushihara.
[URUSHIHARA]
What the crap?
Why is everyone
always such a jerk to me?
He does make a good
point though Miss Yusa;
why don't you
take her shopping?
Sure, maybe after
I get off work?
[SUZUNO] Yes, thank you.
I shall explore the shopping
area until you're done.
[EMI] Sounds like a plan.
[MAOU] Why do I get the
feeling this is trouble
just waiting to happen?
[EMI] Cool.
[SUZUNO] Many thanks.
Hey. Wait. Did you
just change clothes?
I did.
[EMI] Jeez, her options
really are limited.
[SUZUNO] Something wrong?
No. Not at all.
Well, we'd better
get a move on.
[CHIHO] All righty.
Sorry again about
visiting so early.
I sure hope you feel
better soon, Mister Ashiya.
[ASHIYA] That's very nice.
I sincerely appreciate
everything you've done here.
Now, Sire.
Please be the kind, trustworthy
gentleman I know you to be
and escort Miss Sasaki home.
[MAOU] Yeah, sure.
Will do, Mom.
[CHIHO] I like your
bike, Mister Maou.
[MAOU] My steed.
He's called Dullahan.
[CHIHO] Cool. Why doesn't
it have a carrier on back?
[MAOU] Well, he's
a utility bike,
so he wouldn't have
a feature like that.
It's kind
of a shame, huh?
[MAOU] I'd give you a pump,
but there's a pretty
hefty fine if we get caught.
"One person per bike".
Yeah that's not really
where I was goin' with that.
So hey, I'm kinda
curious about something.
What do your
parents have to say
about you coming to hang
out at my "Bachelor Pad?"
[CHIHO] Matter of fact,
they didn't mind one bit.
I was just honest about where I
was going, and they said 'okay'.
Guess we're "Mother
approved," as they say.
Like the cereal?
What about your Dad?
[CHIHO] He was all, "I think
it's great you've already found
a man you want to cook for!"
Speakin' of, since
Miss Suzuno won't be there
to cook for you, do
you have any idea
what you're gonna
do for lunch?
[MAOU] Uh. No. Guess I haven't
really thought about it.
[CHIHO] Oh! So--
no plans, huh? Great!
Do you mind if I
bring you something?
[MAOU] Well, I suppose Ashiya
would be happier knowing
I was eating your
home cooking instead
o' subsisting on
junk food. So, yeah.
Since you offered,
I'll take you up on it!
How wonderful!
Then I'll make sure
it's a hearty,
nutritionally balanced meal,
so Ashiya doesn't get
himself into a panic.
Alright, Chi,
tell me the truth.
Aren't you a little
weirded out that we're--?
[CHIHO] What?
That you're demons and
angels from another world?
Yeah, um-- That.
[CHIHO] Well, since you asked.
I'd be lying if I said
it didn't bother me.
Miss Yusa and I have
been texting each other
back and forth.
So I've learned a lot
about who you are--
and the things you've done.
But I fell for you way
before I knew about
any of that stuff,
so none of it can
change the way I feel now!
I mean just
look at that face.
That is not the face
of a person who wants
to take over the whole world.
Yeah. About that...
Miss Yusa did everything
she could to keep me
from falling for you,
'cause she was trying
to save me from getting hurt.
But I know what's in my heart
and I won't turn away from it.
The only person
who can ever stop me
from caring about you is me.
[CHIHO] Even if you just
think of me as a friend
or a trusted co-worker,
that's totally fine.
Because that
won't change things.
It's not going to change
my mind about how I feel,
and it's certainly
not going to make me
act differently towards you.
Ah jeez, this is
what makes you
humans so scary,
y'know that?
[CHIHO] I do.
Especially us girls.
Mess with one of us and
you might lose a body part!
I'll be sure to
keep that in mind.
[SUZUNO] You are truly loved,
my Good Sadao.
[CHIHO] Miss Suzuno?
How long have you
been standing there?
[SUZUNO] Long enough.
The whole ordeal
was a rare sight to behold.
You're extremely
virtuous,
and quite cute, to be so
honest about your feelings.
Regardless of whom
you've picked.
[MAOU] Huh?
[MAOU] Chi?
Aw, man,
she's gonna break
her neck riding all
crazy fast like that.
Surprising.
[MAOU] What's surprising?
The fact that I'm
concerned about a friend?
Apologies, but yes.
Be honest: what is your opinion
of a person such as yourself?
Whoa. What's with
the third degree?
[SUZUNO] Mere curiosity.
Nothing more.
Well, let's see.
After she was so straightforward
and honest with me,
it's not fair
to her to play dumb
and pretend like
I don't get it.
And besides,
her folks trust me.
At least I mean, well
her mom does anyway,
so I figure I should
take the olive branch
while it's extended.
What's that look for?
Oh. Nothing, Good Sadao.
If you'll excuse me.
I've kept Good Emi
waiting long enough.
If you're headed to the
station, let me walk you there.
[MAOU] Or... not.
[SUZUNO] No.
That would be fine.
[EMI] You find your wallet?
[SUZUNO] Uh.
Yes--Thank you.
I apologize for
keeping you waiting.
[EMI] Please.
It's fine.
So--Um...
We're about to ride the--
what's it called? "Train"?
[EMI] Yeah. We're only
one stop away from Shinjuku,
but it's a bit far to walk.
[SUZUNO] While we're
on the subject.
I should mention. I've
never been on one before.
[EMI] Huh?
[SUZUNO] Although, I did
learn that Tokyo residents
pay for travel
with watermelons.
Do you know where
I might obtain one?
Yeah. That's
not-- wait back up.
Now I'm confused
about something.
How'd you get to Sasazuka
in the first place?
Well that's
a silly question;
I arrived here through
the Gate, obviously.
Oh, yeah.
Obviousl--
Wait, did you
just say the Gate?
Okay.
Just to clarify, you're
saying you're from Ente Isla.
[SUZUNO] Yes. Of course
I am. Did you not know?
[EMI] You have never said
one word about Ente Isla!
[SUZUNO] Maybe not,
but you did!
You asked if I was
after the Devil!
And then you warned
me that it would
end badly if I got too close
to him, and as a favor,
you advised me to
steer clear, remember?
[EMI] Huh?
[SUZUNO] Having survived
countless brutal battles,
I'm not one to
shy away from fear,
but once I heard that even you,
a Hero, considered him a threat,
I had no choice but to withdraw.
Left with no alternatives,
I asked for your assistance.
You then pledged
your aid and gave me
your contact information.
[EMI] Huuuh?!
[SUZUNO] I thought you
said all those nice things
because you
intuited who I was!
How in the world could
I possibly "intuit" that?
[SUZUNO] Didn't it strike
you as being a tad bit odd?
All of a sudden, a sweet
young girl like myself moves
next door, inveigles her way
into an all-male home,
and starts cooking for everyone
like some sort of slave girl?
[EMI] You are the last person
who should talk about
what's ridiculous!
I don't understand;
what exactly was
going through your head
when you asked me
if I was after him?
Uh. No--wait--I--
Look, I don't--
'cause-I'm still trying to
wrap my head around all this.
Why did you ask me if I had
an "intimate" relationship
with him?
Because, you imbecile,
I was informed the two
of you had joined together!
That is a load of bull!
We were forced, coincidentally,
to take down a mutual adversary
together, and that's it!
You sound like an idiot
saying things like that!
And please don't tell me
you actually believed
I was conspiring
with the devil
to exact my revenge
against the Church.
You were the one at
the convenience store
with the sneak-attack
last night!
What about
a convenient snack?
Well, guess the mystery
of the Ente Islan
attacker is solved.
[EMI] The assailant
had the power
to neutralize my sacred sword,
so I knew they
couldn't have been a Demon.
Which means it was you!
Wait. Hang on.
[EMI] She doesn't
have any paint marks.
And she doesn't smell bad.
I did no such
thing, you moron!
I know how powerful
Emilia the Hero is!
Fine.
If that's the case,
then who are you
and what are you doing hanging
around the Devil's Castle?
[SUZUNO in Ente Islan]
[EMI] One sec!
[EMI] I don't want
to be late for work,
so save all the
details for shopping, okay?
[EMI] Relax,
this is how it's done.
[SUZUNO shouts]
[SUZUNO] How dare you?
I haven't the time for this; you
will release me this instant!
[SUZUNO growls]
[SUZUNO] Why do you
insist upon hindering me?
[crash]
I still can't get over that.
"How are those tiny
people inside there?"
It was a flat-screen
television dummy,
not a puppet theatre.
I would appreciate
the dropping of that subject!
[EMI] Where did you
learn about Japan anyway?
Like what is up
with the kimono?
[SUZUNO] I did
a fair bit of research
into the history
of this place.
In every book I read,
yukata and kimono
were the preferred mode
of fashion for everyone.
[SUZUNO] I studied something
called "historical drama."
Several documentaries
gave me some real insight.
[EMI] That
explains a lot.
[SUZUNO] In fact some of them
were incredibly helpful.
"O-arashi Monjiro."
"Lone Lion and Cub."
As well as my personal
favorite, "Three for the Slay."
"Mito Fuku-shogun"
and "Oko-rinbo Shogun,"
though, didn't quite
resonate with me.
Yeah--right.
So. Getting back on topic,
why did the Doctrinal
Correction Council's
head investigator move
next door to the Devil's Castle?
Explain that part to me.
My investigation
started with Olba Mayer.
The only useful details
he had were the location
of Satan's residence and
a vague idea of his lifestyle.
I thought if I kept
tabs on the Devil--
[EMI] Then I'd show up.
Yeah that makes sense.
Okay, but what do
you want from me?
First, let us be certain
we understand one another.
What Father Mayer did to you
was completely deplorable;
I cannot apologize
to you enough for his actions.
And since based on
our initial conversations,
I assumed you knew
I was Ente Islan,
it became quite
clear to me the story
of you joining forces
with the Devil was false.
Olba's will is not the
collective will of the Church.
And while it is not my place
to speak on their behalf;
I would like
to be on your side.
Olba is out of the picture
now. So cut to the chase.
I want for you to
join me in my quest
to eliminate King Satan, and
then return home with me.
The Church would
make your survival
public information,
but they would cover up
Olba's insidiousness.
Do we have a deal?
[EMI] No.
I am doing everything
within my power
to restore your honor,
Hero, so why not?
[EMI] Because, I don't
care what the Church
or the kingdoms or anyone
else thinks of me anymore.
Surely you understand
why I can't just up
and trust someone who works
for your organization.
The same one led
in part by the jerkwad
who caved in a crowded mall
just to kill me and the Devil.
Sorry to disappoint
you, Suzuno,
but unfortunately, that's the
way things have to be now.
[EMI] Olba teamed up
with that idiot Lucifer
in his attempt to murder me.
Emeralda and Albert can
give you a first hand account
of how much trouble
he caused these people.
Or you can ask
Urushihara himself.
[EMI] Besides, I'm a Hero;
taking on the Devil
is my duty, not yours.
Do not interfere.
[SUZUNO] But if we
cooperate we could--
"Doctrinal Correction Council".
Just call it what it really
is: the New Inquisition.
I can't believe
you're with them,
and you still don't get it.
Also, I don't know
what you're up to
with this whole Cooking
for Demons thing,
but tread lightly, 'cause
if you mess with him
or pull any cheap
tricks on him--
[EMI] I absolutely
guarantee you that Maou
will see right through
your little charade.
He may not look it,
but he's still the Devil.
[SUZUNO] I appreciate
the warning.
Good, just promise you'll
also give some thought
to your own position
in the Council, okay?
Oh, I grabbed this
at the station for you.
This one, too.
If you're gonna
be stickin' around,
you gotta figure out
how this place works.
For reals.
[EMI] The way you talk
and dress is more than
a little bit on the
old-fashioned side.
Anyways, I gotta run
or I'll be late for work.
We can go over the finer
details after my shift tonight.
Can you
ever forgive me?
Uh. Forgive
you for what?
[CHIHO] Well.
Your bike. I stole it.
[MAOU] Oh, that.
[CHIHO] I'm so sorry! I'm
so sorry! I'm so sorry!...
[MAOU] No. It's
fine. Chi, stop!
[MAOU] Yep, dead today.
Just like I figured.
The new SFC across the street
jacked all our customers.
[MAOU] And that menacing smile
on Miss Kisaki's face
is freakin' me out.
[KISAKI] This is bad.
I have to go down
to Corporate today
and report our numbers.
Not lookin' forward
to telling them
about our eighty
percent sales drop.
Yeah, no.
[KISAKI] One time an
employee, about my age,
lost big time to a competitor
and as punishment,
got shipped off to Greenland.
[MAOU] For real?
No way we wanna
freeze our butts off
in Greenland, right?
[MAOU] No, ma'am!
[KISAKI] I don't care
what you have to do.
I authorize any means
necessary. Beat SFC!
Yes, ma'am!
[MAOU] Aww,
man this sucks.
Can't believe this is my
first day as fill-in manager.
[BOTH] How can we help you?
[MAN] Pardon me
for interrupting,
I know you must be busy.
I was wondering if I could
speak to your manager, please.
I'm terribly
sorry, sir.
Miss Kisaki's out
on business right now.
But I'm the Shift
Manager on duty,
and I will be happy to assist
you in any way I'm able.
Sadao Maou, I've heard
a lot about you, buddy.
So nice to put a
face with the name.
[MAN] They say you're
sociable, hard working,
and open-minded.
And that you add a
wonderfully human touch
to everything you do.
Wow. I'm uh,
flattered, really.
[MAOU] What's with this guy?
How rude of me.
If you'd pay me the compliment
of accepting my business card?
Ah. Thank you, sir.
[MAOU] You're the manager
of Sentucky Fried Chicken?
Mitsuki Sarue,
how do you do?
Sorry for not coming by
to introduce myself sooner.
As you can see,
I've been a bit busy.
I must admit, this is
a delightful neighborhood.
It is the absolute
perfect combination
of business and pleasure.
And the women
are quite lovely as well.
Yes--that's true.
At any rate, I look forward
to doing business with you,
Mister Sarue.
Hm. Well!
It's a real shame
I can't lay eyes
on your famously ravishing
manager, but-- guh!
[SARUE] Beautiful.
I would be honored
if you'd utilize
those incredibly sensual hands
to prepare a special meal
with extra love, and a side
of passion for yours truly.
Sexy princess.
[MAOU] Sorry, Chi. I prob'ly
should've stepped in
and put that creeper
in his place.
[CHIHO] No, Mister Maou;
totally not your fault!
And besides, who does
that disgusting little weirdo
he think he is?
Wearing those dumb
sunglasses inside?
And so much cologne
I'll be smelling it all day!
Ugh. He won't win!
[MAOU] That's right!
[CHIHO] Huh?
We'll have workable
intel on the enemy soon.
I dispatched my top spy.
[CHIHO] Really?
[ASHIYA] I will not let
you down, my dear King.
I shall thoroughly investigate
'Sentucky Fried Chicken'.
And bring those vile
intruders to justice!
[RIKA] I am a hungry girl;
I can tell you
that much for sure--
Salutations.
Have you completed your
service for the day?
[EMI] Did you seriously end
up just buying more yukata?
Where'd you even get
that kind of money?
[SUZUNO] It was
quite simple really;
I had some easily
converted assets
which I took to a resale
shop called Mugi-hyo.
[SALESMAN] Whoa,
this is the real deal!
[EMI] And I'm sure
they didn't lowball
someone as wise to the
ways of the world as you.
And look here.
I got my own card, too!
[FEMALE ATM VOICE] Please
double-check the amount
and enter your
method of payment.
[FEMALE ATM VOICE] If you
would like a paper copy
of your receipt,
please select the
green "yes" button.
[SUZUNO] Please, what
more do you want from me?
[EMI] Yeah,
great job.
[RIKA] So Emi, I'm guessing
this girl is a friend of yours?
Uh. Well--She's
more like a- y'know,
let's just go with that.
[SUZUNO] I've
waited here all day
because I would make another
request of you, Good Emi.
[EMI] Oh yeah?
[SUZUNO] I would like to go
see Good Sadao's workplace.
Would you accompany me?
This is maybe
not the time.
"Sadao."
I feel like I know that name.
I realize you
don't want me getting
too close to him,
but unfortunately for you,
I cannot simply step aside.
[RIKA] So. Spill the beans...
[EMI] Yep, this is my life now.
[RIKA] I know I'm
like, way butting in,
but you can't work
these dramas out
on your own, you know.
You need a third party
to be an impartial judge...
[EMI] I'm telling you,
Rika, it's not like that!
Don't worry girls,
I'm on the case.
So, where is this Mister Sadao?
[SUZUNO] He works
at the MgRonald's
near Hatagaya Station.
[RIKA] Oh! Well the train'll
have us there in no time!
No way I'm going
with you, you understand?
[FEMALE CUSTOMER A] I know,
this place is way better
than MgRonald's!
[SARUE] Sure, I can take your
order if you're ready, go ahead!