[NARRATOR] Previously on Dragon
Ball, a mysterious girl named
Launch joined Goku and Krillin
on Master Roshi's island.
And now the friendly foursome is
packing up for a new adventure.
How're we gonna get there?
[GOKU] It'll be a tight
squeeze on the Nimbus Cloud.
This will cut it!
[NARRATOR] The old teacher
has finally agreed to train
Goku and Krillin, and so they're
moving to a larger island.
[ROSHI] Master Roshi's
rule number one:
Travel in style!
[ROSHI] Can you do me a favor,
Launch?
[LAUNCH] Huh?
Well, uh, try not
to sneeze, kay?
Yes, I'll try!
[NARRATOR] Master Roshi's
request has nothing to do with
hygiene. As he and the
boys learned the hard way,
Launch goes through an
amazing transformation
every time she sneezes.
Changing from a gentle girl
to a vengeful vixen with
an itchy trigger-finger!
And she won't be pushed around!
[LAUNCH] Wanna dress
me like a doll?
Then please,
don't forget...
[LAUNCH] the accessory
machine gun!
[screaming]
[NARRATOR] Needless to say,
Master Roshi, Goku, and Krillin
will be staying on their
toes. But hey, there's
plenty of reason to smile!
Now that Master Roshi has a
girl to keep him company,
the boys will learn the
ways of martial arts!
Training starts today
on Dragon Ball!
[ROSHI] Anyone up
for a short martial arts
lesson before dinner?
[KRILLIN] Of course, Master!
[ROSHI] Yes, I find
it helps digestion.
Hey, where's Goku?!
[LAUNCH] Oh, I know! He
said he'd have a look
around the island, and then he
went off on that funny cloud.
Wooaah...
[GOKU] Yeah!
[laughing]
[GOKU] Wa-hoo!
Master Roshi, I think
someone beat us to the island.
[ROSHI] About three hundred
someones to be exact.
But don't worry, they just live
here. They're not competition.
Now, let's have a lesson!
You mean it?!
Yeah, yeah-yeah-yeah!
Yeah-yeah!
[KRILLIN] Hmph, what a child!
Just wait 'til he sees
what a real fighter can do.
Should I be
training too?
[ROSHI] Uh? That's up to you,
as long as we can hide
the machine gun...
Well, I guess I'll
train if you guys are.
Ah... ah... ah...!
[screaming]
[yawning]
[ROSHI] Eh?
[LAUNCH] Actually,
fighting puts me to sleep!
I'll go make some food!
Guess she was
just yawning...
That was scary!
Krillin, how dare
you be scared!
A martial arts expert
must never be afraid!
[KRILLIN] Sorry.
I'll try to be more like you.
Now, let's continue with
our fearless training.
[ROSHI] Krillin, do you have
any fighting experience?
Yes, I studied for eight years
at the Magic Orin Temple!
[ROSHI] Alright, then,
very good. I suppose
I can skip the lesson on what
a punch and a kick are.
[ROSHI] Now, before I teach
you boys anything new,
I'll need to test your
current ability.
[ROSHI] Let's see...
We'll start from over here...
and finish at that tree. That's
about a hundred meters, right?
[ROSHI] Where's my stopwatch?!
You want us to race?
[ROSHI] Running is a good test
of speed and strength, though of
course if you're an expert
fighter, you shouldn't be the
one who has to run away.
[chuckling]
I'll run first, Master Roshi.
[ROSHI] Ooh, confident, are ya?
Well, you'll both see why.
I could probably
make the Olympics...
if I wanted to.
On your mark!
[KRILLIN] Hmm...
[ROSHI] Get set!
[GOKU laughing]
Hit it!
[panting]
My, my! You ran it in
ten-point-four seconds!
Well, that's...
pretty darn good.
Yeah, yeah...
It's an okay run...
I usually make it
around ten-point-one.
I don't know what happened, but
I guess the wind was against me!
[GOKU] Yoo-hoo! Master Roshi!
[GOKU] Can I take
a turn at it now?!
[ROSHI] Well,
let's not get antsy!
[ROSHI] Now, on your mark.
[ROSHI] Get set!
What an amateur.
Go!
[GOKU] Uh?
Maybe he's a bit
faster than I thought...
Let's see, now... looks
like eleven seconds even.
That's a good finish,
but Krillin, I'd say you still
beat him hands down.
Oh, it's really not
fair to compare him to me.
[KRILLIN] I set the bar
pretty high, you know.
Yes, well, for rookies,
you both have good potential.
[GOKU] Master Roshi, can I try
again with different shoes?
Don't be a sore loser
and try blame your shoes, Goku.
Look at mine.
They're not exactly meant for
running either, now are they?
But at least yours
aren't all torn up.
[GOKU] I can see my toes!
[GOKU laughing]
Ha! Much Better!
Okay! I'm ready!
[ROSHI] Alright!
Get on your mark!
[ROSHI] Get set!
[ROSHI] Go!
[KRILLIN whimpering]
Wow. Eight seconds flat.
Was I fast?
Who... taught you
how to-to run like that?
What do you mean?
No one taught me.
That'd be silly!
Well, for two young men, you're
at the top of your league.
[chuckling]
[ROSHI] But that's
not good enough!
[ROSHI] See boys, to be truly
great fighters, you must learn
to go beyond the
limits of normal people.
And that's no cakewalk.
[ROSHI] I'll let you
be the timekeeper.
And whose time am I keeping?
Mine, of course.
I just hope I'm still in shape.
[grunting]
[GOKU] Okay, Master Roshi,
are you ready?!
[ROSHI] That's a
good question...
[ROSHI] Oh yeah!
I think I'm ready!
[KRILLIN] Okay!
Then, on your mark!
Get set...!
Go!
That's moving!
What's my time?
Five-point-six seconds!
Five-and-six tenths, huh?
Not too bad.
Can you teach us to do that?!
[ROSHI] What, throw a
purple turtle shell?
[ROSHI] Oh, right,
the running. Of course!
It's just a matter of surpassing
normal human limitations.
Gee, all that running
made my tongue dry.
[ROSHI] Goku, grab me a brewsky!
Okay... What's a brewsky?
Don't worry,
Master, I gotcha!
Ugh, Goku, I have many things
to teach you besides fighting.
Now, are you sure you
weren't raised in a bubble?
[laughing]
Oh, wow! Master Roshi
really is strong!
He's not just a dirty,
old man after all!
[KRILLIN] Launch!
Which way is the refrigerator?
[LAUNCH] Careful!
You're blowing up dust!
[KRILLIN] What?
[LAUNCH] Ah... Ah... Ah-choo!
That's no yawn!
[LAUNCH] Slow down,
you little pig!
[KRILLIN screaming]
[LAUNCH] How's about I
cook you for dinner?!
Oh, look at that! Krillin
just ran the hundred-meter
in just eight-point-eight
seconds!
That's much better than before!
[LAUNCH] You can't run forever,
you little porker!
[LAUNCH] Ah-choo!
Oh, that's funny, I thought
for sure I was in the kitchen!
[LAUNCH] Oh, look,
I dropped my knife!
[KRILLIN whimpering]
[ROSHI] And that's a brief
explanation of how to go
beyond your limits.
Am I making any sense?
[GOKU] Mm-hmm!
[ROSHI] Good. Then we'll work
on applying it tomorrow morning.
Now, you boys have one more
task to perform before we go
inside to that wonderful
smelling supper!
Are we running?
[ROSHI] No, it's a
different kind of test.
[ROSHI] Take a good
look at this stone.
[ROSHI] Have you memorized it?
I think so.
Are you going to eat it?
[ROSHI] What? No, Goku!
Oh, yeah! Still got the old arm.
The test is to throw stones?
Master Roshi, your training
sure is kind of weird.
Throwing stones is
not the test here.
[GOKU and KRILLIN] Huh
The test is to find mine.
Wha--?
You mean the one you just threw?
[ROSHI] Anyone can throw
a stone, just like anyone
can throw a punch.
But to find a stone takes a
focused mind and a calm spirit.
This is what will separate
you from the others.
[ROSHI] And so, the person who
finds it can keep the stone,
and the one who doesn't
can keep their appetite.
[GOKU and KRILLIN]
You mean... no supper?!
[ROSHI] That's right!
And if no one brings the
stone back in thirty minutes,
then neither of
you gets to eat!
Now, hurry up, boys!
Time's already started!
[ROSHI] Watch out for snakes!
[shouting]
[KRILLIN] Darn it!
There's no way down!
We'd better find
a detour, quick!
[GOKU laughing]
Are you crazy?!
Don't worry! I did this all the
time back in the mountains!
Haah!
[GOKU screaming]
Ooh, that one really hurt!
[GOKU] But I've got
to get my supper!
[GOKU] Hello, stone!
Where are you?!
[KRILLIN] That guy
can't be human!
And now he's way ahead of me!
[panicked wailing]
Hmm...
[KRILLIN] Hold up, there's no
way I can find that stone in
half an hour, especially with
Goku taking leaps like that.
[KRILLIN] Maybe there's a...
[snickering]
[KRILLIN] Ooh,
you sly, sly dog.
[snickering]
[sniffing]
Ahh, fortune smiles on Krillin.
[KRILLIN] Hello!
Hello! Man at the door!
Hmm... where's the man?
[KRILLIN] I'm the man, ma'am,
and I need to borrow a pen!
It's an emergency!
A pen?
[KRILLIN] Yes, please.
[sniffing]
Smells like sweat
and turtle shell.
I'm closer.
Perfect-o!
Thank you!
[KRILLIN laughing]
[WOMAN] Tiny, little thing...
Now, all I have to do is
act like I had a really
hard time finding it!
[chuckling]
[LAUNCH humming]
[ROSHI] Now, this
is a magic moment...
[LAUNCH humming]
So, Launch, whatcha
shaking up for dinner?
[LAUNCH] Stew! I got a
really good deal from a
man at the fish market.
Ohh... great...
sounds tasty...
[LAUNCH humming]
[excited grunting]
Master Roshi!
[LAUNCH] Huh?
[panting]
[LAUNCH] Hey, Krillin!
[ROSHI squealing]
[panting]
Huh?
What... were you doing?
[ROSHI laughing]
[ROSHI] G-Gotta go!
[panting]
[KRILLIN] It was hard,
but I found it.
Good job. Very quick!
Nice try, lame-o, but
that's not my handwriting!
[ROSHI] Now get out!
[KRILLIN] Sorry!
Man, I'll never find,
anything in this jungle.
--[roaring]
--[screaming]
Whoah! That was close!
Huh?
[deep growling]
What kind of a jungle am I in?!
[GOKU laughing]
[GOKU] I found it!
Oh! It's Goku!
Stay right where
you are, Goku!
I'm coming your way!
Please don't go anywhere!
I found it! Mmm...
Now, I can have my supper!
How in the world did
you find that, Goku?!
It smells like Master Roshi!
What are you, a dog?!
Wait. I think that
stone might be a decoy.
What do you mean?
It has his handwriting
on it and everything!
Lots of stuff has his writing
on it! He owns this place!
Oh, really?
I'll check it for you.
[KRILLIN] Hmm....
[KRILLIN laughing]
[screaming]
[GOKU] You're cheating!
Give me back that stone!
I'm sorry, Goku!
But I stole it fair and square!
[shouting]
[panting]
Uh? Uwah?
[screaming]
[snickering]
What a well-earned meal!
[GOKU shouting]
Huh? Huhh?!
[shouting]
Boy, he's persistent!
Well, here I go!
Let's brawl!
I'd love to!
But first, you have to
promise you won't cry
to Master Roshi if I cause
you death or permanent injury
Sure! If you swear to
fight once without cheating!
[growling]
[blows landing]
[shouting]
[whimpering]
You give up?
Oh yeah!
Then you have to
give the stone back.
Well, I can't argue with you.
The rock is rightfully yours.
So... take it!
[GOKU screaming]
[GOKU] Wait up, stone!
[KRILLIN guffawing]
And that's what I call...
smooth!
[ROSHI] Hmm...
[softly chuckling]
[ROSHI] I know I shouldn't,
but...
[ROSHI grunting]
[ROSHI] So... close...
I've got it!
Do you time this?!
But now I've got the real one!
What do you know? This
one is real. Good job, Krillin.
[ROSHI] You've
redeemed yourself!
Yes, thank you.
[laughing]
[ROSHI] Dig in, Krillin!
[LAUNCH] Do you like it?
You bet!
Would you like more to
drink, Master Roshi?
Oh-ho, you read my mind!
Well, I didn't know you were
such a gourmet cook, Launch!
Thank you very much!
Just thank the fish!
[laughing]
[KRILLIN] Oh, thank you, fish!
[GOKU moaning]
Yummy! What's in
this tasty stew?
[LAUNCH] Let's see...
what did that man call it?
Oh! It's a puffer fish!
[KRILLIN] Hmm?!
Puf...fer fish?
[ROSHI] But that's... poisonous!
Oh, I... feel ill.
So do I!
Oh, I didn't know!
[moaning]
[coughing, retching]
[rooster crowing]
[GOKU laughing]
[GOKU] What a beautiful day!
Come on, Master Roshi!
Let's train now!
I... think we'll
take the day off...
[ROSHI groaning]
[NARRATOR] Martial Arts training
will continue on the island.
Just as soon as Krillin and
Master Roshi can pick themselves
up off the floor!
On the next Dragon Ball!