[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
Goku paid a visit
to the Red Ribbon
Army Headquarters,
in hope of acquiring
two Dragon Balls.
[NARRATOR]
One after another, soldiers fell
like dominos as our hero
fought his way through
the evil stronghold.
The firepower of the
enemy was intense,
but Goku was
determined to succeed.
He knew the only way to fulfill
his promise of reviving
Upa's slain father, was to
claim all Seven Dragon Balls
and summon the power
of the Eternal Dragon.
A noble task, but one filled
with peril as he headed
for a showdown
against Commander Red.
Fool! He doesn't even know
how to work an elevator!
Somebody explain to me how
the world's strongest army
could lose to this imbecile
[SOLDIER A]
You punk!
You're goin' down!
[GOKU]
Hm?
[SOLDIERS groaning]
We did it!
He's toast.
That wasn't very nice.
[SOLDIER D screams]
[GOKU yells]
[SOLDIERS groan]
[GOKU grumbles]
[SOLDIER F, SOLDIER G whimper]
Forget the hazard pay!
I'm outta here!
[GOKU]
Hm?
[RED] Idiots! Hundreds of
trained professionals
and they can't even
handle one child!
[STAFF OFFICER]
But sir, the kid does display
extraordinary powers.
[RED] I can see that.
I'm only missing one eye.
I don't need you to point out
the obvious, you imbecile!
[STAFF OFFICER]
Uh, yes, sir.
If you had trained
those men properly
in the first place, we wouldn't
be having this problem.
Honestly, I should have
never listened to your sister!
[STAFF OFFICER]
My apologies, sir.
[GOKU]
Hm.
They're right above me.
[GOKU groans]
Maybe I should get a helmet.
[RED cackling]
You may be strong as an ox,
but you're dumb as one too!
The ceiling is reinforced
with a special alloy.
No one can break
through it, not even you!
Just look at that brat.
Now is the perfect time
to wipe him out!
Isn't there one soldier
in this entire Army
that can rid me of this menace?!
[RED] Colonel Violet! I knew
you wouldn't let me down.
She is a perfect example
of the caliber of soldier
we need in this army!
Proactive, dependable and loyal.
[SOLDIERS screaming]
[SOLDIER H screams]
[VIOLET] Hm. Looks like the
Ribbon has finally been cut.
Huh? Hello, Colonel Violet,
what are you doing?
The kid's not in that room,
he's further down!
[alarm sounds]
Sir, she's headed for the safe!
Why that double-crossing
two-timer!
She's proactive all right,
at giving herself a raise.
[RED growls]
[STAFF OFFICER] Commander,
wait! Where are you going?
I can't let you leave
this room. It's not secure.
The contents of
that safe represent
years of hard work
and it belongs to me!
[STAFF OFFICER] Sir, our most
valuable possessions
are still secure: the
Dragon Balls. Forget the safe.
[RED] No, no, no, no, no!
Don't you lecture me!
I'm the leader
around here, got it?!
[VIOLET] It's a shame everything
in life can't be this easy.
[VIOLET cackles]
[VIOLET] Consider this
my severance package.
[RED growls]
You won't get away with this!
[RED] You little jackal!
If that's the way
you want it, fine. But you can
forget me as a reference!
[STAFF OFFICER]
Commander, it looks as though
the rest of the soldiers
are evacuating as well.
What?!
This isn't a democracy!
Get them back here!
Attention all personnel.
No evacuation orders
have been given.
[STAFF OFFICER]
Return to your posts at once.
Failure to comply will be
met with terminal force.
[SOLDIER C whimpers, screams]
Traitors! Every last
one of them, worthless.
[STAFF OFFICER] Commander,
it is my duty to appraise you
of our situation.
And right now we are outmatched.
The boy is too powerful.
[RED growling]
Please sir, we should get out of
here while there's still time.
Retreat from a child?!
[STAFF OFFICER gasps]
[RED] Never...
You overestimate his chances.
[STAFF OFFICER] You mean
you're going to fight him?
[RED]
No, of course not... You are.
[STAFF OFFICER gasps]
I will ready our next plan...
You will remain here
and protect our interests.
I have full confidence in your
ability to resolve this matter.
But, Commander, I--
No more excuses!
You will follow my orders!
You will destroy
the child. Is that clear?!
Clear. Crystal, sir.
Fight well, soldier,
and remember,
the honor of the Red Ribbon Army
rests squarely
on your shoulder.
Hm...
[crash]
Finally.
Are you the person in charge?
No, I'm not the Commander.
[GOKU]
Where is he?
He's safe. Now stop talking.
You will deal with me.
[GOKU]
Wait. I don't wanna fight you.
Just hand over the Dragon Balls.
If you want to see the
Commander so badly,
I'll take you to him...
...in pieces.
[STAFF OFFICER grunts]
[GOKU yelps]
[GOKU grunts, groans]
[RED growls]
Blast, the luck of that child!
But this will finish him!
[STAFF OFFICER grunts]
This is getting us nowhere.
I'll give you one more chance.
Hand over the Dragon Balls
and surrender.
No.
[GOKU] Okay, but let's finish
this soon. I'm ready for lunch.
[GOKU yells]
[STAFF OFFICER groans]
So long! This is
where we say goodbye!
[STAFF OFFICER yelps]
[GOKU yelps]
[RED cackling]
I live for moments like this!
[STAFF OFFICER grunting]
Commander...
How could you
betray me like this?
[RED cackling]
[RED] I don't really see
this as losing a foe,
but gaining four Dragon Balls!
Just one more ball...
Then at last...
My dream to be tall as a
mountain will come true!
[RED] Soon no one will ever
be able to look down
at Commander Red again.
I will become ruler
of all I can see.
And my eyes shall tower
over the heavens!
[STAFF OFFICER]
Commander Red!
Huh?
[STAFF OFFICER]
What did you mean by that?
[RED]
You! You're still--
Alive? Yes, Commander,
sorry to disappoint you.
And I heard every word you said.
Do you mean all
of this was so that
you could gain a few inches?!
You bet! And what's
wrong with that?!
It's a selfish goal.
It has nothing to do
with the Red Ribbon Army!
It has everything
to do with this Army
and my plans for
the organization.
These Dragon Balls are
the tools I need to make
this Army and myself huge!
It would be a grave mistake
to underestimate my plan.
Your lame plan's going
to get us all killed!
I am the Red Ribbon Army!
What's good for me
is good for everyone and
I want to be taller!
All my life I've
drawn the short straw.
I've had to contend with
being a mere pebble
in a land of giants! It is
the curse of my existence.
You couldn't possibly
understand what it's like.
The nightmare of being a genius,
yet trapped inside
this ugly little body!
I understand that loyalty
means nothing to you.
You sold me out for your vanity!
What's really eating you
is there's no commander
in front of your name,
and there never will be!
Do you want to know why?
Because you're small-time.
You're just a lackey,
my errand boy.
At your age it's pathetic!
[STAFF OFFICER] Looks like
I've been promoted...
You squandered your power,
but I will lead the Army
into a new era of greatness.
My first order of business
will be to rule this planet.
[GOKU grunting]
[STAFF OFFICER gasps]
Thank goodness you're alive!
Yes, I am.
Now, let's finish this.
Listen, I'm sorry. But I don't
want to fight you anymore.
I'm a victim just like you.
If that's really true,
why are you pointing
a gun at me?
You scared me, that's all.
Why are you being
so nice to me now?
I told the Commander
not to hurt you,
so he decided to
punish me as well.
You fought the
Commander to save me?
[STAFF OFFICER] He knows
I don't like to fight children,
so he told me you
were here to hurt him.
When I learned you only
wanted the Dragon Balls,
he tried to kill me
to cover up his lie.
Well, why is he on
the floor? Is he asleep?
Yes, he said he was feeling ill,
so he had to lay down.
Bad headache.
If we're not fighting
anymore then do you mind
if I take the Dragon Balls?
[STAFF OFFICER]
I'm afraid the Commander
would miss them
when he wakes up.
Say, why don't we join forces
and collect them together?
But the Dragon will only
grant a wish to one of us.
I understand your concern.
But you have nothing
to worry about.
The Red Ribbon Army has
no interest in the wish.
We have everything we
could possibly want.
The wish is yours.
All we want is to see
the seven Balls reunited.
See, the Commander, he has
a soft spot for Dragons.
[GOKU]
No thanks. I don't believe you.
Besides, I promised Upa I'd
help bring his father back
and you're the reason he
got hurt in the first place.
My deepest apology
if there's been
some misunderstanding.
I'll report this to our
Customer Service
Department immediately...
Give us another chance.
That's all I'm asking.
Hand me your Dragon Balls
and we can be partners.
Wouldn't that be fun?
[GOKU]
I can't trust you.
I don't think you really
care about me or my friends.
I think you just
want my Dragon Balls.
[GOKU grunting]
[STAFF OFFICER groans]
[GOKU grunts]
[STAFF OFFICER]
That kid is like a machine!
Maybe that's the answer.
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU groans]
[STAFF OFFICER chuckles]
You're a tough kid all right,
but you slam into a wall
just like anyone else.
With your destruction,
there will be no one to
challenge my power!
Looks like we're almost there.
It's about time.
I have a feeling Goku's
gonna need our help.
[PUAR]
Don't worry, Krillin.
If there's one thing
I'm sure of,
it's that Goku can
take care of himself.
[OOLONG]
No matter how tough he is,
he still has to fight
an entire army.
Mm-hm. Oolong has a point, Puar.
As skillful as he is,
Goku is still outnumbered,
and the Red Ribbon Army
has quite an arsenal
at their disposal.
Would you guys stop it already!
If you can't think of
anything positive to say,
then shut up!
The good news is he has
all of us to help him out,
especially Master Roshi.
[ROSHI grunts]
Thanks for the
vote of confidence.
I'm sure we'll be fine.
Yes, think positive.
It's easy to beat your
enemies if you focus hard.
Mm-hm. Especially if
you pretend they aren't
wearing any clothes.
--[ALL scream]
--Everyone be quiet!
Save the cheering
for after the battle.
[YAMCHA]
Uh-oh.
[BULMA]
What's wrong?
We're not alone. Something's
heading straight for us.
It could be a
Red Ribbon fighter-plane.
Maybe they know we're coming.
That's not good.
Well, that's typical.
I took this route
to avoid traffic.
I doubt it's one
of the Commander's,
but I'd better
stay out-of-sight.
What do we do?!
Hold on, I'm thinking!
Bad news.
This plane is equipped
for speed, not fighting.
We don't have any weapons!
Let 'em come.
I've got all the firepower
we need right here.
I'll feed 'em a lead buffet.
Whoa! Save your fire
for the bad guys!
There'll be plenty of action
once we get to
where we're going.
But if we start some
half-cocked fight right now,
we may never get there!
And that wouldn't help Goku.
He's right. We don't
know who they are.
Let's just stay out of sight
until they pass.
Good enough. Hopefully
I can take us down
low enough to stay out
of their radar.
This is perfect. If I
can descend low enough,
I'll slide right under their
nose without being seen.
[VIOLET]
Violet, you're a genius!
[YAMCHA gasps]
They've dropped in altitude!
They're heading straight for us!
They've matched my position.
They must be after me.
This doesn't look good, guys.
They obviously know we're here.
We should fly back up
and hide in the clouds.
That sounds good to me.
Now I'm officially freaked out.
These guys must be packing
some serious hardware.
They've been able
to track every move.
They did it again!
They're toying
with me! Well, fine!
You wanna play games,
be my guest.
I'll give you
something to chase!
Looks clear.
I think we lost them.
[ALL cheer]
[YAMCHA screams]
[VIOLET screams]
Did you get the license number?
Boy, I sure am
glad that's over.
Next time, we drive.
[GOKU yelps]
[GOKU yelping]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU]
Hey! Who turned out the lights?!
Let me go! Let me go!
[STAFF OFFICER laughs] It's time
to throw out the trash!
[GOKU groans, screams]
[STAFF OFFICER cackles]
That was easy!
We shouldn't rely
on contract labor.
[GOKU groaning]
Now then, which one
of these features
haven't I tried yet...
Oh, a big red button.
That looks interesting.
[STAFF OFFICER]
Goodnight, kid.
[STAFF OFFICER cackles]
[NARRATOR] Goku finds himself
at the mercy of a madman.
Will his friends arrive
in time to save him?
And what will become
of the Dragon Balls?
The answers to these puzzling
questions and much more
will be revealed next
time on Dragon Ball!