[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball...
Goku continued his training
for the next World Martial
Arts Tournament.
The young warrior
endured various dangers,
including a shocking
showdown against lightning!
[GOKU]
I'm the strongest in the world!
[NARRATOR]
Later, Goku met Karinto,
a kind old man who
helped the eager hero
sharpen his
concentration skills
while teaching him how to fish.
[KARINTO]
It's a keeper!
[BOTH laugh]
[blows landing, grunting]
Ouch!
I believe you've gotten
stronger.
It took you longer
to fall down that time.
[GOKU growls]
You're too strong. I'm fighting
with everything I've got,
but I can't keep up.
[GOKU groans]
[POPO]
Hmm...
[GOKU grunts, yells]
[groans]
Well, nice trick, but better
luck next time. Too slow.
I understand, Mr. Popo.
It's time to start your
new training today.
I'm done with the old training?
Wow! I-Is this is for me?
I like the color
but it's not my size.
Besides, we can't have
you training in rags.
[GOKU]
Haah!
It's perfect! Whoa!
You can do anything, Popo!
Something we have
in common... Follow me.
[clocks ticking]
Whoa!
What a strange room!
[POPO] It's called
the Temple Rotunda.
Past, present, and future...
All time is made in this room.
Sorry, Popo,
but I don't understand.
Think of it as transportation.
It will take you to
your next opponent.
Once you get there,
however, it's up to you.
How strong do you think
my opponent will be?
Strong enough.
[GOKU screams]
[TIEN, YAMCHA growling]
[KRILLIN grunting]
[ROSHI]
Serendipity.
You boys act like you
understand, but you don't.
There are no random events.
Everything happens for a
reason. Goku understands.
That's why he's taking his
training to the next level
while all of you are
still swimming laps.
[TIEN growls]
[TIEN yells]
Having a bad day?
Tien.
[TIEN] This is useless.
I'll never be a match for Goku.
I wonder how Yamcha and the
others are doing out there?
I hope they don't
over exert themselves
and get injured or something.
[ROSHI chuckles]
They're young, they can take it.
I was lifting boulders
when I was five.
Master, do you mean that you've
been training in Martial Arts
since you were a child?
That's right. And I didn't
have it as easy as these boys.
When I was a kid,
we didn't have nice paths
to carry our boulders on.
Master Mutaito made
me walk across
the most treacherous
terrain and without shoes.
You said we.
The Crane Hermit was also
a student of
Master Mutaito's, right?
[ROSHI] Yes, that rascal.
He was impossibly hopeless!
Compared to him, I was a genius.
I was known for
being a keen fighter.
They used to call me
"Turtle the Wonder."
Everyone had great
respect for my talent.
That's something.
And look how you ended up.
It is amazing, isn't it?
I get better with age.
I know it's silly, and
I mean no disrespect, Master,
but I just can't
picture you as a young man.
Well, try!
I can't help thinking
about Tien and the boys.
I wonder where they're at?
Goku should still be
training with Kami.
[PUAR sighs]
It's not the same
without them here.
[BOY]
Wait! Is that Fan-Fan?
Stupid steam! I can't see a
thing! I've got to get closer!
[GOKU screams]
[BOTH grunt, yell]
I can't feel my head.
[FAN-FAN]
Who's there?
Be quiet!
[MONKEY squeaks]
So that was you
making all that noise.
Close! What's the
matter with you?!
You almost got the both
of us in a lot of trouble.
Have we met before?
You look familiar.
Yeah kid,
I get a lot of that.
I'm sort of a celebrity
around here.
[grunts]
I'm known for my superior skill
and my awesome
fighting technique.
[GOKU]
Oohh...
Good, so you're a fighter also?
Yeah. In fact, I'm
Master Mutaito's best pupil.
Master Mutaito, is he strong?
What are you crazy?!
He's practically the
strongest man alive!
Really? The strongest
man in the world?
Do you think you could take
me to him? I wanna fight him!
You're out of your mind.
You wanna fight Master Mutaito?
[laughs]
You got me, kid!
What a sense of humor!
Uhh...
Why are you laughing?
Look, I want you
to tell me the truth.
Do you know Fan-Fan? Do you?
Fan-Fan?
Don't play dumb! The girl
who was swimming just now.
Come on, you didn't drop in
by accident, did you?
You know Fan-Fan!
If she finds out about this...
[whimpers]
Darn! I should have
stayed by the tree line!
I'm sorry. I didn't
hit you on purpose.
You can watch me swim! Okay?
[BOY growls]
[BOY]
Stop clowning around!
Ow!
[growls]
[BOY]
What do you want, Crane?
Wait a minute! Crane?
He looks familiar as well.
[CRANE] How do you ever
get any training done,
sneaking around
the bushes all day?
[BOY] I suppose it's just a
coincidence
that you're here, too, Shen!
You're pathetic.
Everyone knows Fan-Fan
will be Shen's girlfriend
sooner or later.
He's not a shy wimp
like you, Roshi!
She's crazy about me.
What a vivid imagination!
You keep dreaming, Shen. Fan-Fan
would never fall for you!
Ha-ha.
That's where you're wrong.
All she needs is a little push.
Fan-Fan has better taste
than to mix with your kind!
That's it!
[GOKU growls]
[ROSHI groans]
[GOKU groans]
Why am I wasting my time?!
I've got better things to do
than mess with a weakling
like you! Let's go!
Yes.
Why don't you face me without
using your mind tricks, coward?
I've got it! I know who you
remind me of! Old Master Roshi!
What? Old! You need your
eyes checked, kid. I'm only 18!
Interesting, child. You
study martial arts as well?
Yes.
I'm sorry for bringing
him here, Master,
but he insisted on seeing you.
So, which training academy
are you associated with?
Right now,
I'm studying with Popo.
Who?!
[laughter]
Interesting name...
What is yours?
I'm Goku. I was sent here
to fight the strongest man.
I hear that's you.
Will you fight?
Silly child! Be quiet!
Do you accept my challenge?
Nice pet, Roshi.
Does he do tricks?
[MUTAITO]
You have the eyes of a warrior.
I must admit,
I'm curious to learn
if your spirit is as
strong as your stare.
[gasps]
You'll fight me?
That's right. I gladly
accept your invitation.
Master, please... He's beneath
you. Let me fight him instead.
That's enough! I can handle
my own battles, thank you!
[SHEN growls]
All right, then... Shall we?
Aren't you going to
take a fighting position?
I'm aware of your presence,
young man.
I'm quite comfortable
in this position.
Oh... I've never seen
anyone so relaxed for a fight.
Proceed.
Sure.
I can't believe his speed.
He's relentless.
[GOKU]
Haaah...!
[gasps]
[yells]
[GOKU gasps]
[MUTAITO growls]
[yells]
[GOKU grunts]
Master did it!
It's no surprise.
[ROSHI]
Hey, are you okay?
[GOKU groans]
I'm okay. You're strong!
As are you. Your speed
and power are most impressive.
You are a warrior.
Thank you, sir, but I don't
understand. How did you do that?
You barely touched me,
yet you blew me away.
Spiritual Power.
What?!
It's not unique to just me.
Everyone has it. It's the
basic form of human energy.
With proper training,
one can control it at will.
Whoa! You mean my spirit
energy is as strong as yours?
[MUTAITO]
Mm-hm.
With a lot of hard work.
Follow me.
Huh?
Can you separate
the water, Goku?
Separate it?
[MUTAITO yells]
[BOTH gasp]
[yelling continues]
That's amazing!
How incredible!
You're amazement is misplaced.
It's simply hard work.
With concentration,
anything is possible.
Concentrate.
That's right. Clear your mind of
all unnecessary thoughts; focus.
The rest is up to you.
[PUPIL A]
I don't get it.
Why is Master wasting
so much time on that kid?
[PUPIL B] He's never given us
such personal instruction,
not even to you, Crane.
[SHEN growls]
[GOKU yells]
[ROSHI] Haven't you
had enough for today?
You can't do everything
at once, ya know.
[GOKU grunting]
You need a hobby...
[yawns]
You were right.
The stain came right out.
Who does this belong to?
[FAN-FAN] Over here! Little boy!
That scarf belongs to me!
Huh?!
It's Fan-Fan!
Thank you so much
for fetching my scarf.
You saved me a lot of trouble.
My father would've been
very upset if I had lost it.
Sure. It was no problem.
Fan-Fan! I'm dreaming!
My goodness!
You're sweating buckets.
Are you training for something?
--Uh-huh.
--[ROSHI] He sure is!
The kid's slow,
but he's persistent.
Luckily, I'm patient. I've been
giving him a few pointers.
[ROSHI chuckles]
[ROSHI] I've been sweating
a lot myself. I can hardly see.
Maybe you should take
off your sunglasses.
Take care, and good luck.
Right. Thanks!
That little upstart
seems to be getting
very chummy with Fan-Fan!
You'd better set him
straight, Crane,
or there could be trouble.
Fan-Fan is so beautiful.
She brightens everything
she sees and touches,
even this tree!
[FAN-FAN gasps]
Who are you?
[ROSHI thinking]
Rats! The Crane Hermit!
Hello, Fanny.
It's time you gave an answer
to that letter I wrote you.
Oh, the letter. Right.
I thought you'd get the message.
Thanks for the gesture,
but I can't keep your
mother's bracelet.
Anyone in their right mind would
love to date the Crane Hermit!
He can dance!
Excuse me.
I have to be going now.
Don't be a fool!
Everyone who's anyone likes me!
No one refuses the Crane
Hermit and gets away with it!
Shen, find another partner.
My dance card is already full.
[SHEN growls]
My patience with you
has run out, girl!
You will like me,
whether you like it or not!
[SHEN]
I'll put you in your place!
[SHEN yells]
[ROSHI gasps]
[FAN-FAN grunts]
You've gone too far this time,
Shen! How dare you hurt Fan-Fan!
[ROSHI grunts]
Let her go!
Save yourself
the embarrassment, Roshi,
and tell your pet to
meet me at Dead Field.
[YAMCHA]
What? To Korin's Tower?
Yes. Goku has met Korin.
I wanna meet him, too.
Oh yeah. I heard Goku received
training at the tower,
same as Master Roshi.
Is that so?
[GOKU]
Hey, what's the rush?
Why are we in such a hurry?
Did something happen?
No time to explain!
We have to get to Dead Field
and save Fan-Fan
before it's too late!
Here they come!
Here he is, you lousy Crane!
Now, where's Fan-Fan?
What's going on?
What was that for?!
You're in the way!
Fan-Fan is mine!
[SHEN grunts]
Ouch! That hurt!
Are you insane?!
You could have
broken my glasses!
If you didn't want to get hit,
why attack me
in the first place?
You play nice or else!
--[GOKU gasps]
--Oh no! What have you done?!
[SHEN] Nothing, yet.
As long as you don't move
a muscle, neither will he.
--[GOKU growls]
--You coward!
[SHEN yells]
[GOKU grunting]
[SHEN]
Haah!
[grunts]
Why are you still standing?!
[chuckles]
Bye!
[PUPILS chuckle]
[SHEN laughs]
[SHEN]
Imbeciles!
Did you really think I came
without a backup plan?
Things just went
from bad to worse.
I hate to admit it,
but I think Shen's got us!
I'm sorry I brought you
into this, Goku!
[MUTAITO] With concentration,
anything is possible.
Clear your mind of all
unnecessary thoughts; focus.
The rest is up to you.
[GOKU yells]
[growls]
Yes! It's working. We did it!
I don't believe it!
Wow, I wish I could do that.
[PUPIL A squeals, whimpers]
Who's gonna save you now?!
[PUPIL B growls]
[PUPIL B gasps]
Master!
[GOKU growls]
Now I'm really angry!
[SHEN whimpers, gasps]
You have a choice to make, Shen.
Either you leave now,
or you start your training
from the beginning.
[SHEN whimpers]
He's my pupil, so this
is my fault. Forgive me.
I think he became
rotten on his own.
That thing you did
with the fire was great,
just like I taught you.
I'm impressed.
You did? You are?
Sure. It's just a shame
Fan-Fan couldn't see it,
if you know what I mean!
I wasn't unconscious the
whole time. I know what I saw.
Oh! I... I'm so glad.
--[FAN-FAN giggles]
--[MUTAITO chuckles]
[GOKU] I guess if
I could cut through fire,
water can't be much different.
Uh, right. That's the idea.
You can do whatever
you put your mind to.
[GOKU yells, growls]
Why isn't it working?
[GOKU grunting]
[ROSHI] Of course, you could've
just had beginner's luck.
But you keep trying.
It's good... exercise.
It's difficult to tell whether
or not Goku will succeed.
I call this move
the Fly Swatter.
[NARRATOR] Traveling through
time seems to have made
Goku stronger... or has it?
Can young Roshi help his future
pupil harness his Spirit Energy?
Or will failure
be his newest lesson?
Find out next time
on Dragon Ball!