Taking his life
was a big mistake.
Krillin was my best friend!
[TAMBOURINE]
I love my job.
[NARRATOR] The evil
creature known as Piccolo
had hatched a dastardly plan.
First he sent his
henchman, Tambourine,
to fetch the Dragon Balls.
Then he ordered him
to destroy anyone
who would stand in his way.
Here's the list of names.
[chuckles] Good, post them up.
You won't need his
picture any longer.
Hahaha!
They drove back my forces
and locked me in a jar!
Hunt them down, all of them!
Leave not one standing.
Yes.
[NARRATOR] And so the horrible,
murderous scheme was launched.
[snoring]
[barking]
[sounds of fighting]
Huh?
[TAMBOURINE chuckles]
Ahhh!
[screams]
[TAMBOURINE chuckles]
This has to be my smelliest job.
Lousy bums.
[BUM]
Whuwazzat?
Huh? What th--
You ok, buddy?
[BUM]
The mark of the demon!
Ahhh! Ahh! Oh! Oh!
[MAI hums]
Ah!
I uh, I brought your
melon soda, O Great One.
Ahh!!
[sighs]
[PIANO] Ahem. Back to the
matter at hand, Piccolo.
[burps]
We still have to retrieve
the rest of the Dragon Balls.
Hmmm. I have no choice.
I must make another warrior.
Yuck! He's not going to do
that weird thing again, is he?
'Fraid so. Well,
there goes my lunch.
Piccolo, you know
when you lay eggs
it speeds up your aging process.
At the rate you're going
you'll die before you'll be
able to take over the world.
[hmms]
Once I obtain all the Dragon
Balls, aging wont be a problem.
When I've made my wish,
I will be eternally young.
[PIANO]
Hmmm...
Now to create my new warrior.
His sole purpose must be
the collecting of Dragon Balls.
Rise and form to
serve your master.
Rise and form
to serve your master.
Rise and form to
serve your master.
Rise and form
to serve your master.
Rise and form to
serve your master.
Rise and form
to serve your master.
Rise and form to
serve your master.
Rise and form
to serve your master.
[gagging]
[pants]
Congratulations.
So, does it have a name?
Ohhh...
His name is Cymbal.
My child of darkness.
[PIANO]
A musical instrument.
Didn't see that
one coming, Piccolo.
[PICCOLO]
Silence, Piano! Cymbal awakes!
Who do you serve, child?
[CYMBAL]
I serve my lord.
I serve Piccolo.
[PICCOLO]
And Cymbal, do you live only
to find the Dragon Balls?
Yes.
[PICCOLO] Pilaf!
Now would be a good time
to point out the
nearest Dragon Ball!
Uh... Uh...
Uh, there!
That would have to be
the closest one. Umm, yeah.
[PILAF] So uh, would you
like us to take Cymbal along?
Alone.
[PILAF]
Well, I'm sure you know best.
Now.
Pilaf, can I have
a word with you?
[SHU] Shouldn't we be the
ones giving out the orders?
After all who revived whom here?
He should be serving us!
Shh! Quiet!
He hears everything!
I'm sure that when Lord Piccolo
takes over the world,
he'll give us half of
it out of gratitude, right?
Ahhh!
I uh, meant a quarter?
Uh, a small city maybe?
Heh heh heh heh.
[sighs]
[GOKU] Hmm?
Huh? Where am I?
Ow! Gosh, why does
my head hurt so much?
[stomach growls]
Oh, no! My stomach.
Must get food.
Haha!
Oh boy!
[GOKU]
Lunch!
Uh... That fruit's gone bad.
Huh?
Hmm?
[GOKU hums]
Lunch!
Huh?
I don't suppose you'd be
willing to hop in my stomach?
[GOKU]
Didn't think so.
[chuckles]
Dragon Balls. Huh.
And you're telling us,
if you get all seven,
any wish you make comes true?
Yep, but you only get one wish.
So obviously we
should use that wish
to bring Krillin back to life.
Well, I know this
is going to sound bad,
but I really think we should
use the wish to defeat Piccolo.
There's no way we
can beat him on our own.
I know we have
to bring Krillin back,
but that monster's unstoppable.
Is that a good idea, Yamcha?
I thought the Dragon Balls
turned into stone
for a whole year after
a wish has been granted.
Uh, yeah,
that sure is a long time
to let Krillin's body
hang around. Isn't it?
Ew, and what about that smell?
Well, if you ask me the idea of
bringing him back sounds creepy.
Maybe we should leave him alone.
Oh, gee pals, thanks a lot.
Well let's see, I could make a
freezer capsule to preserve him
until we find the
Dragon Balls again.
Maybe one for back-stabbers too.
Hey, I was just sayin'.
Hmm...
Pale, pale gray.
What? Who is pale grey?
Wait! Is this Pale Grey
a great warrior, Master?
[ROSHI]
No nothing like that.
Pale gray is the color
of Bulma's panties.
Hmm?
Hmmmm?
Ah!!
You were staring at my
underwear this whole time?!
[ROSHI]
No! I started at your knees!
[ROSHI] More cocoa anyone?
I'm already up.
Don't you have any
sense of decency, Roshi?!
That's nice!
Kill a guy for trying
to lighten the mood.
I mean, can't you
people take a joke?
This is not the time for jokes.
No, I guess you're right Tien.
[NEWS] There were
three more killings
of world class
martial arts fighters--
Come here! Listen!
[NEWS] Police are baffled as
to the motives of the killer
and why only
martial artists are targeted.
As to the identity
of the killer,
police are left without a clue,
save for a piece of paper found
on each of the bodies with the
word "devil" encircled on it.
When we return...
Can your clothing
drive you insane?
You might be surprised.
Stay tuned for
this special report.
Well, it's already begun.
Um, I hear flights to the
caribbean are cheap
this time of year.
Guys! All the
fighters are in danger!
We've got to warn them!
We'd have trouble contacting
them without the list.
Besides, many
of them use aliases.
We can't stay here
and do nothing.
There's got to be
some way we can help.
I'm feeling so
useless here. Come on!
Well, you are right
about not staying here.
We're sitting ducks
on this island.
Bulma!
[BULMA]
M-hmm?
How long would it take you
to construct another
Dragon Ball Radar?
[BULMA] Hmm...
Well, if I hurry,
about half a day, I guess.
Then get to it. The sooner
it's done, the better.
[ROSHI] We'll leave as
soon as you're finished.
Huh?
Hm? Oh!
We're gonna need a lot
of those freezer capsules.
Oh, now, come on,
that's not very funny, Launch.
I'm glad you're here Tien.
We'll need your strength.
But if Goku couldn't stop him,
I don't know that I'll be
much help, Master Roshi.
Oh, please let our little Goku
still be alive... Poor kid.
I can't go on.
I gotta eat something.
[sniffs]
Ah ha! Something smells good!
Something smells great!
[GOKU]
It's beautiful.
Luuunch!
[chuckles]
Now, it's lunchtime!
[GOKU]
Oh, yeah!
[CYMBAL thinking]
It is near.
[GOKU sighs]
Mmhmm!
[chuckles]
I'm back to full strength!
[GOKU] And now I'm
coming for you Tambourine!
You hear me?!
You're mine!!
I promise you!
Krillin will be revenged!!
Krillin, I am so sorry
I wasn't there to stop him.
Please forgive me.
Now I remember!
He destroyed the Nimbus cloud!
Ah! Oh no, what have you done?!
Ah!!
I'll tear that monster apart!
Hide while you can, Tambourine!
You're going to pay
for what you've done to
Krillin and Nimbus!
You think you got away,
but you took my Dragon Ball.
Ha! And with
Bulma's Dragon Ball Radar
I know just where to find you!
Uh...
Huh? Is this right?
I can't believe it!
Tambourine's right
around here somewhere!
Okay! Where are you? Come out!
Hmmm?
[GOKU]
I know you're there!
Come out and face me you coward!
I'm not a coward!
You're the sneak
that stole my food!
Huh?
That's right!
That fish was my dinner,
and you ate it!
But somebody left it.
There! On that stick!
Oh, man! I was cooking
it on that stick, you idiot!
[GOKU] Hmm?
[NARRATOR] Out of the
fish fry and into the fire!
Is this strange mountain
man friend or foe?
Find out on the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball!