[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball,
Yamcha and Tien came to
blows during the first match
of the tournament quarterfinals.
Not even the mightty
Kamehameha Wave could stop Tien,
who deflected
Yamcha's every move.
[NARRATOR] In the end,
Yamcha fell prey
to his opponent's
cunning deceptions
and extraordinary
fighting prowess,
which dealt him
a crushing defeat.
[NARRATOR] The second
match saw Man Wolf
confronting Jackie Chun.
Right here.
Want a bone?
[NARRATOR]
The beast soon discovered
he was out of his league...
[NARRATOR]
...and out of bounds...
He lost the match,
but won his freedom.
[NARRATOR] Using a little
hypnosis and Krillin's head,
Jackie Chun convinced Man Wolf
the destroyed Moon had returned,
reverting him back
to his human form.
[BULMA] Hey guys...
Huh?
What do you say we surprise
Goku and the others
by buying them all lunch?
Good idea.
Yeah, I'd love
some lunch... Huh...?
Enjoy miss.
Vendor!
Huh?
Over here!
How about bring some of
those meals our way, pal?!
[VENDOR A]
I'd be delighted to, sir. Uh?!
Huh...?
[OOLONG chuckles]
[VENDOR A cries out in fear]
Well, that's rude!
We deserve service
just like everyone else!
Huh... You girls would tell me
if there was something
on my nose, right?
Sir, we need service.
[VENDOR B] Sure... Aaaaa!
[OOLONG] Huh?
The service around
here is horrible!
Now, now, what's
with all the long faces?
We want food,
but no one will serve us.
[SHEN] It's not you.
It's that fellow.
[OOLONG] Ohh...
huh... What is it?
Is that a... mummy?
[SHEN] No. He's not that lucky.
That poor fool saw his
shot at the title go up
in flames during the
elimination round. Literally.
Oh dear...
Who could be so cruel?
[SHEN chuckles]
[ANNOUNCER] The third
match in the quarterfinals
is about to begin.
Krillin opposing Chiaotzu.
Hey, everyone,
did you hear that?
They said Krillin!
Your ears don't
miss a thing, do they?
Of course he said Krillin,
and he's going to knock the
block of that lousy Chiaotzu!
And he'll do it for Yamcha!
Hi, Yamcha.
[YAMCHA] Puar...
Since you're the only one here,
I'm guessing it's time
for the third match, right?
I hope Krillin's prepared
to take on Chiaotzu.
He could be just
as strong as Tien.
You think Krillin
can win, don't you?
Yes... He's a strong
and capable fighter...
But Shen and his followers
are dangerous... deadly.
[YAMCHA] Puar.
Yes?
[YAMCHA] Go to Krillin.
Cheer for him.
And bring me the
news of the fight,
when there's something to tell.
Alright.
You'd better go now. Quickly.
[PUAR] I'll be back soon. Bye.
[YAMCHA sighs]
[YAMCHA] Good luck, Krillin.
You're certainly gonna need it.
[CROWD cheering]
Krillin! Good luck!
Krillin's number one!
This is the third match and a
sequel of sorts to match one,
as both Turtle and Crane
houses suit up for a rematch
with Master Roshi's Krillin
fighting Master Shen's Chiaotzu!
Yes, and the outcome
will be the same, too!
[chuckles] Beautiful!
Krillin's going
to win this time,
so you can wipe that
smug smile off your face!
I'm here!
Thanks for the warning.
What are those?
[OOLONG] They're
pom-poms... Here.
They look like bad wigs.
What do you want me
to do with them?
You're supposed
to cheer with them.
Ya know, make a lot of
noise for the home team!
Like this...
Go Krillin!
Go Krillin! Go Krillin!
Ready? Okay!
Shake those pom-poms
left and right!
We're gonna help
Krillin win this fight!
Go Krillin! Go Krillin! Ah!
Krillin is cool!
He's got no hair!
But at least
he's wearing clean--
[BULMA] Be quiet!
[clacking]
Great sound, don't you think?
[OOLONG] Huh?
[ROSHI] Hmm...
Hey! Good luck, Krillin!
[KRILLIN] Right.
[KRILLIN thinking]
What's he looking at?
What's he thinking?
I should have watched him fight
during the elimination round!
[SHEN chuckles]
And now, let the match begin!
Fight! Come on!
Despite what you may have heard,
fighting requires movement.
[SHEN chuckles]
Heh?!
Wow, that's a neat trick.
Krillin, watch out!
He's just hovering up there.
I'll bet he saves
a lot on airfare.
[CHIAOTZU gasps]
Go, Krillin!
That was fast!
Chiaotzu, left!
Huh? That would be...
No, that's my right. Right?
No, left is over, uh--
Yeah, Krillin! Good job!
Keep it up!
Smart kid! He's gonna push
Chiaotzu out of the ring!
[SHEN chuckles]
[KRILLIN] You're done!
Would you cut it out
and get down here!
What are you?
A warrior or a balloon?!
The flying technique:
Pure Hermit Crane...
Nonsense.
You seem to know a lot
about my master, old man.
That's right...
and his name is Jackie Chun!
[CROWD cheers]
I assure you folks,
this is not an illusion.
Chiaotzu is really
walking on air!
[KRILLIN thinking]
Okay, Krillin, now what?
If I jump attack,
he could dodge and send
me flying out of bounds!
[OOLONG] I'm seeing it,
but I'm not buying it.
It's a trick!
[BULMA] I don't think so.
Watch close...
I've got a surprise.
Just get down here!
[TIEN chuckles]
Dodon!
[yells]
That will be your friend if he
stays in the ring much longer.
Then the person who burned him
in the elimination round is--
That's right. Chiaotzu.
[frightened gasps]
I never would have
suspected that cute kid
as being the psychotic type!
[CHIAOTZU] Hmm...
[SHEN chuckles]
Ah!
Dodon Ray!
Give me a break!
What's he using?
Dodon Ray!
You're still standing?
[TAO] Dodon Ray!!
[GOKU] That's the same
technique Mercenary Tao used!
[GOKU] Hmm?
What did you say?!
Who has the same
technique as Chiaotzu?!
[GOKU] Mmm...
Dodon...
That was the name of the
technique Mercenary Tao
was using when I defeated him.
If you say you beat Tao,
you're a liar.
It's the truth...
Tao killed my friend's father.
He was a great man...
When did it happen?
Hmm... About three
years ago, I guess.
Now it's my turn!
I... will crush you!
Yah!
Ugh...
[TAO] I give up. You win.
Huh?
I admit my defeat.
Pleased forgive me. I'm sorry.
I'll never hurt anyone again.
[GOKU] Uh...
Please let me go.
I-I'm sorry! [sobs]
I guess we can let you leave.
Accept this apology!
Aaaaaugh!
[LAUNCH screams]
[CHIAOTZU chuckles]
[TIEN thinking] Tao was one
of the strongest warriors
I've ever known.
How could this little
twerp have defeated him...?
It's impossible!
Do you have a problem?
[TIEN growls] Tch!
[GOKU] He seemed upset...
Was it something I said?
Goku...
[GOKU] Yes?
Did you really kill
Mercenary Tao?
Yes, Jackie, I really did...
Why does everyone
keep asking me that?
It happened just like I said.
[ROSHI thinking]
Oh, Goku,
for once I wish you
were lying to me.
You have no idea
the repercussions
of what you are saying...
Goku...
Huh?
The man you say you killed...
...is Master Shen's brother!
I didn't know
Master Shen had a brother.
They don't look
anything alike...
But then again Master Roshi
looks nothing like
his sister Baba,
except for the whiskers.
Krillin, get out!
It's too dangerous!
That's right, girl.
If you value your friend's life,
you'll persuade him
to quit the match
before he gets himself killed.
Krillin, give it up!
Warriors don't give up
in the middle of the fight!
This isn't about quitting.
It's about preservation.
He'll win.
Aaah!
[grunting, screaming]
[LAUNCH sneezes]
No!
[LAUNCH snarls]
Hey cue ball, buck up!
Show some backbone, will ya?!
[OOLONG thinking]
Things just got worse.
[CHIAOTZU chuckles]
Krillin, look out!
There's no way
for him to get away!
Krillin, you're
almost off the stage!
Good move, Krillin!
[SHEN growls]
[KRILLIN growls]
[CHIAOTZU laughs]
[KRILLIN thinking] I can't
keep fighting like this...
There has to be
a better strategy.
Come on, Krillin, think!
[KRILLIN thinking]
Wait a minute...
That's it! This has to work!
Go!
Wait! What--Where did he go?!
Left, right?! Oh no!
[KRILLIN] Left...
Right... Left... Right...
Right! Left! Left! Right!
Right! Right! Left!
Left! Left! Right!
Right! Right! Right! Right!
What's he doing?
[ROSHI] Hmm?
[SHEN] Hmm...
[CHIAOTZU thinking]
He's confusing me.
Which is left?
Which is right?!
That should about do it.
[CHIAOTZU] Aaaaaah!
Payback!
Show off!
[CHIAOTZU laughs]
[TIEN] Move...
Master Shen!
I have something to tell you.
Can this wait?
In case you hadn't noticed,
I'm a little busy right now.
[BULMA and OOLONG] Huh?
[CHIAOTZU laughs]
This would be simple if
I could use the Kamehameha Wave.
[growls]
Wait, Yamcha mastered it.
If he can do it, so can I!
All I have to do is try.
Heh...?!
Let's see, all you do
is put your hands together
and say Kamehameha! Wow!
Let me get this straight.
You're saying that my little
brother, Tao, was killed
by one of Master Roshi's
feeble-minded students?!
Well, uh, yes, Master,
but I, uh, I-I assume
it happened on accident.
Someone killing
Tao is no accident.
It's impossible...
Especially if you're assuming
it was one of Roshi's scum!
Chiaotzu, I want you to stop
playing around and finish him!
What's the matter?
Is your pupil having
trouble making good
on all the bloated
threats you've made?!
Well, at least both of
my boys can still walk.
[OOLONG] Sure. But can
they talk at the same time?
Oh yeah?!
Why don't you come here
and say that to my face?!
[OOLONG] I just did.
I heard that,
you insolent oinker!
I fear defeating
Master Roshi's students
will no longer
be enough for Shen.
He wants them dead.
Uh... Do you think
he feels that way
because I killed his brother?
Yes.
Get ready, here comes Dodon!
Ka... Me...
Oh no... Krillin, don't do it!
Don't what?
Listen to me! You're not ready!
Do not try the Kamehameha Wave!
[NARRATOR] The battle
of the blasts has begun!
But will Krillin be able to
control the Kamehameha,
or will the fears of his
comrades come true?
And what of Master Shen's
thirst for revenge?
Will it be quenched with the
demise of Master Roshi's pupils?
The tournament just became
a fight for survival.
Find out who wins,
next time on Dragon Ball!