[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball,
Goku needed to have the
Dragon Radar repaired,
so it was off to the
big city to find Bulma!
[GOKU] Whoaaa...
[NARRATOR] And thanks to one
of West City's men in blue,
Goku made his way to her home
at Capsule Corporation.
[NARRATOR] It was a
time for happy hellos
as Goku was reunited with Bulma
and his dear, old friends!
--[OOLONG] Hey, kid!
--[PUAR] Yaye!
[NARRATOR] But look out, Yamcha!
Not everyone's happy to see you!
The teeny-weeny Bulma resumed
full form to let Yamcha know
that he was fully
in the doghouse.
His popularity with the ladies
had Yamcha walking on air.
But Bulma was not amused!
And she was there to remind him,
that what goes up
must come down.
[YAMCHA whimpers]
[NARRATOR] While Yamcha was
pondering the error of his ways,
Bulma was reducing her
boil to a steady simmer.
Yes... It was love.
[NARRATOR] Little did they know
that lurking in the shadows
was a much more serious
threat to their peace of mind.
Hasky, of the Red Ribbon Army,
and her devious accomplices
had Goku's two Dragon Balls
in their sights.
[HASKY] They tell me
you're pretty powerful, kid.
But you're still just a child!
Those Dragon Balls
are as good as mine!
Wait and see...
[NARRATOR] And so they
went--unaware of Hasky's designs
on Goku's Dragon Balls--to the
great amusement park in the sky.
[GOKU] Hey, the stairs
are moving, you guys!
[GOKU laughs]
Wow! Look at all
those buildings!
This is great!
Wee!
Yay!
Whoa!
[GOKU giggles]
[OOLONG grunts,
PUAR screams]
--[OOLONG] Watch it, buddy!
--[GOKU laughs]
I'm made out of pork, not rock!
[PUAR] I think I
bruised my bunyun...
Ohh...
[ALL gasping]
[BULMA] Pretty cool, huh?
[GOKU] I could ride
this ride all day!
[BULMA] This is just the
entrance, silly!
[gasping &amp; laughing]
[YAMCHA] There's
the end! Hold on!
[ALL yell]
[GOKU] Wow! Look at that lady!
She's beautiful!
[BULMA] That's a statue, Goku.
[GOKU] Yeah, I knew that...
Welcome, everyone!
Please have your tickets ready!
Where are they?
Hold on, would ya?
Uhh...
They were here before.
Welcome to Dream Land!
Tickets, please!
Huh?
Hey, there! Tickets!
I'm not "Tickets"!
My name's Goku!
It's a pleasure
to meet you, Miss.
Bye!
Tickets? Bummer!
We're both broke!
Oh, well!
[HASKY] Hmm!
Hasky! She said we need tickets!
[TICKET GIRL] Tickets!
[TICKET GIRL]
Welcome to Dream Land!
Have a great time!
--[TICKET GIRL] Tickets, please!
--[PIG GUY chuckles]
Where the heck did it go?
Mine's missing, too!
Well?
Nope!
Man, some nice moves!
Wow!
Yeah! Pro-stuff!
Doggone, Hasky!
You could steal the
paint job off of a car!
I swear!
You won't have any problem
getting those balls!
Will you, Hasky?
Ha, ha. No.
[ANNOUNCER] The next
air-schooner will be leaving
in ten minutes
from air-dock one.
Dream Land.
Making your dreams come true.
[ALL laughing]
[GOKU] This is fun!
[laughing continues]
[RIDERS screaming]
[GOKU laughs]
[HASKY grunts]
[GOKU] Hmm?
A walnut?
Hmm...
[RIDERS screaming]
[OOLONG] Hey!
What's wrong, Goku?
Well, I feel like
someone's watching me.
[OOLONG] Are you kidding?!
No. I guess there are a lot
of people in here, huh?
Thousands!
Well, no biggie!
This is going to be much
easier than I thought!
Good.
I know he doesn't look like
much, but he's super strong!
The kid's dangerous!
No problem!
I've got this!
Whoo!
All right!
Let's do it, boys!
Plan "Ball Snatch!"
Comin' at you, kid...
[ALL laughing]
[GOKU] Whoo! Giddy-up, horse!
[PUAR] Yeeh-haw! Yaye!
Man... Look at them.
Not a worry in the world.
Hmm?
[YAMCHA sighs]
Look, if you love
someone, set 'em free.
Why?
Well, if they really love
you, then they'll come back.
Yeah! I've heard that.
It sounds like it might
work with homing-pigeons.
But not girls.
[OOLONG] Yeah, I
know what you mean.
Back in the old days, if I loved
someone, I'd just kidnap 'em!
[OOLONG laughs]
[YAMCHA laughs,
BULMA growls]
Hey! Ice cream!
[OOLONG slurps]
Yum! That's my favorite!
Can I have some?
No way! Scram!
--[GOKU] Just one bite! Come on!
--[OOLONG] No, no, no! Help!
--[ALL] Huh?
--[WOMAN screaming]
[WOMAN] Help me!
Who's that?
Let's find out!
[WOMAN] Let go of me!
[GOKU] Hey! What's going on?!
[THUG &amp; PIG GUY] Huh?!
You! Let go right now!
Uh-oh!
Let's blaze!
[GOKU] Where'd they go?
[YAMCHA] Miss? Uh-oh!
She's out.
[GOKU] Is she hurt?
[BOTH chuckle]
[YAMCHA] I don't
think so. She fainted.
Ma'am? Hello?
Wake up.
[HASKY] Hmm?
Oh, you saved me.
Thank you...
Wow! What a dish!
She's gorgeous!
They... Those bad men...
they tried to... kill...
[YAMCHA] Wow... Heh, heh. Heh...
Blugh!
[HASKY] Huh?!
Hold it! Don't move!
Hey! She's got a booger
on her forehead!
[HASKY sighs]
He's cracked!
That's a mole, Goku! Gosh!
Say you're sorry!
Sorry, mole...?
[RIDERS laughing]
So he thinks he can run off just
because I'm mad at him, does he?
[BULMA growls]
Wow! You really can
tell a person's fortune?
Yes, so could my
great grandmother.
I guess I got the
talent from her.
You mean, you
see the future?
The past as well.
Yes. Everything...
Wow!
You see stuff about me?
Well, yes.
[YAMCHA] Why don't you let
her tell your fortune, Goku?
[GOKU] Okay!
[HASKY] Hmm....
Please. Let go of all
thoughts. All worries.
[GOKU] Hmm...?
[HASKY] You've been
to the north lately...
To a very cold place...
On an expedition;
a mission of some kind...
[HASKY] Oh, my!
You were in great danger!
I also see a tower...
A very large tower...
Muscle Tower!
You're right! That's incredible!
[OOLONG] You mean,
it's all true?
Every word!
[ALL gasp]
Do you see anything else?
Of course...
Just a moment...
You have something...
concealed...
Con-what?
Hidden...
Oh, yes!
I see!
You have two balls!
They're very important and
they're hidden in your clothes!
Huh?
Oh, wow! She's
right again, guys!
Young man...
May I see them, please?
I believe that they hold
the key to your future.
Well, I guess so. Why not?
[HASKY] Yes! Perfect!
As soon as the lights go out,
I'll switch the real balls
with the fake ones.
[HASKY] Get ready, Hasky.
This is it!
[HASKY gasps]
[GOKU] There!
[ALL scream]
[HASKY whimpers]
Well, thanks! It was great!
You knew all about me!
Not all about you,
just the private parts!
[laughing]
[HASKY] I can't tell if
he's an idiot or a genius.
Goku, I was just
thinking! The two balls?
Maybe she meant
the Dragon Balls!
[GOKU] Oh, yeah!
[GOKU] I forgot all
about the Dragon Balls.
[HASKY gasps]
Are these them?
[BOTH gasp]
[grunting, crashing]
--[HASKY groans]
--[GOKU] Hmm?
What's that?
Clumsy oaf!
Let's go!
[GOKU] Hmm?
[THUG and PIG GUY grunting]
So! It's you again!
Well, you're not
getting away this time!
--[THUG] Let's get out of here!
--[GOKU] Oh, no you don't!
[GOKU grunts]
[YAMCHA] I'll hold 'em, Goku!
[GOKU] Huh? Oh, thanks!
There he goes again.
Let's go help!
[HASKY] Perfect! Pretty boy's
got the Dragon Balls...
[HASKY] It was those
crooks, wasn't it?
[YAMCHA] Uh?
You won't let anything
happen to me, will you?
[YAMCHA] O-Oh, no!
Of course not!
[YAMCHA whimpers]
[HASKY giggles]
[HASKY] He's like
putty in my hands.
[RIDERS laughing]
[GOKU laughs]
[BOTH] Huh...?
[screaming]
[OOLONG] Roadblock!
Busted! Big time!
[BULMA sighs]
This being mad stuff is
getting really boring...
[BULMA] Maybe I should let
Yamcha off the hook...
After all, he can't help it if a
bunch of silly girls like him.
Don't be scared,
you'll be fine!
[HASKY] You're so brave...
I'm not scared with you here.
[YAMCHA squeals]
[YAMCHA screams]
[YAMCHA whimpers]
[fireworks popping,
YAMCHA screaming]
[BULMA] Hmm...
[BULMA] How strange...
That sounded like Yamcha.
Gosh! I guess you don't like me.
What?! No! That's not true!
[HASKY giggles]
[YAMCHA whimpers]
[HASKY] I knew it!
I felt it, too!
[YAMCHA whimpers]
[HASKY gasps]
You witch!
I'll bet you gave lousy
fortunes, didn't you?
[HASKY] Move, old man!
[HASKY grunts]
[YAMCHA yells]
[HASKY yells]
[HASKY giggles]
What?! Yamcha?!
[BULMA growls]
[BULMA] I'm gonna kill him!
[YAMCHA grunts]
[BULMA growls]
[BULMA] You are so dead!
It's over!
[YAMCHA grunts]
Hmph!
[BULMA] That idiot!
Ugh! What a disgrace!
Well! That was awfully
nice of your girlfriend!
I've got what I came for!
You! What gives? Who are you?!
Hasky! And you're Chump!
But you're not
the only one.
You're all chumps.
This whole park's
about to blow up!
[YAMCHA gasps]
At least you'll all get to die
while having fun at Dream Land.
[bomb beeps]
[HASKY] Later, dude.
Don't die too hard.
Hold on! Why are you doing this?
I don't get it!
Well, I get a million zenni
for the Dragon Balls,
and another million for
blowing up that little kid.
Don't be offended.
It's strictly a money matter.
Nothing personal.
Sayonara! To tell you the truth,
I think you're kind of cute.
[HASKY giggles]
[BOTH grunt]
[GOKU] Hey! These two wanted
to say that they're sorry!
[YAMCHA] Goku! That woman
took the Dragon Balls!
Look! She's a bad girl, Goku!
You've got to break the
box hanging on her hip
or else the whole park's
going to blow up!
[ALL gasp]
Get the box, Goku!
Smash the box!
[GOKU growls]
Come to me, Flying Nimbus!
[GOKU] Haaaaa!
[GOKU] Pull over, lady!
What? Shoot!
[HASKY] Ciao!
[GIRL hums]
[GIRL screams]
[HASKY gasps]
[GOKU] You're in big trouble!
Who me?
You're friends are
the ones in trouble!
They're going to blow up
in ten seconds!
But why?
That's the way
the ball bounces!
[HASKY laughs]
[GOKU] Ball? What ball?
Hey! Look out!
[HASKY screams]
[HASKY grunts]
[GOKU] I think you'd
better hand those over.
Forget it, kid. Buzz off!
Well, okay.
[GOKU giggles]
[GOKU] If that's
the way you want it!
[HASKY laughs]
[GOKU] Goochy-goo! Ha, ha,
goochy-goochy-goo-goo!
[HASKY] Stop it!
--[HASKY laughs]
--[GOKU] Tickle, tickle!
[OOLONG] I almost died
and I didn't even know!
[PUAR] Thank goodness!
You're rotten company when
you're terrified, Oolong!
Guys, I think I should go
back and look for Bulma.
What do you mean? C'mon,
we looked all over the place!
She's not there!
See! There she is!
She's home already!
Bulma!
Uhh... Hmm?
[OOLONG] Uh-oh... I'm no
expert on chicks, but I'd run!
[PUAR] Oolong, hush!
[YAMCHA] I'm...
glad you're okay.
I was worried about you.
[BULMA growls]
[YAMCHA grunts]
[ALL gasp]
[BULMA ] I've had it
with you, Yamcha!
I'm going to collect the
Dragon Balls and ask the Dragon
for a man who
doesn't lie and cheat
and who doesn't have a fan club!
Let's go, Goku!
[GOKU] Uhh...
[BULMA] Goku! Come on!
[GOKU] I guess I'll
see you later, guys.
[YAMCHA] Goku!
Thanks...
Sure! You bet!
All right! Forward ho!
It's you and me, kid!
Just like old times!
[GOKU laughs] Yeah!
[NARRATOR] As Goku and Bulma
ride off into the sunset,
the promise of a new
adventure lies ahead.
[NARRATOR] But not every
cloud has a silver lining.
And though the two friends
are off to a tranquil start,
little do they know that
rough seas lie ahead.
Join us next time
on Dragon Ball!