[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball, the long awaited
World Martial Arts
Tournament finally started up!
From all across the globe,
fighters and fans
gathered to take part
in the earth's craziest display
of Martial Arts know-how.
[BULLHORN GUY] No pushing!
It makes me nervous!
I'm sorry but the audience
is not allowed inside
the elimination round area!
It would be a major
fire hazard and--
Well then how
are we supposed
to see our friends
and boyfriends fighting?!!
Just close your eyes
and pretend you're there!
[CHAIRMAN] Hello? Hello?
Testing, one... two... okay...
Well... first we'd
like to thank
each one of you fighters
for coming all this way
to the Tournament because
of course if you didn't come
there wouldn't be much
of a show to watch...
If anyone here
is of the counting nature,
you may have noticed
that there are
one hundred and thirty seven
fighters packed into this hall,
representing countries
and species
from all over the world...
[KRILLIN] One hundred
and thirty seven??
And half of them have
kneecaps taller than I am!
[CHAIRMAN] Unfortunately...
Out of all you
guys here only eight
will get a chance to fight
in front of the crowds
in the Tournament finals!
So fight hard in
the elimination round
and let's try to
not have any whining!
Gee, what's the point of windows
when you can't reach them?
Change into a
stool or something!
[OOLONG] Whoa Bulma!
I don't just change on
command! Get Puar to do it!
Don't be a baby Oolong!
I changed the last four
times! It's your turn!
Now get down there!
Come on...! Why me?!
I'll yell piggy!
[OOLONG thinking]
Some things never change...
the wicked mistress
and her poor pig slave...
Okay...! But I ain't
changing into a stool!
[BULMA] Fine. What ever.
[OOLONG thinking] Guess
that's why mountain climbers
don't wear skirts...
[BULMA] I still can't see!
Lift me higher!
Hey...! Move it!
[grunting]
[BULMA] I can see!
I can see inside!
[OOLONG] Great, Bulma.
That's the important thing...
I mean... who cares
if my spine's cracking...
[CHAIRMAN] Now listen
to the rules carefully
because I can't stand
repeating myself...
You will be divided into
four tournament blocks
and the top two from each block
will advance to the finals.
[CHAIRMAN] We'll be
playing single elimination...
A person loses when they
land outside the ring,
lose consciousness,
or says "I give up."
But killing your opponent
is strictly forbidden.
Anyone who does so
will be disqualified!
And no weapons, either!
Claws may be used but
only if they're natural!
Fights that aren't
finished in under one minute
will be decided by points!
Now, please move to the
boxes and take a number...
You can look on the
boards to find your place.
And please, no trading...
[KRILLIN] Ninety three for me...
What did you get?
A... seven and a zero...
[YAMCHA] Looks like
you're both in block three.
Huh?
Oh no...!
That's bad...!
I don't want to
go up against Goku!
But we're on opposite ends
so you don't have to fight me!
[KRILLIN] Oh! Too bad...
[GOKU]
What's your number Yamcha?
I'm thirty five...
That's block two.
[GOKU] Is that good?
[YAMCHA] Actually it's just
perfect 'cause I didn't want
to be put in the same
tournament block as you.
[GOKU] But why not?
Ah... So you were
scared just like me!
That's not it...
I just want to wait
for the real tournament...
That's where the ring is bigger
and there's no time
limit to stop us...
I've been waiting for this Goku,
so you better make it through...
Oh, I'll make it!
Well then, I'll see
you in the ring!
[KRILLIN] How in the world
can you and that Yamcha guy
be so confident...
...when we're
surrounded by like,
twenty thousand
pounds of muscle?
'Cause none of
these guys were trained
by Master Roshi like we were!
But Goku, the old man
never taught us to fight!
He just gave us
dirt to move around!
Don't worry Krillin
I bet if we try hard enough
we'll be okay!
Right... Dandy...
Hello everyone, I'm going
to be your ref today
so if I could get
fighters number 69 and 70
into the ring now
that'd be super...
Hey... Seventy's my number...
Good luck, Goku!
Oh... Watch out...
We got a top competitor
from the diaper brigade!
I just hope he
doesn't make a mess
on the fighting ring floor...
Goku's already up...
Now I'll finally
have the chance to see
what fighting tricks he learned
from that crazy old man.
Look, it's Goku's turn!
[grunting]
Aaaah...
[OOLONG thinking] Well that's
an interesting angle...
Oolong, just stay put!
It's too bad I'm not a pervert!
Eh. Where's my fighter?
[GOKU] Right here!
[MR. MUSTACHE]
What is this, a joke fight?
I've fallen on my rump
and squished bugs
bigger than you are!
Is that so?
You have one minute to fight...
Hah! I just need one second
to crush this pest between
my thumb and forefinger!
Begin.
Huh?
Oh, I really crushed him!
No, I'm okay!
Huh?
[surprised murmuring]
Unreal!!
Mhmm!!
Awesome...!
Goku knocked him flat!!
[OOLONG] Careful!
Don't... look...!
Huh?
Hey... is there a
reason you keep acting
like a weirdo down there?
Number seventy advances...
Uh... Guys, what
just happened there?
The big oaf got carried
away and lost his balance!
That's what
I call embarrassing...!
Beat by a baby!
[YAMCHA thinking]
That was no accident...
Goku knocked him
down with one touch...!
Master Roshi's
technique, no doubt...
Wow...!
It sure was lucky how
he fell out of the ring!
Not really...
What do you mean?
Krillin... I'm thinking
we shouldn't use
our full strength,
at least not yet...
Hold on... Why not?
It could be bad!
[ORIN PUPIL 1]
What do we have here?
It's our old punching bag!
H-Hello...
It's been a long time
since I've seen you Krillin,
when you ran crying out
of the Orin Temple!
[KRILLIN chuckles weakly]
But look...!
His new clothes are sooo pretty!
Now surely you're not trying
to fight in the World
Martial Arts Tournament!
[KRILLIN] Well yeah, um,
I was thinking about it...
How horrible...!
Making all these real fighters
waste their time on you!
[ORIN PUPIL 1] Have you
forgotten what we taught you?
That runts are always runts?
No... I remember...
[ORIN PUPIL 2] Oh look!
His number's 93!
Would you like to know who
your opponent's gonna be?
Uhhh...
You're lookin' at him!
Ehhh?
Just like old times... huh?
Just try not to be
too hard on me, Krillin!
Why'd you let them
talk to you like that?
Cause...
Cause everything they
say about me is right, Goku!
They've known me
longer than anyone.
They know the truth...
Maybe... I should drop out...
No, you won't...!
You're going to give
that guy all you've got!
But I thought
you said it'd be bad
if we used our
full strength here.
We'll take a time-out
from that rule
because those guys need to
know what you're made of...!
So you show 'em!
Hey...! There he is!
There's Yamcha!
Where...? Show me!
He's there by
the number 2 sign...!
You see him?
[BULMA]
Oh I found him! Yamcha!!!
[BULMA] Hey sweetie!
Can you hear me! Yamcha!!
[BULMA] Come on Yamcha!
Don't you want to wave?
[OOLONG] Whoa there!!!
[OOLONG] Abandon ship!
Pig going down!
My poor behind!
[BULMA] Aahh! I've gone blind!!
Aaa! Help me! There's
something on my face!
[MAN 1]
Would ya look at that...?
[MAN 2] I am! I am!
[BULMA] Somebody
give me hand...!
I can't see anything!
Hey!!!
What is this,
Peeping Tom day?!
It's you...!
Why wouldn't you just
let go of my face?!
I'm sorry... I grab
when I'm scared!
I just love... fighting!
Thanks... I am not
speaking to you Oolong.
[OOLONG] What?
After I defended you from
that drooling army of perverts?
Yeah, somehow I can't
see it as honorable
when you're getting
free looks of your own!
[OOLONG] Come on!
Just think of it as
payment for my services!
Well then I'm not
buying the ice cream!
Fine... Take checks?
So I wonder where
Master Roshi went, you guys.
He's been gone
for quite a while.
[BULMA] Humph!
That old creep's probably hiding
out in the ladies' rest room.
I'm more concerned about getting
to see that elimination round!
My shoulders are
officially off limits!
Oh, that's too bad.
I was gonna take you
to the candy store
if you turned into a ladder.
Oooh baby!
[REFEREE] Gee we're really
making progress here aren't we?
Well let's get fighters number
93 and 94 in the ring please!
Oh gosh, that's me!
You can do it Krillin!
Right...
I have to admit that
I'm kind of jealous
you get to be
in the ring with him.
Don't worry. I'll give
'em a good slap for you!
I bet you'll be surprised
at what you can do!
Just give him a good tap!
I think my body went numb.
You didn't run
away this time...
I can't say that's
a healthy move,
but at least your
less of a chicken!
Beeeegin!
Which bone should I break first?
[screaming]
Huh?
Well, I'd say
93 is the winner...
You see?
Delivering milk and moving dirt
must be good training after all!
And I bet those guys won't
call you runt from now on!
Guess not...
Well Bulma,
I hope you're ready
to visit the candy store...!
Change now!
[OOLONG] To the windows, men!!
Hey look, there's
a hole in the wall!
Alright...!
So we don't need
you after all, Oolong!
[OOLONG thinking]
Who likes candy, anyway?
[BULMA] Look!
Yamcha's about to fight!
Yay! Go get him Yamcha!!!
Ha ha! I'll give you a freebie!
Just try and hurt me!
[chuckles]
How's that...?
[BALD REFEREE] Knock out...!
35 advances!
[GOKU]
Yamcha's really doing well!
We've gotta' make
it to the finals now!
You bet!
[NARRATOR] And so it is!
After months of
sharks and wasp bites,
Goku and Krillin are finally
putting Master Roshi's
training to the test!
And they're kicking
some serious butt!
Number 70 wins!
Yay Goku!
[REFEREE] Begin!
[GOKU] Say...! Nice posture!
Thanks!
Krillin?
What are the chances
he'll live through that?
Not too likely...
Ha! Nice try...!
Sucker! Hahahaha.
Now let's see,
what sort of counterattack
should I use... Hmmm...
How did you...
That was my famous Dragon Stomp!
Right! Here I come!!
Okay, I give up!
I give up now!
Well that... was easy...
[NARRATOR]
And while the boys plowed
through the fighters in Ring 3,
Yamcha continued to
take victories of his own!
And their path to
the final Tournament
became more and more secure.
[NARRATOR] On and on,
knockout after knockout,
until the eliminations came down
to the final, deciding bouts!
Whoever wins this fight will be
the first from Ring Two
to advance to the finals!
Fighters 35 and 40,
please take your positions!
[GOKU] Do your best, Yamcha!
It's Wolf Fang Fist time!
You humans come up
with the wildest names to
make your moves sound tough...
But I'll show you how
a real wolf attacks!
Oh my Yamcha!
Oh gosh...! Is he hurt?!
[BALD REFEREE] And that's a win!
35 has just earned a
spot in the big show!
Whoa...! Yamcha's
full of surprises!
That fight gave
me indigestion...
He won!
I just knew he would!
Way to go!
Thank you...! Cool move, right?
Yeah!
[REFEREE] We're into the
final stretch, you guys...!
Fighters number 70 and 83
please come to the ring!
Winner of this match will
go on to the Tournament...!
How exciting!
That's my number!
Go get 'em!
You know it!
Goku! Throw him from the ring!
That sounds fun!
[LION FIST thinking]
And now for the sacred stance
of the Lion Fang Fist!
Begin!
[LION FIST thinking]
What strange fighting posture!
He's unguarded on all sides!
Just come and hit me
if you want to, mister!
Where'd he go!
Head's up!!
Get ready!
Where's your technique?
[REFEREE] Out of
the ring! 70 advances!
You'll be in the
tournament for sure!
Those were
some nice moves!
It was so much fun!
[YAMCHA thinking]
I always knew Goku was strong,
but there's something
different now...
[REFEREE] Now for the last
match in the Ring 3 Bracket...!
Numbers 93 and 97 please report!
Okay...! Just take
care of this guy
and we'll go to
the finals together!
Right!
Begin!
[BEAR] Make the pain stop...
[REFEREE] Fighter 97 surrenders!
That means 90 is
on to the finals!
[KRILLIN] I did it! I did it!
[GOKU and KRILLIN]
Going to the tournament!
We're going to the tournament!
[YAMCHA] And Krillin is
a good fighter, too...
This is gonna be a long day!
So all of them
advanced...! Neat-o!
I'm so happy!
[ROSHI] So am I...!
Well... About
time you showed up!
[NARRATOR] So the
elimination round has ended
with quite favorable results...!
Goku, Krillin, and Yamcha have
all advanced to the finals...!
Soon they'll be fighting
against the toughest
warriors in the world...!
The ring will be bigger,
the time limit will be gone,
and there'll be thousands
of fans cheering them on!
There's no doubt about it...
The best is yet to come,
on Dragon Ball!