[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball,
Goku took on the fourth
challenger in a bizarre
tournament to determine the
fate of the seventh Dragon Ball.
Lucky shot.
Goku, get out of there!
He's going to use your
thoughts to destroy you!
Stop! What are you doing?!
You're going too far!
[ALL gasp]
[NARRATOR] The winged warrior
threatened Goku
with his Devilmite Beam,
a deadly ability
which allows him
to convert his opponent's
negative thoughts
into destructive rays
of pure energy.
Master, I'm confused.
What is a Devilmite beam?
It is a force of
unimaginable evil
that has destroyed more lives
than any war or
pestilence combined.
[ROSHI]
Long ago,
there was a mighty
but compassionate warrior.
His power was beyond measure,
yet many foolish upstarts
tried to destroy him
in hopes of making
a name for themselves.
They were all unsuccessful,
until one day,
the devil man appeared.
Knowing he could not compete
against the warrior's strength,
the devil man
attacked using his mind.
He discovered he could exploit
his opponent's negative
thoughts, no matter how faint,
and convert them into an
energy beam of immense power:
The Devilmite Beam.
It amplified any dark thought,
anger, malice, aggression,
and caused it to expand until
his opponent's heart
literally exploded.
[ROSHI] It was the death
of a great hero,
and the birth of
an even greater evil.
You've known
about this all along
and yet you let Goku
go out there by himself?
--[gasping]
--What?!
The least you could have done
was warn him! Really!
It's too late now, Bulma.
[laughing]
[ALL yell]
[SPIKE] Darkness swells
and fills his heart...
Now, rise! Come forth!
Rise! Rise!
Slowly tear this boy apart!
[laughing maniacally]
Now you die!
No! Stop it!
Think positive thoughts!
[ALL yell]
Darkness... explode!
Darkness explode!
Darkness--
Wow... Can you make
a color besides pink?
I don't get it.
[neck cracking]
Are you ready to start now?
This kid is not normal.
Devilmite Beam, hear my command!
Strike the boy down
where he stands!
Now...
...prepare to die!
The lightning adds a nice touch,
but do you think the
explosions are over-the-top?
You will not survive
this time, runt.
Darkness, hear me...
Through flesh and bone swell!
Rise! Rise!
Goku!
Darkness... explode!
Next time can you try purple?
[yelling]
No!
I need a vacation!
Upa... Look up.
Way to go, kid!
You really showed him!
We won!
I knew you could do it, Goku!
This doesn't make any sense!
The Devilmite Beam
works on everyone.
For you to be
immune to its power
means you don't carry
a single negative thought!
Huh... I guess I don't.
A pure mind, void of evil?
Not even my crystal ball
could have seen that coming...
It's over! What a relief!
Although I must say I didn't
doubt Goku for a minute.
Yes, but it
was not Goku's skill
that saved his life,
merely chance...
And their battle
has not ended just yet.
Still, his performance
against that Devilmite Beam
was impressive.
I can't help but wonder
how you would have done.
I wouldn't have gotten
a second chance.
[ALL laughing]
How do you think
you'd do under the beam?
[laughs nervously]
Ohhh... I'm so scared!
He's going to hurt me!
[ALL yell]
[GOKU] Stop joking around.
Are you ready to do this or not?
Beware...
The Devilmite Beam
isn't my only weapon...
...if you get the point.
[ALL gasp]
You have weapons! I don't!
This isn't a fair fight!
You can beat him, Goku!
Hey, watch out for his spear!
If you don't fight fair,
it's your choice,
but I'm not giving up!
You're going down, boy,
and I'm the one who's
going to put you there!
Not today.
Goodbye!
I can't hold on!
[SPIKE laughing maniacally]
I hear the fumes will kill you
before you even
touch the sludge...
[SPIKE laughing maniacally]
[ALL gasping]
[SPIKE laughing]
Looking for something?
[yelps]
Good work, Goku!
Yay! Yay!
Goku!
Fighting is just deplorable...
Go, Goku! Give him
a hard right! Smash him!
Sorry about your ceiling, Baba.
[ALL cheering]
I won two! Who's up next?
I've... never seen anyone...
Goku's power is unheard of.
He skipped extraordinary
and went straight to miraculous.
One more fight and we win!
That was flawless.
What a great match!
I knew you had it in you, Goku.
You're unstoppable!
Save your accolades
for later, boy.
You haven't won anything yet!
[GOKU]
We won!
Just one more match and
then I can get the Dragon Ball!
Your boastful antics won't
get you anywhere in this arena
and they're giving me
a splitting headache!
You'll do better to watch your
tongues and be silent!
I can't wait till you
witness my fifth fighter.
He's out of this world.
Number five,
your match is at hand!
[MASK MAN]
Hello there.
Uh, hi.
That's number five?
What's he going to do?
Fight Goku or entertain him?
[MASK MAN] Baba,
may I ask a favor of you?
[BABA] Yes, what is it?
[MASK MAN]
Thank you...
Seeing as this is my first
match I've been afforded
in some time,
I'd like to mark the occasion
by fighting outside,
on the grand arena.
I think the fresh air
will do us all some good.
Indeed. Let's bring this
out into the light of day
where everyone
can see your victory!
[laughing]
I hate disappointment.
[MASK MAN]
Of course. I'll do my best.
Yes, yes. I'm sure you will.
In fact, I'm counting on it.
[MASK MAN] These fights
are like the weather.
No guarantees.
[laughing]
Exactly.
It's the unpredictable nature
of this game that attracts me.
That, and of course the money.
I can't believe your luck.
Judging by the competition,
I'd say you've got
this one in the bag.
Are you sure about that?
This guy's more of a
lounge singer than a warrior.
Tell him, Yamcha.
Now, I wouldn't go that far,
but he definitely
seems a lot less hostile
than the bunch
we've been fighting.
But you're forgetting
he is number five,
and I'm sure Baba
saved her best man for last.
Do you mind?
I'm trying to lift
his spirits here.
Oh, what's wrong, Goku?
Are you tired or something?
No... It's not that.
It's just...
He... He smells good.
Uh, okay...
Well, just don't eat him.
I think that's
against the rules.
It's strange.
I can't explain it...
...but somehow...
...it makes me feel comfortable.
[UPA]
Huh?
How exciting!
I should have sold tickets!
[MASK MAN] Excuse me, Baba...
[MASK MAN] Actually, there is a
slight problem, a concern.
Master Roshi...
You've been pretty quiet.
Is there something
that's bothering you?
Come on, lighten up, Roshi...
You saw how strong Goku was a
minute ago--He's invulnerable.
No, no...
I wasn't thinking about that.
Well then what are you
worried about, Master Roshi?
That masked fighter...
Something's familiar.
His voice is like
an echo from the past.
[gasp]
I can't place it...
But I can't shake the feeling
that he's an incredible man.
Huh? By incredible
you mean strong?
[PUAR gasps]
He's a strong one, all right.
That's quite evident by my
sister's confidence in him.
That scrawny thing
doesn't look stronger
than a toothpick.
Huh? You mean to tell me
that's what this is all about?
This is good!
[laughing]
I love surprises!
Pardon! It's time for
your afternoon snack.
Snack time already?
I hadn't noticed.
I guess the time really does
fly by when the fights are fun.
Today I have a
special treat for you.
A delectable array of
some of your favorite dishes
like jellyfish gelatin
and chocolate mouse pie
with a tangy mosquito sauce.
Ah! Looks scrumptious!
How about a nice cup
of egg-presto?
It's my own special blend.
Egg-presto, my favorite,
and such a wonderful aroma!
What is your secret?
Egg whites and
a dash of nutmeg.
Nutmeg, of course.
With a hint of fish scales!
This really hits the spot!
Goku has been ready
to fight for a long time,
while you're just sitting there
eating and having fun! No fair!
Can we start fighting?
[BABA] Certainly, certainly.
Anxious to lose?
[BABA laughing]
Now...
Get ready! The last match
is about to begin!
It goes on 'til
one of you surrenders.
In the unlikely event
that Goku manages to win
this match for his team,
I will disclose
to him the location
of the final Dragon Ball.
[KRILLIN]
It's all up to you, Goku!
[YAMCHA] Yeah. No pressure.
I promise I'll do my best.
[MASK MAN] That's all anyone
can ask, or you can offer.
[GOKU] What?
Thanks.
What's that guy up to?
He's Goku's opponent,
but he acts like his friend.
Ready... Begin!
If my instincts serve me,
this is going to be
an interesting fight.
[GOKU thinking] This one is
nothing like the others...
But is that good or bad?
[MASK MAN] When you're ready.
[NARRATOR] As Goku's
friends watch the battle,
several questions
burn in their minds:
Can the young hero defeat
his mysterious opponent?
Why does this masked man
seem so familiar to both
Goku and Master Roshi?
This is the final match in
Fortuneteller Baba's tournament.
Who will emerge victorious?
Find out in the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball!