[NARRATOR] When we last
left the Dragon Ball gang,
Goku said his goodbyes to Bulma,
and ventured off alone across
the land heading toward the
island of the Turtle Hermit,
Master Roshi.
[NARRATOR] With the old
teacher's help, Goku sought
to improve his
skills of martial arts.
[GOKU] Hey, this place
is right by my house!
I've never seen it
from the sky before!
[GOKU laughing]
I'm hungry...
Hey, Master Roshi
must have some food!
Yay, let's go!
[whimpering]
[BULMA screaming]
[OOLONG] That baby's
like a deep-fryer...
And I was almost
a well-done porkroast!
It's a good
thing we jumped.
[BULMA] Help me!
I'm stuck here!
[OOLONG] Hey, just let go!
Huh?
[BULMA] Ow!
[YAMCHA] You okay?
Yeah, but the
plane sure isn't!
Those ships still
have some kinks in 'em.
Yamcha, what now?
Not sure. And that
was our last capsule.
[jungle noises]
[rustling]
[BULMA] Huh?!
[PUAR screams]
Why did we have
to crash into this place?
It's creepy!
It's not... so bad.
[screeching]
[BULMA squealing]
Let's move it, quick!
[voice screaming]
--[voice screaming]
--[BULMA screaming]
Wasn't that a human voice?
Well, I don't care what it
was, we're leaving!
[YAMCHA] Bulma!
--[OOLONG] Wait for me!
--[PUAR] Yamcha!
[voice screaming]
[panting]
Yaah!
[snickering]
Yipee!
[GOKU] Woah, whee!
[GOKU laughing]
[GOKU] Whoa, whoa, whoa, ha!
Oh!
[GOKU] Tidal wave!
[GOKU laughing]
It's cold!
[GOKU] That shortcut
must be nearby!
[GOKU laughing]
[GOKU] Found it!
[GOKU] Whooaa!
[GOKU] Whee!
[GOKU laughing]
[GOKU] Sharp turn!
Whee!
There it is!
[GOKU] Hello! Master Roshi!
I'm here!
Hey, where is he?
[WOMAN] That's right
girls, and here we go!
[WOMAN] One-two!
One-two! One-two!
That's right! Let's
get those legs moving!
All the way up! One-two!
One-two!
[ROSHI] One-two! One-two!
Heh, heh, isn't that fun?
[GOKU] There he is!
[ROSHI] Ahh, aerobics...
A gift from the heavens!
Hello!
Yes! Keep on truckin'!
[GOKU] Master Roshi?
[ROSHI] And one, and two,
and one for you and me...
[ROSHI] And one-two, one-two...
Hey Master...!
[GOKU] Ro...shi!
[GOKU laughing]
Oh, Goku! It's you.
I'm here for training.
Now, hold on! I'm
doing my morning workout!
[ROSHI] One-two!
One-two! Oh yeah!
[ROSHI] One-two, double time!
[ROSHI] There we go ladies!
Don't we feel the burn?
Master Roshi, I'm hungry!
[ROSHI] The refrigerator's
in the kitchen, kid!
[ROSHI] Grab something you like!
[ROSHI] Like I am...
[GOKU] Is this what he means?
Woah! Why's he keep
his food in this box?
[ROSHI laughing]
[chomping]
[slurping]
[WOMAN] One, and two,
and three, and four!
[ROSHI chuckling]
[WOMAN] Keep it up,
we're almost there!
[GOKU] Mm! Wow! It's
like winter in here!
See you tomorrow
morning! Buh-bye!
Good one!
[grunting]
[ROSHI] Hmm?
[screaming]
[GOKU groaning]
I've been ransacked!
Where did you put all my food?!
[GOKU chuckling]
Even ate my last
stick of butter...
Now, why was it you came here?
Well, we're done hunting
Dragon Balls for now.
And you said you'd teach me
martial arts! Remember?
Oh, lessons...
How pleasant...
[GOKU] And I can
stay for a while!
I brought stuff!
Did you by any
chance bring that girl?
You mean Bulma?
No, she went back
home with our friends.
[GOKU] They're probably
having fun in the city by now.
[BULMA panting]
[OOLONG] Gee...
[OOLONG] Walking on sand
is hard on the thighs...
[BULMA] Yeah...
[BULMA] I don't know why
it's taking so long...
[OOLONG] Are we sure
our miserable trudging is
trudging the right way...?
[BULMA] Of course.
The city is due north.
Huh?
Puar, compass!
Right! Here goes!
Huh?
[YAMCHA] South!
We've been going south!
Please don't joke, Yamcha!
I swear we started north!
[YAMCHA] Ugh... I'd
kill for some water...
[OOLONG] Or a slice
of bunt cake...
Dumb leg!
[YAMCHA] Yeah, let's
change that bandage.
[BULMA] Thank you, Yamcha.
Uh?
[chuckles]
Spare the cheese!
Huh?
[OOLONG] Hey, what's that?!
[YAMCHA] Uhh, must
be a sandstorm.
[heavy panting]
He's gonna make me so strong!
[ROSHI] I tell ya' Goku,
studying martial arts
is no Sunday picnic!
[GOKU] I don't mind.
I know I'll have to work hard
to get stronger than you!
[ROSHI chuckles]
Really, kid.
You could learn some manners.
[GOKU laughing]
But, you know, my
lessons don't come free!
[GOKU] Huh?
You must find
me a young gal!
It's the only way I
can start training you!
Okay!
But what's a "gow"?
A gal! A fun girl
I can go on a date with!
Ohh... That's kinda weird.
But if I find this girl,
then you'll train me?
Oh yeah!
[GOKU laughing]
[GOKU] Yippee!
[ROSHI] Hold on there, Goku!
Are you sure you
know what to look for?
A stallion like me has
very particular tastes!
You want someone
who'll be your friend.
Well, that'd be nice...
But I've got a
few other guidelines.
I'm a sucker for nice skin.
She's not too young,
but not too old.
And funny, too!
That's a lot.
But what does her
skin have to do with it?
[ROSHI] Uh?
Well, uh, I guess that's a
lesson for another time.
Okay! I'll find
you someone nice!
That's my boy!
[ROSHI] Did you
know your tail's gone?
Yeah, I'm not sure
where it went to!
Guess it got bored!
[GOKU] Bye Master Roshi!
[ROSHI] That boy is strange.
[ROSHI humming]
[ROSHI] Yeah, you sly
turtle-man! Feel that boogie!
[ROSHI] Now which of these
shells says "stud-muffin"?
[ROSHI humming]
[GOKU] Hey! Master
Roshi! She's here!
I'm coming!
[ROSHI screaming]
[gong crash]
Isn't she great?!
I'm ready to play!
Looks like your first
lesson won't be in Martial Arts!
Oh man!
Now, which of
these is prettier?
I like both!
What are you a saint?
Just get me one of these girls!
You got it?!
I don't see the
difference, but okay!
[GOKU] Bye again!
Goodbye.
There's no telling who he'll
bring home this time!
I better hide!
[ROSHI] Let's see,
is my breath okay?
[ROSHI coughing]
Well, not too bad!
[ROSHI] Oh! Here he comes!
Yoo-hoo!
I'm back!
[ROSHI] Please don't
be chunky...
Maybe he's asleep.
Now what does
this guy want?
[ROSHI] Goku! Goku!
[GOKU] Master Roshi,
Is this girl your type?!
Oh, you bet!
I'd say you just
hit the jackpot!
So you'll train me now?!
Oh, yes!
[ROSHI] Well, uh, let's begin
that lesson, uh, shall we?
I want you to ask that
girl there if, uh, she'd like
to go on a walk with me.
How is... that training?
[ROSHI] You want
to learn or not?!
[GOKU] Lady!
I'm supposed to
ask you if, um...
[ROSHI] I'm so romantic.
I'm back!
[ROSHI] No, no!
He screwed it up for me!
She said she
won't walk with you.
What do you mean?!
Well, she'd have a
much better time if you guys
went for a swim instead!
[ROSHI] Oh, it's
too good to be true!
What now?
[ROSHI] Well, now I go
accept her invitation!
[ROSHI] Wow!
Everyone knows swimming is a
second or third date activity!
She must be crazy about me!
[ROSHI] Now, buckle down, Roshi!
It's time to show
off your moves!
Hi!
Hi...
Do your legs hurt?
'Cause you've been running...
[ROSHI] all through my dreams!
Pardon?
I don't have legs.
So, you're a mermaid,
are you?!
[ROSHI] I knew there was
something fishy about this!
[ROSHI] I guess I can still
try with her human half!
[ROSHI] Well, uh, I'm like a
turtle, and you're part fish...
So, what do you say you
and me go inside and learn
more about our species?!
I get it! The lesson is
to keep your guard up!
Exactly.
[ROSHI] Yes.
Well, I'm glad
you paid attention
to the first lesson, Goku.
Never be open to an attack!
Got it!
[ROSHI] Good. Now, for your
next lesson, you will find me
another young gal,
who is very much like
the last one,
except for the fish part.
[GOKU] What? Again?!
I told you:
martial arts are not easy!
Yeah, okay!
[ROSHI] That do-gooder
Turtle is still on vacation!
I gotta make the best of it!
[GOKU] Look, Master Roshi!
Somebody's coming this way!
[ROSHI] What?! Is it Turtle?!
[ROSHI] I should've known
he'd spoil my plans!
No, wait...
It's a someone in a boat.
[growling]
[shouting]
Who's the goof?
Better help him, kid.
Yeah, thanks.
Ah! You're the great
Master Roshi, right?
[ROSHI] People tell me that.
Master, my name's Krillin
and I've come all the way
from a village in the East.
Please allow me to be your
humble student and learn
to fight like you.
Well, that's a
long way to come.
But, unfortunately, I do not
train every boy who shows
up at my door. Sorry.
[ROSHI] Hmm?
Maybe some quiet reading
will change your mind...?
[ROSHI] Ooh! Gimme gimme!
I brought it just for you.
So, who are you anyway?
His pupil?
Yeah, I'm Goku!
Doesn't seem
that you like fighting.
I like marshmallows!
What's that gotta
do with anything?
Well, I'm hungry and
your bald head looks like one!
What did you say?!
Don't you know that everyone
who's serious about martial
arts shaves their head?!
Look at Master Roshi!
He shaves!
[ROSHI] Nope.
I'm naturally bald.
[ROSHI] Krillin, after
careful consideration...
Yeah?!
I've decided to
take you in as my student,
but only if you go help
Goku find me a girl!
I.. trust that you know...
the kind I like...?
[KRILLIN chuckling]
[KRILLIN whispering]
That's it!
Write that part down!
I know my master's tastes!
Then what are we waiting for?!
Jump on that Nimbus
Cloud and find me a date!
A Nimbus?
Yeah, that's his name!
You named a cloud?
C'mon, jump on up!
Okay...
Hey! What's the deal
with this thing?!
[ROSHI] Only those
who have a pure heart
can ride the Nimbus Cloud...
And that means...
you've been hiding
something from us!
Don't hurt me!
I just have some magazines
that I'm not supposed to read!
You mean... you have more?
I'm sorry, Master Roshi!
I didn't show you
because the first one
seemed to do the trick!
Here, have 'em!
[ROSHI chuckling]
Here, take them all!
I don't want them anymore!
Here! And that's one...
and two... and wait...
[ROSHI screaming]
[KRILLIN] Here's one,
here's another one.
[NARRATOR] So, Master Roshi has
taken two students on this day.
But what will
come of these boys?
Will they be friends?
Or foes?