[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball...
The World Martial Arts
Tournament opened with
Krillin versus Bacterian --
owner of the nastiest finger
that ever existed!
[NARRATOR] Smell after raunchy
smell, this king of funk
hit Krillin with every foul odor
the human body has to offer!
And poor Krillin was stunned.
[NARRATOR] Thanks to Goku's
constant encouragement,
Krillin was able to
catch his second wind!
Bacterian, however,
had saved his
deadliest attack for last--
the deep-throated,
mucous-filled luggi of death!
[NARRATOR]
But Krillin prevailed,
and put the big oaf to rest,
with a whiff of
his own medicine!
[BACTERIAN]
I'm done.
[NARRATOR] Krillin has scored
a victory over poor hygiene
and advanced to the next round.
But the celebration
can't last long!
It's time for another big match,
today, on Dragon Ball!
[CROWD cheering]
[KRILLIN giggling]
You did it! You beat him!
Goku it was awesome!
I don't know about you guys,
but I loved that fight!
I'd say that Krillin
boy is goin' places!
[WOMAN 1]
Oh, but he's so little!
I bet Master Roshi's
going crazy!
[KRILLIN chuckles]
Hey...
W-Where is he, anyway?
[GOKU]
Hey Bulma,
do you know where
Master Roshi is sitting?
[BULMA] Sorry Goku, we lost
track of him in the crowd.
[PUAR] He keeps leaving
us and we think
it's to go look at girls...
Well gee, that's not very nice.
Then he didn't watch my fight?
Oh hold on Krillin,
maybe he did.
[GOKU sniffing]
I smell him!
[CHUN laughs]
May I ask what the
lipstick is for, sweetie?
Let's say it's for
guys like you.
Oh, well my name's Jackie Chun!
Perhaps you and I can
have some coffee?
Sorry, but my attention
is on someone else.
[CHUN]
Hm...
Hey! I think she likes ya, son!
[NAM] Brothers and sisters,
keep your strength.
I have not forgotten you.
[BOY VILLAGER panting]
Big brother I am so thirsty.
Not a single drop
is left for us.
Even the carrots are
too thirsty to survive.
The sun takes us all.
The rain season will
come in two months.
We'll buy water from the city
to last us until then.
Nam, this drought
has lasted long
and we have spent
all the savings we have.
The crops have failed
and there is nothing
to buy the water with.
Then I must enter
the upcoming Tournament.
There is a reward
and with it I can buy
enough water for us all to live.
It is the only choice we have.
[NAM]
The only choice...
[NAM grunting]
Ahh. This man has spirit.
Now everybody get ready!
It's time for the
next great match!
[GOKU] Master?
[KRILLIN] Hello?
Come on boys, I'm in the
middle of my speech here.
[CROWD cheering]
[ANNOUNCER] I've got to admit
I've been waiting
for this one, folks!
It's young against old!
Yamcha vs Jackie Chun!
Well, here I go!
Good luck, Yamcha!
That was a super kick, Krillin.
Oh! Thank you very much, mister!
[CHUN giggles]
There's something funny
about that guy...
He's so wasteful.
[GOKU]
I'm so hungry!
[KRILLIN]
But you just ate! Gosh!
[GOKU]
Oh wow!
[GIRAN]
Huh?
[GOKU]
Now this is more like it!
Well, dig in!
[GOKU]
Oh yeah! I was really starving!
Nam, the last of our valuables
have been gathered in this bag,
so you can sell them
in the city to pay
for your trip.
[stomach growls]
Huh?
[stomach growling]
[NAM] Uh...
[GOKU giggles]
[GIRAN gasps growls]
I know that
you're hungry! Eat up!
No... I can't.
[GOKU yelps]
What was that for?
You took my food!
No one does that!
[KRILLIN yelps]
Stop your wasting!
I'd like to see
you try and stop me
Mister Skin-and-Bones!
[ANNOUNCER]
And here are the fighters!
In the orange and green uniform,
the young and fearless, Yamcha!
Bring it home, Wolf-boy!
It's what you've
always wanted, Yamcha!
Enjoy it!
I wonder what this mysterious
Jackie Chun guy looks like.
What's it to you, Bulma?
I thought Yamcha
was your boyfriend!
He is!
But I can still keep my
eyes open for an upgrade!
And in the black and
white outfit-- Jackie Chun!
Peace, dude!
Dude? Has that guy been
stuck on a desert island?
Well, so much for intrigue!
That guy's just a
crusty old geezer!
Go Yamcha! Hurray!
[YAMCHA]
Jackie Chun...
I've never heard of
a fighter by that name.
But if he's made it this far,
I bet he's got
some good moves.
Gentlemen, take your
positions! Let's go!
[YAMCHA] He doesn't even
put up his guard.
And I can't sense
his fighting energy.
That means he's either foolish,
or extremely confident.
[YAMCHA]
Wait, I remember now.
[CHUN yells]
[CHUN laughing]
[YAMCHA]
But what was his technique?
I'll attack him quickly
and watch him move.
[YAMCHA yells]
[YAMCHA grunting]
[YAMCHA gasps]
That time you almost touched me!
Huh?
But he's a geezer!
Your fighting moves
are big and fun to look at,
but I'm afraid most of them
are just a waste of energy.
I'll show you!
[YAMCHA yells]
[YAMCHA grunting]
You have to see this, Krillin!
That old man is dodging every
punch like it's nothing!
[KRILLIN]
Hm?
[ANNOUNCER]
Unbelievable!
Yamcha has launched
an aggressive attack,
but can't even lay
a finger on Jackie Chun!
Who knew the elderly
could move so fast?
The old man's just
having fun with me!
But let's see him laugh
at my Wolf Fang Fist!
Goku, you know Yamcha, right?
Would you say he's
a pretty decent fighter?
[GOKU]
Yeah, he's really good!
I fought him once and he used
some crazy attack move on me!
[KRILLIN] Then if he can't
touch this Jackie Chun guy,
I think we're in trouble.
To be honest, I don't feel
too good about this.
There's no need to worry.
Yamcha still hasn't
used his Wolf Fang Fist.
I'm still worried.
Wolf Fang Fist Attack!
[YAMCHA grunting]
[CHUN grunts]
[YAMCHA]
[KRILLIN, GOKU gasp]
[GROUP gasps]
[YAMCHA]
Huh?
[YAMCHA screams]
Allow me to present you with
this refreshing winter breeze.
[CHUN grunts]
[YAMCHA screams]
[BULMA screams]
[GOKU screams]
[KRILLIN gasps]
[CHUN chuckling] How did you
like it? Wasn't it cool?
That was a joke.
[ANNOUNCER]
Why-Why that's a ring out!
Jackie Chun is the winner!
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER]
What an amazing fighter!
Jackie Chun seemed
to have that victory
under his belt from
the first hit of the gong!
Am I right?
I don't get it! How did he--?
But he never even touched me!
Ah! Yamcha lost!
Yeah. And who's gonna have
to fight against the old man
in the second round?
It's me, isn't it?
Uh, Uh-huh.
Don't worry Krillin,
maybe that old guy
just got lucky
when he beat Yamcha.
First it was that sewer-face
and now I'm up
against a super-hero...
[GOKU giggles] Yam--
[KRILLIN] Hey.
He might not be in the mood
to talk right now, Goku.
Oh...
That last move...
I couldn't... even see it.
It's energy from within.
Maybe someday I'll
teach you how to do it.
Say, don't I know
you from some--
[ANNOUNCER] This next match
should be a doozy, folks!
Both these challengers are
new to the fighting scene,
and I really have
no idea what to expect--
It's Nam versus Ranfan!
[RANFAN chuckles]
[CHUN moans]
Excuse me, boys.
Oh, Ranfan!
Did you see me win?
I was very studly!
[YAMCHA]
Hm...
Goku, where's Master Roshi?
Have you seen him?
He's in the crowd.
Puar told us that
he's looking at girls.
So he's not watching you fight?
Guess not. But Puar
could be wrong.
Goku smelled him!
Oh, really? Interesting...
[YAMCHA]
Something fishy is going on.
Man, I wish I were smarter!
[CHUN]
Hm?
This young man's brain is just
sweating out seriousness!
All this time, and he
hasn't smiled once!
[CHUN] Everyone else
here is fighting for fun,
or for the title at most,
but not this guy.
There's something more to him.
Meh.
[BOY VILLAGER panting]
Nam...
So you can sell them
in the city.
[BOY VILLAGER]
Goodbye big brother. Goodbye...
[CHUN]
Hm...
[CHUN] Perhaps my plans
will have to change, after all.
[YAMCHA]
I've got it!
Jackie Chun and Master Roshi
must be related!
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER] Fighting in the
orange and fuscia robe,
the ever-silent, Nam!
[ANNOUNCER] And to my left,
wearing the blue tank top
and green pants, is Ranfan!
Be gentle!
[ANNOUNCER] Let the third
match of the tournament...
...begin!
[NAM]
Oh-- hm.
[RANFAN grunting]
[NAM groaning]
[RANFAN, NAM grunting]
[NAM growls]
[NAM yells]
[RANFAN screams]
Hm?
[RANFAN whimpers]
[RANFAN screams]
It hurts!
[ANNOUNCER]
What's this?
It seems Ranfan
has collapsed in pain!
[RANFAN sobbing]
Oh! You hit too hard!
Uh... I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to!
Good one Nam!
Go on and make the nice girl
cry why don't you!
[YAMCHA]
He could be his brother...
[NAM] Uh, oh, I-I'm so sorry--
[RANFAN sobbing]
[NAM stammering]
[RANFAN cackles]
[RANFAN yells]
[NAM groans]
[NAM screams]
[RANFAN chuckles]
[NAM panting, groaning]
[RANFAN grunting]
[NAM grunts]
Huh?
I was warned that
people in the city
would try to trick me
from my goal.
[RANFAN gulps]
But I swore that
I wouldn't let anything
stand in the way from saving
the lives of my people!
[ANNOUNCER]
Uh-oh! Nam's temper is rising!
I'd say he's preparing
for a big attack!
Ooooh...
You're so brave!
Don't you make a mockery of me!
[RANFAN yelps]
[RANFAN grunting]
[NAM grunts]
[RANFAN growls]
[RANFAN panting]
Just one question...
Oh?
[NAM gasps]
[CHUN yells]
[NAM whimpers]
You think pink's
a good color on me?
[NAM whimpers]
[RANFAN chuckles]
You tough boys are all alike.
Oh baby!
How fresh! How beautiful!
How scantily clad!
Uh?! It's that vulgar laughter!
I'd recognize it anywhere!
[CHUN] Go on Ranfan!
Give him the full treatment!
[YAMCHA] Jackie Chun
isn't Master Roshi's friend,
or student, or even
his brother! He can only be...
Master Roshi himself!
It's no wonder I was beaten!
[CHUN]
Now let's see a good high-kick!
Oh yeah!
Nam!
[NAM whimpers]
[CHUN laughs]
[RANFAN giggling]
[NAM whimpering]
[CHUN laughing]
I guess it's a good thing
I didn't get matched up
with her after all!
[NAM whimpers]
[GOKU] Why does he keep
backing away from her, Krillin?
It's like when you're tired
but you can't sleep.
[RANFAN]
What's the matter, Nam?
Don't you like what you see?
[NAM yelping]
[ANNOUNCER]
What a development!
Ranfan's undressing
has just been a ploy
to force Nam out of the ring!
And I do believe
it's going to work!
[RANFAN]
Hm?
Ee...
Hey! Why aren't you fighting?
The village...
How much longer can we hold on?
Nam, you mustn't
hold anything back,
because if your mission fails
this village will
have nothing left.
[BOY VILLAGER panting]
Big brother, I'm so thirsty!
[NAM] I promised
I would not let them down!
[RANFAN]
This act is getting old.
[ANNOUNCER]
Here it is people!
Ranfan is making her final move!
[NAM] Wait! All I must do
is close my eyes...
...and fight her
with my other senses!
[RANFAN grunting]
[NAM grunts]
Huh?
[NAM yells]
[RANFAN yelps]
No way!
Huh?
[CROWD cheering]
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10!
And that's an official
knock out, people!
Nam brings home the win!
[RANFAN whimpers]
I only meant to stun her.
[CROWD gasping]
[CHUN] Please step
back everyone! I'm a doctor!
Okay, let me just...
...check for a heartbeat.
[ANNOUNCER] Excuse me, sir,? I
think you should go wait inside.
[ANNOUNCER coughs]
Sir?
Oh yeah, that is
definitely Master Roshi.
[NARRATOR] The World
Martial Arts Tournament
continues to heat up!
And next on the list--
the monster beast,
Giran vs Goku! On Dragon Ball!