[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball,
after decades
of being imprisoned
by the Turtle Hermit's
Master, Mutaito,
the evil King Piccolo escaped
and began a new plot
to conquer the world
using the Dragon Balls.
Fortunately,
the mountain boy, Yajirobe
was able to cut through
the King's minions,
preventing the extraterrestrial
from getting his clutches
on the magical orbs.
Out of fear of being recaptured,
Piccolo sent his chief
enforcer, Tambourine,
to destroy all members of
the Martial Arts Society.
His first victim was Krillin,
whom Goku vowed to avenge.
I told you I'd make you pay!
I'll never forgive you
for killing Krillin
and my Nimbus Cloud!
And I want my Dragon Ball back!
This is truly hilarious!
You want to fight me again?
Last time I was hungry, but now
I'm full and ready to beat you!
[PICCOLO] Beat me? You're not
even in the same league.
I'll stop you, one way
or another! You'll see!
[NARRATOR]
With that, the showdown began.
This one's for Krillin!
[radar beeping]
[ROSHI]
I hear you saved my turtle.
[GOKU]
Who are you?
[ROSHI] I'm Master Roshi,
the Turtle Hermit.
A long time ago,
Gohan told me
he was raising a
small boy who had a tail.
[GOKU] That's me!
Gohan was my grandpa!
[ROSHI] Who is this?
[KRILLIN]
Hi, my name is Krillin.
It's an honor to meet you.
I've traveled all the way
from a small village
in the east.
I want to be your pupil
and learn the secrets
of Martial Arts!
[GOKU, KRILLIN laughing]
[GOKU]
This is going to be fun!
[CHIAOTZU] Hey look!
Eh?
[CHIAOTZU] It's flashing!
With any luck that's the
monster who destroyed Krillin.
If it is, I have a feeling
that's where we'll find Goku.
Mm-hmm. If he's alive.
[TAMBOURINE
chuckling menacingly]
Come on. You talk big.
Let's see if you can back it up.
I'm waiting.
Stop that!
Huh?!
[GOKU yelling]
[choking]
[GOKU growling]
I sure hope I never end up
on that kid's revenge list.
[radar beeping]
Hey! It's moving again!
Do you think that King
Piccolo is onto us yet?
Well, whoever it is,
their movement is erratic.
Let's go after them.
I gotta admit, Goku,
ya did a first-rate job.
That monster
deserved what he got.
You remember your promise.
He's mine now.
[GOKU] Sure.
All right! I'm starving!
[TAMBOURINE groaning]
Why is he moving?
You little rat!
Oops, looks like
I stopped too soon.
Unbelievable!
How could we, the warrior tribe,
be beaten by you?!
Pathetic human.
[growling]
[laughing]
Fool! He was obliterated!
I told you! We are
superior to the human race!
[chuckling]
[GOKU]
You're not very smart, are you?
[laughing]
That blast was pretty
weak, if you ask me.
[growling]
Now it's your turn to feel the
same pain that you gave Krillin!
Wait! You're my lunch!
Power Pole Extend!
Ka...
...Me...
...Ha...
...Ha!
[nervous whimpering]
Your majesty, what's wrong?!
A headache?!
Sire?!
He's gone. Tambourine is dead.
What's going on out there?!
This shouldn't be happening!
No! Tambourine!
What kind of
creature is out there
that could defeat these people?
I'm not sure
I want to know, sir.
[PICCOLO] Listen!
[PILAF] Yes?
[PICCOLO]
Take this vessel to wherever
Cymbal and Tambourine
were killed.
I'll destroy this
new adversary myself.
Thanks a lot! You've completely
annihilated my dinner!
What am I supposed
to eat now, huh?
Sorry. I was so upset
I forgot all about it.
I had everything ready!
Aww, you already started a fire.
Yeah. I've tried 'em raw, but
they just don't taste as good.
Well, be patient.
I'm sure if you keep
that Dragon Ball,
another one will
be by soon enough.
[PICCOLO grunting frustratedly]
Two of my finest
warriors were destroyed
as if they were mere amateurs!
I don't know who is
responsible for this outrage,
but I will personally
see to their destruction
for interfering with my plans!
Oh, wait!
What is it?!
The Dragon Ball
we've been chasing
has been moving in odd patterns.
I wonder...
It's just as I feared!
According to the map,
there are three Dragon Balls
clustered together
and moving towards a fourth!
Well, well, well...
Does that mean someone else
is after the Dragon Balls?
Do we have some competition?
It looks that way! What now?!
Wait, they've stopped!
It's near here, Master.
We're close.
I hope this new ball
also leads to Goku.
[TIEN]
It's right over there.
I don't like the looks of this.
[yelling]
[ROSHI]
We're being attacked!
Chiaotzu!
Right!
Chiaotzu, you stay and
guard the plane, all right?
Okay.
[ROSHI]
Let's be careful.
[startled gasp]
Master Roshi!
I'm okay. Keep going. I'm fine.
[ROSHI] I wonder if anyone would
ever find this place habitable?
It's secluded enough for a base.
[ROSHI yells]
Master, are you all right?!
Master!
What?
[ROSHI]
One, two, three, four, five.
Hey, it's the six-star ball.
We did it!
All we need are three more.
This was way too easy.
Who would've hid it here?
Well, it wasn't a human,
that's for sure.
[ROSHI]
Those crows, see? Feathers.
[TIEN] Crows?
[ROSHI] Maybe they picked
it up from somewhere else
and brought it here.
[TIEN] That could explain
why the movement
was so strange
on the radar.
[ROSHI] True, and crows
are attracted to shiny objects
like our six-star friend here.
[TIEN] I see.
I feel like we're being watched.
Let's get out of here.
Mm-hmm.
Huh? Ah!
I never should have
waxed my head! Shoo!
Let's make a run for it!
[ROSHI]
Best idea I've heard all day!
[ROSHI] That's my head,
not a bird feeder! Scram!
Here, this might help!
Master! Hurry!
Come on!
We've been lucky so far.
We've managed to collect
four Dragon Balls
without too much trouble.
[ROSHI] Speak for yourself. I
hope this doesn't leave a scar.
King Piccolo doesn't appear
to be in much of a rush
to expand his collection.
I wonder what he's up to.
Maybe he doesn't need them.
He's probably preoccupied with
exterminating martial artists.
[CHIAOTZU]
The radar's flashing!
One, two, three, four, five.
I count five dots!
Tien, turn around!
With only three
Dragon Balls left to find,
you know it's possible
this is the one
Piccolo's henchman stole
before he killed Krillin.
If you're right,
that means we're
about to have to
fight him first-hand.
It's going to happen
sooner or later.
I just hope we're ready.
I'm sure we're going to win.
I'm afraid the odds
of us winning
a head-on battle
aren't too good.
Our best bet is to sneak in
through the back door,
surprise him,
and take the ball
while he's not looking.
Then the Eternal Dragon
can defeat him.
That's too passive
for my taste, Master.
I say we fight him
hand-to-hand and destroy him!
I understand how you feel, Tien.
But he's much stronger
than you may think.
With our combined strength,
Piccolo still has us
at a disadvantage.
Our best bet is to concentrate
on bringing all the
Dragon Balls together.
Then we'll let the Eternal
Dragon exterminate King Piccolo.
But Master,
I thought our purpose
in gathering the Dragon Balls
was so we could
resuscitate Krillin.
The Eternal Dragon will only
make one wish come true.
And once the Dragon
grants that wish,
the balls are
scattered again, correct?
After one year, we can gather
the orbs back together again.
At that time, we will
revive Krillin. I hope.
What about the Containment Wave?
That's a ridiculous
idea, Tien Shinhan!
Forgive me, Master,
but it worked before.
That's what Master Mutaito used
to capture Piccolo, wasn't it?
In exchange for his life.
Besides, there's no
guarantee that it would work.
If we failed,
Yamcha would be the only one
left behind
to carry on the fight,
and he's in no condition
to defeat Piccolo.
I understand.
For Master to have such a
reaction to my suggestion,
there must be more to the
Evil Containment Wave
than I realized.
I can't believe
this is happening!
They're on the move again and
now they have four Dragon Balls.
What are we going to do?!
Calm down! They can gather
all the balls they want.
They can't use the
power without all seven.
Let's not interrupt their work.
Let them hunt down the remaining
six. Saves us the trouble.
Then when they've
gathered them all,
we'll take them
in one fell swoop.
Hmm. Good idea.
We will turn our
immediate attention
on finding those responsible
for the deaths of
Cymbal and Tambourine.
I'm starving.
The sky is clear
as far as I can see.
No sign of any monsters.
You said someone would
be coming if I kept this.
I'll go take
another look around.
Call me when you
catch someone, okay?
I'll give you the ball then.
--Huh?!
--[radar beeping]
Goku, did you hear
what I just said?
It's right on us!
The Dragon Ball is
right around here somewhere!
[radar beeping increases]
It's here!
You mean another Dragon Ball?
Above!
What's that?! It's not
like any bird I've seen.
[NARRATOR] The Turtle Hermit's
greatest fear has been realized.
King Piccolo
has found Goku first!
Can Goku survive
against such an
overwhelmingly
powerful adversary?
Find out on the next
action-packed adventure
of Dragon Ball!