[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball,
Goku traveled to West City
to have Bulma repair
the broken Dragon Radar.
On his first trip
to the big city,
Goku found he had a lot
to learn about urban life.
But after a quick challenge
fight on the street corner,
Goku amazed the crowd
and earned some cash
to make his search
a little easier.
Or so he thought, until he
encountered a pair of thugs
looking to take advantage
of his innocent nature.
They found out soon enough,
that our young hero is
much more than he appears...
Finally, Goku was
steered in the direction
of a kindly police officer,
who, after a little prodding,
guided him safely across
town to Bulma's home
at the Capsule Corporation.
Stay tuned; Goku's urban
adventure continues today!
Bull-maaa!
It's me, Goku! I'm down here!
Bul-ma!
Oh-ho! Stope that there!
You really don't have to
yell like that, you know?
You can step up
and use the intercom.
What's an intercom?
Uh... Good day.
Uh... We're here to
speak to Miss Bulma
if she's available,
please, there.
[ROBOT MAID]
Bulma is not on the premises.
She has not yet returned
from her school day.
Whoa... How can that pole talk?
Oh... that's right,
it's not quite time
for school to let out yet.
What should-- Hey!
Get away from there!
What now?
Should we wait here?
Yeah, I'll wait, but you
can go ahead and leave.
Oh nooo! How do I know for
sure that you're her friend?
I'd be in big trouble with the
boss there if I led a crook
to the home of Dr. Brief!
I'm not a bad guy!
You don't have to
worry about me!
[POLICEMAN] Well,
anyway, Capsule Corporation
is one of the most important
companies in the world.
The Briefs are very influential.
It's hard to believe a strange
little fellow like you
would know them. One can
never be too careful, you know.
Hey, I'm picking up
Bulma's scent!
[GOKU sniffs]
Huh? Her scent?
[GOKU] Huuuh.
[POLICEMAN sniffs]
[POLICEMAN] I don't know, son.
I don't smell anything there.
[loud music plays]
[engine blasts]
[brakes squeal]
Bulma!
Huh...?
[GOKU] Hi!
Goku! What're you doing here?
[loud music plays]
How in the world did
you find this place?
Well, I almost didn't...
But Mr. Police here
gave me a ride!
Right. So are you actually,
uh, related to the Dr. Brief?
Oh yeah. He's my dad.
So, what brings you
here to see me?
I came to ask for help.
I'm pretty sure I broke
the Dragon Radar.
Do you think you
could fix it for me?
[BULMA] Well, sure, no problem.
Let's go take a look at it.
'Kay!
[POLICEMAN] I don't get it.
I didn't smell a thing.
How'd he know she
was coming, there?
Wait! Miss, excuse me!
I hate to ask, but do you
think you could check out
my bike while you're at it?
It hasn't been
running very well there.
[BULMA] Yeah, whatever. Okay.
[POLICEMAN] Hey, is it
a school holiday today?
Did they let you out early?
[BULMA] I got bored,
so I skipped out.
[POLICEMAN] I'm gonna
pretend I didn't hear that.
I'm home!
[ROBOT MAID]
Good afternoon, Miss Bulma.
[GOKU gasps]
What are you?
So, where's my dad?
[ROBOT MAID] Dr. Brief is
presently located in the garden.
Oh. Okay.
I really liked the
stuffed quail last night.
Why don't you make some
for us again, tonight?
[ROBOT MAID] It would be
my pleasure, Miss Bulma.
[GOKU raspberries]
[GOKU giggles]
[GOKU] Hold on! I'm coming too!
[beeping]
--[GOKU gasps]
--[POLICEMAN] Whoa-ho-ho, Nelly!
[GOKU] Hey, we're outside again!
[BULMA] No, we're still indoors.
This is our first floor garden.
[DOGS barking]
[POLICEMAN] There are cats
and dogs all over the place!
Yea, my dad rescues
unwanted animals,
mostly dogs, cats and dinosaurs,
and gives them a home here.
Oh!
[POLICEMAN squeals]
Oh, don't mind him.
Dad! There you are!
Who's your guest?
[BULMA] I've told you
about him before.
This is my friend Goku.
Yes, of course!
I have heard a lot about you,
but I thought you were
just a little fellow.
You certainly don't look
twelve years old to me.
Uh, uh, well,
you see, I'm not...
No, Daddy!
Not him! My name is Goku!
Oh, so you're the boy?
That's me!
That makes sense.
You're much shorter!
This is the great scientist
who invented the Dyno-Cap?
In-credible!
[BULMA growls]
[DR. BRIEF] You're short,
but you look pretty strong!
[GOKU laughs]
Hi!
[SCRATCH] Meow!
We're going to go
upstairs to my room now.
Check out the policeman's
motorcycle for him, okay?
Come on, Goku! Let's go.
Hey, no smooching
up there, you two.
Understand?
You're so embarrassing!
That's my job.
[drill whining]
[GOKU] Wow...
That looks difficult!
Do you really know
what's wrong with it?
Yeah, it looks like the A-2
circuit just got knocked loose.
This is very delicate, Goku.
You have to be more
careful with it.
But I am.
I always keep it
right here in my shirt.
[BULMA] Well knowing you,
somehow, I doubt that's
a very safe place...
There! All done!
Thank you!
[GOKU laughs]
Goku, you've got two?
That's all you've
been able to find?
Taking it easy, are you?
[GOKU chuckles]
No, the Dragon Balls just
aren't very easy to find.
Well, using the radar, I don't
see how it could be that hard.
Hmm.
With my help, you'd find
the rest in no time, ya' know?
No thanks.
I don't need any help.
You would just slow me down.
Oh, is that so?!
I guess next time you'll
fix the radar yourself!
[GOKU] But you can't even
ride on the Flying Nimbus!
[BULMA laughs]
Yes! Yes I can!
So you're saying you're
completely good now?
I am an exceptionally
good person!
My only crime is
being beautiful.
Uhh...
Watch!
This is my newest thing.
What's it do?
It's my own invention,
the Microband.
When I push this button,
I shrink to a fraction
of my normal size!
[GOKU] Whoaa!
That is really neat!
You're not even
as tall as my knee!
[BULMA] Sometimes
I even amaze myself!
And as long as
I'm shrunk like this,
you'll be able to carry me with
you on the Nimbus no sweat!
Yeah, I bet that'll
work just fine!
Come on, Goku, please?
Let's try it just once!
I'll take you on a
guided tour of the city!
[BULMA squeals]
[GOKU gasps]
[WOMAN] Oh, my,
you must be little Goku!
Hi there!
How do you do?
I'm Bulma's mother, Mrs. Brief.
[MRS. BRIEF giggles]
[BULMA squeals]
[MRS. BRIEF laughs]
Uhh... Uh...
--[BULMA growls]
--[MRS BRIEF] Oh!
Bulma, darling,
you scared me!
What are you doing
underneath my foot?!
Mom, you stepped on me!
I don't understand why you
want to shrink yourself anyway.
Watch your step when
you come in my room!
I'm sorry for all the noise,
but she's at that age.
Well, anyway, would you
like some refreshments?
Mother, would you
just leave us alone?!
Oh! You're in...
such a mood!
[BULMA screams]
Hey, where are
Oolong and Yamcha?
Ugh...
Do both of them still
live here with you?
Well, yes, Yamcha
and Oolong should be
around here somewhere,
but Yamcha and Bulma
are having a little--
Mother, be quiet!
--A tiny little lover's tiff!
--[GOKU] Ohhh...
We don't need
to talk about this!
Hmm...
A "tiff"?
[STAFF OFFICER]
If the reports are true, sir,
it would seem that
this boy defeated
all of Tower
guards by himself.
General White's forces have
been completely destroyed.
In addition, it seems he
now has two Dragon Balls
in his possession...
One from White,
and one from Silver.
[RED] Do we know where he is?
[STAFF OFFICER] Yes, sir.
We believe we have
pinpointed his location.
According to our Dragon Radar,
his current position is here.
Which puts him somewhere
within the limits of West City.
[RED] West City?
[STAFF OFFICER] Mm-hmm.
[RED chuckles]
So he's right there in our
master thief's hometown.
How unfortunate.
--[RED chuckles]
--[STAFF OFFICER] For him.
I've given Hasky 1 million
zeni as payment to secure
the Dragon Balls and
return them to us.
[RED chuckles]
Excellent.
[STAFF OFFICER] Yes, and if past
performance is any indication,
I have no doubt it is
money well spent.
[STAFF OFFICER] Hasky has made
a career out of successfully
pulling jobs most
would call impossible.
"Impenetrable Security"
is merely a phrase
to be proven wrong...
In my opinion, the title
"Master Thief" barely begins
to describe this
level of talent.
[STAFF OFFICER]
Last time, if you'll recall,
we received our merchandise
ahead of schedule,
and the authorities were left
without a trace to follow.
I believe I can say
with confidence,
Hasky will find the boy...
and the Dragon Balls.
[RED chuckles]
[CROWD gasping]
[CROWD gasping,
murmuring]
[GUYS gasping]
[CHILDREN laughing]
Rats! We didn't get
nothing today!
Yeah, thanks to that
kid with the tail!
That little brat cost us some
big loot this afternoon, huh?
[gun fires]
[THUG squeals]
[THUG] Hasky!
[BOTH whimper]
Well, boys, you look
alarmed as usual.
Hasky! Uh,
to what...
To what do we owe this
unexpected pleasure?
I could use your help
with a little information.
What d'ya need?
I'm looking for a little boy.
A boy...?
[BOTH scream]
[BULMA] Hmph.
A fight? What for?
You see, Bulma doesn't
like it when...
[GIRLS chattering excitedely]
What is that?
[GIRLS] Yamcha! We're waiting
for you! Come out!
Who's making
all that noise?!
Welll... Yeah, they're back.
That gaggle of screaming
girls is Yamcha's fan club.
[GOKU] What?
[BULMA growls]
[GIRLS yelling]
[GIRLS scream]
[GOKU growls]
I wish they'd be quiet!
Hey! Stop yelling!
Yamcha's not even
here right now!
Oh, wait, that's
not Yamcha!
He's small!
And strange!
[GIRLS mumble]
Is there something
wrong with them?
Why?
I don't understand why
they're acting like that!
[BULMA growls]
[GOKU whimpers]
Shut up! Go away!
There's no telling when
Yamcha will be back!
[GIRLS] Hmph!
Hey, let's go.
I'll take you
sightseeing in the city.
Hmmm?
So... do you see now?
Yamcha is what they
call a catch, you know?
He's good looking
and rich, too...
That makes him popular
with the girls,
and Bulma doesn't like it!
[BULMA growls] Just drop it!
Oh, no! There's
that temper again!
[wrench clicks]
[DR BRIEF] All right.
That ought to have it
running, good as new!
Thanks there,
Dr. Brief! Good job!
Bulma, where are you off to?
[BULMA growls]
What difference
does it make?!
She's at that age.
[BULMA] Okay! What do
you say we get moving?
You've got a whole city to see!
Great!
Oh, Nimbus!
Ho-ho!
[BULMA] Guess
that's my cue!
Ho-ho! Ho ho ho ho!
So, ready to go?
Let's do it!
Rich people. They really
are a different breed.
[POLICEMAN screams]
[crash]
You fool!
You're a cop, you should pay
attention to your driving!
[POLICEMAN] I'm so sorry!
It just got away from me!
How cool!
I love it up here!
Look! Over there!
[BULMA] That's the biggest
shopping mall in the city!
[GOKU] Let's go then!
[GOKU gasps]
This street is busy!
[PIG GUY] Whoa!
It was that kid!
[BOTH] Huh?
[GOKU laughs]
Huh...?
[GOKU] What is that?
[BULMA] It's an amusement
park! It just opened.
I've never been there.
Hey, why don't we go?
Yeah?
It looks like so much fun!
Huh?
Oh, yeah, let's spend
the whole day up there!
Great!
Huh?
Yamcha!
[BULMA growls]
Nimbus, go down there!
Hey, wait!
Stupid Yamcha!
[GOKU] Yam-chaaa!
[YAMCHA yells]
[GOKU] It's Goku!
I'm here!
--[PUAR] Yaay!
--[YAMCHA] Goku!
[OOLONG] Hey, kid!
What's shakin'?
Hey, Oolong! Hey, Puar!
What brings you here?
So, did you come
to see Bulma?
Yeah! I've got her right here!
Uh.
[GOKU squeals]
[BULMA] Shhh!
Mm-mm!
Huh...?
What was that?
Nothing.
You, uh, hear about
Bulma and Yamcha?
She's got this kid
sleeping in the dog-house,
if you know what I mean.
I guess. I mean I...
I sure got the feeling
Bulma didn't want to see him.
Did... she... say that?
[YAMCHA whimpers]
[BULMA growls]
[BULMA] Why can't Goku
keep his big mouth shut?!
[YAMCHA whimpers]
Are you okay?
So, its...
just like I thought.
She really doesn't
like me anymore...
Don't let it
break your heart.
As much abuse as
that girl gives you,
you're better
off without her.
[BULMA growls]
I agree!
Don't tell anyone I said so, but
I think she's a spoiled brat!
Everybody says so...
And she's too sensitive!
Look, you've put up
with her long enough!
[YAMCHA sighs]
[YAMCHA] I suppose you're right,
she does get mad a lot,
she's thoughtless...
And she's hard to handle...
[BULMA growls]
But still, she's the only...
[BULMA] Well, I'm SO
sorry I'm SO awful!
[PUAR] Huh?
[ALL gasp]
Ah! B-Bulma?!
Bulma, wait!
I'm sorry!
We gotta go right now.
Where?
We're still going to the
amusement park, aren't we?
Sure, okay!
Hey, wait!
We're going to the same place!
Wow! How strange!
What a coincidence!
This is just so odd!
Isn't it, guys?
[OOLONG &amp; PUAR] Huh?!
[BULMA] Ooooh!
It is so incredibly rude
to talk badly about
a girl behind her back!
I'm sorry! Wait, Bulma!
Well, well, I'm suddenly in the
mood to ride a roller coaster.
I have been meaning to go
and check this place out.
Ice cream!
This is gonna be so fun!
[GOKU] Hmmm?
What's up, Goku?
[GOKU] Uhhh...
Oh, it's nothing.
[HASKY]
So, "Goku", is it?
Pleasure to make
your acquaintance,
even if it is only for
the last day of your life...
[HASKY] They tell me
you're pretty powerful, kid.
But you're still
just a child!
Those Dragon Balls
are as good as mine!
Wait and see!
[NARRATOR] Goku and his friends
prepare to spend a day of fun
at the amusement park.
But with a dangerous criminal
like Hasky on their trail,
the price of admission
includes a ticket to danger
on the next Dragon Ball!