[NARRATOR]
Deep within the shadows
of his secret headquarters,
one of the most ruthless
members of the Red Ribbon Army
sculpts his body
to deadly perfection.
Slowly, with
meticulous precision,
he pushes towards the limit
of his physical prowess,
which seems as boundless
as his lethal intellect.
He is more than just
a soldier for hire.
He is ambitious. He is brutal.
He is Colonel Silver,
one of the driving forces
behind General Red's acquisition
of the Seven Dragon Balls.
He will stop at
nothing to reach his goal.
Even now, he is no doubt
hatching another fiendish scheme
to secure the next Ball
and demolish anyone
who gets in his way.
[SILVER] Next.
Hmph!
[ERRAND BOY] Yet another
magnificent performance,
Colonel Silver.
[SILVER] I expected
more of a challenge
from professional boxers.
[ERRAND BOY] Commander Red
is waiting to see you, sir.
Mm-hmm...
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, amidst
far more tranquil surroundings,
Goku is regaining consciousness
after the explosion
of Pilaf's fortress--having
been narrowly saved
by his faithful Flying Nimbus.
Huh?
Ow, my head!
Hey! Nimbus! Nimbus!!
Uh, that was scary...
Who were those guys?
[RED] Enter.
[RED chuckles]
Nicely done.
Quick reflexes,
unflinching nerve.
Your instincts serve you well.
The last person to walk through
that door lost an eye.
Needless to say,
he's no longer with us.
You, however, have what it
takes to go far in this outfit.
Nothing succeeds
like excess...
Wouldn't you agree, Colonel?
Yes, I am pleased to serve.
[RED] And so you shall.
The six-star ball is
finally within my grasp.
Thanks, in part,
to your efforts.
Unfortunately, this
collectible is only valuable
as part of a complete set.
Four additional
balls are all that stand
between me and
global domination.
Study the map closely.
The marks on the screen
pinpoint the exact location
of the remaining Dragon Balls.
I must have them!
Well, unfortunately there are
other interested parties
who feel the same way.
[RED]
Those who disturb our agenda
are to be eliminated
with extreme prejudice.
I don't tolerate opposition...
[RED]
...by anyone!
[screeches]
[SILVER gasps]
[RED chuckles]
[RED] You get the point?
Hahahahahahahah.
Yes, general.
[GOKU] The radar says the next
Dragon Ball is really close.
Hmm... it must be in
this forest somewhere...
[stomach growling]
Boy am I hungry.
Say, I bet there's a
snack-tree down there!
[GOKU] That looks tasty!
Wait! Hey! Wait!
That's mine! Uh?
[monkey noises]
Ah, you can keep it.
Aw, poor little monkey.
Hey!
[growling]
[stomach growls]
Yeah, I could really use
some food right about now.
What are you saying?
Is that fruit for me?
[GOKU] Hmm?
Wow! Thanks, you guys!
I'm starving.
[SILVER]
It's out there. I know it is.
[SILVER] I want the
entire jungle searched.
Dig it up, burn it down.
I don't care.
Just find me that Dragon Ball!
Whew... I ate too much.
[frantic monkey sounds]
Wow.
I wonder how long
I've been sleeping out here?
That's strange...
...the radar shows
the Dragon Ball is moving.
[KRILLIN] Ninety-one, uff...
Ninety-two, uff...
Ninety-three, uff...
Ninety-four, uff...
Ninety-five, uff...
Ninety-six, uff...
Ninety-seven, uff...
Ninety... e-ei-ght, uff...
Ninety-nine, ahhh!
Nine hundred ninety-nine?
That's all you got in ya boy?!
[panting]
Snack time you two!
Whaaa--ooo...
W-o-o-o-o-o! Heh-heh!!
Feel-the-freeze, baby!
Oh, Krillin.
What's the matter?
Don't you want some ice cream?
Well... I'm kinda tired.
Tired? If Goku could heard that,
he'd be laughing
his head off right now!
Be fair...
Goku is in no way
an ordinary child.
You can say that again...
He's great.
I wonder where he is?
You think he's still searching
for those Dragon Balls?
It's a worthy pursuit
but he'll be busy
for quite some time.
Those balls won't fall into his
lap like the one I gave him.
Do you know about
the Dragon Balls?
Where they come from, I mean.
Why yes...
I remember hearing
the great legend once...
But I doubt you're ready
for such a heart-wrenching tale.
This is powerful stuff
we're dealing with.
[LAUNCH] Oh!
You're right, Master,
but I think she can handle it.
Mm. Yes. I'll bet she can...
Anyway...
The legend, as I was told,
goes something like this:
In the beginning there
was only one Dragon Ball.
It was huge--I mean
really huge. It had to be.
It held all of the mystical
energies of the universe!
An ancient tribe discovered it,
and was inspired by
its magnificent power.
They built a shrine around it,
and protected the orb
by placing it in the mouth
of a giant dragon statue,
said to be its eternal guardian.
You should have seen
the detail on this thing.
It was incredible!
Scales made of rubies,
teeth of pearl.
Speaking of pearl,
they also say there was
this one native girl who--
[LAUNCH and KRILLIN]
Get on with it!
[ROSHI] Yes, well,
the tribe enjoyed years
of prosperity until one day,
evil paid a visit
to the village in the
form of a band of thieves.
These agents of
darkness stormed the temple
in an attempt to
steal the Dragon Ball
for their own selfish gain.
They were shocked to discover
the true power of the ball.
To ensure such an attack
would never happen again,
the Dragon Ball was divided
into seven smaller orbs
and scattered across the globe.
Separately, the
Dragon Balls were useless,
but when all
seven were united...
Then a single
voice could summon
the eternal dragon for
one wish, and one wish only.
Some wishes were pure,
but others were tainted
by blind ambition.
This led to pain and suffering,
as an unjust few wished
for power and
dominion over mankind.
But as the story goes,
there will one day come a hero,
who will use the
Dragon Balls for goodness,
and bring peace and
unity to the world once more.
That's an incredible story.
Just imagine, getting to wish
for anything your heart desired!
I would ask
for ultimate strength.
What would you wish, Roshi?
Me, I uhh---
How about a big napkin?
Master, your nose.
Ooh?
Yeah, well now, let's see.
What could old Roshi ask for?
A new shell?
or perhaps a bigger island?
or maybe happiness
and world peace.
A piece of something
that's for sure!
[laughs]
[KRILLIN] I guess all that
heroic stuff is out the window.
Don't you have something
you should be doing right now?!
Like what, sir?
Like going outside
and earning your muscles
the old fashioned way!
Yes, sir!
All done?
One wish...? Easy.
[KRILLIN thinking]
One thing's for sure.
If I had the Dragon Balls,
I'd never have to
play taxi to a turtle.
If I had a wish...
I know what I'd ask for...
Hey! Dragon Ball,
where are you?
Dragon Ball!
[monkey laughter]
So then accounting tells me
they'll have to take it
out of my next paycheck
and I'm just like,
"wait a minute, man!"
The ribbon should
come with the uniform.
Free! End of discussion!
At least you didn't
let 'em walk on ya!
A Dragon Ball
just hit your head.
Huh?
I think I smell a promotion.
Let's get 'em!
They're getting away...
Shoot 'em!
[SILVER] This is Silver.
[SOLDIER A] Colonel,
we've found the Dragon Ball.
What?!
[SOLDIER A]
Th-The monkeys have it.
Have you caught them?
[SOLDIER A] W-Well, not yet.
Idiots!
Incompetent morons.
Must I do everything myself?!
What are you waiting for? Drive!
[DRIVER] Sir!
That smells like--
[SILVER]
Fire! Now! Everyone!
Fire!
[GOKU] Hey! Stop it!
Who's yellin'?
You talking to me, pip-squeak?!
Stop destroying the forest, now!
Come on and make me! Lil' brat!
Hold it right there!
Hands up!
Or else you're barbecue, kid!
No!
So?
We searched all of
them nothing yet, sir.
We're still looking
in the forest.
Hey, you... monkey boy.
Huh?
You're the one who
attacked the Ox King!
I'm Colonel Silver.
Pleased to kill you.
[GOKU] I'm not afraid of you!
[GOKU] Wha--
The Dragon Ball.
Hey! Wait up!
Soldier, your rifle! Now!
[SOLDIER F] But, sir!
They're too far away!
That's an impossible shot!
[GOKU] Umph!
Get me that ball... Move it!
[NARRATOR]
Hanging on for dear life,
Goku watches helplessly as
the Five-Star Ball plunges
into the river below.
Where will the
Dragon Ball end up?
And will Goku
and his new friends
survive this latest cliffhanger?
It's a long way down,
and the only way out is up,
where the sinister
Colonel Silver waits.
It's a showdown
you won't want to miss
on the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball!