[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball,
the tournament
preliminary round ended
with 8 finalists
having been chosen:
Goku,
Yamcha,
Krillin,
Tien Shinhan,
Mercenary Tao,
the mysterious girl warrior,
Junior,
and Hero.
[KRILLIN]
Excuse me, but who's Junior?
Well, that would be him.
You call him Junior?
[NARRATOR] With a frenzied
roar from the crowd,
the tournament began.
The first match was Mercenary
Tao versus Tien Shinhan.
[NARRATOR]
Tien wasn't the only one
with friends in the audience.
Tao's brother, the Crane Hermit,
decided to show up as well.
Tao vowed to destroy Tien
before the tournament's end.
[ANNOUNCER]
Ready! Let the match begin!
[TAO chuckles]
Just like old times, huh?
Yes.
[NARRATOR] All eyes turned to
the match, some with vengeance,
some with concern.
Tien's colleagues
watched anxiously
as the cyborg's sinister
plot began to unfold.
[TAO]
You look nervous. Don't be.
Pain should come easy for you.
[ANONYMOUS grunting]
[HERO] It's, uh, strangely
quiet, uh, don't you think?
[ANONYMOUS] Hm. I hear many
sounds that invade the silence.
[CROWD murmuring]
[ANNOUNCER sighs]
[MAN thinking] Why do I always
get stuck behind the big hair?
[SHEN chuckles]
[OOLONG sighs] Doesn't a
fight require, uh, movement?
[LAUNCH grumbles]
They're like statues.
It's been ten minutes.
Tien can't move.
It's Tao who can't move.
[YAMCHA, KRILLIN]
Huh?
[ANNOUNCER] Well folks, this
fight may have just started,
but already we're
witnessing a stalemate.
Neither participant has moved
a muscle since this match began.
[TAO thinking] Remarkable!
Tien has a perfect defense.
[TAO thinking]
I can't find a vulnerable spot
on his entire body.
[TAO thinking] My brother
was a little too thorough
with your training.
This is going to be
harder than I thought.
Will one of you please throw a
punch before we all fall asleep?
[gasps]
[SHEN using ESP] Hello,
Tien Shinhan. Can you hear me?
I interrupt this boring
excuse of a match
to bring you this
little bulletin:
You cannot defeat
my brother, Tao,
because he's the one who
taught you defensive strategy.
A shame all that knowledge
was wasted on a loser like you.
[growls]
[thunder rumbles]
[TIEN groans]
[panting]
[gasps]
[TAO cackles]
[TIEN yelps]
[groans]
[SHEN using ESP]
How could a failure like you
ever hope to best my brother?
You were never a match for him.
Not then, and certainly not now!
[gasps]
[TAO yells]
Huh?
[TAO groans]
[gasps]
[ANNOUNCER]
Whoa! Now that's more like it!
That was a lucky shot.
The minute they moved,
Tien Shinhan dealt his opponent
a crushing blow! Amazing!
Tien...
[laughs]
Well done. You've
improved a little.
You're no longer tripping
on your own feet!
[laughs]
[TAO]
Seeing as how you've grown up,
I no longer have to hold back!
Prepare for pain!
[TAO yells]
[TAO groans]
Tao!
[GROUP cheering]
[growls]
[yells]
Wait a minute. There's
something I need to say.
[TAO]
Huh?
[KRILLIN, YAMCHA, GOKU]
[gasps]
It's too late to beg
for mercy, weakling!
I'll forget what you did
to Chiaotzu. Stop this madness.
[chuckles] You fool,
don't talk as if
you're in control
of this situation!
You're just scared!
[TIEN using ESP]
You're mistaken.
I've grown much stronger
than you realize.
[TAO yelps]
Don't talk behind
my back, coward!
You think you're
stronger than me?
I'll enjoy taking
you down, Tien!
Sir, I didn't ask
for any of this.
I take little pleasure
in fighting you.
[grunts, laughs]
Very funny, Tien. Hilarious!
Your arrogance has
just sealed your fate!
Now die!
They're moving so fast.
I can't tell what's going on.
[ROSHI thinking]
Tien's speed is incredible!
That's fast.
I'll say! Tien is fantastic!
He's avoiding every move
Tao that throws at him!
He makes it look easy.
[yells]
[gasps] No!
Try to understand. What I say
to you is out of concern,
not disrespect.
You and your brother
taught me how to fight.
I am grateful for your guidance.
I do not wish to see you lose
in disgrace. Leave the ring now!
[TAO growls]
I'll rip your eyes out!
[CROWD gasps]
[TAO groans, screams]
We'll do this the
hard way. Move!
[ANNOUNCER]
This is a surprise!
[yelping]
[ANNOUNCER]
Tien Shinhan is attempting
to escort his opponent
out of the ring!
That's new.
[TAO yelping]
[gasps]
[TIEN groans]
[ALL gasp]
--[CROWD gasps]
--No, Tien!
[TIEN groans]
[ANNOUNCER] Possession of
a knife by Mercenary Tao!
Tournament rules prohibit
use of weapons in the ring.
Tao is disqualified.
The winner by default
is Tien Shinhan!
Oh, be quiet! I don't
care about your match!
[cackles]
As long as I can
kill Tien Shinhan.
Yes, take your revenge! That's
what you came here for, Tao!
Annihilate all of
Turtle Hermit's students!
They don't deserve to live!
[TAO cackling]
[growls]
[cackling]
You are defeated! Just
admit it. Prepare to die!
What respect I had for you
has now turned to pity.
You have no honor!
You're mistaken.
I have plenty of honor.
The honor of killing you!
That's it. Keep your silence.
My blade will finish
this conversation!
The match is over!
You are not allowed
to kill each other in the ring!
Please, put the knife
down and leave!
You're next!
[ANNOUNCER yelps]
I'd be happy to lend a hand.
We can take him together, Tien!
No, stay where you are.
I'll take care of this.
[TAO]
Die!
Tien, look out!
[TAO grunting]
No!
I hope you didn't pay
a lot for this toothpick.
[TAO yelps]
[TIEN growls]
[TAO cackling]
Did you really think
I'd be so easily defeated?
Admit it, Tao.
This fight is over.
[cackling]
[gasps]
[TAO] I've been dying to
use this one all day!
Introducing the Super Dodon Ray!
[ROSHI]
Eh?!
Super Dodon Ray?
That doesn't sound good.
[cackles]
This new version far
exceeds the original
in its destructive power.
Its lethal force incinerates
anything it touches.
Tien, get out of there.
It's not safe.
That ray; it's
unstoppable! Tien!
[TAO cackles]
[TAO] I've adjusted the ray to
match your biological signature.
There is no escape. No matter
where you go, it will track you.
Go ahead! I'm not afraid!
[CROWD gasps]
[CROWD screams]
No! Don't!
[OOLONG yelps]
[OOLONG]
This pig knows when to exit!
[LAUNCH]
Hey! If Tien stays, so do we!
Ha! Not so arrogant
now, are you?
Some things never change,
do they, Tien? Ha!
You act tough, but inside
you're just scared!
[TAO]
Prepare yourself!
[CROWD gasping]
[TAO]
Super Dodon Ray!
[TAO yells]
Enjoy! I hope it's painful!
[yells]
[CROWD yelping, screaming]
[TAO yelling]
[TIEN panting]
Tien?
[gasps]
[TAO] I-I don't
believe it. It can't be!
[TAO] Ho-How could
you have survived it?
I had you in my sights.
There's no way you could
have escaped doom!
The ray was flawless!
[TIEN yells]
[TAO groans]
[CROWD gasps]
[gasping]
[CROWD cheering]
He did it!
Excellent job, Tien.
--Yeah!
--[PUAR] I'll go tell Chiaotzu!
Uh-uh-uh!
You guys should have
listened to me.
I knew Tien had
this thing in the bag.
--[LAUNCH grunts]
--[OOLONG groans]
Then why did ya
try to sneak away?
Please let me go!
[ANNOUNCER] It's all right,
folks! You can breathe again.
Whew! What a wild opening!
Just the kind of intensity
you've come to expect
right here at the World
Martial Arts Tournament!
Again, since Mercenary Tao used
a weapon, he has lost the match.
Tien Shinhan wins the match
and will go on to compete
in the semi-finals!
[CROWD cheers]
Tien Shinhan performed
as well as I expected.
He finished Mercenary Tao
with just one punch!
[SHEN yelping]
He'll be asleep like
this for a few days.
Please take him home and never
show yourselves around me again.
Thank you, Master.
[SHEN growls]
You traitor! You will
not die peacefully,
I assure you of that!
It's you who won't die
peacefully, old Crane!
You were great!
[TIEN]
Thanks.
[KRILLIN] The way you handled
the Super Dodon Ray was amazing!
I was really impressed!
[YAMCHA]
That's enough.
He needs to be left alone.
Amazing!
I never thought Tien would grow
into such a well-tempered
and powerful warrior.
There is nothing more that
this master can teach him.
Strong guy.
Fighting Tien won't be easy.
[GOKU]
Now it's my turn! I can't wait!
This should be some match!
I'd better stretch.
I'd be excited too if I was
--fighting a pretty girl.
--[GOKU] If she fights as well
as she yells, I'm in trouble.
Hello.
[ANONYMOUS]
Hmph!
Uh...
[ANNOUNCER] It's time to turn
our focus to the second match
in this exciting tournament!
Goku, who nearly won
the last championship...
It'll be great to
see Goku in action!
[ANNOUNCER] ...whose name is
being withheld by request.
This lovely lady proved
in the preliminaries
she can hold her own
against the boys.
Go ahead, Goku.
Try to impress me.
[ANNOUNCER] To accommodate the
young lady's unusual request,
we will refer to
her as Anonymous,
throughout this match.
[GROUP gasps]
It seems like you're always
angry about something.
There's a lot to be angry
about, when I see you!
Uh... Uh...
[ANONYMOUS]
Hmph.
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
[NARRATOR]
As the tournament continues,
there are more questions
to be answered.
Who is this pretty
and mysterious girl?
And what has Goku done
to make her so upset?
Find out when we return
for the next chapter
in this exciting tournament,
only on Dragon Ball!