[NARRATOR] Last time on Dragon
Ball, Goku took on King Chapa
in the first preliminary match
of the World Martial
Arts Tournament.
[CHAPPA]
Stop hiding! You hear me coward?
[groans]
[NARRATOR] Much to the
astonishment of his peers,
Goku enjoyed a flawless
victory over King Chapa,
displaying incredible
speed and agility.
However, there was
one competitor
who was not impressed.
Junior, King Piccolo's
alter ego.
The fighting continued
as Krillin, Yamcha,
and Tien Shinhan
proved their own
magnificent skills
with one victory after another.
Unfortunately, Chiaotzu
did not fare as well.
[NARRATOR] More shocking
than Chiaotzu's injuries
was the identity
of his attacker.
[TIEN]
No! You're dead!
[NARRATOR] None other
than Goku's old nemesis,
Mercenary Tao.
[GOKU gasps]
Mercenary Tao!
[NARRATOR] Now half machine, the
assassin vowed to destroy Goku
during the tournament,
as revenge for the disfigurement
suffered in their
last confrontation.
[CROWD shouting]
No one may enter!
Stay back!
[OOLONG]
Boo!
What do you mean only
fighters are allowed inside?
That's discrimination!
Authorized personnel only.
Patience everybody.
[CLERK]
Make room for the injured!
Everyone please get back!
[ROSHI growls]
The tournament just started!
Not a good sign.
--[BULMA] Oh!
--[ROSHI] Hm?
Chiaotzu!
Be strong, Chiaotzu.
I'm going.
[LAUNCH]
Me, too.
[CROWD murmuring]
[siren blaring]
Whoever did this is incredibly
strong. Who could it be?
[FIGHTER A groaning]
[TAO chuckles]
[groaning]
Fool, don't touch me!
[JUDGE]
We need another stretcher!
[GOKU thinking]
He may look like King Piccolo,
but his strength and
skill seem far superior.
He's had excellent training.
[FIGHTER B laughing]
Get ready. I'll tear you limb
from limb in five seconds.
[yells]
[FIGHTER B]
You're going down!
[FIGHTER B yelling]
Out of bounds!
Number 64 is the winner!
[CROWD cheers]
[groans]
[YAJIROBE grunts]
[FIGHTER B grunts]
[coughing]
Someone should teach
you some manners!
[yelping]
You won't get away with this!
[YAJIROBE coughing]
[FIGHTER C yelling]
[yelling]
[FIGHTER D groans]
[JUDGE] Out of bounds! Number
two proceeds to the semi-finals!
Thank you!
He'll go all the way
to the finals.
Maybe farther. Remember,
last time he won second place.
[cackles]
[FIGHTER E groans]
[JUDGE] Number 35 goes on
to the semi-finals.
[KRILLIN yells]
[JUDGE] Number 16 proceeds
to the semi-finals.
[yells]
[JUDGE] Number 22 goes
to the semi-finals.
--[FIGHTER F gaging]
--[CROWD gasping]
[JUDGE] He's out! Number 51
proceeds to the semi-finals.
Please let go of your opponent!
[GOKU]
He doesn't say much, does he?
Speaking of bad news,
it looks like Mercenary Tao
will advance as well.
[JUDGE] Number 44 goes
on to the semi-finals!
[cackles]
Be on your guard. I think he's
serious about destroying us.
[FIGHTER G groans]
No more, please!
[JUDGE] Number 59 proceeds
to the semi-finals!
[KRILLIN] What skill! I think
she's stronger than Launch!
[GOKU]
Hm. Now that I think about it,
maybe I have seen her
somewhere before.
There are still two
more to be selected.
I wonder who they'll be?
I'm not worried.
[toilet flushes]
[HERO]
Oh! Oh, no!
[HERO groans]
[HERO]
Here we go!
I'm sorry, sir,
but you may not enter
unless you're a staff
member or a participant.
Wait, you don't
understand. I, uh, I...
[MONK]
It's time to go.
Please, you must let me through!
[MONK]
Don't do this, sir.
--[MONK] Enough! No, no.
--Please don't do this!
--It's not what you think!
Number 70, number 70!
Report to the ring at this time,
or you will be disqualified.
No, no! Wait a minute!
I'm right here!
[MONK gasps]
[HERO] I had to go to the
bathroom, but I'm ready now!
I am! I...
[HERO grunting]
[HERO panting]
Ha! They must have
made a mistake.
This guy looks like
somebody's father.
[YAJIROBE thinking]
You've got to be kidding.
It's time to begin.
Oh yes, I'm coming!
[HERO] That's a nice, uh,
mask, you got there.
[yells]
Uh...
This is gonna be
painful to watch.
[clears throat]
Sir, your zipper.
[yells]
[HERO yelps]
[CROWD laughing]
[HERO]
I gotta fix it!
Begin!
[yells]
Okay. You asked
for it, old-timer.
[HERO yells]
[HERO yelps]
[YAJIROBE groans]
[JUDGE] Knock out! Number 70
proceeds to the semi-finals!
Aw! This guy's gonna turn
the fight into a comedy!
Hello and congratulations
to all of the semi-finalists.
Please come forward
at this time.
You will once again draw lots
to determine the pairing
for the next round.
How humiliating.
I can see the headlines now,
"Yajirobe Defeated by Nerd!"
I'm glad I was wearing a mask!
No one is that clumsy!
Who is number 70?
[ANNOUNCER]
And please, as a general note,
check your costumes before
you enter the ring.
[YAJIROBE]
Ha! I didn't wanna fight
in this boring
tournament anyway.
There are better
opponents in the forest!
Besides, when you win that
fight, you get to eat 'em!
[rattling]
[ANNOUNCER] Now, if there
are no further questions,
you may all draw lots.
Hello again. Nice moustache.
--[KRILLIN laughing]
--[ANNOUNCER gasping]
It's impossible!
You can't be here!
[ANNOUNCER]
I saw you die!
[screams]
[ANNOUNCER] Oh, please,
spirit from the afterworld--
Oh, stop it! I'm not a ghost.
I just came back to life again.
[NARRATOR]
With the drawing completed,
it was time for the
semi-final matches
of the 23rd World Martial
Arts Tournament to begin.
However,
never had such a
diverse or opposing
group of warriors
entered the ring.
Excuse me, but,
uh, who's Junior?
He would be known as Junior.
You call him Junior?
[whiteboard squeaking]
[ANNOUNCER] The first match
will be Mercenary Tao
versus Tien Shinhan.
The second match will be
Goku versus Anonymous.
The third match will be
Junior versus Krillin.
And the fourth match will
be Hero versus Yamcha.
[CROWD cheering]
How is Chiaotzu doing?
He's okay. His body
is covered in bruises,
but there are no broken bones.
Finally, some good news.
Here they come!
[ALL gasp]
It's a shame that Chiaotzu
couldn't join you,
but you've done well.
Good job, guys.
My only concern is that strange
guy who beat up Chiaotzu.
You might know him, Master.
He's the Crane Hermit's
younger brother, Mercenary Tao.
[ROSHI] What?! Did you
say Mercenary Tao?
I thought Goku destroyed him?
Apparently he survived
the explosion
and turned himself
into a cyborg.
And he said the only reason
he joined the tournament
was to kill Goku and Tien,
and now he's about to fight
Tien in the first match!
That is a problem. Tao is
from the same house as Tien
and therefore, knows all
of his fighting techniques.
I'm afraid Tien is
at a disadvantage.
There's really nothing
to worry about.
[YAMCHA, KRILLIN]
What?
Tao doesn't stand a chance
against Tien Shinhan.
[SHEN]
Wanna bet?
[GOKU, YAMCHA, KRILLIN]
Huh?
[KRILLIN]
It's the Crane Hermit!
[cackles] I can't wait to
see your disappointment
when my brother wins.
[ROSHI]
Where did you come from?
Let me give you a piece
of advice, Roshi.
Gather up your boys
and get out of town
before it's too late.
You will lose.
Now, let's get
one thing straight!
These young fighters wear my
colors out of respect, not duty.
They have surpassed their
training with the Turtle House.
My boys have all grown up and
are now independent fighters.
[SHEN]
You expect me to believe
they wear these lame
rags by choice?
[ROSHI]
Believe what you want!
They chose to honor
the Turtle House,
but they do not serve it.
That's right!
Even though it may be hard
for you to understand,
we respect our Master!
That only proves that
you're dumb enough
to follow an inferior leader.
Hey!
My brother's cybernetic implants
not only gave him a body,
but increased strength
beyond human potential.
Tien Shinhan nor any
of you fools can stand
a chance against him!
[SHEN] The fight was
over before it began!
Some things never change.
That guy's still a jerk!
The real monster in that
family isn't Mercenary Tao.
[intercome chime]
[SPEAKER]
The matches will begin shortly.
At this time, all
participants are requested
to gather at the main stadium.
[CROWD cheering]
Finally, it's time!
Good luck. I'll be
watching your fights.
I can't wait to see how
much you've all improved.
But don't push
yourselves too hard.
You must know when to cut back.
[YAMCHA, KRILLIN, GOKU]
Okay.
[BULMA]
Yamcha! Krillin! Goku!
[PUAR]
Good luck, you guys!
[YAMCHA, KRILLIN, GOKU]
Thanks.
There go the finest pupils
a master could ever have.
[OOLONG] Gee, there's so many
people jammed in here,
you can't even see the stage!
Any ideas?
Huh?
I don't have a clue.
The answer's right
under your nose.
A-Achoo!
Now what could you
do with those?
Crowd control.
Ah...
[CROWD screaming]
You know the drill, people!
Let's move it, come on! Run!
[laughs]
[CROWD screaming]
Goku, listen. Mercenary Tao
was a terribly strong
killer, wasn't he?
And now we hear that
he's even stronger.
So, why did you say there
was nothing to worry about?
It's simple, really. Because
Tien Shinhan is much stronger.
[KRILLIN] But wait, Tao was Tien
Shinhan's teacher, wasn't he?
Enough about that.
Are ya hungry?
[GOKU]
Beans!
If you eat one, you won't eat
anything else for 10 days.
[BOTH chuckle]
Those are Senzu beans, aren't
they? We have some, too.
A-ha! Uh...
See?
What? You mean you
went to see Korin?
Yep. So did Tien Shinhan
and Chiaotzu.
We all four climbed
Korin's Tower together.
After we did that,
we each went our separate ways
and continued our training.
[GOKU]
You did? We all did it!
[KRILLIN]
Yeah, while we were there,
we met someone called Yajirobe.
He was with Master Korin and
he looked kinda strong,
so we told him
about the tournament.
But I never saw him, did you?
[GOKU] No, I haven't seen
Yajirobe in a long time.
I don't think he'd come.
He doesn't like tournaments.
Gimme a break!
I did come, but I lost!
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you for your patience.
The wait is over!
We will now begin the 23rd
World Martial Arts Tournament.
[CROWD cheers]
Great view.
Yeah, who needs tickets
when you've got Launch.
Your cheers validate the
excitement surrounding us today.
Yet this is only a part
of the incredible journey
the fighters have endured
to compete in this tournament.
The preliminary round began
with 72 skilled participants,
which were reduced down to 8.
Those few fighters
that remained,
are truly the mightiest group
of athletes in the world!
And they are here to
entertain you, the loyal fans!
Who will become
our new champion?
The first match
will be Mercenary Tao
versus Tien Shinhan,
who may now enter the ring!
[CROWD cheers]
Go smash that creep's
circuits, Tien!
Sure thing. Uh--?
Good luck.
Relax. Enjoy yourself,
Tien Shinhan.
I won't kill you in this
match, only wound you.
I'll take care of
both you and Goku
after I've won the Championship.
For now, enjoy the
crowd's adulation.
[CROWD cheers]
What is he, a robot?
That's not fair!
Get him, Tien! No mercy!
You have to win the
Championship again!
[ANNOUNCER] Okay, ready?
Let the match begin!
[TAO cackles]
Just like old times, huh?
Yes.
[TAO]
You look nervous. Don't be.
Pain should come easy for you.
[SHEN thinking]
Traitor! Now it's time
for you to pay the price!
Focus.
[NARRATOR] The battle
between student and teacher
is about to begin.
Stay tuned for round
one on Dragon Ball!