[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball,
the tournament grew more
intense when Junior struck
Goku where it hurt
the most, his pride.
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
Do you wanna know why you're
gonna lose this match?
Because of your
bleeding heart mercy.
You must make Kami very proud,
being his perfect stooge.
[GOKU growls]
I'll stop you!
[PICCOLO JR. cackles]
[PICCOLO JR. yells]
[KRILLIN]
Hey, wait, the Dragon Balls.
Goku, Kami's safety
doesn't matter!
[GOKU gasps]
[Using the power
of the Dragon Balls,
the dragon can heal his wounds.
Hey, you're right.
Why didn't I think of that?
[PICCOLO JR.]
Get out of my sight!
[GOKU]
Ka... Me... Ha... Me...
Ha!
[NARRATOR]
In a flash of blinding light,
the arena was struck by terror.
Goku's battle cry
shook the heavens.
And above, the crowd's
pandemonium gave way
to Junior's screams of horror!
[PICCOLO JR. screams]
[ROSHI grunts]
--[ALL groaning]
--[CHICHI coughs]
[ALL gasping]
Goku?
[GOKU]
Uh?
[GOKU panting]
[ALL sigh]
He won!
[KRILLIN laughs]
No. Look up.
[KRILLIN]
Huh?
[ANNOUNCER]
[gasps]
Wha-? Somehow he survived,
but that's impossible!
[ALL gasp]
[PICCOLO JR. growling]
You have failed!
You thought your simple
parlor tricks could destroy me.
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
But as you can see,
I'm still here!
Yeah, I know. Are you going
to float up there all day,
or can we continue this fight?
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
Well, tick-tock.
I'm waiting, impress me.
[ALL gasp]
Uh...
I don't like this game.
[ANNOUNCER] Goku launched
a devastating attack that was
nothing short of spectacular!
However, either by extreme luck,
or extraordinary stamina,
Junior has survived,
and he doesn't seem happy.
Uh?! Uh...
He could use a new tailor.
Yep.
[ANNOUNCER] Uh... Yes, sir!
Things are getting tense.
[WOMAN gasps]
Sit down! I can't see.
Wh-What if...
What if they recognize him?
Well, then things are
gonna get a lot worse.
Ya know, that looks
like King Piccolo.
[CROWD]
Huh?
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
--Hey, that's King Piccolo.
--Huh?
King Piccolo? We're doomed!
--[MAN] He'll destroy us all!
--[PICCOLO JR. growls]
He looks mean with those horns.
And ugly.
Silence, you worms!
I am King Piccolo, reincarnated!
[KRILLIN groans]
Let it be known
throughout the world,
once I've disposed of Goku,
I will be your King once again!
Not only has King
Piccolo been reborn,
but his reign of terror as well!
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[gasping]
[PICCOLO JR. laughing]
[PICCOLO JR.]
Run!
[laughing continues]
Out of my way you, you idiot!
--[DRIVER yelps]
--[THIEF growls]
[KING]
What? Piccolo?
Yes.
[KING thinking]
The horror has returned.
[NEWSMAN] We interrupt your
regularly scheduled program
to bring you this
breaking story.
Our reliable sources have
confirmed that a contestant
at the 23rd World
Martial Arts Tournament
has declared himself
King Piccolo, resurrected!
[CROWD gasping]
[panting]
[THIEF B]
Outta my way!
[MOPED DRIVER]
That's my hog!
[ROSHI, YAMCHA gasping]
[ANNOUNCER stammers]
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
[gasping]
[BULMA whimpers]
[ANNOUNCER whimpers]
Attention, ladies and gentlemen,
if you can hear my voice, run!
It's true! The fighter known as
Junior is in fact King Piccolo!
--[LAUNCH] We're right here.
--[ANNOUNCER whimpers]
Break time's over.
No more distractions.
[GOKU]
Hm.
Go! Get out of here, all of you!
I can't do this if
you're still in danger.
Okay.
Sorry, looks like you've
lost your audience.
--[BULMA chuckles nervously]
--[ANNOUNCER whimpers]
[whimpers]
Goku, leave!
No, I have to fight.
Forget about destroying
this world.
I won't let it happen.
Why don't you reserve
passing judgment until
after you've seen
my latest technique?
What?
[PICCOLO JR.]
It's a real showstopper.
[PICCOLO JR. grunting]
[grunting continues]
[yells]
[yelling continues]
He's glowing.
That can't be good.
--[BULMA, OOLONG gasping]
--[PUAR screams]
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
What?!
[PICCOLO JR. grunting]
[PICCOLO JR. yells]
[ANNOUNCER whimpers]
Not good!
That's big.
[gasping]
Ah!
[ALL gasp]
[GOKU stammers]
[laughs]
[GOKU gasping]
Ha! From up here,
you look very small.
Incredible! How did you
make your clothes grow?
[ANNOUNCER whimpers]
Hey! Isn't that
against the rules?!
Uh, I'm afraid there's no
rule against getting bigger.
We left the rules
a long time ago.
Ah!
[grunts]
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
[yells]
--[PICCOLO grunts]
--[GOKU groans]
[ALL scream]
[GOKU grunts]
I'm allergic to flying debris!
[laughing]
--[GOKU grunts]
--[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO JR. yells]
[GOKU]
Ah!
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
[GOKU grunting]
Nice speed.
[PICCOLO JR. yells]
Missed me!
[GOKU groans]
--[GOKU groaning]
--[PICCOLO pants]
--[YAMCHA] No!
--[TIEN gasps]
Goku, wake up!
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
Goku!
--[BULMA] Move!
--[LAUNCH] Hurry!
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
[GOKU groaning]
[ALL quiver]
Goku, let me help you!
[PICCOLO JR. grunts]
[GOKU]
No, don't.
Uh. Why?
I can't accept your help, not
without forfeiting the match.
[ALL]
Uh...
[chuckles] You'll forfeit
more than that, puny human,
by the time I'm
through with you!
Junior has achieved
quite a feat.
He's increased his size
without sacrificing his speed.
[GOKU] Your size
doesn't intimidate me,
and it won't help you!
Really, now are you
certain of that?
Oh yeah!
[PICCOLO JR. grunts]
[GOKU grunts]
--[GOKU grunts]
--[PICCOLO JR. groans]
[GOKU grunts]
Amazing.
--[GOKU grunts]
--[PICCOLO groans]
--[PICCOLO gasps]
Goku!
Only he could do
something like that.
[PICCOLO JR. groaning]
[GOKU chuckles]
Goku's training must
have included a course
on how to defy
the laws of physics.
Huh?
After expelling a great deal of
energy on his Kamehameha Wave,
he managed to topple a giant.
You're right,
Master. I forgot.
He will win.
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
You insolent maggot.
[GOKU chuckles]
[PICCOLO JR. growls, yells]
--[PICCOLO JR. yells]
--[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU, PICCOLO JR. grunting]
That's it, get him!
Dodge, flip, spin, punch!
--[PICCOLO JR. yells]
--[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU grunting]
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
[GOKU grunts]
[PICCOLO JR. yells, groans]
[PICCOLO JR. groaning]
[GOKU groans]
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
[BOTH gasp]
[PICCOLO yells]
--[OOLONG] Watch out!
--[PUAR screams]
[stammering]
Goku!
[PICCOLO JR. grunting]
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
--[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
--[GOKU muffled grunts]
He's been crushed!
Goku has been pinned
underneath Junior's foot!
That creep.
He was a great warrior.
[PICCOLO JR. grunting]
[ROSHI, KRILLIN]
Eh?!
[TIEN, YAMCHA gasp]
[PICCOLO groaning]
--[PICCOLO groaning]
--[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU grunting]
[YAMCHA]
C'mon, you can do it!
--[PICCOLO JR. growling]
--[GOKU grunting]
You can beat him, Goku!
--[PICCOLO JR. growling]
--[GOKU grunting]
[PICCOLO screams]
[PICCOLO groans]
[GOKU]
Mm.
[growls]
I hate you.
Ha, ha! I told ya your
size didn't matter.
It won't help you win the match.
All it really does is
make you a bigger target!
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
You think one lucky throw
is an accomplishment?
[GOKU gasps]
[PICCOLO JR. grunts, chuckles]
Why do I get the feeling
you're about to get taller?
[PICCOLO JR. grunting]
[PICCOLO JR. yelling]
[GOKU yells]
--[ALL quiver]
--[ROSHI] Now that's big!
[PICCOLO JR. grunts]
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
What do you think?
We're in trouble.
[BULMA, PUAR gasping]
Goodbye.
Unbelievable!
He's as big as a volcano,
and he's about to erupt!
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
[ANNOUNCER]
Run for your lives!
Goku, come on! It's over!
[laughs]
Your friend is right!
[NARRATOR] Our hero's problem
just got a lot bigger.
Now that Junior is a giant,
is this the end for Goku?
Find out next time,
on Dragon Ball!