[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball,
Yamcha faced Tien
as the Quarterfinals
of the Martial Arts
Tournament continued
with a breathtaking display
of fighting prowess.
[NARRATOR] Tien, star pupil
of Master Roshi's rival,
Master Shen, seemed
an equal match for Yamcha
as they battled one
another with unbridled fury.
[PUAR] Block, Yamcha!
--[PUAR] Punch him out!
--[BULMA] Hit! Hit!
[BULMA] Hit! I said hit!
[YAMCHA] Hyaaaaaahh!
[NARRATOR] It appeared as
if Yamcha was destined to win
until Tien broke his spirit...
and his leg.
[NARRATOR] Tien Shinhan
was declared the victor
and Yamcha was
rushed to the hospital.
[NARRATOR] And now,
the match between Jackie Chun
and Man Wolf is about to begin.
Things could get hairy,
so stay tuned!
[CROWD cheers]
[SASNAKRA] Alright,
the next fight is Man Wolf
versus Jackie Chun.
And accordin' to this here map,
they're pretty big fellas.
I think you're holding
it upside down there.
Fancy letters.
Hey! Look over there!
Isn't that one of the finalists?
Tarnation! That's Pamput.
My momma said he's a distant
cousin on my Uncle Roy's side.
He's cute.
Ooooo...
[SUZZI] Here comes Tien!
Aren't his dark
eyes just gorgeous?
[BARBARA]
Yeah, all three of them.
Girls, we have to
get some autographs.
Mhmmm.
I can't hold it!
Oh boy! Uhhhh...
Huh?
[GOKU] Could you point me
to the nearest bathroom...
Huh?
[GOKU]
Thanks, bye!
Well, when you gotta go...
...you gotta go.
[ANNOUNCER] The Championship
Round is about to continue
with Match two.
Get ready to see some of the
strongest men in the world!
[girls squealing]
[BARBARA]
Can I have your autograph?
[adoring sighs]
[CHUN grunts in effort]
[MAN WOLF thinking]
How dare he mock me?
I hate nose... hair!
The things I do
to look handsome!
[CHUN] I'm hairier now
than when I started.
Maybe I should try
using a stronger facial cream.
Where's Jackie Chun?
Ah, you have some fans.
They obviously forgot
I was hosting the event.
[girls squealing]
[BARBARA]
Can I have your autograph?
[SUZZI] I like your hair.
Hi, it's a pleasure to be
in touch with today's youth.
So, uh... Let's touch!
[giggling]
That's sweet.
[growls]
Huh?
Oh, how horrible!
It's a monster!
It might be like, someone's pet
or, like, an exotic animal that,
like, escaped from the zoo.
Maybe it has, like, a name.
Ask.
No way!
[growls]
Ah! Save us!
Help! Oh...
[SUZZI] Thank you, Mr. Chun!
--[RACHAL] You're the best!
--[CHUN] You're welcome.
[BARBARA] Thanks.
[SUZZI] Hi there!
Gee, you're tall...
[RACHAL] Is your third eye
real or is it just a tattoo?
[SUZZI]
You must be little Tien Jr.!
[CHUN] Hmm...
[MAN WOLF growls]
I'll get you, Jackie Chun,
if it's the last thing I do.
This is all your fault!
Wha?
[MAN WOLF]
All your fault! Your fault!
[ANNOUNCER]
Easy there, big fella.
Wouldn't want ya
to cough up a fur ball.
Why don't you come with me?
I know a great manicurist who
can help you with those claws.
[MAN WOLF] I'll see you later!
Interesting...
And why do you suppose he
hates Jackie Chun so much?
Chiaotzu!
[CHIAOTZU] Mm-hmm...
Ahh, that's why!
The match is about to start.
I should be there.
Yamcha, does it hurt to walk?
No, not really. Thanks to you.
Hey!
Aw, what a sweet couple!
Quiet! Can't you see
he's in severe pain?!
--[BULMA] Let's go.
--[YAMCHA] Wait!
Gyaaaaahhh!
[gong crash]
[YAMCHA screams]
[ANNOUNCER] It's time for
Match two of the Quarterfinals,
and the moment you've
all been waiting for:
The return of defending
Champion Jackie Chun
as he takes on the
Wolf-Man... Wolf!
Sorry about that,
man... Man Wolf.
Ha ha! All right!
Anyway, is everyone
in the audience ready
for some hair-raising action?!
I've been waitng for this
moment a very long time, Chun!
A punch for every day
I've been waiting!
You must be confusing
me for someone else.
There's no possible reason
for you to hate me,
considering we've
never even met before.
You fool! Don't insult me!
Do you expect me to
believe you don't remember
what you did in this very
ring just three years ago?!
Three years ago?
Aw... Poor Chun.
What fun.
Maybe he really, really
wanted the title last time
and he's mad at Jackie
for winning the tournament.
Mm-hmm. Great!
Looks like we've got company!
[KRILLIN] I'm sure
they're up to something,
especially the little one.
[GOKU] I wonder why they're
so interested in this fight?
I smell trouble...
We'd better keep a
close eye on those two.
Here, Chun, let me
jog your memory!
Sorry, I'm still
drawing a blank. Unless--
Stop pretending!
If this is about the
incident at that party,
I can assure you it
was an innocent mistake.
Do I look like
I go to parties?!
She didn't tell me
she was involved.
But then again, we, uh...
...didn't... really... talk...
This isn't about a party!
It's about how you
ruined my life! Think back!
Jaken!
Paper!
Scissors!
Rock!
Let's play it one more time!
Paper!
Lightning Surprise Attack!
[GOKU screams in pain]
[MAN WOLF] In an instant my
entire life became a nightmare.
Oh, no! Goku!
That young Goku has transformed
himself into a gigantic ape!
I've never even heard of
this fighting technique!
[APE GOKU growling]
[yelling]
When Goku changes like that,
he loses all sense of himself!
Well then, I'm afraid
there's only one way
to take care of this!
Ah!
Okay, beast...
...I can't let you hurt people!
[APE GOKU screams]
[screaming]
[MAN WOLF yells]
[TIEN] And that's why Man Wolf
hates Jackie Chun so much.
I'm surprised Jackie
has any friends at all.
Thanks to him,
we'll never be able to
enjoy the moon again...
Now Man Wolf must
be a wolf forever.
[TIEN] Mm-hmm.
I was a man...
Handsome... Adored...!
Now I'm the
laughingstock of nature!
All because of you!
[KRILLIN] Hmm?
People... People used to
shower me with praises...
Now I'm lucky if they
give me a dog biscuit!
Do you know how that feels?!
Well, uh... no...?
Moon...
You destroyed the moon...
Oh yes, of course...
So, uh, what did it cost you?
Countless insults.
"What a horrible beast!"
"Quick, look away!
Don't make eye contact."
The indignation!
No one understands.
I can't imagine why.
Now that you're done sharing
your feelings, can we fight?
You took away the moon
and robbed me of my humanity!
I think I deserve some
of your precious... time!
But it's hard to stay awake.
[yawns]
Come and get me when you're
ready to fight. [yawns]
Big mistake!
I don't know about you,
but I wouldn't be turnin'
my back on that critter.
Old Chun is done...
Huh?
I sure am glad we're
watching this live.
They never show nothin'
like this on T.V.!
[growls] Finally
I will have my revenge!
[yawns]
[KRILLIN]
Jackie's gonna get ambushed!
Nope.
Where is he? Jackie?
Turn around.
[MAN WOLF] Show yourself!
Right here.
Ah!
[CHUN] Hyup!
[MAN WOLF] Why you...
[growls]
[shocked gasps in crowd]
[KRILLIN chuckles]
You seem angry...
You should try to relax a bit.
Jackie Chun's one of
the best fighters ever.
I hope that I can achieve
his level of skill someday.
[TIEN] Given that
I can't view myself,
it's rare I see such
exceptional ability in the ring.
Jackie Chun is as close
to perfect as is possible
without being me.
He will be a worthy adversary.
He doesn't stand a chance.
Of course... But he'll try.
His strength is matched
only by his control,
the mark of a great warrior...
It's going to be an
immense honor to break him.
Stand still!
Seems I should give
you the same advice.
The more you move,
the more you hurt yourself.
I'm not clumsy!
Do you hear me?!
I have a black belt to prove it!
Not to mention the
time I spent touring
with an ice skating revue!
Ah! Look at all those people!
I didn't know
I had so many fans.
[CHUN] And I think
someone's even waving at you!
Nope! It's just a vendor
selling my t-shirts.
[CHUN] Hm?
You wanna start
that countdown today?
One... two... three...
I've got goose bumps.
Those catchy?
[ANNOUNCER] Five.. six...
seven.. eight...
I don't think that guy's
gonna stay down, do you?
Uh, nope.
You're not getting
off that easy!
I trained hard for
this victory. It's mine!
[pants]
You stole everything from me,
but you won't
rob me of my revenge!
[CHUN] You tried fighting me.
That didn't work. What next?
Are you going to try to slay me
with more of your
witless banter?
Not quite! I'll just use
this big, sharp knife!
Oh!
Attention all
knife-wielding Man Wolves!
It is a violation
of tournament policy
to bring weapons
onto the premises.
I don't care about
the tournament.
I'm here to make you pay!
Well then, why don't you quit
whining and get this over with.
I've got autographs to sign.
Nice try... Bye, bye.
[CROWD gasps]
You don't need a knife to bring
attention to your discomfort.
Uh, what are you saying?
I sympathize with your situation
and agree that you have
a genuine grievance.
What?! You agree with me?
[CHUN] You have issues,
but I want you to
calm down and play nice.
Ugh! Don't patronize me!
I'm not a dog you
can order around!
I recognize your intelligence.
You are in complete
control of your faculties.
Hand me your paw... now.
Hey, what's the big idea?!
Stop toying with me!
We're just talking.
Now sit.
Scoundrel!
You did that on purpose!
[CROWD laughter]
Listen to them!
They're all laughing at me!
Want a bone?
[CHUN] Come on, boy!
Here you go! Fetch!
Man Wolf... is disqualified...
The winner is Jackie Chun...
[CROWD cheers]
Hey, no fair. You tricked me!
Only so I could help you.
I'm not your enemy.
[CHUN] I think I can
restore your humanity.
Why should I trust you?
[CHUN] The Bound Technique
I used to immobilize you
can last for days.
Can you afford not to trust me?
He's cool.
He certainly thinks
of everything,
but how can he change a wolf
into a man without the moon?
[CHUN] Krillin, come here.
[KRILLIN] Sure thing.
Uh, what's up, Jackie?
Stand here and face the crowd.
[KRILLIN] Hm?
Now focus on Krillin's head.
Since I doubt you called me
out here to work on my tan,
I assume my head is
stand-in for the moon?
[CHUN] Mhmm.
That's the plan, boy.
[KRILLIN] I'm happy
to help out, Jackie.
But if my head could turn
lunar we'd all be in trouble.
It would turn Goku
back into a monster.
Your head won't
work on its own,
but under hypnosis,
it should fool him.
[CHUN] Clear your mind
and focus on Krillin's head.
Ohhhh...
Watch as it changes
into a full moon!
All of your thoughts
are transfixed
upon its brilliant glow.
[CHUN] Feel its power
course through your veins
as it separates
beast from man...
[CHUN] Now change!
Uh...
[chuckles]
It worked! I'm normal!
What some call progress
I'll never understand.
Jackie Chun, I don't know how
to thank you, but thank you!
Your face says it all.
I'm cured! Now I look
like everyone else! Goodbye!
Just think of the money
I'll save on shampoo alone!
By his reaction,
I guess there are no mirrors
where he comes from.
Yeah, but maybe he'd
look better with a beard.
[ANNOUNCER]
A wolf changing into a man.
You saw it here first, folks!
Who said we never
try anything new?!
Wishing you good luck
would be pointless.
Huh?
Get going.
The third match is about
to begin as Chiaotzu faces off
against our very
own moon boy, Krillin!
[NARRATOR] What power dwells
within the mysterious Chiaotzu,
and will Krillin be strong
enough to stand his ground
against this pint-sized menace?!
The answers lie just ahead,
on the next incredible
episode of Dragon Ball!