[NARRATOR]
Previously, on Dragon Ball...
Goku met Kami,
the Guardian of the Earth,
and learned that Piccolo
transferred his powers
to a new incarnation, Piccolo
Jr., just before he died.
Goku has agreed to train
with Kami for three years,
hoping to become strong enough
to beat Piccolo once and for all
at the next
Martial Arts Tournament.
[GOKU]
I won't let you down, Kami.
[NARRATOR]
In exchange for Goku's vow,
Kami recreated
the Eternal Dragon,
and it didn't take long
for Bulma to choose a wish.
Master Roshi, Krillin, Chiaotzu,
and everyone else
killed by Piccolo
have all been
brought back to life.
[ALL cheer]
[NARRATOR]
Goku must learn a great deal
to stand a chance
against Piccolo's new form.
Now his difficult
training begins.
Mr. Popo, are you sure
this'll make me stronger?
Even you asking is wasteful.
Countless unnecessary moves.
Like the wings
of a fledgling bird,
they can flap,
but they cannot fly.
Uh, okay.
You must be like a stone.
A stone?
Calm and still, so that rain and
wind cannot move you. You see?
Oh, that's easy!
[GOKU chuckles]
[GOKU] How's this?
I look just like one, right?
[GOKU grunts]
Stones do not have voices.
Ouch! You're making
my head bumpy!
Nor do they feel pain.
[GOKU growls]
[insect buzzing]
[GOKU thinking] Being a stone is
a lot harder than it looks.
[growls]
Yaah!
[gasps]
[KRILLIN grunts]
Nice run!
You've improved, Krillin.
And I'm still set on easy mode.
[YAMCHA]
Hold up, little buddy.
I think it's my turn to tap in.
Yeah, let's roll.
Hey, Puar, can you help me?
Sure. I do this for
Yamcha all the time.
Huh...?
Shh!
Aah!
[BULMA]
Chop, chop, Puar.
You don't want my skin to look
like a fire engine, do you?
[OOLONG laughs]
[groans]
[ROSHI chuckles]
[BULMA]
Now don't miss any spots, okay?
[ROSHI] You don't have to
worry about that, my princess.
--[PUAR groans]
--[OOLONG chuckles]
--[ROSHI chuckles]
--Huh...?
--Yee-haw!
--[BULMA screams]
[ROSHI groans]
Back-spasm!
That's it! You dirty old man!
[screams]
[ROSHI] Oh, okay,
we've learned our lesson here!
Please, put the gun down!
[GOKU thinking] So this is
what it's like being a stone.
It's neat. You're
always relaxed,
and your mind just
wanders around, like a bee.
It's like dreaming, but better.
I get to pick whatever
I want to think about.
[cheering]
[GOKU thinking] Hey, I wonder if
Master Roshi and Krillin
are back to life yet.
[GOKU thinking]
I sure do miss them.
And Chiaotzu, too.
[GOKU chuckles]
[grunts]
[POPO]
Mm-mm-mmm.
Oh.
[GOKU thinking] Oh. Stones
don't think about things either.
They just sit,
and think of... nothing.
Now you're learning how to
truly relax your mind, Goku.
[GOKU snores]
Okay, maybe a
little too relaxed.
Let's try this from a
new angle, shall we?
I'm going to practice
my stick routine.
Watch me, and don't move.
Sounds good to me!
[squeals]
[POPO]
Are you frightened?
No, why would I be?
I saw the stick's not
long enough to reach me.
[POPO] True. Now,
keep staring at it closely.
[POPO]
Don't move.
[squeals, grunting]
[POPO]
If you move, you fail the test!
Hey!
Okay! I give up!
Why did you move
from your position?
Because that stick grew like my
Power Pole. It was gonna hit me.
Incorrect. It's no Power Pole.
It's just a regular,
finely carved piece of cedar.
Huh?
Hey, you're right, but
that doesn't make any sense.
I'm sure I saw it
moving closer toward me.
It was an
optical illusion, Goku.
You can't always trust
what your eyes see.
Huh?
[POPO] That's why
you must see without them.
What am I doing now?
I want you to put on that
blindfold and catch this cat.
[bell rings]
I get it. So I use my
ears instead of my eyes!
[GOKU laughs]
I got ya, kitty!
[bell ringing]
Uhh...?
Hey!
[bell ringing]
Hold on.
How'd you get
all the way over there?
Huh?!
You really move fast!
[meows]
[bell ringing]
Over there again, huh? Tricky.
Wait? This way? No, that way.
Slow down a second!
[GOKU]
Hey!
Gotcha!
Ow! That didn't work.
[gasps]
Hey! Two bells? That isn't fair,
Mr. Popo. You cheated!
What am I supposed
to learn from that?
Well, maybe you're supposed
to use another sense.
Like what?
One cannot describe
sight to the blind.
You'll have to stumble
upon it yourself.
And the sooner
you relax your mind,
the sooner it will come to you.
To learn something,
I think of nothing.
Wow, Mr. Popo, I have a
long way to go, don't I?
--[GOKU laughs]
--[POPO chuckles]
You said you learned all of
this up here with Kami, right?
Do you think I can do
the same training
that you did with him now?
Pretty please?
It isn't pleasant.
Are you sure you want to?
Yes.
Fine. Follow me.
I trust Mr. Popo has warned
you of the dangers of this.
[GOKU]
Mm-hm!
I'll do anything you tell me.
You risk a pain far
worse than death.
It doesn't matter.
Go to Mount Rumble,
fetch the Sacred Crown
and place it on your head.
[GOKU]
A sacred crown?
You mean those round things
that kings and queens wear?
That's correct.
Ooh, that sounds exciting!
I'll go get that crown
and be back here in no time!
Oh, wait a second,
I just have one question.
Where exactly is Mount Rumble?
[POPO] I'll take you there
now. Just stay where you are.
What is this place?
It's a special
transportation room.
It allows the Guardian of Earth
to go anywhere he desires.
Whoa!
Crazy! Where am I?
Wait up!
[GOKU]
Hello.
Do you know if there's a place
called Mount Rumble nearby?
Very scary! It sure looks like
a place a sacred crown would be!
[GOKU laughs]
Thank you!
[giggles]
[grunting]
[yelping]
[GOKU thinking]
It feels creepy around here.
I hope there aren't
any monsters at the top.
Why do they call it
Mount Rumble, anyway?
[chuckles]
[GOKU] There it is!
The crown! Wow, it's shiny.
That's great!
Didn't have to beat a monster!
I was at least expecting
some wild dogs or something.
[gasps]
It's sticking to me!
[screams]
[squeals]
[GOKU] Struck by lightning,
that's just bad luck.
[gasps, yells]
[squeals]
[GOKU thinking] The lightning
must be aiming for this crown.
Gotta go!
[squeals]
[GOKU screams]
[GIRL]
Pipi!
Pipi! Where are you?!
We'd better turn back, sweetie.
[gasps]
[GIRL]
Mom! It's that boy I saw!
[GOKU]
Hmm...?
[GIRL giggles]
Well, hello again. Did you
save me from the mountain?
[MOTHER]
Yes, and not a moment too soon.
Churi spotted you in the water.
[CHURI]
Mm-hm!
[GOKU] Your name's Churi?
Oh, my name is Goku.
Hi, Goku.
So, you live here
with just your mother?
[CHURI]
Yes. And Pipi, of course.
Pipi?
Pipi's the name
of Churi's pet bird.
They go everywhere together.
She's taken care of him
ever since he was
a little, fuzzy baby.
[CHURI whimpers]
Ohh...
Pipi flew off yesterday and we
haven't been able to find him.
Churi is worried sick.
You don't have
to be upset, Churi.
As soon as I get done
with my mission,
I'll help you track
him down myself!
Oh, do you mean it?
[GOKU]
Mm-hm!
And what is your mission, Goku?
We don't get visitors much.
Well, I'm supposed to
climb Mount Rumble
and take the Sacred Crown
without getting zapped.
The real Sacred Crown?
Yeah. Why, have you heard of it?
Uh-huh. Right, Mom?
It is a well-known legend
throughout the mountains.
They say that whoever
retrieves the crown
will become the strongest
fighter in all the world.
Whoa! Really? How cool!
I'm gonna be the
strongest in the world!
Huh?
[GOKU]
What?
[GOKU thinking]
I've got to get all the way down
without the lightning
hitting me. But how?
It's so fast,
I don't have time to react.
[GOKU screams]
[GOKU thinking]
It doesn't even seem possible.
[CHURI screams]
Help! I'm slipping!
[MOTHER]
Hold on tight! Don't you let go!
You're gonna have to pull
yourself up, somehow, sweetie!
[CHURI]
I can't! I'm scared!
[GOKU]
What's going on?
[MOTHER]
Churi's on the roof!
We don't have a ladder!
I-I can't help her!
[GOKU] Oh, okay. Tell her
not to go anywhere.
I'm on my way, Churi.
[CHURI screaming]
[GOKU]
Just give me your hand, okay?
[GOKU] Keep stretching.
You're a little too far away.
[CHURI]
I can't!
[CHURI screaming]
[gasps]
[CHURI]
Are we safe?
[GOKU]
Yeah! That was kind of fun.
Oh, Goku, I can't
possibly thank you enough.
[laughs]
So what were you doing
on the roof, anyway?
I... I thought if I went
someplace high,
Pipi would see me
and come back home.
You really care about
him a lot, don't you?
My goodness, Churi. You should
be ashamed of yourself.
What if Goku hadn't been here?
Pipi was close. I could feel him
flying through the air,
looking for me.
Wow, amazing. He was
all the way up in the sky,
but you could tell where he was?
[CHURI]
Mm-hm.
You imagined it.
[gasps]
Uh?
[CHURI]
There!
What are you
talking about, sweetie?
[CHURI]
I'm right here!
[MOTHER]
Churi, please!
Can't you hear it?
Hear what?
You're starting to worry me,
dear. Please come back inside.
[CHURI squeals]
[CHURi laughs]
[CHURI]
Pipi! You're really back! Yeah!
[CHURI laughs]
[CHURI]
I knew it was you!
You have the loudest
chirp in the world!
What did you run away for?
It's truly a blessing.
I guess. I was thinking
more like confusing.
How did you know he was here?
I'm not sure.
I felt him chirping.
Felt him?
[laughs]
[GOKU thinking]
She felt him.
She heard him without her ears!
--[CHURI gasps]
--Thanks a lot, Churi!
Are you leaving?
Well, come back soon.
[GOKU thinking] What Mr. Popo
said makes sense now!
I've got to see the lightning
with all my senses!
I've got to feel it!
[GOKU]
Aahh...
[GOKU thinking] I'm calm as
the sky, and still as a stone.
[KAMI]
Hmm...
[POPO]
You must use another sense.
Feel the movements
of the air around me,
and then you'll
be able to see me.
You need to get rid of
your redundant moves.
You must be more
tranquil than the sky
and yet quicker than lightning.
I feel it!
Uwaah!
I'm the strongest in the world!
[squeals]
[GOKU screams]
[NARRATOR] Mastering his senses
is harder than Goku thought.
Was that fourth
bolt of lightning
more than our little,
headstrong hero can take?
Will he ever stand up
on Mount Rumble again?
Don't miss the next
exciting Dragon Ball!