[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
[GHOST]
Behold, Fortuneteller Baba!
[BABA]
Good.
Oh my, you've brought
me young ones this time.
[NARRATOR] Unable to locate
the last Dragon Ball,
Goku and his friends paid
a visit to Fortuneteller Baba
in hopes of learning
its whereabouts.
Unfortunately,
they were not prepared
to meet the condition
for Baba's service.
[BABA] Before taxes,
and with our coupon,
it will run you roughly
around 10,000,000 zeni.
What's the matter?
Is that a lot?
I beg your pardon, ma'am,
but-but we don't have
that much money!
[NARRATOR] So the spooky
Fortuneteller gave them
another payment option.
One financed with danger.
Wait. So let me
get this straight.
You want us to fight your
five guys in a series
of one on one matches,
and if we win,
you'll tell us our
fortune for free?
That's right. You're correct.
But I warn you,
think this through carefully.
You are children and these
are no ordinary fighters.
I'm no child, and my
friends may be small,
but they can handle themselves.
We're prepared for
your challenge. Right?
Of course we are.
I say bring it on.
We can take 'em!
I'd like to help you,
but I left my spear back home.
I'd prefer to be a
spectator on this one.
Okay. Looks like it will
be the three of us.
Hmph. Oh, so the three
of you brave souls
think you can take on
my five warriors?
[laughs] Now this
I've got to see!
[KRILLIN chuckles]
I know the odds are uneven,
but don't worry.
We'll go easy on 'em.
And, what are the
rules of the fight?
It's very simple.
We'll continue until one person
is either thrown into
the lake or gives up.
You're right. It's quite simple.
I like it that way.
Losers swim.
I sure hope your fighters
are ready to take a bath.
Well, what fine spirit.
Now, which one of you
is going to fight first?
Come on, isn't it obvious?
Splendid.
[GOKU]
Hey, Krillin! Good luck!
Yeah, well, get comfortable.
You might be there a while.
There's gonna be five
wet fighters before
I leave the ring.
Just put 'em down quick.
Don't worry. It's me.
I remember everything
from the last tournament...
Including the roar of the crowd.
[crowd cheering]
Fangs, the Vampire, come forth.
"Fangs, the Vampire"?
You gotta' be kiddin' me.
[BABA cackles]
[UPA, GOKU gasp]
A bat?! This is a joke, right?
I'm a fighter, not a zookeeper!
[FANGS laughing]
Whoa! How did he do that?
[FANGS grunting]
Whoa! That guy needs a tan.
What, is he gonna
dance or fight?
Now, let the match begin.
[KRILLIN thinking] Hm. This
weirdo doesn't stand a chance.
Ready, Set, and Go!
[KRILLIN thinking] I was hoping
for a little challenge...
Oh well.
[FANGS mumbling]
You got lucky. But that
won't happen again.
[FANGS yelling,
KRILLIN groaning]
[FANGS cackles]
Don't go getting carried away.
That was a lucky shot
and I'm not going to
give you a second one.
You don't know who
you're messin' with!
[FANGS mumbling]
Stop dancing...
Ooh...
Hm?
...and fight!
[KRILLIN yelling]
[KRILLIN]
Woah...
I don't get it, Yamcha.
Why did he turn
into a bat again?
I don't know. But he's
up to something.
[KRILLIN growls]
[KRILLIN gasps]
[KRILLIN grunting]
[KRILLIN panting]
[YAMCHA]
Calm down, Krillin, and breathe.
You must concentrate
on his movements. Focus!
[FANGS cackles]
[KRILLIN gasps]
[KRILLIN grunts]
Hold still!
[FANGS cackling]
[FANGS yells]
--[GOKU] Behind you!
--[PUAR screams]
Look out!
[FANGS laughs]
Whoa! Get off of me! Let go!
[FANGS growls]
[ALL gasp]
[ALL gasping]
[FANGS slurping]
[KRILLIN yelping]
Whoa! What's the big idea?!
Stop biting me,
you sissy! That tickles!
Come on, Krillin!
Fight him,
get outta there! Move!
[ALL scream]
Tell me something I don't know!
This guy is nuts! He's like
a human vacuum cleaner!
This really bites!
[KRILLIN grunting]
Alright! That's it!
You're going down!
[KRILLIN]
Hey, get off my back!
Good... Keep up the good show.
This is what I call
quality entertainment!
Krillin! Shake him off!
[KRILLIN grunting, yelling]
[FANGS groaning]
[KRILLIN groans]
[ALL gasp]
[KRILLIN grunting]
[KRILLIN]
What is this?
What's the matter?
Are you alright?!
[FANGS cackles]
Thanks. I skipped breakfast.
Are you free for lunch?
You could be the
main course!
[FANGS hums]
Yummy!
[KRILLIN groaning]
You've lost a lot
of nutrients.
You need to be replenished.
Give up and you
will be restored.
[GHOST laughing]
You're supposed to fight,
not eat me, fang-face!
Easy, Krillin! She's right.
Your head looks like a
big tomato! Now settle down!
[KRILLIN groans] Think happy
thoughts. Think happy thoughts.
Happy thoughts! There.
[GOKU giggles]
That's a neat trick, Krillin.
From here it almost looks
like you have some hair!
[YAMCHA giggles]
Shut up!
Oh no! He's leaking!
I don't feel so good.
[FANGS cackling]
[KRILLIN moaning]
[FANGS yells]
[KRILLIN groaning]
[KRILLIN yelling]
[GOKU, YAMCHA, UPA gasp]
[FANGS laughs]
Fill him up, Ghost.
[GHOST laughing]
[KRILLIN groaning]
He'll be good as new.
Krillin, are you okay?
Hang in there.
What happened? Didn't you
wanna fight all five?
That's what I was doing
until you broke
my concentration!
[FANGS grunting]
Krillin has been defeated.
Who will be the next
to challenge my fighter?
[GOKU, YAMCHA]
Hm...
[KRILLIN] That fight was rigged.
I want a rematch!
Forget it. You're not fighting.
Oh! I got a good idea.
What is it?
I don't have all day, folks.
We're kind of on a schedule.
[KRILLIN] Well, how do
we get ol' bug eyes
to go along with it?
Simple. We'll just ask her.
She never said
we couldn't do it.
Puar's right.
Enough! We're running
into lunch!
[YAMCHA]
Sorry 'bout that.
We were just discussing
our lineup. It looks like
we're all gonna
have to fight.
Of course, genius!
What did you expect?
[GOKU] Ma'am, would it
be alright if Puar and Upa
fought together since
they're so small?
It's up to you.
[FANGS] Ha! Why not.
Two heads are better than one.
Please tell me one
of you just ate pizza.
[UPA, PUAR whimper]
[BABA] It seems he
accepts your terms.
[GOKU]
Thank you.
[YAMCHA] Uh, could you just
give us a minute here?
We need to talk about something.
Hurry.
Well, one of you has to do it.
[KRILLIN]
I thought we decided on Upa?
Fine by me.
Okay, let's do it!
[BABA] I've got to set up
an age restriction...
This is ridiculous!
--[BULMA] Master Roshi?
--[ROSHI] Yes?
Is this Fortuneteller Baba
character really trustworthy?
[OOLONG] She sounds like
a certifiable nut-case
if you ask me.
I understand your concerns,
but have a little
faith, will ya?
The old gal's been
tellin' fortunes
for about 500 years.
She knows what she's doing.
500 years?
[OOLONG] And that's the best
name she could come up with?!
Settle down.
She'll be able to locate
the last Dragon Ball.
No problem.
Great. So why did I waste
my time making the Dragon Radar?
We could have asked
your Fortuneteller
the whereabouts of the
Dragon Balls from the beginning.
[OOLONG] Yeah. We should
have contacted the old lady
a long time ago.
What a waste of time.
No, it's a bit more
complicated than that.
What do you mean?
Hm... Let's just say Baba
can be a 'killer' businesswoman!
In fact, I suspect
the boys are in
more than a little
bit of danger.
--[BULMA] Huh?
--[OOLONG] Oh...
[ROSHI chuckles]
But then again,
I've been wrong before.
[OOLONG, BULMA groan]
[YAMCHA] Remember,
you'll have to act fast
so don't waste
any time out there.
[PUAR &amp; UPA]
Right.
[FANGS cackling]
Go Upa! And go Puar! Good luck!
Watch out, he's a biter!
[YAMCHA] You can do this.
He's nothing. Just focus!
[FANGS cackling]
[PUAR, UPA whimper]
Let the match begin!
[UPA, PUAR yelp]
[FANGS yells]
[UPA, PUAR whimper]
Now Upa! Breathe!
[FANGS growls]
[FANGS groans, screams]
Get away from me, kid.
You smell like garlic.
Vampires hate garlic! Garlic!
[FANGS coughing]
[FANGS yelping]
[YAMCHA, GOKU, KRILLIN cheering]
[BABA grumbles]
[FANGS yelping]
This is madness!
I can't take it anymore!
[PUAR screams]
Forget garlic mouth,
you look good to me!
[PUAR whimpers]
[FANGS cackles]
[PUAR screams]
[FANGS yells]
I can transform, too!
[FANGS grunts]
[FANGS screaming]
[ALL cheering]
[FANGS sobbing]
[FANGS] What did you
have to do that for?
I wasn't gonna
bite you... Honest!
You're just a big baby
with bad teeth.
We're not scared of you.
[FANGS whimpers]
[FANGS screaming]
[UPA]
He's getting away!
Not yet!
[FANGS yelping]
Thirsty?
[FANGS screams]
[PUAR]
Hmph!
[BABA grumbles]
[ALL cheering]
[YAMCHA]
See, team work.
Good thing I wore him down.
[BABA laughs]
Impressive.
And now that the
warm-up match is over,
let's see how you fare
against my real fighters.
That was incredible.
You fought better than Krillin.
I was just getting started.
You both did your jobs
very well, so take a break.
Now it's my turn to fight.
Great.
Thank you, Yamcha.
Ready... Bring out your
fighter and let's go.
Vigor. I like that.
But I wonder if
you'd be so anxious
if you knew whom you
were about to fight.
Krillin was overly
confident as well
and look what happened to him.
Like I told you,
I'm not a child.
So save your concern
for my opponent.
This isn't my first time
in an arena.
Yamcha, let me fight with you.
I'm sure you could
defeat them all, Goku,
but I need the practice.
Don't worry, you'll fight later.
So let's go.
I heard your lunch
is gettin' cold.
You go, Yamcha!
Knock their lights out!
Watch out. She's tricky.
Are we gonna fight or not?
Bring out my opponent.
Careful, my friend.
Pay attention.
Your opponent is already here.
Huh? Where? I don't see anyone.
I told you that old
lady can't be trusted.
Wha--? Look at that!
Uh... That's weird.
Your opponent is a bug?
A bug.
[BABA grumbles]
Of course not!
[YAMCHA]
And all this time I didn't think
you had a sense of humor.
Come on, Baba, joke's over!
Do I look like
I'm capable of humor?
Hey, bright-eyes...
The reason you can't
see your opponent
is because he's invisible.
What?! How can I fight
what I can't see?!
What's invisible?
[BABA laughs] It means
see-through, transparent.
In other words, you won't
know he's there
until you've been hit.
[GOKU, UPA gasp]
I don't have time to give
you a lesson in physics.
Close your mouths, watch the
fight and visit your library.
Now, let the match begin!
[YAMCHA growls]
[SEE-THROUGH laughs] Guess which
hand I have behind my back.
Is it the left...
[YAMCHA groans]
[SEE-THROUGH]
...or the right?
[YAMCHA groans]
--[GOKU, UPA, KRILLIN gasp]
--Oh no! Yamcha!
[YAMCHA grunting]
Show yourself, you lousy coward!
[BABA cackles]
[YAMCHA grunts]
[YAMCHA]
An invisible man.
Next time, I'm definitely
bringing a coupon!
[YAMCHA screams,
SEE-THROUGH cackles]
[YAMCHA grunting,
SEE-THROUGH cackling]
[YAMCHA panting]
Where is he?!
[BABA cackles]
You're an experienced fighter,
show us what ya got!
[YAMCHA panting]
[YAMCHA grunting]
[GOKU]
I don't get it...
How is Yamcha supposed
to fight someone
that he can't even see?
He's not. That's the point.
Its dirty fighting...
[KRILLIN] If Yamcha could
just lay eyes on him,
I know he could beat him!
That's it!
What's it?
Go find Master Roshi
and bring him back here.
And Bulma! We'll need her too!
Okay, but why?
Don't ask questions, just go!
If you say so... Flying Nimbus!
[GOKU grunts]
That's not fair.
He gets a cloud;
I'm stuck on a ball!
[YAMCHA groans, yells]
--[KRILLIN] Are you okay?
--[PUAR] Yamcha!
[BABA]
Stay back!
The rules state a fighter
cannot accept aid
from a member of his team.
Please don't give up.
You can beat him.
Yamcha, just hang
in there long enough
for Goku to get back.
[YAMCHA grunts]
Yamcha!
Fight!
Protect yourself.
Right!
This doesn't make any sense...
How can Bulma and Roshi help?
[YAMCHA screaming, groaning]
[YAMCHA]
What am I supposed to do?
I'm a sitting duck out here!
Whatever you've got planned,
Krillin, you better hurry.
[BABA cackles]
He won't last much longer.
[YAMCHA pants]
Wait a minute! Wait...
I've been doing this all wrong.
I've gotta calm down and focus.
If I can't see him...
maybe I can hear him.
Yamcha! Move!
What are you--
[KRILLIN]
Shhhh! Be quiet!
[footsteps]
[NARRATOR] Can Yamcha
defeat his invisible opponent?
And what does Krillin want
with Master Roshi and Bulma?
Does he have a plan or
is he just looking to add
to the cheering section?
Find out on the next thrilling
chapter of Dragon Ball!