[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
The first match of the
semi-finals began
as Goku took on Tien Shinhan.
[GOKU]
Haah!
[TIEN yells]
Look out below!
Goku is falling fast!
[TIEN] Have you been wearing
that underneath your clothes
throughout the
entire tournament?
It must weigh a ton!
[GOKU]
Kami insisted.
It's not much different
than Master Roshi's style...
He wore a turtle
shell to gain strength.
It's pretty much
the same principle here.
[NARRATOR]
Once he shed the weights,
Goku felt as light as a feather,
and enjoyed a phenomenal
increase in speed and agility.
Goku entertained the crowd
while he tested
his newfound quickness...
Soon, the action continued
with a surprising twist.
[GOKU] This belt does
belong to you, right?
[NARRATOR]
Goku was so fast,
even Tien couldn't
see his movements.
[TIEN]
Hey, my belt!
[NARRATOR] Even Junior,
Goku's nemesis, was intrigued,
but Tien remained determined,
declaring that if three eyes
were not sufficient
to track Goku, he would use 12!
[TIEN growls]
[growls]
[yells]
[TIEN growling]
Is it just me, or is
Tien beginning to glow?
I see it, too.
It's like he's on fire.
[growling continues]
[gasps]
[TIEN yells]
[TIEN chuckles]
[gasps]
[chuckling continues]
[GOKU whimpers]
[TIEN chuckling]
If you think that's something,
wait till you see what's next.
[gasps]
[TIEN grunting]
[chuckling]
What? Two more?!
[gasps]
[GOKU] Tien Shinhan!
What have you done?!
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
Nice move. Finally,
some entertainment.
Wait, four against one?
That's not fair.
Wow, incredible!
[ANNOUNCER] Tien Shinhan
has split into four!
Presumably, by using the
After Image Technique.
Ready?!
[TIENS yell, chuckle, grunt]
[GOKU yelps]
Raah! Rrgh! Haa!
[GOKU grunts]
--[GOKU gasps]
--[TIEN yells]
[GOKU screams]
[chuckling]
[YAMCHA thinking]
What in the world...?
That's not... the
After Image Technique.
Those punches felt real...
[GOKU]
Images can't hurt people.
[TIENS laugh]
That's true. This is my ultimate
technique... Quadruplication!
Oh... that's new.
I thought Tien Shinhan was an
only child. Quadruplets, whoa!
Hello! Launch, wake up!
He said "Quadruplication."
It's a technique.
[BULMA growls]
[ROSHI thinking] Hmm. There's
a new spin on an old classic.
You've actually split
into four separate people...
But how in the world
did you do it?
[TIEN chuckles]
Right now, you must be thinking,
"How am I going to
handle four Tien's?"
The answer is, you're not!
[GOKU gasps]
[gasps]
[TIENS yelling]
[TIEN]
I'm right behind you, Goku!
[growls]
[GOKU yells]
--[groans]
--[TIEN growls]
[GOKU yells]
[CHICHI]
Goku!
[ANNOUNCER] Judging from
the beating Goku just took,
I'd say four Tien Shinhans
are tremendously more
powerful than one!
Goku certainly has
his hands full.
[ANNOUNCER]
Goku has yet to fully recover.
Perhaps he's worse off
than originally thought.
Can he muster enough
strength to continue the match?
[GOKU whimpers]
[CROWD cheers]
Yeah, keep going.
[TIENS]
Charge!
[growling, yelling]
[GOKU growls]
[TIEN gasps]
Where is he?
[GOKU]
Over here!
[TIENS gasp]
[GOKU]
Haah!
[gasps]
[TIEN grunts]
[TIENS grunting]
[GOKU laughs]
Good one, Goku.
He moved quickly
and caught us off guard.
[GOKU grunting]
But...
He can't hide from all
of us at the same time.
[TIENS yell]
[ANNOUNCER] In a peculiar move,
all Tien Shinhans
have dispersed across
the four corners of the ring.
What are they planning?
Tien, what are you doing?
[chuckles]
[TIEN]
Now!
[gasps]
[GOKU screams]
[CROWD screaming, gasping]
[screaming]
[ROSHI chuckles]
[CROWD murmuring]
I don't see him anywhere,
do you? Where did he go?!
[gasps]
There!
Focus!
The sky lights up as Tien and
his doppelgangers
shoot intense energy beams
into the clouds above!
[gasping]
Heh!
[GOKU screams]
Goku!
[GOKU groans]
It looks as thought
the beams have found
their intended target,
zapping Goku,
who is now falling to the
ground like a speeding comet!
No, Goku!
How did he find Goku
in those clouds?!
Tien's perception
must be super human!
Let's hope the same thing can
be said for Goku's bones.
He's going to be hitting
the stage pretty hard!
[CHICHI gasps, sobs]
[CROWD gasping]
[yelling, cheering]
[ROSHI whimpers]
[OOLONG squeals]
Game...
...Over.
[ANNOUNCER]
Goku isn't moving!
And after that beating,
who can blame him?
Tien Shinhan appears to
have won this this match!
[CHICHI screams]
--Goku!
--Wait! Wait!
Let go! He needs me! Goku!
Calm down! Goku hasn't
lost yet... Look.
Huh?
[GOKU groans]
[TIENS gasping]
[GOKU]
Ow!
[CROWD cheering]
[TIENS gasping]
[laughs]
This... can't be!
Tien Shinhan is left stunned
as Goku rebounds from his fall
as though nothing had happened!
[GOKU giggles]
That was a good one, Tien.
I'm a little sore.
A... A little?!
Remarkable... I get the feeling
we could drop an entire city
on top of him and all
he'd get is a headache!
Careful. Next time
you might not walk away.
Heh! There won't
be a next time...
You won't use
the same trick again.
You sure?
[ROSHI thinking] Yet again,
Goku does the impossible...
Ya know, he's about as
honest as you can get,
but when it comes to the laws
of physics, he's a wanted man!
[ROSHI thinking] As I've
watched him grow over the years,
it seems what makes
him so special
isn't his strength or speed.
It's his endurance.
No one can break him!
I respect you, Goku.
But I will win at any cost.
Okay.
[TIEN] "Okay"? What does that
mean? I'm trying to tell you
you're in danger.
If you stay in this fight,
I will hurt you, or worse!
Hah! I've already found two weak
spots in your strategy, Tien.
I'll be fine.
[TIEN growls]
You see his weakness,
Goku, and I see yours.
My technique was perfect.
You don't know what
you're talking about!
If you're uncertain,
why don't you just try it again.
You'll see.
Oh, I'll do it again, all right.
And this time
I'll use my full power!
I tried to be polite
and give you a way out,
but you wouldn't take it.
Now the consequences
are on your head!
[giggles]
What weak spots do you
think Goku's talking about?
[YAMCHA] Maybe he hit his head
harder than we thought.
[GOKU]
What are you guys waiting for?
I'm ready when you are.
Let's get this over with!
Fine!
It's not clear why, but it
appears the four Tien Shinhans
are preparing to repeat
their last performance!
Will Goku have
better luck this time,
or will this move put Tien
back in the winner's circle?
[TIEN]
Now!
There he is!
It's no use, Goku.
You can't escape!
Fire!
Sorry to disappoint you, Tien.
But my future looks
bright from up here!
Solar Flare!
[TIEN screams]
My eyes!
[screaming]
Goku has created a
light so intense,
it's as if he threw the sun
itself in Tien Shinhan's face!
[TIEN screams]
[ANNOUNCER] Ironically,
this is the same technique
Tien Shinhan used in
the previous tournament.
Only this time,
it's being used against him!
Goku's plan is working,
as the dazzling lights
take their toll on Tien,
and anyone else not fortunate
enough to be wearing sunglasses.
This is weak spot number one...
Your eyesight's a
little too good.
[TIEN]
I thought I was the only master
of the Solar Flare Technique.
[TIEN growls, yells]
[TIEN snarls]
[gasps]
Wrong way. I'm over here!
[TIEN growls]
[TIEN] I see you!
This was a bad idea, Goku.
You have to rely on
your sight, same as me,
which means you're also
at a disadvantage.
I have to disagree... There are
two of you behind me, right?
One is planning a
knife-hand attack,
and the other, a right
round house kick.
You guessed!
How can you be sure?
[GOKU] Training. I won't
bore you with the details.
[ROSHI thinking] I wasn't
aware of some
eyes-in-the-back-of-your-head
technique!
I'd better take
some night classes.
I think that's enough...
Lesson finished.
I assume you can see
clearly again?
Good. Then there is no need for
me to hold back any longer.
Holding back?
How did you manage that?
All this time...
...you've been
so busy... losing.
Your second weak spot
hurt you the most.
It's what cost you this match.
Do tell!
You made the first one worse
by breaking up into four!
No!
[GOKU yells]
[TIEN gasping]
[yelling continues]
[TIEN grunts]
[grunting]
[yells]
[gasping]
[TIEN screams]
[BOTH gasp]
[GOKU grunting]
I win. Don't get up
on my account.
That's an impressive technique.
I wish I'd known of it earlier.
There've been a lot of enemies
I would've loved to use it on.
But I don't think it
works in a fight like this.
Not only were you
split into fourths,
but so were your strengths.
[ROSHI thinking]
Good reasoning.
Nice to see Goku has
worked on sharpening more
than just his fighting skills.
I won't pretend
I'm not wounded...
But it's only my pride...
You did a good job, Goku.
Congratulations.
That's it? Congratulations?!
Thanks for piling me up
like a stack of pancakes?!
Come on, Tien! Don't you want to
know how he did it?! I sure do!
Yeah, me, too!
Nice speech, but how
did he figure it all out?
It's unbelievable!
I guess that's why he's
the big hero and I'm... not.
[CHICHI] There are no small
heroes, only sidekicks.
[KRILLIN]
Thanks...
[CROWD cheering, laughing]
Ah, oh! Okay, it's official!
Tien Shinhan is out of bounds,
ending an unprecedented battle!
Goku wins the first
match of the semi-finals
and now goes on to the
championship round
where the 23rd Master of
Martial Arts will be determined!
Ah, well done, Goku.
You won! You won!
I'm so proud of you!
[GOKU laughs]
Enjoy the adulation of
the crowd while it lasts...
When I crush you, those
cheers will turn to sorrow.
[NARRATOR]
On the road to victory,
Goku has faced many
impossible challenges.
However, none have
been as treacherous
and diabolical as Junior.
Their confrontation begins
next time on Dragon Ball!