[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball,
the World Martial Arts
Tournament began
with its super intense
elimination round!
Over one hundred fighters
entered the foot-flying fray,
and Goku and Krillin plowed
through them one by one!
But hold on!
Krillin and Goku aren't the only
ones advancing to the finals...!
Yamcha will be there too!
[GOKU chuckles]
[GOKU and KRILLIN chuckle]
[GOKU] Excuse us please!
[KRILLIN] Coming through!!
[GOKU] Sorry about that! Oops!
[KRILLIN] Oh! Watch your toes!
I don't think we'll find
Master Roshi any time soon
when all we can see
are people's pants legs!
[GOKU] Hello, sir!
Hm? Huh? Hmm...
Can you help?
Eh?
Uhh... Huh...
Hey, I found 'em, Krillin!
[GOKU chuckles]
Roshi! Where've you
been all this time?
Oh, uh, this place is
like a cattle herd...
I just went to the restroom
and the toilet line
was a mile long.
Well, while you were out
on your bathroom adventures,
Krillin and Goku
really kicked tail!
Yeah and Yamcha made it too!
Yes, from what I heard
they just breezed
through their matches.
But I suspect the
finals will be different.
I got you something, Bulma.
Huh? Why?
[ROSHI] I saw this
shirt in the gift shop,
and it just screamed your name.
You... bought me that?
[ROSHI] It's a
token of friendship!
Wow! That's so sweet!
[BULMA and ROSHI chuckle]
And I got you this golden
souvenir key chain, too!
Oh, wow! Thank you...!
I didn't know you
could be so nice!
[ROSHI] Now could you
do a nice man a favor?
As a friend?
[BULMA groans]
[ROSHI] Could you squeeze into
that tight little
shirt I got you
and show off your
curves a bit more...?
You think?
Yeah...? Yeah?
[ROSHI giggles]
[BULMA] Pervert!!
[punch]
[ROSHI yells]
[ROSHI whimpers]
Maybe you should have entered
the tournament yourself, Bulma!
[GOKU] Oolong!
Huh?
[GOKU and KRILLIN chuckle]
[OOLONG] Goku...! Wowzas!
You were incredible
in there! For real!
We were cheering
the entire time!
And I turned into a ladder!
[GOKU] That's great!
Huh?
Well done, boys. Well done.
Thank you!
It was just like a dream..
But I knew we were going to
win the whole time, of course.
[BULLHORN GUY] The World Martial
Arts Tournament will soon begin!
If you're one of
the eight finalists,
please meet in the
main hall immediately...!
Thank you!
Well you boys had
better run along then.
[GOKU] Yeah! Guess so.
[GOKU] I'll look for
you in the audience!
[OOLONG] Do it
for the glory, kid!
Hmm. Now...
[BULMA] That boy never
ceases to amaze me...
[OOLONG] Huh?
Hey... The old man...
went AWOL again!
I swear there's something
wrong with his head...
[crowd cheering]
[YAMCHA] So you saw
Bulma and Puar?
[GOKU] Yeah...
Oh, and Bulma said, "Hi."
Huh?
[JACKIE CHUN] Hmm. So you're
one of the fighters, huh?
Well, that means we have
something in common! Hehehe...
[FIGHTER]
Hmph.
[JACKIE CHUN]
Hmmm...
[JACKIE CHUN chuckles]
Hm?
[GOKU sniffs]
[KRILLIN]
Who's the stink-bucket?
[YAMCHA] That's Bacterian.
[YAMCHA] He's got
Herculean strength,
but that comes second
to his offensive odor!
They say he's never taken a
bath since the day he was born!
[YAMCHA] His opponents
can only fight
with one hand because the other
one has to hold their nose!
He takes advantage
of this to win!
[KRILLIN]
That's a dirty trick.
[GOKU] I think
I'm gonna pass out!
Now can I have your
attention, please...?
I need you all
here at the front!
[GOKU and KRILLIN laugh]
[ANNOUNCER]
On second thought, mister,
why don't you stay in the back?
You'll be drawing lots to
determine your opponents
and the order of the fights,
so come up when you're called.
Let's keep this orderly
and civilized, people.
[JACKIE CHUN]
Ehh... Sonny?
[ANNOUNCER] Yes?
--[RANFAN] Hey!
--Why don't you be a pal
and put me in the ring with her?
--[ANNOUNCER] Eh? Huh?
--[RANFAN] Oh...
I don't take requests!
[JACKIE CHUN thinking] Young
people are so unreasonable...
So, your name is... uh... Nem?
Nam.
A five.
[ANNOUNCER] Let's see...
I guess that puts you
in fight number three...
Now... Monster Beast Giran?
[GIRAN]
Ah.
[ANNOUNCER]
You drew number eight,
that means the fourth fight.
[ANNOUNCER] Bacterian?
[ANNOUNCER] Number one...
First fight.
[ANNOUNCER] Yamcha?
Yeah.
[ANNOUNCER] Number four...
That's fight two.
Where's Krillin?
Oh...! Here!
Can you reach it... sir?
I got one!
[groans and shudders]
[KRILLIN] Hu... Huh?
[ANNOUNCER] Number two...
That puts you in fight
one against Bacterian!
Now... Gaw-what?
Gaw... Kay... Uh...?
[GOKU]
Uh... Uh...
Come on now...!
Gaw-kay-uh!
[GOKU]
Uh... Uh... Huh?
Hmm...
Six, seven, eight...
We're not missing anybody...
Uh... Sorry to butt in,
but that spells Goku.
Huh?!
Heh... Oh... yeah...
How silly of me...
All right, people...
Is there anyone in
the house named Goku?
Me!
[ANNOUNCER]
You've drawn number seven...
That's the final fight.
[ANNOUNCER] Ranfan?
Mhmmm?
[ANNOUNCER] Number six.
Jackie Chun?
Yo! Mm, mm...
[ANNOUNCER] Number three!
This will be
single elimination...
In a full,
regulation-sized arena...
You lose... if you fall
outside of the ring,
stay down for ten
counts, or give up...
But poking in the eyes
or hitting in the private
parts is not allowed!
What parts are private?
You know what I mean...
It's the... things
that make us boys!
But what... aaaabout my parts?
Gaaah!
Okay everyone, I think that's
enough questions for now!
So just stay here and I'll
come back when it's time.
[GOKU] One more thing!
Where's our lunch?
[ANNOUNCER] Huh?
Don't you think it's a bad idea
to eat a meal right
before your fight?
You might get cramps that way!
I will eat!
Uhhh...
Well, I'm sure we can round
up something, don'tcha think?
But of course...
Come with me.
Are you coming too?
Uh... I think I'll pass...
I'm too nervous to swallow.
I finished it. Is there more?
Now, ladies and gentlemen!
Are you ready?
That's right, people!
It's time for the 21st World
Martial Arts Tournament!
Okay, and here are
the big match-ups
for the tournament's
first round.
First match:
Bacterian versus Krillin!
Second match:
Jackie Chun versus Yamcha!
Fight three:
Ranfan versus Nam!
And match four:
Gaw-ku--no, uh--
Goku versus Giren!!
The first match between
Bacterian and Krillin
will begin momentarily, so
don't go to the lemonade stand!
Before we get things fired up,
let me remind you
that this year's winner
will receive a prize of
five hundred thousand zeni!
With that said, let's welcome
the esteemed director
of the Tournament,
who has a few words of
wisdom to start this baby off!
Please go ahead, sir.
[silence]
[clears throat]
Ruff!
[ANNOUNCER]
Isn't that profound?!
And now, the first
match of the tournament!
Would the contestants
please come down?!
[crowd cheers]
Just keep punching, Krillin.
I'm positive you'll win!
[ANNOUNCER] Fighting in the
bright red uniform is Krillin!
He's one of the youngest
competitors we have this year!
And fighting in the soiled
brown briefs is Bacterian,
who as you probably noticed,
has a very distinctive
odor about him!
Smells like we got
here just in time!
It smells like we
should have been late!
Hope that boy beats
Bacterian quick
so we can get him off the stage!
--[GOKU] Psst! Hey!
--[KRILLIN] Hmm?
[KRILLIN laughs]
I'll be cheering
for you from up here!
[GOKU laughs]
Okay, guys!
Let's try to keep
this nice and clean...
[ANNOUNCER]
All right, scratch that.
It's clearly not possible.
So, uh, just try not to get
anything on the audience, okay?
Let's get those
punches... flying!
[BACTERIAN] Hello, boy!
You come closer! Yes?
[BACTERIAN]
Huh...?
I miss you... Tricky!
[BACTERIAN] Now...
I've got some trickies too!
[BACTERIAN]
And here... Try this!
[BULMA] Oh... Vomit!
[BACTERIAN] Smelly finger!!!
[ANNOUNCER]
And Krillin goes down
after he's hit by
the smelly finger attack!
[MONK] One...! Two...! Three...!
[ANNOUNCER]
It seems the horrid smell
is too much for
the little warrior!
[ANNOUNCER] It's an
assault on his senses!
[BULMA] I think
I've been traumatized...
[OOLONG] Get up Krillin!
[various cheers for KRILLIN]
[BACTERIAN]
You say good-bye!
[ANNOUNCER] Bacterian
has caught his opponent
in a terrible choke-hold!
Krillin's smoothly-shaved
head is looking like a cherry!
[KRILLIN groans]
[ANNOUNCER]
No, wait! A blueberry!
Quick, Krillin...!
Hit his arms away from you!
[KRILLIN struggles]
[MONK] One...! Two...!
[BACTERIAN]
You made... me hurt!
[ANNOUNCER] Krillin made
a strong counter assault!
But now he's dangerously
close to a ring-out!
[BACTERIAN] Up and down!
And up and down!
Up and down! Up and down!
Up and down!...
[ANNOUNCER]
What's this?!
Krillin seems to have
Bacterian by the pant-seat!
[BACTERIAN]
Here's a surprise!
[BACTERIAN grunts]
[ANNOUNCER]
Oh! What cruelty...!
Bacterian has resorted
to chemical warfare...!
This could be the end!
Oh, my goodness!
How can one person do
so many disgusting things?
[ANNOUNCER] Bacterian
just keeps on stomping!
[ANNOUNCER]
Wow, folks...!
I've never seen a
beating so ruthless!
And Krillin is too stunned from
the body odor to defend himself!
[BULMA]
It's so awful!
[BACTERIAN]
I am tricky!!
[BACTERIAN guffaws]
[MONK] One...! Two...!
[BULMA] Go...! Go...!
[PUAR] Please!
[ALL THREE] Krillin!
Krillin! Krillin! Krillin...!
[CROWD] Krillin!
Krillin! Krillin! Krillin!...
[MONK] Five...! Six...!
Come on...!
It's not over yet!
Uh... Uh...!
Krillin! Hey!
Focus your mind and
you won't smell him...!
Just think about it!
You don't have
a nose, remember?!
[KRILLIN shudders]
Hey...! He's right!
[MONK] Nine...!
[ANNOUNCER]
Hold on, folks!
Krillin has stood up!
It seems he's
caught his second wind
after Bacterian's breaking wind!
How does this boy do it?
Thanks for the tip, Goku!
Now... My turn!
Okay, stinky not
enough for you?
Then here's
super-special tricky!
[ANNOUNCER] Oh, my...!
Could it be...?
Bacterian is now preparing
for his most notorious
attack move...!
It's the deep-throated,
mucous-filled
loogie of death...!
No opponent has
ever withstood it!
[BACTERIAN]
I'm done... for!
[ANNOUNCER] What a
roller coaster, folks!
Krillin has won the round with
a come-from-behind knockout!
Yeah!!
[crowd cheers]
[GOKU &amp; KRILLIN] We made it!
We made it! We made it!
Awesome job, Krillin!
Thank you, Goku!
[GOKU &amp; KRILLIN
laugh and cheer]
[ANNOUNCER] Well! If we learned
anything from this match,
it's that no matter how used
you are to your own stench,
you'll always be stunned
by someone else's!
Now, I just hope they
can clean up the arena!
[cheering continues]
[NARRATOR] So, after an
exciting--and unusual--
round of fighting,
Krillin has advanced
from the first round
of Tournament play!
But with the
strangeness of this match,
one can only wonder what the
next fights will have in store!
Don't miss the next Dragon Ball!