[NARRATOR] The high seas,
wondrous and enchanting--
Their blue waters filled
with untold treasures
and numerous forms of life,
both familiar and mysterious.
[NARRATOR] Today, the waters are
calm and peaceful... until...
[CAPTAIN]
Something's headed right for us!
It's closing in! Fast!
Hard to starboard. Move!
[SAILOR]
Aye, Captain! Hard to starboard.
Hey, kid! Are you okay?
What are you doing
in the water?!
Hi!
Will you please point me in
the direction of Papaya Island?
I seem to have gotten lost.
Thank you!
Hey... Was that a mermaid?
[PILOT] Attention, passengers.
We have encountered
some mild turbulence.
For those drinking coffee
or applying makeup,
we do apologize.
In just a few moments, we will
be landing on Papaya Island,
home of the World
Martial Arts Tournament.
At this time, we ask that
you remain in your seats
and make sure your lap belts
are securely fastened.
We're finally here.
This is exciting.
It sure is,
especially since you're
going to win the tournament.
Yamcha could be the
champion of the tournament
if I let him win.
Yeah, sure.
And just to keep things fair,
when we do fight,
I'll tie my hands
and keep my eyes closed.
Um, not to put
a damper on this,
but aren't you boys
forgetting something?
Or should I say someone,
namely Goku?
Goku, Shmoeku.
My money's on Jackie Chun!
He did win last time,
after all...
I hate Chun! He's the one who
beat Goku! Let's kill him!
It's okay, Launch. Settle down.
Help...
Sir? Are you all right?
Is something the matter?
I want off
this plane right now!
I see.
Land or get me a parachute.
Either way, I'm leaving!
Sir...
I'm sorry,
but it's impossible
for anyone to leave
the plane before it lands.
Please sit back
and try to relax.
Can I get you a pillow
or some peanuts?
I don't want peanuts.
I want this bird on the ground!
Now go tell the captain!
Yes, sir.
[OOLONG] I'll take some peanuts.
[growling]
Master, please
get control of yourself.
This is embarrassing.
[YAMCHA] From now on,
I'm travelling alone.
Time to eat. I'm starving!
Fruit!
Perfect!
[TIGERS growling]
Oh, look at the tigers!
They must be hungry, too...
Here!
Eat!
Go on, there's plenty more
where those came from!
Uh oh!
What's wrong, kitties?
These are tasty!
[roaring]
What's wrong?
[GOKU yelling]
Great!
Roshi couldn't wait
to leave the plane,
but now we can't get him
out of the airport!
If he doesn't hurry,
we'll miss our check-in
for the Tournament.
Hey! Wait up!
You won't believe what I found
crawling in the
airport's commissary.
I just have one question.
Why me?
[KRILLIN]
Hey, front door service!
[TURTLE]
That's a matter of perspective.
[YAMCHA] Need a lift?
There.
Thank you, Yamcha.
[BULMA] I hope I don't
run into anyone I know.
[ROSHI] All in all,
that was a nice flight.
[KRILLIN] The competition hall,
please, and make it snappy.
[DRIVER] Yes, sir.
Finally!
It feels great to be back.
It's like I never left.
Yeah.
Are you boys
going to sign up?
[KRILLIN] Oh, yes, sir!
[RECEPTIONIST]
Thank you, Yamcha...
...and... Krillin.
[ROSHI] I'm just curious.
Has a boy named
Goku registered yet?
Goku...
Oh yes, that young boy who won
the vice-championship last time.
No. According to
my records, he hasn't.
That's strange.
Where could he be?
What's holding him up?
He'd better hurry.
If he's not careful,
he'll miss the entries.
It's not like him
to be late...
I sure hope he didn't
forget what day it is.
Entry time is just about up.
Don't worry. He'll be here.
He was really looking
forward to the competition.
He'll wait to show up at
the last minute, just watch.
I don't see what
all this fuss is about.
Fighting with rules. How boring.
If anyone else
but you had said that,
I would have thought
they were bragging.
Sweet sauerkraut!
I almost forgot to sign up!
Waugh!
Say, there's a name I'd
like to enter in the tournament.
Jackie Chun.
Jackie Chun?
You don't mean the Jackie Chun
who won the championship
at the last competition?
Mmm-hmm!
I don't believe it! You're him?
Shh!
See?
I-I see.
Let's keep this little secret
just between you and me.
Sure!
Jackie Chun is on the list.
Oh, there's only
five minutes left.
He's not going to make it.
Master...
Goku is going to make it
in time, isn't he?
Just keep your eye on that road.
He'll be here.
Uh, hey, you were
chatting with that clerk
like you were best friends.
That's none of your business!
[CRANE] Hello.
Nice to see you've come out
of your shell, Master Roshi.
Hermit Crane, what a surprise.
After all these years,
you're still alive.
The lines on your face
are just as deep, old friend.
That was rude.
Relax. I didn't come
here to start trouble.
In fact, I heard
a silly little whisper
that your pupils did quite well
during the last tournament.
I guess the saying is true,
anything can happen.
What's it to you, huh?!
You're out of your league,
Roshi, admit it.
You were privileged
by my absence last time,
but we both know
fighting against my team
is an exercise in futility.
Not even Jackie Chun
could handle my boys!
Do yourself a favor and go home.
[chuckling]
I sympathize with your crew.
I really, really do.
Inadequacy is always such
a tough pill to swallow,
but it sure beats
public humiliation.
Thanks for the concern.
It's nice to see some
things haven't changed.
Like you're still
full of hot air.
You'd better stay out of my way!
We're not turning
tail for you or anyone!
You've been warned.
Now suffer the consequences.
Let's go!
I've wasted enough
time on these fools!
Master Roshi,
who was that weirdo?
His name's Master Shen,
but I used to call him friend.
Time's almost up!
We have one minute left.
He's late!
Relax.
Puar, I want you
to transform into Goku
and register as him.
Right!
Wait! Look, here he is!
Hello, everybody!
Wait up! I'm coming!
Hey, Goku!
Long time no see!
You got here just in time! Cool!
I know. What have
you guys been doing?
Waiting.
[ALL laughing]
That was a good one!
Goku is here.
Is he in time to register?
Yes, of course.
[ROSHI] Thank you.
What have you
gotten yourself into now?
You look filthy!
It's good to
see you again, Bulma.
Are my eyes deceiving me,
or have you gotten taller
since the last time I saw you?
Oh, yeah!
[KRILLIN thinking] So he's grown
a few inches. Big deal.
Most of it's hair anyway!
Yo, Goku!
You look awfully winded
for someone who rides a cloud.
Where is the Nimbus
and why were you late?
Master, I thought you
said not to bring the Nimbus.
You said I should
rely on my own strength.
Right... I did say that.
I have one question.
Did you swim here?
Yeah, part of the way.
From a place called Yahhoi.
From Yahhoi?!
That's impossible.
It's on the other side
of the Earth!
The scary thing here
is that I believe you.
What? Uh... Huh?
The important thing is
you're here and registered.
Now what do ya say we
go grab a bite to eat?!
Food!
It's customary to
feast before a big fight,
and since they
don't come any bigger
than the World
Martial Arts Tournament,
we should dine on the best
meal this town has to offer!
[ALL] Yeah!
Good idea!
I'm going to eat
until I bust!
[ROSHI] How about I just
make us all some sandwiches?
[chattering]
[stammering nervously]
--I couldn't eat another bite.
--What'd you think of dessert?
Weren't they delicious?
What? What do you mean
you can't pay the bill?
Shh!
[ROSHI] Not so loud.
Listen, I know
what you're thinking,
but I can pay my bill.
It's just going to
take a couple of days.
By then I should
have 500,000 Zeni.
I'm telling you the truth!
I believe you, sir!
[GOKU] Krillin, was
training with Master Roshi
as challenging
as it was last time?
Definitely.
If you remember the
program we did together,
multiply that by a hundred.
When I wasn't farming
and delivering milk,
I was lugging around
a hundred pound stones!
A hundred pound stones?
That does sound challenging!
[ROSHI laughing awkwardly]
You don't look well.
What's the matter?
Was there a problem
with the manager?
How many times
do I have to tell you
to be quiet and
mind your own business?
[laughing awkwardly]
I don't know what came over me.
Must have been
something in the soup.
Hey, I've got a good idea.
Why don't we all
go back to the hotel
and play a nice game of cards?
--[BULMA] Oh no!
--[PUAR] Bulma got a Joker!
[ALL laughing]
[YAMCHA] Oolong, pick a card.
What is this?
It's the Joker.
All right, choose a card.
Second from the left.
Good choice.
[TURTLE] Oooh...
[giggles]
[PUAR] I'm finished!
[YAMCHA] I'm out!
[OOLONG] Me too!
Here you go.
[OOLONG laughing menacingly]
[ROSHI] Pick one!
Which one should I choose?
Just pick one up!
I think I'll take this one...
I'm finished!
--[OOLONG laughing]
--[ROSHI whining]
That means you lose.
Good night.
[ALL] Good night!
[ROSHI laughing menacingly]
[knock on door]
Hello!
[BOTH growl]
Oh, silly me.
This isn't my room.
Since I'm here,
I might as well give you
these extra blankets
in case you get cold.
[BOTH growls]
[yells]
They're cranky.
[snoring]
[KRILLIN] Yamcha!
Who could sleep
with all that racket?
At least we can get a
jump-start on the competition.
Yep.
Huh?
Hey, aren't those
the guys who held
the top 3 spots in
the last competition?
That's them, all right.
Just my bad luck.
[KRILLIN] I don't
remember our competitors
being this big last time.
It feels great
to be back in red.
I've missed this outfit.
Just between us,
how much stronger
do you think Goku's gotten
in these last three years?
Uh...
I'd say he's somewhere
between tough and invincible.
Hey guys!
Just wanted to
wish you good luck
before the fighting starts.
Fight well!
[ROSHI] Listen, boys,
go in there and
show them how it's done.
I'm counting on you!
Right!
[ANNOUNCER] The Preliminary
Matches are about to begin.
All competitors please
enter the hall at this time.
Wait! Where is Master Roshi?
Huh? He was right here
a second ago.
Knowing him,
I'm sure he's trying
to find a way
to get into the hall.
Oh my gosh! It's Jackie Chun!
Where's my camera?!
Don't worry.
They're selling autographed
postcards in the lobby.
Hello?
Goku. It's good
to see you again.
How are you?
Great! Are you here to fight?
Unless they tell me otherwise.
I sure hope so, sir.
I've been
training for a rematch.
[chuckling]
I'll bet you have!
You've got a fire
in that belly, kid.
Don't ever lose that.
[ROSHI thinking]
As Master Roshi,
I could never get an accurate
measure of your true strength,
but as Jackie Chun,
I know you'll give me
everything you've got.
Good evening and welcome
to the 22nd World
Martial Arts Tournament!
It is my privilege and honor to
preside over this special event,
which has become so popular,
it will now be held
once every three years!
This one promises
to be the biggest yet,
with a record-high attendance of
one hundred eighty-two fighters.
All of you are talented martial
artists in your own right.
However, only one will be
crowned the World's Champion!
[NARRATOR]
Goku is about to face off
against a horde of the fiercest
warriors he's ever encountered,
next time on Dragon Ball!