[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball,
Hero faced off against Junior
in the second round
of the semi-finals.
The importance of
their battle became clear
when Hero revealed
his true identity as Kami,
who had returned to prevent
Junior, his alter ego,
from destroying the world.
[PICCOLO JR.] You know
our fates are intertwined.
You won't do
anything to hurt me!
The humans showed me a way
of getting rid of you
without harming myself.
[PICCOLO JR.] Huh? What-What
are you going to do?!
[NARRATOR] Hero unleashed
the Evil Containment Wave,
in hopes of capturing
Junior's soul.
[NARRATOR] Hero's plan backfired
when Junior surprised him
by reversing the technique.
Ill-prepared for such an attack,
Hero succumbed to
the power of the wave
and was swept into its grasp.
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[NARRATOR] Kami was able
to release Hero's body
and make a final plea to Goku
just before his imprisonment.
[PICCOLO JR. yells]
[GOKU gasps]
[NARRATOR]
With Kami bottled up,
only Goku stands between
Junior and his quest
for global domination.
[CROWD gasping, murmuring]
[laughs]
[GOKU growls]
[ANNOUNCER whimpers]
[gasps]
Hero appears to be unconscious!
[ANNOUNCER]
One...
Two...
[ANNOUNCER]
Three...
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[PICCOLO JR. thinking]
You can count all day,
but it won't do you any good.
Without Kami guiding him, Hero
is just like any other human,
a worthless shell.
Kami's fate is in my hands now
and I shall keep him safe inside
this bottle for all eternity.
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
Nine...
Ten!
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER] Junior wins
the match by knock out
and will now advance to
the championship round!
And his opponent will be Goku!
[CROWD cheers]
What on Earth is going on?
Beats me.
[ROSHI thinking]
I've seen this before.
Goku?
[GOKU growling]
[GOKU thinking] Kami! He's
trapped in that bottle!
You won't get away with this!
Hero! Hero, are you all right?
Come on, please! Wake up, Hero!
Hero, can you hear me?
Please wake up!
Can you hear me? Hero! Hero!
[HERO grunts]
Oh.
You're all right. Welcome back!
--[CROWD applauds]
--[HERO stammers]
[applause continues]
Ah! What's-What's going on?
Did I miss something?
Is this where the Martial Arts
Tournament is supposed to be?
[ANNOUNCER gasps]
Yes it is. You must have
banged your head pretty hard.
[GOKU growls]
[PICCOLO JR.]
Hm-hm.
[HERO]
I think I better find a seat.
[CROWD applauds]
Excuse me. Excuse me.
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
[HERO thinking] This doesn't
make any sense, not at all.
All I was doing was getting
some soda and some pickles--
--[BOY] Hey, Dad!
--[HERO gasps]
What a great fight!
[HERO]
What?!
Yeah! Wow! I didn't know
you could fight!
I have the strongest
dad in the world!
[ANNOUNCER]
Next up, the final round,
as Goku and Junior battle
for the championship.
The most spectacular,
unprecedented match
is expected to take
place here today.
So get ready!
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER]
The fight will begin
following a
ten minute intermission.
Intermission is for weaklings!
I'll be right back.
[OOLONG]
Wait, I--
Where is he going?
How should I know? But he's
been leaving every five minutes!
[BULMA] That's strange. What's
more important than the fight?
Knowing that mischievous
man like I do...
...he's probably out
looking for a date.
[OOLONG laughs]
Put a sock in it, oinker,
or, so help me, I will!
[whimpers]
Everyone gang up on the pig.
[PUAR giggles]
[thunder rumbles]
[thunder rumbling]
Troubles, boy?
No, just hand over the bottle.
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
What bottle? Oh, you mean this
little thing? You want it?
Give it!
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
[thunder rumbles]
Anything you desire.
[chuckles]
[PICCOLO JR.]
Here.
Ooh! Ah, ah!
[PICOOLO JR. chuckles]
[GOKU growls]
--Hah!
--[ALL gasp]
[gulps]
[thunder cracks]
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
Sorry, my hand must have
slipped. How clumsy of me!
[laughs]
Whatever will you do now?
You can have it, but you'd have
to kill me. And he'd die, too.
[thunder cracks]
Hope you're prepared
for lots of pain.
I'm assuming Kami covered
that in your training.
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
Huh...?
Huh?
[GOKU growls]
[PEOPLE yelling]
For once I'm lost, Goku.
Explain it to me.
Yes, it's pretty obvious
that Junior would like nothing
more than to rip you to shreds.
So, what's the history
between you two?
Tell us what's going on!
I gather from his bad looks
and his bad attitude
that he must be a
member of Piccolo's tribe.
Come on, Goku, tell us.
Uh... It's difficult.
[YAMCHA] Is there
something you're not allowed
to tell us about?
[KRILLIN]
Don't be silly.
[CHICHI]
Let us help you.
Oh no! Is he--
[GOKU]
Junior is...
[gulps]
...King Piccolo.
[thunder cracks]
But that's impossible, Goku! It
can't be! You exterminated him!
I'm completely lost here.
Help me to understand,
because this just
doesn't make any sense!
Didn't you destroy Piccolo
and save the world?!
Yes, I killed him.
[GOKU growls]
[PICCOLO growls]
I'm coming at you with
everything I've got!
Good luck! I'll block it!
[GOKU growls]
[PICCOLO growls]
It's time for
your terror to end!
[GOKU yells]
[PICCOLO yells]
[PICCOLO groans]
He's won for now but my legacy
on this planet will survive!
[PICCOLO grunts]
Huaah!
Good luck, my son.
Get revenge for my demise.
Destroy all of my enemies!
[grunts, groans]
[GOKU screams]
[GOKU]
According to Kami,
the egg King Piccolo released
contained his entire essence.
And Junior hatched
from that egg,
so he must be King Piccolo
reincarnated.
It's strange, but Junior
seems to possess greater powers
than his father.
One way or another, I must
find a way to stop him!
[thunder cracks]
My rain dance worked.
Yeah, right.
So, make it stop.
[ROSHI] I never thought we'd
have to face another Piccolo.
No matter what we do,
he always seems to return.
But wait, wasn't it
Piccolo who emerged
when Hero was
struck by the wave?
Perhaps it's a trick.
What if Junior got ambitious
and captured Piccolo
so he could take over as ruler?
[GOKU] The person you saw
resembles King Piccolo,
but it wasn't him.
[TIEN] Well, it's not like
there's a lot of
Piccolo look-alikes
running around.
Whoever he is,
he must be related.
--[GOKU] Mm-hm.
--[KRILLIN] Just tell us!
He only masqueraded as
Hero to get to Junior.
Who is he?
His brother?
His mom?
He's Kami.
--[gasping]
--[KRILLIN] Who's he?
You see, Kami and King Piccolo
were born together as one.
[GOKU]
Piccolo is pure evil.
Kami cast him aside, creating
two beings, one good, one evil.
They are connected. If one dies,
they both suffer the same fate.
That's crazy!
That explains it.
The Evil Containment Wave, it's
the only thing Kami could use
to vanquish Piccolo without
sacrificing himself, anyway.
Too bad it backfired.
Tien Shinhan, is it possible for
Kami to escape from the bottle?
Could we free him?
If you can remove the cork, yes.
But the only way to get to the
bottle is down Junior's throat.
Then it's impossible!
It's not like Junior's
just gonna cough it up.
He's extraordinarily strong!
Krillin's right. Even if
we all fought him together,
our combined strength would
be insufficient to stop him.
You're forgetting one thing,
Tien, Goku's increased strength.
I'll stop Junior. I promise.
To bear such a burden,
it's unfair, Goku.
But since the Evil
Containment Wave failed,
you are our last chance.
I think Junior knows
you are a threat,
that's why he's
come to stop you.
[PICCOLO JR.]
That's quite a story.
It's Piccolo!
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
When it comes to being
a nuisance, Goku excels.
No one is more
troublesome than he.
Perhaps your savior would
have a little glimmer of hope,
had he not been so
lazy during his training.
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
Your friends think
you have skill,
but we both know the truth.
You were just a little
boy who got lucky.
But three years is a long time,
and I have grown stronger.
You're not the only one.
[laughter]
[PICCOLO JR.]
Keep up the brave facade.
Once I've dispatched
you from this world,
it and all your friends
will be mine!
And there's nothing
you can do about it!
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[PICCOLO JR.]
The intermission is over.
Come, it is time
I fulfilled my destiny!
[ANNOUNCER]
Ladies and gentlemen,
your patience is
about to be rewarded.
The final match of the 23rd
World Martial Arts Tournament
begins now! Welcome
the contestants!
Goku and Junior!
[CROWD cheering]
Are these great seats or what?!
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
Goku, you're the greatest!
Hey, stop shouting.
Who will be the next
Master of Martial Arts?!
[CROWD cheering]
Don't look so sad, Goku.
You won't have to say
goodbye to your friends.
I'll send them to
oblivion to meet you!
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
Goku, don't listen to him!
I know you can defeat him.
You just have to!
I promise to do my best,
but he is one strong adversary.
You'd better!
Goku, you'd better not
get yourself hurt!
I don't want to become a widow
before I'm even married. Okay?!
[chuckles]
I'll do my best!
Good luck, Goku!
The world is counting
on you! No pressure!
[ANNOUNCER] The crowd is
getting extremely anxious,
and it's no surprise!
After all, these two warriors
have one thing in common:
They're both superhuman!
Cover your heads and get ready!
[KRILLIN thinking]
I know Goku won't let us down.
He's strong, but Junior
may be stronger!
The entire world
is at stake here!
[ROSHI thinking]
Good luck.
[ANNOUNCER]
No one knows what may happen
during the course of
such a sensational battle,
but these two warriors
are sure to entertain you!
[chuckles]
You should feel honored.
Why is that?
Because I am your executioner!
We're with you, Goku!
Pummel him!
[ANNOUNCER] Ready... on my
mark... get set... begin!
[PICCOLO JR. yells]
[GOKU yells]
[BOTH growling]
[BOTH grunt]
[PICCOLO JR. bellows]
[GOKU yells]
--[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
--[GOKU grunts]
[groans]
--Haah!
--Aaah!
[GOKU, PICCOLO JR. grunting,
blows landing]
Looks like it's an even match!
You're right.
Goku!
[gasping]
[PICCOLO JR. bellows]
[grunting continues]
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
[grunting, growling]
[PICCOLO JR. yells]
[CROWD gasping]
--Yaah!
--[PICCOLO JR. grunts]
[laughs]
--Haah!
--[GOKU screams]
--No!
--Goku!
Huwaaah!
[GOKU screams]
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[ANNOUNCER screams]
[CROWD screaming]
--[ANNOUNCER whimpers]
--[CROWD gasping]
[chuckles]
[ANNOUNCER] It appears that
Goku is down for the count!
--[CHICHI gasps]
--Get up!
Goku!
[ANNOUNCER]
One... two... three...
[NARRATOR] After a rousing
start, the final battle
of the tournament
has ground to a halt.
[ANNOUNCER]
Five...
[NARRATOR] Goku's endurance
seems to have failed him
against Junior's
superior powers.
Will Goku recover in time,
or is this the beginning of the
end for him and everyone else?
Find out next time,
on Dragon Ball!
[ANNOUNCER]
Eight...