[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball,
Mercenary Tao returned
as a vengeful cyborg
bent on destroying Tien
Shinhan in the first match
of the World Martial
Arts Tournament.
However, one blow from
Tien ended his evil plot.
Love was in the air as Goku
swept his opponent
off her feet...
After identifying herself as
ChiChi, Goku's childhood friend,
the two quickly became
engaged to be married...
Goku was confused, but the
crowd certainly approved.
[NARRATOR]
The third match saw Junior,
King Piccolo's alter ego,
take on Krillin...
Junior assumed his
victory would be swift,
but Krillin's fighting skills
took him by surprise.
[PICCOLO JR. gasps, groans]
[yelps]
[KRILLIN chuckles]
[NARRATOR] It seemed both
warriors were evenly matched.
That is, until Junior threatened
to unleash his full power.
[PICCOLO JR.] I shall give you
my full power. Unrestrained!
[NARRATOR] Krillin responded
with unflinching determination
as Junior escalated the
match into an all-out war.
And now, the battle continues!
[KRILLIN panting]
[KRILLIN grunts]
Goku... How powerful do you
think Junior really is?
[GOKU]
I think we're about to find out.
[CROWD whispering]
[BULMA whimpers]
That Junior guy
gives me the creeps.
He's just staring at Krillin.
I've seen walls that are
more exciting than this.
[TIEN thinking] Amazing...
His spirit energy is so strong.
I can actually see his aura.
[chuckles]
Be smart, Krillin.
Take this chance I'm
offering you to withdraw.
Challenging me is a mistake.
In your dreams!
[ANNOUNCER]
Uh-oh. It looks like things
are heating up in the ring!
Attempting to
scare his opponent,
Junior has advised Krillin
to withdraw from the match.
[chuckles]
Stop!
Stop laughing!
[yells]
[KRILLIN grunting]
[KRILLIN]
Huh?
[KRILLIN grunting]
[KRILLIN growls]
[KRILLIN panting]
Ha! You are amusing.
Where's that real power
you were bragging about?!
Ah, feisty. Are you sure
you're ready for it?
I can handle anything you can
dish out! Come on! Ha, ha!
[KRILLIN]
Ya!
[grunts]
[growls]
This is gonna hurt a
little bit. But rest assured,
I won't kill you...
[PICCOLO JR. thinking]
Not yet.
But sooner or later, you will
interfere with my plans
for world domination. [laughs]
And that's when I'll strike,
and you will cease to exist!
[ROSHI]
Hm...
[CROWD murmuring]
[KRILLIN thinking] What in the
world is he going to do?!
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
[grunts]
[PICCOLO JR. grunts. laughs]
[whimpers]
[PICCOLO JR. yells]
What!?
Krillin, move!
[yelps]
[KRILLIN groans]
[laughs]
Krillin!
[yells]
[KRILLIN groans, screams]
You should've quit!
[KRILLIN thinking]
This'll be my last chance.
I'd better make it count!
[KRILLIN]
Ka... Me... Ha... Me...
It's over, Krillin!
[KRILLIN]
Ha!
It worked!
Hm?! Where did he go?!
Behind you, Krillin!
It's a trap!
[PICCOLO JR.]
Looking for me?
[KRILLIN yelps]
[KRILLIN groans]
[ANNOUNCER whimpers]
[GOKU gasps]
K-Krillin!
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[PICCOLO JR.] How disappointing;
I didn't want to kill him.
Not before breaking
every bone in his body!
[gasps]
--[KRILLIN grunts]
--[PICCOLO JR. gasps]
--No... it can't be!
--[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER]
Krillin is back on his feet!
Brace yourselves, for it seems
this fight isn't over yet!
[laughs]
That's better.
I'm done.
[ANNOUNCER]
After showing more stamina
than any fighter could
hope to muster,
Krillin has decided
to stand down.
Therefore, under
tournament guidelines,
Junior wins the match.
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER] Although he lost,
Krillin's skill and bravery
has given us one of the most
breathtaking performances
ever seen in this ring!
Krillin, that was
a fantastic match!
You've made great progress.
I'm really amazed
by your technique!
Yeah, the only thing
missing was a win.
[CROWD cheers]
Oh, boy! Way to go Krillin!
Now that's what I call
self-improvement!
Good work!
The journey you've made
since arriving at my
island is amazing!
Who's the goof?
Better help him.
[KRILLIN coughs]
Yeah... thanks.
Ah! You're the great
Master Roshi... right?
[ROSHI]
Some people call me that...
Master... My name's Krillin
and I've come all the way
from a village in the East...
Please allow me
to be your student
and learn to fight like you...
[KRILLIN giggles]
[ROSHI thinking] You should
feel proud, Krillin...
I certainly do.
What a struggle! You handled
it like a champion!
[PICCOLO JR. thinking]
Who would've guessed that
that runt had it in him?
Conquering this world may be
more difficult than I thought.
[ANNOUNCER] Repairs on the
ring are now complete.
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER] The stage is now set
for our fourth and final match
before the semi-finals begin.
If the last fight
is any indication,
this one should be a doozy!
Let's turn our attention
to the fighters.
What makes this match so unique
is the diversity
of its players...
Experienced warrior, Yamcha,
takes on novice, Hero!
[HERO laughs]
Wow, so many people!
I guess they'll let
anyone fight these days.
Nah, I'll bet he's an actor.
Hey, I may have
struggled to stay alive,
but you'll have to
struggle to stay awake.
You're just jealous.
Luck of the draw...
This won't take long.
I'll be back in a minute.
[CROWD cheers]
[PUAR] Good luck, Yamcha! You're
the best! The B-E-S-T, best!
He knows how to spell!
I almost feel sorry for that
guy having to fight Yamcha.
I don't think this'll
take very long.
Right. One punch from Yamcha,
and it's lights out!
[giggles]
[OOLONG grumbles]
I'm very honored that you would
take the time to fight me.
[YAMCHA]
Huh?
Yeah... No problem.
It's kinda what I do.
Yamcha must be one of
Goku's close friends.
It's too bad he's fighting that
nerd. There's no way he'll win.
[ANNOUNCER]
Ready contestants... And begin!
[YAMCHA thinking]
He's so silly.
That's an interesting
technique you got there.
Feel free to attack
whenever you're ready.
Okay. I appreciate
your kindness.
No problem.
Ya know, I can't help but notice
how serious you've
been lately...
Is, uh, something the matter?
You used to be so cheerful.
Sorry... I've been preoccupied.
I have a strange
feeling about Hero.
Oh.
Don't worry... Everyone here
thinks he's strange.
That about does it
for the warm up.
I'm limber and ready for action.
All right, go ahead.
Let's see what you got.
[HERO yelling]
[laughing]
That guy makes a great clown!
Yamcha... Go easy on him, okay?!
[HERO yells]
Ya!
[yelps]
[yells]
[CROWD murmuring]
[CROWD laughing]
[ANNOUNCER]
In a moment of pure slapstick,
Hero lost his balance,
accidentally kicking
Yamcha's side in the process.
Who knew clumsy could be
such an effective weapon!
[laughs]
For someone who can't fight,
you're doin' pretty good...
With moves like that,
who knows what's next.
Uh, yes. Thank you. I mean,
sorry. Now I'm embarrassed, I...
[CROWD laughing]
[YAMCHA thinking]
I'm the one who's embarrassed!
This fight should have
been over before it began.
I'd better end this now, while
I still have some credibility!
Listen, Hero, you seem like a
nice guy, but this is a match.
So why don't we get back to it
and save the laughter
for after the fight.
It'll be all over
soon, I promise.
[YAMCHA thinking] I don't
wanna hurt the old fella.
I'll just kick him
out of the ring.
[yells]
[YAMCHA screams]
[yelping]
[YAMCHA screaming]
[CROWD laughs]
[ANNOUNCER]
Ooh! That looked painful.
Who would have thought
Yamcha could fall victim
to circumstance a second time?
So much for experience.
At this rate,
accident-prone Hero will
chalk up another win in no time.
[chuckles]
Since this was a
self-inflicted injury,
we will forgo the countdown
and allow poor
Yamcha to recover.
[CROWD laughing]
Oh boy, poor Yamcha.
That's a bad hit, but
he'll recover... Right?
His body, but not... his pride.
[ROSHI thinking] Hero...
Nothing happens by accident.
[YAMCHA whimpering]
Ha-How nice of Yamcha to give us
a preview of his victory dance.
Let's show him our support
with a big round of applause.
Audience!
[CROWD cheers]
[YAMCHA thinking]
I trained three years for this?
Say, that was a toughie.
Maybe you should've
warmed up first...
I can give you a few pointers...
I have some.
Ha, ha, ha, I appreciate your
concern, but as you can see,
I'm in fantastic shape!
Oh, I understand...
Yeah, don't worry...
Accidents happen
to me all the time.
It must be very difficult
struggling in one's
chosen profession.
You seem awfully confident,
especially for someone
who has so little
experience in the ring.
You don't really expect
to beat me, do you?
I'm an optimist.
[laughs]
Optimism is great...
But to defeat me,
you'd need nothing
short of a miracle.
Miracles happen every day.
Come on, you're not a fighter.
Don't be so sure. What you see
isn't always what you get...
And besides, I've done
a good job so far.
Yeah... When it comes
to luck, you're powerful.
Thanks. So, are you
ready for a surprise?
[YAMCHA]
Uh-huh...
Watch.
[YAMCHA groans]
[gasping]
[YAMCHA groaning]
Who are you?!
[HERO chuckling]
You were paying so much
attention to my theatrics,
you never realized the
subtle moves I was making...
Didn't your master
ever teach you,
that you should never judge
power by appearance?
If you take nothing else
from this fight...
remember the golden rule.
Perception is a great defense.
I was right. It's all an act.
I'll bet even his name is phony.
[whimpering]
[YAMCHA]
I see what you mean.
Your act was very
convincing... It fooled me.
Yeah. I'm good.
Oh, yes... When it comes
to lies, you're a master!
Doh...?
I don't believe in using
deception as a tool...
I fight my battles
the old-fashioned way!
Poor boy. And I thought
I was an optimist...
You must enjoy humiliation.
[yells]
All right. We'll do it your way.
It's certainly
more entertaining.
Say hi to my Wolf-Fang Fist!
[yells]
[HERO]
No.
Nuh-uh.
[gasps]
[yells]
Forgot something.
[YAMCHA groans]
Never leave your
feet unprotected.
[gasping]
Who... is this guy?
Where'd he come from?
Don't stop now...
Is that all you've got?
[NARRATOR] The mysterious Hero
is obviously a skilled fighter,
but who is he really?
Will Yamcha's skill be
enough to defeat him?
Find out, as their
match continues,
next time on Dragon Ball.