[laughs]
I'll get you, kitty!
You're fast!
[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball,
Goku began a rigorous
training program
to prepare himself for the next
World Martial Arts Tournament,
and his meeting with
King Piccolo's alter ego,
Goku attempted
to outrun lightning.
The hero rejoiced
over his supposed victory,
until the truth
became shockingly clear.
Goku took a more subtle
approach to his problem
by clearing his mind
of all worry
and focusing on
the world around him.
Slowly he became attuned to the
rhythm of his environment and,
with help from Master Mutaito,
learned his spiritual energy
was a mighty tool,
powerful enough
to cut through fire.
[NARRATOR] But his attempt
to cut through water
was unsuccessful,
leaving Popo and Kami
in doubt of his potential.
Unwavering,
Goku continued to practice
with a young Turtle Hermit,
who he met through time travel.
Will Goku pass this new trial?
The answer is coming up next!
[groans]
[yawns]
[GOKU] Hello, Popo.
Would you mind
being my fighting
partner once in a while?
[POPO]
Hm?
A bit early. You're still
working on your mental training.
Mmm. I understand, Popo.
But, I'd still prefer
a sparring partner.
[POPO]
Hm...
Aah!
[POPO]
Given the proper stimulus,
anything can flourish.
[POPO] Oh, I've come up
with a marvelous idea!
You wish to continue
your training, correct?
[GOKU]
Mhm!
Then I have a solution. I will
provide you with a partner.
Really? Great!
Is he going to be strong?
He'll be as strong as you are.
Perfect!
Give me your head for a moment.
Uuuh... Like this?
[yells]
What did ya do that for?!
All will soon be made clear.
Your practice begins at noon.
[GOKU] I can't wait to meet
my new sparring partner!
Whoever Popo gets, I hope
he's strong and dedicated;
Someone like me.
[patting, fabric rustling]
Hmmm. Hm!
[birds chirping]
[ALL grunting]
[panting]
Korin's legend... Is he
really that famous?
Believe me, Yamcha,
I was skeptical at first,
but it's true.
Korin is more than
just a person.
It's a sacred land deep
in the woods to the west.
One who successfully climbs
Korin's Tower will meet him.
He's said to be the greatest
Martial Arts Master of all time.
[ALL grunting]
Deep in the woods?
It doesn't sound like
anyone knows where
his tower is exactly.
That's true. All we know
is to head to the west.
[TIEN grunts]
[murmuring]
--[TIEN, YAMCHA grunt]
--[OLD FARMER] Uuh!
Uh! Uh! Uuh?
[car engine revs]
[upbeat music plays
from car stereo]
[MAN whistes]
--[KRILLIN panting]
--[MAN] Hm?
[continues panting]
[CHIAOTZU panting]
[MAN]
Hm?!
[MAN yelling]
[MAN whimpers]
[grunting]
Do we always have to
pick the hardest path?
Just think of it as
part of our training.
[grunting]
Ah! Hm.
[humming]
That's it!
[grunting quickly]
[POPO]
Ah! All done!
[GOKU] Hey Popo! When am I
going to meet my new partner?
Be patience, young one!
[grunting]
Mmmm?
Uuh...
Uh... Popo, is this--
is this my partner?
He doesn't look
very strong to me.
You may be surprised.
Uuh.
[POPO] There are no rules
to speak of in this match.
Simply continue fighting
until one of you gives up.
Hmm.
[GOKU] I can attack him
as much as I want to?
Correct.
[laughs]
Thank you!
He doesn't say much, does he?
[POPO]
You may begin!
[grunts]
I can't sense anything from
him. How can he be so calm?
[grunts]
Wow!
[chuckles]
[wails]
It's like fighting a mirror.
He moves the same as me!
Mm?!
[GOKU] The air is
very thin up here,
but he isn't
out of breath at all!
[MR. POPO blowing air]
[chuckles]
--[baloon pops]
--[GOKU] Aah!
Aaah!
[groans]
You should never allow
outside influences
to distract from a fight.
You're a worthy
opponent, all right.
Ah!
[grunts]
It's called the
Afterimage Technique...
Isn't it neat?!
[GOKU laughs]
Blah-ha-ha-ha!
Nah-na!
[laughs]
[groans]
How'd you know where I was?
That was impossible!
Aaah!
Ah-aah! Okay, I've had
just about enough of this!
Ah! Ooh!
[chuckles]
Uah!
[yells]
Ta-da! Surprised?!
[whimpers]
P-Po-Popo! What is that?!
It's a doll that looks
and reacts like you.
I brought it to life
with water and clay.
It's a fascinating technique!
A doll! No wonder I didn't
sense any life from him!
You may continue now.
Hey, wait!
Fine! I'll join you!
[distant fighting]
This should be interesting.
This is crazy!
I can't be beaten by a doll!
Aah!
[laughs]
[yells, groans]
[groans]
[GOKU] The doll knows
something I don't.
I can't see his moves
but he can see mine.
[POPO]
Now you understand.
Your Spiritual Energy
provides a trail
that the doll
can easily follow.
[GOKU] Maybe I've been giving
him the wrong kind of energy!
Ka... Me...
Ha... Me...
Ha!
Oh no! He used
the Afterimage! Aah!
[hoarse exhales]
Aah!
[groans]
I was wrong, Popo.
We're not the same.
He's much stronger than me.
Listen to me, Goku. It's as
I've told you before, dear boy.
Your speed and skill are
matched evenly with the doll,
only you haven't
finished your mind training.
[GOKU]
Mind training.
[POPO]
Mhmm.
A warrior's strength is
always important in a battle,
but it is not enough.
The mind is also
a powerful weapon
and must be developed
just like your muscles.
If you do not master
your mind training,
you will never be able
to defeat the doll.
I won't be beaten!
Not by a doll!
I have to win.
I'll never give up.
You missed my point.
[GOKU yells]
Don't be hasty. You'll only
waste valuable energy.
Just calm down.
[GOKU grunts]
I have to remain calm.
That's it...
Just free your mind.
Incredible! He's so calm.
I can't sense anything.
Something about that doll
reminds me of Popo.
I have to clear my mind.
Yes, you must.
It's very important.
[GOKU]
Come on, focus!
If I can let go
and concentrate,
I should have
a fighting chance.
That's what
you've done, isn't it?
[GOKU] Shake if off!
Every thought.
Hm?!
[GOKU groans]
You can't mimic the doll.
Shake off all negative thoughts.
This is most unexpected--
and if nothing changes soon,
you might lose
more than just this fight.
I'm trying, but we're
just too much alike!
[panting]
[yelling]
[breathing slows]
[GOKU grunts]
Ooh!
Mm?
I-I did it! I hit him! Uh!
Hmm.
Uh--aah!
That's not calm,
that was lucky. Concentrate!
I have... to remember...
how I did that!
[inhales deeply]
[exhales deeply]
♪
[bellows]
[running footsteps]
Uuuah...
I did it! I mastered my mind
training and defeated the doll!
Not exactly.
[GOKU]
Huh?
It was just good timing.
The doll's energy ran out.
[GOKU]
Uuuh...!
Uuuh...
I thought I defeated him
with my skills.
No, you still
need more training.
[GOKU groans]
[thud]
[snoring]
[YAMCHA, CHIAOTZU
breathing deeply]
[NARRATOR]
Yamcha and the others
continue their long trek
to Korin's Tower.
Will they make it?
And if so, will Korin
agree to train them?
With less than
three years before
the next World Martial
Arts Tournament,
will Goku be able to
complete his training in time?
It's a race our hero
cannot afford to lose,
for waiting to challenge
him at the competition
will be none other than
Piccolo's alter ego.
Stay tuned for the next
adventure on Dragon Ball!