[NARRATOR]
Three years have passed
since Goku defeated
King Piccolo.
[NARRATOR]
It is time once again
for the World Martial
Arts Tournament.
Catman, is that one word or--
[CAT MAN]
Two.
[NARRATOR] Fighters from
across the globe
have gathered to compete
in the prestigious event.
[OLD MAN chuckles]
Those of you who wish to
take part in the tournament
must complete your
registration forms today.
Fighters who miss the
deadline will be ineligible
to participate in tomorrow's
preliminary schedule.
Thanks.
[LAUNCH]
Awe...
[MAN] Just can't wait to
see some of this fighting!
They're late, all of them.
Let's hope it didn't
slip their minds.
I didn't have a chance
to remind them.
Awe...
Don't fret. I doubt any
of them would forget this.
[ROSHI] Still,
it has been three years.
That's a long time.
[LAUNCH]
Too long.
[tires screech]
[taxi door clicks]
Ah!
--[ROSHI] Oolong, Puar, hello!
--[OOLONG, PUAR chuckle]
Hey guys! Long time no see!
Master Roshi!
It's so good to see you!
[ROSHI chuckles]
And you're looking
well fed, Oolong.
I think your ears
have grown a bit.
Mmm. Actually, I had them
reduced a little.
[PUAR laughing]
Don't worry. I'm sure
the others will notice.
To be honest, it's not
my ideal conversation!
Ooh...
[romantic music plays]
[chuckles]
Oh! [giggles]
[yells]
Launch! Has it really
been three years?
Bulma!
Have the um, boys arrived?
Not yet.
[chuckles]
What do you think
of my new dress?
[LAUNCH]
It's absolutely stunning!
It certainly fits
in all the right places.
Is that cashmere? Let me feel.
Oh! Hands off, Roshi!
[yelping, yelling]
You're as strong as ever!
You haven't changed one bit!
By the way, do you know
what happened to Yamcha?
I thought he was
coming with you.
He did return to the
West City for a short while,
but then he
left again soon after.
He left to train all by himself.
That's right! By himself!
[laughs]
Yamcha too, huh?
So did Krillin.
He never came back afterwards.
Uh... What's up with that?
They grew up,
followed Goku's example,
and set out on their own.
They must be very strong now.
I can't wait to see them!
[ROSHI]
Mhmm!
[GIRL]
Balloon! My balloon!
[GROUP]
Hm?
[crying]
Balloon!
[sobbing]
There now.
Don't cry little girl.
I'll get your
balloon down for you.
[GIRL]
Mm? Mhmm!
[BULMA]
Here, hold this.
[BULMA grunting]
I can't... reach it.
Uuh!
[grunting]
Oolong, why don't you
give it a try?
What do you want?
If you can't reach it,
what makes you think I can?
Couldn't you turn yourself
into a ladder or something?
Oooh! It's raining.
[ROSHI] Hold on a second.
I've got an idea! It's simple.
I'll give you a boost and
then you grab the balloon.
Yes? No?
Uh, maybe?
Yeah, right!
Uh! Just trying to help.
[MAN]
Hey guys!
[ROSHI]
Heh?
Is this a friend of yours?
No. Oolong, do you
know who this is?
[OOLONG]
Mn-mm.
Puar?
[PUAR]
No. Un-huh.
[LAUNCH]
Huh?
[gong chimes,
dark dramatic music plays]
Here you are, Bulma.
Mm. Who--How do you
know who I am?
Master Roshi, I'm pleased
to see you again.
All of you are looking well.
Uh. Master?
[MAN]
Uh-huh.
Where are Krillin
and the others?
Haven't they arrived yet?
You can't be!
No way!
Eh, Goku?
[BOTH yell]
What? O-Of course it's me.
Who else would I be?
Uh.
The rain is starting to let up.
Maybe we'll see the sun
today after all.
[LAUNCH, BULMA]
Aah...
Hey, are you really Goku?
Stop it! Maybe you
can't tell who I am
because of this
thing on my head.
I'll take it off so I'll
look a little more like me.
[BOTH]
Uh...
[BOTH] Ooh...
[whimpers]
[BOTH scream]
Now do you recognize me?
Who else but me
has hair like this?
[BOTH scream]
--[BULMA] Uh...
--[GIRL] Lady?
Balloon.
Uh, oh yeah!
[GIRL]
Thank you!
[giggles]
Funny, I remember you
being a lot taller.
And you used to be much shorter.
Yeah. I guess I've grown
since you last saw me.
[PUAR, OOLONG]
You sure have!
You can't blame us for not
recognizing you right away.
You definitely have
Goku's hairstyle.
Uuh!
Bulma! What happened? It looks
like your lips are bleeding.
No! It's called
lipstick, you moron.
Ooh...
It really is Goku!
Attention! Last call
for applications!
I repeat, last call
Goku, you'd better
hurry up and sign in!
Yes sir. Have Krillin and
the others done so already?
[ROSHI]
They're not here yet.
Hmmm... Okay.
I'll be right back.
I still can't believe it.
It's just amazing!
It's unbelievable!
Who would have thought
Goku could grow up to be
so tall and handsome?
Just wait! I'm sure Yamcha
will look even better!
You really think so?
Ugh! What am I, a coat rack?
[bird chirping]
[GUIDE] The application booth
will soon be closing.
Those who have not
signed in, please hurry.
[ROSHI clears throat]
Uh, I have a few
friends that seem to
have been unavoidably detained.
Can I sign in for them?
Sorry, that would be a
direct violation of the rules.
All competitors must complete
their application in person.
Master, what's wrong?
[ROSHI]
Mm.
One of them, Tien Shinhan,
is defending champion.
Mm. Rules are rules.
All right. How long do we
have before you close down?
Five minutes.
Five?! Minutes?!
[LAUNCH gasps]
I'll go take a look.
[BULMA]
Uuugh!
Hmmm... Uh?
[GUIDE] The application
both will be closing
in three minutes.
Great!
Don't worry!
We will close in two minutes!
[OOLONG grunting]
--[tires screeching]
--[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH sigh]
[BULMA]
Uh...
[ROSHI] I can't believe it.
They're not going to make it.
Puar, any sign of them?
[PUAR]
Mmm.
No, I'm afraid not.
We close in one minute.
Aah!
Oolong, transform into the
guys and sign in for them.
I could do that,
but the problem is
I need one minute to recover
after each transformation,
which means...
I can only be one person.
I might be able to
turn myself into Yamcha.
[ROSHI]
Hmm.
I might could pass
for Tien Shinhan.
How could they
be late for this?
They've only had
three years to get here!
That isn't fair, Bulma.
I feel sorry for them.
[grunts]
It's time.
[ALL gasp]
[GUIDE yawning]
We are now closed.
[ALL sigh]
[ALL gasp]
[yelps]
They're here!
It's Tien Shinhan! He made it!
[KRILLIN]
Hey!
[laughing]
[KRILLIN laughing]
[YAMCHA]
Hey!
--Yamcha!
--Puar!
Well, you'd think we've been
gone a long time or somethin'.
It has been
a long time, Master.
Mhmm!
I know you can't believe it,
Master, but it's true.
I've gotten a lot taller
since you last saw me.
[chuckles]
[ROSHI chuckles]
[GOKU] Krillin!
You look great!
Huh?
This is wonderful!
We're all together again!
Uh, G-Goku? Is that you?
Yeah.
[laughing]
Oh, Goku! It is you!
Oh-ho-ho!
I've missed you!
This is great! I never got
the chance to thank you!
[laughing]
They told me how King
Piccolo's goon killed me,
but you brought me back.
You're incredible, Goku!
I--I just don't know
what to say!
Um. I'm just
happy you're back.
It's good to
be back. Thank you.
[OOLONG laughs]
[YAMCHA] That's Goku?
I can hardly believe it!
[TIEN]
I know.
He's grown up so much.
Yes, and his power
must have grown as well.
Mhm! He was strong, but now
he must be invincible.
This should be an
interesting tournament.
Hm! I can't wait to
show him what I've learned
in the past
three years as well.
I've made hotel
reservations for all of us.
So why don't you all
go get comfortable,
and save your energy
for the match tomorrow.
[ALL]
Hm?
Great, thanks Master Roshi!
Master Roshi, aren't you
going to participate
in the tournament this time?
I think I'll
stand down this time,
and give you boys
a fighting chance.
Wow, Goku, I just can't
get over your height.
I mean, I always thought that
I would be the giant out
of the two of us.
[GOKU]
Really?
[BULMA]
Mm!
Oolong, don't you just
love Yamcha's ponytail?
[OOLONG]
Huh?
Ugh! Why? What do I
look like, a hair-dresser?
[thunder]
[BULMA giggles]
So, tell me all
about your training.
Was it as difficult
as I heard it was?
Yeah. It was very challenging.
[laughs]
[GOKU] Your strength
must have increased a ton!
Well, wait until
you see me fight!
Yeah, I'm sure
you'll be awesome.
[laughs]
I'm sure we'll find plenty
of tough warriors to battle!
Hmm.
[GOKU]
And King Piccolo's alter ego
is sure to be one of them.
[PICCOLO groans]
[KRILLIN] Earth to Goku.
Something wrong?
I'm fine. How's the weather?
[KRILLIN] It's raining again.
How did your training go?
Goku?
[GOKU snoring]
--Um... Goku?
--[GOKU snoring]
[chuckles]
Uh...
Sound asleep!
[snoring]
[humming]
I wish you the
best of luck, Yamcha.
Thanks. You know,
for the past three years,
I've thought of nothing
but this tournament.
I'll finally show them
all what I'm made of.
Tien Shinhan. Are you okay?
I'm all right.
The time has come at last
to settle the matter with Goku.
Okay.
I wonder what sort of
training Goku endured
while he was away?
Hm! It doesn't matter.
I'll still
defeat him in the end.
[car horns honking]
[clock tune chimes]
Mom, I'm going to go look!
[MOTHER sighs]
Son! You'll get wet!
You need an umbrella!
[laughs]
[clock song plays]
[laughing]
[clock song continues]
[laughs]
Oooh! Aah!
[clock song stops]
[people screaming]
[BOTH gasp]
[yells]
[MOTHER screams,
BOY yells]
[BOTH whimper]
I'm eternally grateful, sir.
[MOTHER gasps]
[thunder]
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH scream]
[BOTH snoring]
[snoring]
[people chattering]
[BOTH]
Aah! Aah!
[MAN chuckles]
The preliminary round
is about to begin.
Will all contestants
please report
to the fighting arena
at this time.
Master, did you remember
to bring my uniform along?
No, young man.
Your old uniform
no longer suits you,
both in size and stature.
You've all surpassed my lessons.
What you wear is your own.
It's up to you now.
[GROUP]
Thanks!
[ALL laughing]
[grunting]
[humming]
Ta-da! Eat your heart out!
Isn't it great?
I knew Master Roshi
wouldn't let us
have our old uniforms back,
so I had this one altered.
What do you think?
[YAMCHA]
Hm!
Seems like we know
the same tailor.
[KRILLIN]
Uh! Mmm!
[GOKU]
Me too!
[chuckles]
Oh great. Next thing ya know,
you'll both be
shaving your heads!
[laughs]
Goku! What happened
to your tail?
Oh that? I got rid of it.
[KRILLIN]
Uh...
You see, it turned out that
the moon could be restored
if I lost my tail.
So that's what I decided to do.
[KRILLIN]
Uh...
[YAMCHA]
Hm.
[BOTH chuckle]
Did you ever
find it again? Ha-ha-ha!
[grunts]
Huh? What's the matter?
I was joking.
[GOKU]
Hmm!
With that face, I'd say
he's one of Shen's boys.
Do you know who he is, Goku?
--[TIEN grunts]
--[CHIAOTZU] Huh?
No! He looks like...
But that's... impossible!
[GOKU] Piccolo! I knew you'd
show up sooner or later!
[NARRATOR] Tensions flare as
King Piccolo's alter ego,
Junior, makes his
grand entrance.
How will his presence
affect Goku and the others?
Is Goku strong enough
to defeat the alien?
The World Martial Arts
Tournament begins next time,
on Dragon Ball!