[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball,
Goku flew into a blind rage
upon meeting the mystical Kami,
mistaking him for
the villianous Piccolo.
[GOKU] I should've known
that you were still alive,
you big monster!
[GOKU groans]
It is you who
fails to understand.
--This is not Piccolo.
--Let go of me!
[GOKU growls, gasps]
What do you mean?
There's a good reason
you mistook me for Piccolo.
My name is Kami, and I am indeed
the guardian of this planet,
but it wasn't always that way.
I remained at the Lookout
and became the next Guardian.
Piccolo went down to
Earth to incite disorder...
[NARRATOR]
Goku's fears were put to rest.
Kami agreed to
grant Goku's wish,
on the condition that he train
at the Lookout for three years.
[KAMI] Unfortunately, my powers
will not bring them back.
Uh... Uhh...
The one being that has that
ability is Shenron, the Dragon.
I guess I'll just have to
recreate him,
and let Earthlings use
the Dragon Balls again.
You can really do that, Kami?
[FISHERMAN] You gonna hog the
bathroom all morning, Ahab?
[grunts]
[FISHERMAN]
Well, at least the sun's out.
[yawns]
[gasps]
[AHAB]
What is that thing?!
[BOTH whimper]
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH scream]
[KAMI] Well, Goku, it's time for
me to make good on my promise.
Mr. Popo, please
fetch the Eternal Dragon.
[POPO]
Right away.
Listen, Goku,
you must understand.
Once the dragon's alive,
this is out of my hands.
[GOKU]
Mm-hmm!
[POPO]
Here it is.
[GOKU]
Wha...?
Ah. I didn't realize he was
this badly damaged, Mr. Popo.
Is it possible to fix him?
Yes, it's easy.
Is that really
the Eternal Dragon?
Not exactly. No, not yet.
You see, Mr. Goku, Kami must
first breathe life into it.
It's my job.
But when he was destroyed,
I had decided not to
bring the dragon back.
When I first created
the Dragon Balls,
I did so in order to
encourage acts of bravery
and give the people of
Earth a sense of hope.
But I soon learned that
the hearts of man
are easily corrupted.
People began killing one another
in order to attain
the Dragon Balls.
Their greed and lust for power
turned my noble, pure endeavor
into one of evil.
However...
You've changed my mind, Goku.
I was beginning to believe
that all people
were greedy and
dishonorable, but,
you've shown me that there are
people
that have kind and
untainted minds and hearts.
[YAJIROBE]
Hello up there!
[KORIN chuckles]
--[KORIN yells]
--[YAJIROBE screams]
[YAJIROBE]
What are you doing?!
I was about to
ask you the same thing.
You seem a little jumpy.
You worried about Goku?
Don't be ridiculous.
I just thought
I'd keep an eye out for him
in case he fell down from
that Guardian Lookout, okay?
Right...
You can't fool me. I know you're
a just big softy underneath.
Go away! You're
makin' my head hurt!
[YAJIROBE]
Hmm?
Yajirobe, what is wrong
with your stomach?
Uh, I... I think I over
did it at lunch today.
[KORIN laughs]
Oh, you did, huh? For some
reason I don't believe you.
--[YAJIROBE] S-Stop it!
--[KORIN] Come here!
What are you
hiding under there, huh?
[KORIN]
Ah-ha!
[YAJIROBE whimpers]
Senzus?
Didn't you learn your lesson
the last time this happened?
Bite me, fur-ball!
You're just being stingy.
You'll never get on the
Nimbus behaving that way.
You don't know that! I might!
I'll ride it someday!
You just wait!
Don't hold your breath, okay?!
I'll hold it if I want to!
[KORIN]
Hmph!
Done.
[GOKU laughs]
Stand back, please.
[POPO]
All right.
You, too, Goku.
[yells]
[screams]
Wait! Where is he going?!
He is searching for
the Dragon Balls.
Typically, they must
remain in their stone form
for a full year before the
dragon can be summoned
to grant a wish, but
this time I've decided to
make an exception for you
and your friends, Goku.
Really?
[GOKU] Do you think I could go
and watch my friends
come back to life?
Don't tell me you've already
forgotten your promise
to remain here at the
Lookout and train?
Oh, that's right.
You'll stay for three years.
Then you'll be able to
see your friends again
at the next tournament.
You know about the tournament?
Are you a psychic or something?
There's something
you should know, Goku.
Piccolo will be coming to
the tournament to challenge you.
So you must be prepared.
Piccolo? I thought I killed him!
Are you sure he's alive?!
Unfortunately, I am.
Moments before Piccolo died,
he created an egg
that contained a child,
a virtually identical
replica of Piccolo,
possessing his powers,
his brain,
and his tendencies for evil.
The child is growing
as we speak.
In three years time, he'll be
strong enough to face you again.
I don't believe it!
As long as you are here, Piccolo
won't be able to attack you.
That way you can train
for the next three years
without any disturbances.
Then, you'll be strong enough
to defeat him, perhaps.
I am prevented from
destroying Piccolo myself
in light of a
minor technicality.
The fate of the Earth
rests in your hands
because you are the only
person capable of defeating him.
Understand?
I... I understand.
Can you promise me that, Goku?
[GOKU]
I won't let you down, Kami!
Let's get started!
I'm totally focused now!
[GOKU growls]
Haah!
[GOKU] Um, but first, I have
to pee. Where's the bathroom?
[BOTH gasp]
Down the hall,
first door on your left.
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU] Gotta go, gotta go!
I-I don't know if I can hold it!
Uh, Kami? You and Piccolo
are one entity, right?
So if Goku kills him, he will,
um, I guess, kill you as well?
That is correct.
I have brought all
of this on myself.
I must now answer for it.
No entity can strangle
himself with his own hand,
but I have finally found
a way to rid the world
of the horrors I have caused.
I know this won't
be easy, Mr. Popo,
but you must carry on without me
until another
guardian can be found.
I'm feeling very... perplexed.
Rough workout?
Well, don't work too hard.
We still have three years before
the next tournament, you know.
Yes, I know.
[TIEN] But I'm afraid three
years won't be enough time.
Huh?!
That's a Dragon Ball, right?
[YAMCHA]
Um, yeah. Well, used to be.
[OOLONG laughs]
[OOLONG chuckles]
[BULMA]
Now, what does today feel like?
It'll work, guys. You'll see.
[OOLONG]
Huh? What did you say?
[BULMA]
Oh, nothing.
Hey, what's wrong?
[BULMA gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[YAMCHA gasps]
Did you see that?
What's going on? Why'd it glow?
Yamcha...
Do you think...?
[BULMA]
Mm-hm!
[BULMA giggles]
[BULMA]
Oh, please let this work.
Come on! Come on!
Please, Shenron!
Help us, Shenron!
Come on! Help us!
[ALL scream]
What's happening?!
[PUAR screams]
[BULMA whimpers]
He's really here!
I can't believe it!
He actually came!
[SHENRON growls]
S-Say something.
We thought you'd been
destroyed, Mr. Dragon.
Kami saw that Goku's
purpose was noble.
And so, he chose
to resurrect me.
If I faint, catch me.
Where is Goku?
Kami has chosen Goku
for an important task,
and he is now training
at the Lookout.
You will see him again
at the next tournament.
Who is Goku training with?
Wait. You'll know soon enough.
Now, your wish.
We wish for you to
bring back to life
all of our friends who were
killed by Piccolo
and his monsters!
Krillin, Master Roshi,
and Chiaotzu!
It will be so.
W-Wait a minute.
W-What about all
the other innocent people
that Piccolo killed?
You should help them, too!
Oh, that's a lot of people!
[SHENRON snarls]
Very well, all of the people
who were killed by Piccolo
shall be brought back to life.
[ALL cheer, laugh]
[BOTH gasp]
[BULMA gasps]
[ALL laugh]
[ROSHI chuckles]
[TURTLE gasps]
[TIEN laughs]
[CHIAOTZU laughs]
Your wish has been granted.
Now I must go.
Welcome back, guys!
[ROSHI chuckles]
Was I dead the whole time?
[OOLONG laughs]
Pretty hard to believe,
isn't it?
Yeah it is!
Hooray!
[laughter]
Right now, I bet there are some
really happy people, somewhere.
[cheering]
[MONK]
King Chapa! King Chapa!
You're alive! It's a miracle!
[gasps, screams]
[muffled grunting]
Wow! All of my
wounds are healed!
[KRILLIN] I can't believe
Goku did this for us!
I could marry that guy!
I can sense he defeated Piccolo.
What I don't know is
where he's at right now.
We're not positive,
but the Eternal Dragon said he
was training at Kami's Lookout.
Uh, yeah.
At Kami's Lookout?!
What's the matter?
Is that a bad thing?
No, not at all. It's amazing!
It's just so hard to believe
it's even possible.
What? You know something?
Spill the beans.
I don't like going off
of hearsay,
but if this dragon is correct,
and Goku's training at
the Lookout with Kami--
Well, I guess it would help
if you knew Kami's other name.
Guardian of the Earth.
[ALL gasp]
Well, I sort of remember
something like that being said.
That-That's impossible,
Master Roshi!
You're joking with us, right?
It can't really be the truth!
[ROSHI]
Mm-hm.
It's true. Goku is something
very different from you and I,
and Kami's obviously
recognized it.
To be honest, I'm chopped liver
in comparison to that
monkey-tailed boy.
He's a kid and he's already
surpassing us in strength.
Now that he's
training with Kami,
we'll never catch up with him.
Well then, I'll just have
to train twice as hard,
twice as fast, and twice as long
for the next three years,
that's all.
Yeah, me too!
Me three!
[ROSHI laughs]
Well said!
That's the spirit, guys!
Chins up!
That reminds me, Bulma.
I have a question.
[chuckles]
What?
I was wondering if you...
If you would, uh, give me a
welcome-back smoochie-kissy.
[snarls]
[ROSHI whimpers]
[ROSHI]
How about a handshake?
[GOKU]
Is it okay if I move now?
Stay still, please.
Goku, you must now focus
your mental energy.
I'm bored.
Don't talk. Eyes shut.
[GOKU chuckles]
[YAMCHA grunting]
Thank you, Goku. I'll see
you at the next tournament.
[NARRATOR]
Goku's wish has been granted,
and everyone has
begun their training
for the next tournament.
I have to pee.
Hold it!
[NARRATOR] But will three years
be enough time to train Goku?