[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball:
General Blue bested Goku
by paralyzing him
with his psychic powers.
All seemed lost until
a little mouse showed up
to break the spell.
Apparently, the fearless General
doesn't like furry rodents.
[BLUE yelps]
My eyes!
[GOKU grunts]
[BLUE groans]
[NARRATOR] Goku defeated General
Blue, but it seemed the pirates
would have the last laugh as
the hideout began to collapse.
Yet, the approach
of impending doom
did not deter our hero from
going after the Dragon Ball.
Meanwhile, Bulma
and Krillin opted
for the safe approach
and ran for their lives.
[NARRATOR]
Goku's search was successful.
However, navigating his way
out of the crumbling structure
proved extremely difficult.
Convinced her friend
could not have escaped,
Bulma decided to
leave without him.
[BULMA]
We barely made it out alive
and we were running
as fast as we could.
Goku wasn't going to leave
without that Dragon Ball.
[GOKU grunting]
Alright, let's go!
[KRILLIN]
Oh... Goku, where are you?!
[KRILLIN whimpers]
Goku? Wait a minute! He's okay!
[GOKU grunts]
Goku!
[GOKU groans]
[BULMA gasps]
[KRILLIN] Goku!
[GOKU groans]
Goku! Hey!
Faster!
Come back!
We're over here!
[GOKU grunts]
Quick, get in!
Hurry!
[GOKU laughs]
Hi guys!
[KRILLIN, GOKU grunt]
Let's go!
Faster, Bulma!
[GOKU grunting]
How are you doin'?
That was scary, wasn't it?
[MOUSE squeaks]
Quiet! I'm trying
to concentrate!
We're not out of
the water yet. Huh?
[BULMA, KRILLIN, GOKU scream]
Is it just my imagination
or are the rocks
getting bigger?!
[KRILLIN, BULMA screaming]
I'm too young to die!
[BULMA gasps]
It's blocked!
[KRILLIN]
We're done for!
Uh, hey, maybe we
could go through there.
[BULMA]
Huh? Great eyes, kid!
Perfect! This passage
might lead to the surface!
Hold on, everyone!
We're getting outta here!
[KRILLIN]
Are you sure about this?
It looks like a tight fit.
[KRILLIN, BULMA yelping]
[KRILLIN] A-At least things
can't get any worse!
[BULMA]
You were saying?
[KRILLIN]
It's not fair!
[GOKU]
What's wrong?
[BULMA]
Things just got worse.
Why aren't we moving?
I don't see any bubbles!
No...
...power! Sinking.
[KRILLIN yelps]
[KRILLIN]
It's not fair!
What did I do to deserve this?!
It's not fair! Why? Why?
[BULMA]
I'm too beautiful to die!
[MOUSE squeaking]
Huh?
We've got to do something!
Krillin. This is Mouse.
He saved my life, so make sure
you take good care
of him for me.
Huh? What do I look like,
an animal trainer?!
Now everyone
take a deep breath.
[KRILLIN, BULMA]
Huh?
Goku, what are you doing?
Ka..
Me...
[KRILLIN gasps]
Is he nuts?!
Ha...
[KRILLIN gasps]
[GOKU grunting]
[BULMA gasps]
Me, Ha!
[BULMA grunts]
[KRILLIN grunts]
[BULMA grunting]
[KRILLIN grunting]
[GOKU grunting]
[BULMA grunting]
[KRILLIN grunting]
[GOKU, BULMA, KRILLIN yell]
[GOKU laughing]
Nimbus!
[BULMA yelps]
[KRILLIN yelps]
[GOKU laughs]
Good work, Goku!
Yay! We did it!
[GOKU, BULMA, KRILLIN cheering]
[BLUE chuckles]
[GOKU laughs] Sure feels
great to be back on land!
My sentiments exactly.
I sure am glad to have
a friend like you!
And you were gonna leave him...
[BULMA growls]
[KRILLIN sighs]
Just think, we almost had it.
I could have been a millionaire.
All that treasure!
[BULMA chuckles]
Huh? Bulma!
I got a souvenir.
Whoa!
[GUARD gasps]
Yes, sir! Sorry sir!
It won't happen again, sir!
I was really awake
the whole time!
[KRILLIN] But how in the
world did you get it?
[BULMA laughs]
[GUARD gasps]
Just look at this diamond!
Look at the size of
this thing! It's huge!
That's amazing, Bulma.
I'm glad you showed it to me.
For a minute there I thought
I was gonna have to
start calling you Mr. Bulma.
[BULMA]
It's bigger than the sun!
This beauty would look great
on an engagement ring!
Don't you think?!
Mm-hm...
Oh, I almost forgot
about the Dragon Ball.
[GUARD gasps]
[GOKU gasps]
Oh, no. Three stars?
I really thought this one was
going to be my grandpa's ball.
That wasn't the one
you were looking for?
No!
Are you going to keep
looking for those things
until you find the one that
was your grandfather's?
That's right.
I'm not gonna stop.
Fine. But you'll have
to do it without me!
I'm through. No more
crazy adventures!
I thought you liked
looking for the Dragon Balls.
Isn't that why you came along?
You sort of invited yourself.
I wouldn't have if you
had bothered to mention
the Red Ribbon Army was
trying to destroy you!
[GOKU]
They weren't that tough.
Look how easy it was
to beat General Blue.
[BULMA] If that's your
idea of fun, great.
Me, I'd like to live long
enough to enjoy my diamond.
[GUARD] They took out
General Blue and his forces?!
These kids aren't human!
Anyway, why don't we
continue this conversation
back at Roshi's place.
We even have transportation,
courtesy of the Red Ribbon Army.
I can't go anywhere until I get
something to eat. I'm starving!
[GOKU] Maybe we can find some
food in one of these houses.
Come on!
[GUARD gasps]
[BULMA] Alright. We'll go inside
and get some food and that's it!
This place gives me the creeps.
[beeping]
[BEAR] Headquarters calling
Sector 12, repeat,
Headquarters calling
Sector 12, over.
This is Soldier 23
with the Blue Camp, over.
[BEAR]
Report status, over.
[GUARD whimpering]
[GUARD whimpers]
[BEAR]
Report, over.
[GOKU]
Ah...
[KRILLIN grunting]
[GUARD whimpers]
[GOKU]
Huh...
Hm. Doesn't seem
to be much here.
[KRILLIN]
Uh-huh.
[BEAR]
Headquarters to Blue Camp!
Come in, Blue Camp.
Awaiting transmission.
Respond immediately.
Do you copy, Blue Camp, over.
[BLUE grunting]
[BEAR]
This is a secure transmission.
Awaiting reply.
Request status report, over.
W-Wh-Where is that coming from?
[STAFF OFFICER]
It doesn't make sense, sir,
but according to our radar,
the Dragon Ball
is now in the Blue Camp.
We've lost contact.
I can't get a response.
[RED]
Try again.
Yes, sir.
[RED growls]
What's goin' on over there?!
[BEAR] This is RRA Headquarters
calling Blue Camp.
Are you there, over? Come in.
[GOKU]
RRA?
[BULMA, KRILLIN]
Red Ribbon Army!
[BEAR] Our radar shows the
Dragon Ball is at your location.
Can you confirm that? Over.
Over? Over what?
[KRILLIN gasping]
[BULMA] Goku!
Huh? Identify yourself, soldier!
[GOKU]
Are you a boy or a girl?
[RED growls]
Do you think this is its head?
It's not a person! It's a--
[BULMA, KRILLIN scream]
[CROWD scream]
[RED growls] You idiot, I am
Red! Supreme Commander Red!
You have a funny face.
[RED]
Attention!
Stop shouting!
[CROWD screams]
[RED growls]
Who does this guy think he is?
Do you have any idea
who you're messing with?!
[GOKU]
Nope.
[RED, STAFF OFFICER]
Hm?
[RED]
I am the Red Ribbon Army.
Ow!
[CROWD yells]
[BEAR] It's gone dead, sir.
We've lost communication.
Huh?
Maybe he'll call back.
[GOKU grunts]
Goku, are you crazy?!
He was being too noisy.
Enough! We're leaving!
[GOKU]
What about food?
Starve.
[GUARD whimpers]
Enough with the food!
Hurry up, let's go!
[GOKU]
Okay. I'm ready.
Are you sure you're not hungry?
They've got plenty.
Fly!
[GOKU]
Yippie!
[GUARD grunting]
[GUARD groans]
I've never been so
scared in all my life.
[water dripping]
I'm only in the reserves!
What's the meaning of this?
Explain yourself, soldier!
Yes, sir! There must have
been 100 of them! No, 1,000!
[GOKU]
Mm! Mm! Mm!
Here you go. Take it.
[KRILLIN laugsh]
I hope Master Roshi likes it.
I'm going to offer it
to him as compensation
for the submarine
we destroyed.
Do you think he'll go for it?
Are you kidding me?
Bulma, this is fantastic!
He'll flip out!
With a jewel like that
he could probably buy
1,000,000 submarines or more!
[KRILLIN sniffing]
Now what are you doing?
Oh, you know,
just making sure
it wasn't made of glass.
[BULMA]
Why you little--!
You were not!
I ought to wring your--
[GUARD groans]
[gun fires]
[BLUE]
Hm.
Apology accepted, soldier.
Now, you can sleep all you want.
[BLUE] Where were you
off to in such a hurry?
[BLUE laughs]
I'm coming to get you.
[LAUNCH humming]
[LAUNCH gasps]
Ah-ah-ah-ah... whew.
[ROSHI giggling]
[HEADPHONE VOICE]
Okay, here we go!
Stretch those legs.
Feel the burn!
That's it!
Now everyone, on your knees!
Got a firm grip on
your partner? Gooood!
Now bend forward and back.
And forward, and back.
Get into a rhythm. There you go!
Are you gettin' sore?
Then you must be
doing something right!
Now roll over, on your back!
Okay. Pelvis tucked,
spread your legs wide.
Now lift those legs
up in the air.
Shake, shake, shake
like you just don't care!
Good! Goood!
Oh brother, he's at it again.
[GOKU]
Heeeeeeey!
Huh?
Master Roshi!
Look who's here! Master?
[ROSHI giggling]
[TURTLE]
Hey!
Hey Master Roshi!
Don't bother me
when I'm exercising!
But Master, I thought
you'd wanna know
the kids are back.
Hello!
Hey, we're home!
Heh! Thank goodness
they're all safe!
[ROSHI]
What?! Did I hear you right?
Do you mean to say
you're giving this to me?
[BULMA]
Yep!
Ho-ho! But this thing must
be worth a ton of money!
Yes, sir! I'd say
over a billion zeni.
Bi-Bi-Bi-Bi-Billion zeni?!
Whoa! That's a lot of gem!
That would certainly buy
me a few exercise tapes!
Why I don't even know if I
can count that high, Bulma!
Nice to know you're going to do
something worthwhile with it.
You know, considering we
almost died trying to get it.
That was just
a theoretical example!
Do you really think
it's worth a whole lot?
Don't be silly! Of course it is.
We're talkin' big bucks!
Well, alright. I was kinda
partial to that submarine.
You're not going to turn around
and ask for it
back later, are you?
I would never do that.
Maybe I should hold onto
it for safe keeping...
That way you won't be tempted
to spend it on something
you might not
really want to buy.
Are you insinuating
that I don't make
sound financial decisions?!
Yes.
[ROSHI] Why you no good--
I'm gonna buy myself--
[BULMA] Come on. There's no
point in arguing about it.
She's right, especially since
I'm the one holdin' the gun.
[ALL gasp]
Hand it over before someone...
...gets hurt.
Uh... Hand over what, Launch?
I've already given my
donations this year.
Don't shoot! I surrender.
[LAUNCH growls]
Give it!
Ah! Okay, okay!
[BULMA] Who is that?
[GOKU] Launch.
[LAUNCH]
Thanks.
Launch?
Yeah. You've met
her before, remember?
But she's nice.
[BULMA, GOKU yelping]
Hands up and shut up!
[ALL whimpering]
[LAUNCH]
That completes our transaction.
[LAUNCH laughs]
Later!
She's getting away
with the diamond!
We've gotta find
a way to stop her!
You got a capsule
for that, do ya?
Because if you do,
I'd love to see it.
Don't you have some
kind of 'special powers'
or something you can use
to get her back here?!
Sorry. It doesn't work that way.
If it did, I'd be the
luckiest man alive.
So that's it?
We just give up?
Not at all.
We just have to wait
for her to sneeze again.
She'll change back
into the nice Launch
and bring the diamond back!
The brat's base
must be somewhere
in the vicinity.
[BLUE]
Ah ha! There you are!
[BLUE cackles]
Time to take the Dragon Balls,
just as soon as I
have taken my revenge!
[BLUE yells]
[BLUE yelling]
[BLUE growling]
[BLUE growls]
[BLUE yells]
[ROSHI] Right. She'll be
back, next millenium!
[BULMA]
It's hopeless.
Nooo! That diamond
is mine! I want it!
Bring it back! It's not fair!
Master, please!
Control yourself!
It's okay, Master, I'll go
get you another one.
No! That's impossible!
[BLUE cackles]
There's no need to get so upset.
Life is too short. Well,
at least yours is anyway.
[NARRATOR] What sinister
scheme does the General
have in store for Goku
and his friends?
Beware the chilling
wrath of General Blue
on the next unbelievable
episode of Dragon Ball!