[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball...
Yamcha met his defeat
in the arena known
as the Devil's Toilet.
[NARRATOR]
However, Goku evened the score
by defeating Bandages
the Mummy with one punch.
His next opponent,
Spike, the devil man,
was armed with
his Devilmite Beam,
a lethal weapon that
could destroy a person
by turning their own negative
thoughts against them.
[NARRATOR] Luckily, the beam
had no effect on Goku
since his heart was pure.
Just one more match and then
I can get the Dragon Ball!
[NARRATOR]
The fifth challenger's identity
was concealed behind a mask.
From the first moment they met,
Goku felt a strange familiarity
with his mysterious opponent,
as did Master Roshi.
The young warrior
entered the match
assuming he could defeat
this masked fighter with ease.
[NARRATOR] He was wrong.
Fight him, man!
Destroy!
Goku, are you okay?
He's stronger than I thought!
That move is one of the
most difficult to achieve.
To sustain it for that amount
of time is just incredible!
Who is that guy, Master Roshi?
[BABA] Destroy that kid!
Do you hear me, Masked Man?!
Stop dancing around
the issue and pummel him!
I want to see some good
old-fashioned fighting!
This match has been going on
for over 2 minutes
and no one has
even lost a tooth!
[BULMA] You've lost enough
for all of us, now be quiet!
[BABA] What are you waiting for?
There are no cameras!
Stop posing
and get back to work!
[ROSHI] That pose...
It seems familiar.
I've seen it somewhere
before... but where?
[BULMA] What...?
[ROSHI] Looks like
this match is up in the air!
Please land safe!
Look out!
He's falling!
Yes!
--Goku!
[MASK MAN] Hey, Baba, I can
see your whole palace from here!
Oh, Goku!
Goku, are you down there?
[BABA]
You have until the count of 5.
One! Two! Three!
Four! Five!
[BABA cackles, gasps]
[GOKU growls]
[ALL gasp]
[growls]
[MASKED MAN gasps]
[gasps]
[gasping]
Look out!
Move it!
[MASK MAN thinking] Goku's
training has served him well.
I can't believe he
absorbed that kick...
What has he been eating, lead?!
Was that your best move?
Maybe you should
take some lessons.
[ALL cheering]
[BABA thinking]
My mysterious warrior
may be enjoying this
challenge a bit too much.
There's an uncanny similarity
between their fighting styles.
I don't like it.
[ROSHI thinking] Who is he?
Everything about him
seems familiar.
It's right on
the tip of my mind.
Eh...
Go!
[MASK MAN] Well, I've got
something special for you.
You'll appreciate this.
What?
[MASK MAN] Ka...
Me...
[MASK MAN] Ha...
Impossible!
[MASK MAN] Me...
[MASK MAN] Ka...
[MASK MAN] Ha...
No!
[MASK MAN] Me...
Wait... Stop it!
If that's what I think it is,
things just went
from bad to worse!
[MASK MAN] ...Ha!
[screaming]
[MASK MAN] Huh?
Where is he?!
[MASK MAN] He's learned
the Afterimage technique!
[GOKU] Yoo-hoo!
[GOKU] Hello!
This is fun!
[laughs]
[gasping]
[GOKU] La-la-la-la-la!
[MASK MAN]
That boy definitely gets around.
[ROSHI thinking]
The Kamehameha Wave...
There's only one person who
could be behind that mask,
and that's impossible.
[MASK MAN thinking]
The Afterimage is a
difficult maneuver,
yet he handled it with ease.
I'm amazed at how far he's
come in such a short time.
Get ready! It's my turn!
[MASK MAN laughs]
[MASK MAN] But choosing an
aerial attack was a big mistake.
With no cover and
minimal maneuverability,
he's afforded me ample time
to devise counter-measures,
and left himself wide open
for another dose of pain.
Ka... Me...
[MASK MAN]
Huh? What's he saying?
Ha...
Me...
[MASK MAN]
Speak up, son, I can't hear you.
What was the last part?
[GOKU] Ha!
[ALL yelling]
[MASK MAN] Uh-oh.
[screams]
[yells]
[BOTH grunt]
Get up, get up!
[MASK MAN grunting]
Can you hear me now?
Do you surrender,
or do I have to
give you another punch?
[BOTH laugh]
Yeah!
[BOTH] Yipee!
Now Baba will finally tell us
about the last Dragon Ball!
Right!
--We won! We won!
--Champions!
With that mask on,
I can't tell if
you're asleep or awake.
Say something.
[MASK MAN chuckling]
What? Uhh...
[chuckling continues]
[GOKU] What...?
[GOKU squeals]
[MASKED MAN chuckles]
I think I'm going to... fall...
[MASK MAN chuckling]
Goku!
Goku had him beat!
This isn't fair!
It's not Goku's fault
he loses his power
when someone grabs his tail!
Eh? No, it's not!
But how did Baba's
fighter know about it?!
It didn't help that Bulma
was shouting it out
when we were inside...
Maybe this guy
just got lucky...
[MASK MAN laughs]
[MASK MAN]
Okay. Now that I've got you,
what should I do with you?
Uh... You could put me down.
I'm feeling dizzy.
[BABA laughs]
Looks like you finally
met your match,
which means I won't be showing
the Dragon Ball after all.
Please...
There's something definitely
fishy about all of this...
This masked man looked like
he knew what he was doing.
How the heck did he
know about Goku's tail?
Curious...
[YAMCHA]
This guy fights just like Goku,
and he seems to know
everything about him!
You're right...
That's how he can
anticipate Goku's moves.
And why they
have the same powers.
[ROSHI] Yes!
What are you
getting at, Master?
Are you saying
you know who this guy is?
[ROSHI]
Oh yes... I believe I do.
[ROSHI] Yamcha!
Yeah?
You were right.
This walking enigma knows
everything... about Goku.
[gasping]
What do you mean?
Well, look at them.
They're like mirror images
of one another.
Tactically speaking, of course.
Connected like shadows.
[BOTH] What?!
[MASK MAN] What do you say
we call it a day, kiddo?
I... can't.
[MASK MAN] Okay.
[gasps]
[screams]
[GOKU grunts]
It's my fault.
[laughing]
Don't stop now!
You'll lose your rhythm.
Back and forth. Back and forth.
[laughing]
Make him suffer.
Stop hurting him!
Won't somebody help him?
Cut the dramatics, Roshi...
Who is he? Tell us.
Who cares about him?!
Upa's right.
We have to save Goku!
Master Roshi...
We have no choice but to
watch this play itself out.
--Say what?!
--No!
Why?!
Because as hard as it is
to accept, it isn't our place.
The living have
no jurisdiction here.
The man Goku is fighting--
he's not of this world...
As impossible as this may sound,
that Masked Man is really...
...Gohan, Goku's
deceased grandfather.
[NARRATOR] The fate
of the seventh Dragon Ball
rests in Goku's weary hands,
and right now,
those hands are full
as he desperately tries
to stay in the fight.
Can our hero regain his strength
in time to win the final match,
or will he meet defeat at the
hands of his own grandfather?
Find out next time,
on Dragon Ball!