[NARRATOR]
Last time, on Dragon Ball!
[BULMA]
Come on, Krillin, step on it!
They're gaining on us!
I really hate back seat drivers.
[NARRATOR] Goku, Bulma,
and Krillin embarked on
a deep sea adventure to
hunt down another Dragon Ball.
But General Blue and his men
were tailing the trio
in order to take the prize
for the Red Ribbon Army...
[ALL yell]
[NARRATOR] General Blue
put the squeeze on our heroes
in a high-speed
underwater chase!
But a close scrape
against the cave wall
left Goku and his friends
free and clear.
At least, for the moment.
Uh, wow! What happened
to all the water?
[NARRATOR] The three emerged
inside a mysterious cavern,
but so did the Red Ribbon Army!
General! It looks like
those pesky kids
are trying
to make a run for it.
Get them and quickly!
[NARRATOR] Goku, Bulma,
and Krillin gave General Blue
and his forces the slip in the
dark recesses of the cavern,
until Goku made
a startling discovery!
Yaaaahhahahah!
[screams]
Sounds frightening...
Soldier, check it out.
Yes, sir.
[NARRATOR] After he
recovered from the shock,
Krillin quickly realized
that Goku's practical joke
could actually be
the find of a lifetime!
The mark of the pirate.
This must be the place
Master Roshi was talking about.
The Pirate's
sunken treasure. It's here!
[NARRATOR] Unfortunately,
Krillin isn't the only one
with treasure on his mind.
[BLUE] Supreme Commander Red
will be most pleased.
I can't believe we found
the pirate's secret hideout!
I'm gonna find
tons and tons of treasure,
and I'm gonna be so rich!
You sure are in a good mood.
Don't tell me you've forgot
those army guys
are still after us!
I'd rather find
a room full of food
than one full of gold!
[KRILLIN] Ooh, I wish
I had bigger pockets!
Or a wagon!
Or even better, a wheelbarrow!
[SOLDIER] Commander!
Hm?
[SOLDIER whispers]
What do you mean
"pirate's treasure"?
Please,
I need you to stay still!
[RED grunts]
[SOLDIER] Sir, it has been
reported by General Blue
that in his pursuit of
the boy and his companions
he may also have discovered
a secret cave in which
pirates have hidden a large
stash of gold and jewels.
Hmmm. Well, is that right?
Sir, please don't move!
[grunts]
The pirates' loot
and the Dragon Balls?
General Blue must be
trying to make amends
for his past mistakes.
He was to blame for
the failure at the boy's base.
[STAFF OFFICER]
I have my doubts about him.
With his dismal record,
I'll be surprised if he can
pull off something this big.
Well, increasing our
rewards, that's fine,
but bringing back the Dragon
Balls, that's essential.
Make sure General Blue
understands that this is
his last chance to prove
his worth to this army!
Yes sir!
Oh, yes, I think that's it!
You're done with the portrait?
Let me see it!
[PAINTER] Uh, yes, right away.
[RED]
Hm. It's genius, genius!
You've captured my
commanding presence perfectly!
Now I see why you're called the
greatest painter of your time!
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Yes, he has portrayed very well
your great dignity
and imposing masculinity.
Mhm!
[grunts]
I've told you before, never
just stand directly beside me!
I'm sorry, sir.
Treas-ure, treas-ure!
How much longer
do we have to walk
to get to the end
of this tunnel?
I'm gettin' hungry!
[laughs] This cave will make
an absolutely perfect grave
for those three little pests.
We're gettin' close!
[KRILLIN] Ooh!
[GOKU and BULMA] Aah...
[KRILLIN] Hey, the path
gets much smoother here!
Why would a bunch
of pirates want to
decorate their walls
and floor with polka dots?
Who knows?
They can cover the walls
with the funny papers
for all I care. Come on.
Whoa!
I thought those dots
seemed kinda weird!
[whimpers]
What was that all about?
It must be
some kind of booby trap
to protect the treasure.
See, those spears shoot out
of the holes in the wall
if an intruder
steps on one of the spots.
It's a good thing
you're so short!
Hey, you're no
giant yourself, buddy!
How are we
supposed to get through here
without coming out
like Swiss cheese?
[whimpers]
And those army creeps
are still after us!
What are we supposed to do?
Hmmm. We'll be okay
if we don't touch those
round things
on the floor, won't we?
What are you talking about?
They're all over the place!
How are we supposed to
get through here
[BULMA]
without stepping on them?
Huh? Look at them!
We'll just jump!
Huh?
Here I go!
Amazing!
That's more than fifty feet!
[GOKU] Okay Krillin,
it's your turn!
[KRILLIN] I see! No problem!
I can do that!
No, don't try it, Krillin!
You'll be skewered!
Goku's not a normal kid!
Don't worry,
it's no sweat for us.
I trained with
Master Roshi too, you know.
It'll be a piece of cake!
[yells]
[laughs, yells]
[GOKU] Uh, are you okay?
That sure was close!
[GOKU] You jumped too high!
[GOKU]
Okay, Bulma! You try it now!
[BULMA] Are you guys nuts?!
There is no way
I can jump that far!
Huh? General Blue, sir!
So, where are they now?
Um, well,
it looks like they are
just a couple of
steps ahead of us, sir.
And?
Uh, and we have
been able to determine
that the boy and the others
are completely unarmed.
Well, well, is that right?
They must have left their
submarine in such a hurry
that they left their
weapons behind them.
I'm certain they were able
to overpower the others
because they had
very advanced firepower...
but now
without their arsenal...
they are nothing more
than a band of brats.
[laughing]
Victory is as good as mine!
Here, hold on tight!
Goku, you've got to
slow this thing down!
I'm going to fall off!
You should exercise more.
Retract slower Power Pole!
Oh, please be careful!
Now you're shaking it!
[BULMA grunts]
[panting]
That wore me out!
Are you okay?
Don't patronize me!
Fine! Let's go then!
[KRILLIN grunts]
[whimpers softly]
[thud, thud, thud]
Well, it seems solid.
[KRILLIN] Yeah, but be careful!
[SOLDIER F panting]
General Blue, the enemy is...
is on the move again!
They must have found something.
[chuckles]
The time has come,
my good men...!
Get those fools...
and crush them!
[ALL yell]
[SOLDIERS grunting]
The Dragon Balls and the
treasure will soon be ours!
Oh, I'm so wonderful!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Huh?
What was that?
[screams]
My company!
They've fallen into
some sort of booby trap!
Sorry, sir. I guess
we're kinda stuck here.
I can see that! You idiot!
[BOTH yell]
I see... That makes sense...
The floor is engineered
to attack any trespassers.
That's odd...
I'd like to know
how those kids got through.
[BLUE] And the pirates
must have had some way
to get around that trap.
[BLUE] There must be
a secret passage somewhere.
[BLUE] A-ha...!
What's this...? I found it!
He-he. Looks like I'll just
have to handle you myself.
Little punk, I'll outsmart you.
Uh-oh, it's dark in there.
That figures.
[ALL gasp]
[GOKU]
It's the skeletons again!
[KRILLIN] Creepy!
These skulls have lights
coming from their eye sockets!
I hope this isn't another trap!
I wouldn't rule it out...
You never know what these
pirates could have rigged up.
[yelps]
[ALL yell]
[stammers]
[BOTH stammer, whimper]
Oh! That's lava!
It's what?
Lava! From a volcano, stupid!
It's so hot,
if we touch it, we'll melt!
[grunts]
[yells]
Please! Please, shorts!
Don't fail me now!
Stop wiggling! Pervert!
What do you think this is,
a... a peep show?!
Wha--? What are
you talking about?
Of course I don't. Ooh.
[BULMA] Liar! Shut your eyes!
O-kay!
You'd better have
both eyes closed, Krillin!
But I do!
[BULMA] I can still
feel you looking at me!
Cover your eyes with both hands!
Goku help!
[BULMA] You are so disgusting!
How can you treat
a lady that way?
'Kay!
[ALL yelling]
[KRILLIN] He-he!
Goku!
Power... pole... extend!
[ALL yell]
[screams]
[BULMA, GOKU, and KRILLIN yell]
[ALL groan]
Whew! We made it!
Why didn't you listen to me?
I told you those pirates
could set up anything!
You almost got us killed!
Uuh!
[screams]
Uh... Hey, did you guys
just hear something?
Mmm, no, not me.
[BULMA] It must have been
your imagination.
Okay! Let's get going
and find the treasure,
but carefully this time!
[BLUE yelling]
[BLUE laughing intensely]
[chuckles]
Wow! It's like a city in here!
[BOTH] Yeah...
[GOKU] Look at this place!
[BULMA] It's the pirates' port!
[KRILLIN] Sure is
a strange location for it!
Hm. I know, it's really
strange that something like this
is hidden inside a cave.
Yeah, it's no wonder
that no one was ever able
to find the pirates' base!
Oh, yeah, this has gotta be
where they
stashed their treasure.
It's around here somewhere,
I just know it!
[BULMA] Hey, wait a minute!
That huge submarine...
If it's in here,
then there must be
another way
in and out of the cave!
Huh? Why is that?
They didn't have
capsules in the old days.
They couldn't just make the
submarine small and carry it.
So I bet to
travel out to the sea,
they had to go under the port.
[KRILLIN] Oh, I get it now.
[chuckles]
I think I'll just postpone the
unlucky end of these three
until they have delivered
the Dragon Ball
and the treasure
into my little hands.
Uah...
Mm.
I think we've got company.
The army?
Uh-uh. Whatever it is,
I don't think it's human.
[yells] What do you mean,
it's not human?
Hm?
Hmmm.
[beep]
[GOKU] Huh...
It's there!
It's a pirate ghost.
I just know it!
[beep]
[KRILLIN and GOKU yell]
[BULMA screams]
Hm...?
Watch out!
[ROBOT] Argh, matey.
What in the world is that?
[ROBOT] Shiver me timbers.
It-It's a phantom!
No it's... a robot!
A robot?
[ROBOT] Walk the plank.
Whoa!
[ALL yell]
[BULMA yelps]
[ROBOT] Argh.
[GOKU yells]
[KRILLIN yells]
[ALL yelling]
[screams]
Oh!
[NARRATOR] It seems
the pirates have left more
than just treasure
behind in their cave!
"X" marks the spot
for adventure--
next time on Dragon Ball!