[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball...
Goku recovered from his
exposure to the frosty elements
in the home of his
rescuer, Suno.
To show his thanks, he then
headed off to bring home
the village chief who
is being held hostage
in the Red Ribbon Army's
Muscle Tower.
[NARRATOR] Once inside,
Goku came face to face
with the monstrous
Major Metallitron,
but a Kamehameha Wave brought
the robotic hulk down for good.
Next, the wily Murasaki tried
to halt Goku's progress
using every technique in
his ninja's bag of tricks.
But in the end, his
skills were no match
for Goku and his Power Pole.
Murasaki called upon
Android Number 8
to take up the battle.
[MURASAKI] Your job is to
spread mayhem, not philosophy!
[NUMBER 8] I can't do it...
[MURASAKI] W-What?
You're nothing but a
yellow-bellied coward!
[NARRATOR] Number 8
teamed up with Goku,
and together the two
braved their way
to the top of the tower--
Where General White
was waiting for them...
[GOKU] Hand over
the village chief now!
General White, Sir. Please
put an end to your evil ways.
I think it is you
should be surrendering!
--Wha--?
--Huh...?
[BOTH yell]
[WHITE laughs]
[GOKU screams]
Oh! Oh no...
He's crushed!
[GOKU groans]
Ah... Oh...
The fifth floor...
[GOKU grunts]
Wha... What happened?
We fell down here...
This is the fifth level.
[GOKU] Huh?
Uhh...
[GOKU] Eww...
[GOKU] What's this
creepy room for?
[NUMBER 8] Uhh...
I don't know...
I was told floor five was
secret, and off limits.
[WHITE laughs]
[WHITE]
Glad you could drop by.
Now listen carefully, fools.
That is if you ever want
to climb out of this pit.
[GOKU growls]
[WHITE chuckles]
Hand over the Dragon Ball
that you're concealing, boy.
And while you're at it,
surrender that little
Dragon Radar, too.
[GOKU] Why would I give
anything to a bad man like you?
[WHITE snickers]
To save your own hide!
[WHITE chuckles]
[WHITE] But if
that's how you feel,
then I'll be glued to my monitor
watching as you are reduced
to nothing but a pile of
little chicken bones
that you put in soup!
[GOKU] Uh-oh,
he closed our exit!
Uh... What did he mean by that?
I'm not sure.
But why are you collecting
Dragon Balls?
Are you planning some bad wish?
Uh-uh.
One of the balls
belonged to my Grandpa.
I'm trying to find it so I can
keep it, to remember him by.
That's a relief, I just
knew you were a good guy.
[low rumbling]
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU] Wh-What?
The wall is moving!
Where's it going?
[soft growling, snorting]
[crunching]
[crunching, slurping]
[NUMBER 8 whimpers]
[whimpering continues]
[NUMBER 8 screams]
[CREATURE] Hmmm...?
[NUMBER 8 yelps]
[CREATURE burps]
[CREATURE roars]
[NUMBER 8 gasps]
It's enormous!
I-It's c-cold...
What are you, crazy?
Don't worry about me.
I'll be fine!
--[squeaking]
--[SUNO gasps]
[SUNO] Huh? Huh?
Oh!
[SUNO] Aww!
[SNOW MOLE squeaks]
Oh! How did you sneak in here?
[SUNO] Aww...
[SNOW MOLE squeaks]
[SUNO giggles]
Did you stray away
from your family?
I'll bet your mom and dad
must be worried sick about you!
[SNOW MOLE squeaks]
[squeaking]
[SUNO gasps]
[MOM &amp; DAD MOLES squeaking]
Oh! There they are now!
Off ya' go!
[SNOW MOLE squeaks]
[SNOW MOLES squeaking]
[SUNO giggles]
[squeaking continues]
Ah, I wonder if Goku has
found the village chief yet...
I hope that they both
make it back safely...
Ahh... Ah--
[CREATURE roars]
[GOKU growls]
[CREATURE snarls]
[NUMBER 8 whimpers]
[WHITE laughs]
[WHITE] This is the end,
my little friend.
Buyon there is
going to eat you alive!
Oh, yeah?
He's big, but I can beat him!
Oh, Goku!
I'm... scared!
Hey, don't worry. I've fought
tougher guys than him before!
You poor sap!
You may be strong,
but nothing will stop Buyon
from satisfying his appetite.
[BUYON growls]
[NUMBER 8 squeals]
[GOKU yells]
[BUYON laughs]
[GOKU] Huh?
Wh-What?!
That punch didn't even faze him!
Well then how about a kick?
Take this you big lump!
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU shouts]
[BUYON laughs]
Oh, Goku!
Are you okay?
[GOKU groans]
What's with this guy?!
His body's so jiggly
that everything I try
just bounces right off of him!
Aaugh...
Ha-haaa!
Now you get it!
He's invincible!
[GOKU growls]
I know I can find
a way to beat him!
[BUYON chuckles]
Oh no! What's that?!
[chuckling continues]
[GOKU screams]
What's happening?!
[WHITE chuckles]
[GOKU screams]
[BUYON chuckles]
[NUMBER 8 gasps]
[GOKU screams]
Oh no! Snap out of it!
I need you, Goku!
Don't let him eat me!
[GOKU stammers]
Is it warm in here...?
[WHITE chuckles]
[BUYON growls]
[GOKU babbles]
[crunching]
[NUMBER 8 gasps]
Goku!
[WHITE chuckles]
[laughing]
You're making me hungry!
[WHITE laughs]
[NUMBER 8 whimpers]
[BUYON growls]
[BUYON grunts]
[NUMBER 8] Huh...? Huh?
[GOKU grunts]
Aahh...
[grunting continues]
He's alive!
[GOKU grunts]
Oh, boy, I'm glad to see you!
Whew!
That sure was close!
Another minute and he
woulda gobbled me down!
[WHITE growls]
Miserable brat!
[BUYON growls]
[GOKU grunts]
No! You will not
get me with that again!
[BUYON growls]
[roaring]
How can I beat him?
All I can do is run!
I gotta try something
else; this isn't working!
[BUYON roars]
Goku, you look exhausted.
[GOKU] Yeah, and I'm
getting hungry, too...
Ooh! I got it, time to
try my Kamehameha Wave!
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU] Eighter, step back!
This oughta stop
that guy in his tracks,
but it always makes
me so hungry!
[GOKU growls]
Sorry, tummy, but here goes!
Ka...
me...
ha...
haa!
[BUYON laughs]
[GOKU] No...!
[GOKU whimpers]
But that's...
That's always worked before!
[NUMBER 8 gasps]
[WHITE laughs]
What's the matter, boy? No luck?
I could be persuaded to
give you another chance.
Hand over the
Dragon Ball and radar,
and I'll get you and
your pal outta there.
No deal!
I already told you! I'm not
going to give you anything!
Stubborn fool!
Do as you wish.
It makes no difference to me.
You can't protect the ball when
you're a pile of horse meat!
No more playing around, Buyon!
Destroy them!
[GOKU] Just try it!
[WHITE] Devour those two!
--[WHITE laughs]
--[GOKU &amp; NUMBER 8 gasp]
--[NUMBER 8] No!
--Ah! Eighter! Eighter!
[GOKU gasping
I'll save you, Eighter, hang on!
[NUMBER 8 grunts]
You okay?
Yes, thanks to you.
[BUYON growls]
[GOKU grunts]
[BUYON laughs]
[GOKU groans]
I know there's
got to be a weakness
somewhere in this guy's body!
Let's go!
[GOKU] Haa!
[BUYON grunts]
[BUYON chuckles]
[GOKU grunts]
Ah, we must give up.
There's no way out.
[GOKU groans]
It's wrong to think
like that, Eighter.
My Grandpa taught me
you should always have hope!
Oh, okay...
[BUYON laughs]
[GOKU] Laugh now, 'coz you
won't be laughing for long!
I don't get it!
He can't be unstoppable!
If only his body wasn't so...
flabby!
If he was firmer, I wouldn't
bounce off like that!
Wait a minute!
[SUNO] I didn't think we'd
be able to thaw you out!
How did I get here, anyway?
Me. I found you in the woods.
You were stuck
out there, frozen stiff.
I got it!
I got an idea!
[GOKU hums]
You do? What is it?
[humming continues]
Oh, yeah, that's it!
I've got it all figured out!
Wait'll you see this!
You're joking!
Just give up! He's unbeatable!
[GOKU] He's beatable!
Just wait and see!
[GOKU] Hi-ya!
[WHITE gasps]
[GOKU] Ha!
[GOKU squeals]
[BUYON gasps]
[GOKU whimpers]
[GOKU] Eighter, how can
you stand this cold?
Oh! I am not affected
by temperatures at all.
[GOKU] Well, I'm
freezing over here!
I can't take it!
Can you keep me warm
in your jacket?
[BUYON grunts]
How is he?
Is he frozen?
He is! That's some
smart thinking!
I think he's hardened enough!
We got 'im now!
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU whimpers]
C-Cold!
[BUYON grunts]
[BOTH] Yeah!
[WHITE gasps]
This boy is unreal!
[BOTH laughing]
Now, then...
[WHITE screams]
[GOKU] Surprise!
Hey, this place
sure nice and toasty!
Power Pole extend!
[GOKU] Hey, Eighter!
Grab on!
[GOKU] Don't worry, its safe.
[GOKU] Just a little bit more...
[WHITE] You should never
let your guard down.
That stings!
You've got to be kidding!
Bullets don't even effect you?
I felt it!
That really hurts!
You better stop it!
[NUMBER 8]
Thanks a lot, friend.
[GOKU laughs]
Waugh! This can't
be happening to me!
[GOKU growls]
This is your last
chance, mister!
Let the village
chief go now!
[NARRATOR] Goku has finally
conquered
the terrible Muscle Tower
and its evil guards.
The only remaining obstacle
between him and his goal
is the terrified General White.
Their struggle begins,
next time on Dragon Ball!