I will crush you!
[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball...
It was the final act in
the power play between
Goku and Tao, and Goku
had the upper hand!
[GOKU] You're breathing
gives away your next move!
[NARRATOR] Goku's trip to
the top of Korin's Tower
had made him
significantly stronger
than the last time
the two faced off.
[NARRATOR] As a result,
Mercenary Tao was forced
to resort to dirty tricks
to stay in the fight.
But with one swift
kick Goku turned
Tao's own tool against him
with fatal consequences.
[NARRATOR] After Commander Red's
hired thug was out of the way,
Goku set out to take on the
entire Red Ribbon Army.
Following his Dragon Radar
to Red's lair,
Goku hopes to recover
the remaining Dragon Balls
and bring Upa's father
back to life with a wish
to the Eternal Dragon!
[RED grunts]
[clapping]
Nice shot, sir, really.
[RED] I've told ya before,
an underling should never
look down at his leader!
[STAFF OFFICER]
You're right, sir!
[RED]
Hmph!
What a glorious day!
The sun is shining,
I'm on top of my game,
and before long, I will
own all the Dragon Balls!
As soon as
Mercenary Tao comes back
we will only have two more
Dragon Balls to track down.
[STAFF OFFICER]
Then it's only a matter of time
before the Red Ribbon Army
rules the world! Right, Sir?
[RED growls]
[phone ringing]
Red here. Speak!
[SOLDIER A]
Commander!
We have had a very
interesting conversation
with Colonel Violet
in the field.
She claims to have recovered
another Dragon Ball.
Excellent.
[beeping]
[DIVER gasps]
Colonel Violet, we found it!
It was right where
you said it would be!
You sure?
I'm still so far away.
Better speed up!
[DIVER gasps]
[ALLIGATOR roars]
[MEN yelp]
That big ol'
alligator seems hungry.
Don't ya think we should
feed him something?
You look like you
could whet his appetite!
[DIVER screams]
[KHAKI CAP screams]
[MEN screaming]
Help!
It appears you picked
a pretty lousy time
to go for a swim, boys.
[DIVER] No! What are you doing?!
[KHAKI CAP] Colonel!
[ALLIGATOR roars,
MEN scream]
[DOG GUY gasps]
[VIOLET]
Who's that?
[PAK PAKS yelling]
What's the deal with these guys?
[DOG GUY]
It's the barbaric Pak Pak tribe!
This is their territory!
Come on, baby!
[MONKEY screeching]
Oh!
Oh, poor baby.
[DOG GUY]
Ow!
Huh?
Would ya look at that?
The pilot's napping! I think
you'd better go home now.
[PAK PAKS yelling]
[PAK PAK 1 grunts]
[BULMA]
Hm...
[ROSHI]
Hm.
Why don't you
take a break, Bulma?
Your ice cream's melting away.
[BULMA] I'm in the middle
of something here.
I'll be there in a minute.
Goku could be just
about anywhere.
Can you really find him
with this little thing?
Gimme that! Hands off, missy!
Uh, Commander?
Colonel Violet has returned.
She's waiting for you
with the Dragon Ball.
Hm...
Sir, good afternoon, sir.
Sorry I wasn't here sooner,
but I hit a little snag.
Good work, Colonel.
This one makes six
when Tao comes back
with the rest of them.
That radar, you know
the one you got from the kid?
It made finding the Dragon Ball
a walk in the park!
[RED]
Excellent.
Now hand the radar over
to General Kappa
and instruct him to locate
the final ball immediately!
Yes sir!
Um, about the reward...
How uncouth!
Hmph.
[RED] It's okay. We did have
a deal. Good work, Violet!
May you triumph, sir.
[BULMA]
It's finished! It's finished!
[BULMA giggles]
My best work yet!
[BOTH]
Hm...
Okay! Watch this!
[BULMA grunts]
So,what do ya think?
It's my scout plane camcorder!
That's great!
You made this with stuff you
found around the house?
I must say I'm truly impressed!
Such ingenuity
deserves a reward!
How 'bout a kiss?
Why do you always have to
ruin a compliment like that?!
I was afraid of this.
The receiver is too weak.
I'll have to adjust the
external antenna on the roof.
It's kind of low tech,
but it should work...
Hey, Launch, will you
give me a hand?
[LAUNCH]
Sure!
[BULMA] We'll have it up
and running in no time!
[LAUNCH]
Are you sure this'll work?
[BULMA]
Of course it will!
[ROSHI]
Hm.
[ROSHI giggling]
Look at that!
Now let's go in for
a little close up action!
[ROSHI laughs]
Oh, yeah! Take it off!
[ROSHI] What happened?!
You dumb machine!
You made me miss the best part!
[BULMA] Okay! It should
work perfectly now!
Ah! That's it! That's it!
I've been a good boy lately!
[ROSHI] I deserve
a little reward!
[ROSHI laughs]
Come to Papa!
[ROSHI laughing]
Oh yeah!
[BEARDED GUY]
Huh?
Huh? What's wrong?
[ROSHI retching]
Commander Red.
The four Dragon Balls have
passed through sector B.
The calculations show they'll
arrive at headquarters
in approximately 15 minutes!
It's about time Tao returned!
[beeping]
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU yelps]
What is that?
It's looking at me!
See there! It's Goku!
[LAUNCH, TURTLE]
Oh!
[ROSHI]
He seems to be in one piece!
No doubt about it, it's him!
[ROSHI] I wonder if
he's on his way here.
[BULMA]
Well, I can find out!
No, he's heading away from us.
It looks like he's
heading towards
two more of the Dragon Balls.
That rascal's up to something.
I smell trouble!
Hm. Wait a minute...
[LAUNCH] I think that point
might be right around
the area where the Red Ribbon
army has its command center!
[ROSHI, BULMA] What?!
[TURTLE] No!
That can't be! He wouldn't
do anything so reckless!
I taught him better than that!
[BULMA]
I'll find out for sure!
You don't mean...
You're going out there?!
No, I'll just make
the camera fly towards
the Dragon Balls and
we'll see where it ends up!
Why are you following me?
Just tell me, do I
know you from somewhere?
[GOKU yells]
Whoa, he's gone!
He must be late for dinner!
Why else would he go so fast?
Commander! There seems to be
an unidentified flying object
approaching at a
high rate of speed!
You dolt, it's Mercenary Tao!
[SOLDIER]
No, sir!
It appears to be a scout plane!
Then initiate the
defense sequence. Right now!
[SOLDIER]
Yes sir!
It's within close range now.
We'll switch to zoom view.
[BULMA]
Uh-oh! We've been spotted!
Aiee! Time to move!
--[ROSHI] Bulma, go right!
--[LAUNCH] No! Go to the left!
[SOLDIER] It's about
to break through the perimeter!
It's so fast.
Like a runaway meteor!
Goku! What are you
thinking, ya' dumb kid?
[ROSHI] The boy is sometimes
too confident for his own good!
--[BULMA screams]
--[ROSHI] Huh?
My camera!
Good! Now switch the
defense system over
to stand-by mode and let
Mercenary Tao get through.
He should be here soon.
Oh! Goku's in trouble!
There's no way he can make
it through there alive!
He's in a pickle alright.
Okay, it's up to me.
I guess I'll go and get
the boy out of this mess.
How do you plan to get there?
That's right. We do
seem to be stuck here
without any transportation.
Yamcha! If we could just
get in touch with him!
[TURTLE] Why don't you just
call him on the phone?
Because we don't have
a telephone either!
[TURTLE] Uh, it's none
of my business,
but why don't you just make one?
You seem pretty handy
with electronics...
You can do it!
You're right. I can. Good plan!
[BULMA mumbling]
Sometimes genius just
needs a bit of a kick start!
It's done!
[DR. BRIEF]
Hello?
Dad... It's me. Is Yamcha there?
I need him.
[DR. BRIEF]
Bulma! I'm glad it's you!
I've got a joke for you.
You see, there was a troll,
a pilot, and a bus driver
at an all-you-can-eat
restaurant--
Dad, save the joke
and get me Yamcha now!
Well, that's her loss.
It was a real rib-tickler!
Where have you been?
Your father said
you went to hunt for
Dragon Balls with Goku.
Mm-hm... Mm-hm...
That girl...
She's up to something.
No way! He's going
there? By himself?
Sure... Yes...
[OOLONG thinking] I sense a
good deed in the works!
Better make myself scarce.
[YAMCHA]
Okay, no problem. I'm on my way!
Puar! Oolong! Come here!
[OOLONG thinking] Rats!
We've gotta go help Goku!
He's going to fight
the Red Ribbon Army!
[PUAR screams]
Uh, d-d-did you say
the Red Ribbon Army?
I guess you've
heard of them, then.
They're tough. But excitement's
just what I need
after a stint in this dull town!
Hey! Almost there!
Commander Red,
Tao is due back here
in exactly 3 minutes
and 40 seconds!
He returns at last!
[beeping]
[YAMCHA]
Everyone get in, quick!
That must be it!
[NARRATOR]
The Red Ribbon Army stronghold
is just ahead, and so is
the adventure of a lifetime,
as Goku attempts a
one-boy assault on General Red
and his lethal forces.
I've been waiting for this!
[NARRATOR] Courage.
Strength. Determination.
All qualities necessary
to successfully challenge
a foe such as General Red.
For his legions of Red
troopers are notoriously
treacherous and powerful.
Fortunately, Goku possesses
these attributes and more.
One need only review his
past accomplishments against
the Red Ribbon Army to verify
his status as a true hero.
With its superior
resources and technology,
the Red Ribbon Army emerged
as a mighty force
which swept the land
like a plague,
inflicting death and destruction
to all who would not
submit to it's iron will.
Bent on conquest and power,
the Army set out to obtain
the seven mystical Dragon Balls.
They combed all
parts of the globe,
unleashing a reign of terror
that would become
its dark legacy.
Woe to those unfortunate enough
to cross Red's path.
They struck without warning,
laying waste to whole cities
and burying the cries
of the innocent in a storm
of explosions and fire.
No one could oppose
such invincible evil...
Until Goku...
His was a power unlike
any the world had known.
Try as they might,
not even the Red Ribbon Army
could contend with this
boy and his Power Pole.
His quest for the Dragon Balls
led Goku into
countless conflicts.
But one after another,
his enemies fell.
He even found time to make some
new friends along the way.
The Dragon Balls
were scattered across
the farthest reaches of the
world and General Red's
unscrupulous methods
of acquiring them
left no boundary unscarred.
But no matter the menace,
Goku was there
to even the odds
and stamp out evil.
And he wasn't alone,
with allies such as Yamcha,
Master Roshi, Puar, Oolong,
Bulma, and Launch,
all at his side to aid
in the fight for Truth,
Freedom, and Justice...
It isn't easy, and peril
exists at every turn.
But no matter the danger,
wherever evil raises
it's ugly head to persecute
the innocent, there is one
who will always be there
to set wrongs right again...
[NARRATOR]
Goku, Champion of Good.