[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
[TAILOR gasps]
If I were to pay you,
it would make me look weak.
Please, sir, I meant
no disrespect.
I only ask for what is mine.
Yes. You have made that clear.
No-no-no-no-no--!
[TAO]
I believe I made my point.
[GOKU]
I have the water!
[NARRATOR] While Mercenary Tao
prepared to renew
his search for the
missing Dragon Ball,
Goku succeeded in winning
the Sacred Water from Korin!
Goku drake deep, hoping to find
his strength
instantly increased.
But Korin revealed that there
was no magic in the bottle.
Goku's powers were increased
by his hard work alone.
[GOKU] Thank you,
Master Korin, for everything!
[NARRATOR] Goku made
his way down the Tower,
completely unaware that
the evil mercenary was already
hurtling through the sky on
his way to the Land of Korin...
The infamous villain is
looking for a rematch
in which he hopes to claim
Goku's Four-star Ball...
...and his life.
[NARRATOR] Goku's descent
into danger continues, today!
[beeping]
[RED laughs]
He's on the move.
We should have the
Dragon Balls soon.
[STAFF OFFICER]
Hm?
[RED growls]
Scissor beats rock?
[RED groans] Not scissor,
stupid, cigar! Cigar!
Oh... yes.
I'm truly amazed at how
far you've come in life...
...without a fully
functioning brain!
[STAFF OFFICER growls]
[RED growls]
A-Are you sure you
wouldn't like to send
some of us to help Tao?
I mean, just in case.
I'm sure he can handle it.
I need you here for
more pressing matters,
like handing me my cigars!
Right.
It's been three days already...
I wonder if Goku has made it
to the top of the tower yet?
Huh? Wha--?
[UPA gasping]
You-You killed my father!
That's right. I have killed
many things, little heathen.
And you're next.
[UPA grunts]
[UPA whimpers]
[UPA screams]
[UPA yelps]
Now, listen to me
very carefully...
Where are you hiding
the Dragon Ball?
It's not here!
Speak up, savage,
I can't understand you.
The orange shiny ball.
You have it. Where is it?
If you want the pain
to stop, talk.
I can't breathe.
If you won't cooperate,
then we have nothing
further to discuss.
[UPA screams]
Flying Nimbus!
Huh?
[UPA gasps]
Did you miss me?
Ah! You are alive!
Thank you, Goku!
Everything's going to be
okay now. Don't worry.
[TAO]
I've never fought someone twice.
This will be interesting.
[UPA]
How was your trip?
Did you get to the
top of the tower?
Did you drink the sacred water?
Yep.
And I'm a lot stronger now!
Wonderful!
[GOKU laughs]
Upa, I want you to stay
on the Nimbus, okay?
Okay.
[GOKU grunts]
Don't you ever
hurt my friend again.
You've no idea how lucky
you are to be alive,
much less talking.
No one has ever
survived my Dodon Ray.
Kings and peasants alike
have fallen to its power.
My grandpa protected me.
It was his Four-Star Ball
that was under my clothes.
Ah, yes.
The missing Dragon Ball,
which I carelessly forgot
to relieve you of during
our last encounter.
I won't make that mistake again.
I must say, I've been
looking forward to this moment.
Though I don't know which
will be more entertaining,
taking the Dragon Ball from you,
or ramming it down your throat.
[UPA gasping]
[TAO]
There is a very thin line
between bravery
and stupidity, child.
You don't really think
you'll win, do you?
I'll give you one last chance.
Give me my Dragon Balls
or I'll take them back.
[TAO laughs] What a vivid
imagination you possess.
Three seconds. That's how
long you have to live.
[TAO yells]
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU growls,
[TAO groans]
[GOKU grunts]
[TAO whimpering]
[TAO groans]
I don't believe it.
He's winning!
Your three seconds are up,
and I'm still here.
Yes... I see...
It's only been three days
and yet your strength
has increased immeasurably.
I spent my time practicing
for this fight...
Those days at the top of
Korin's Tower helped a lot.
The sacred Tower of Korin?
You climbed to
the top? Impossible.
Oh, and I suppose while there,
you drank the Sacred Water,
didn't you, huh?
It took a while,
but I finally did it.
[TAO thinking]
So it is true.
I thought it was just
superstition, legend.
But that would explain
the boy's increased strength.
I'll be--
No matter. I will
still destroy him.
I'm glad you found a way
to amuse yourself
with the time you had left,
though it won't
make any difference.
Fight.
[TAO growls]
I don't fight. I annihilate.
And when I'm done with you,
you will be nothing more
than dust in the wind.
[GOKU] Whatever you call it,
you hurt people.
And I'm going to stop you.
Big words for
such a small mouth.
Whatever you learned
atop that tower
won't be near enough
to save your hide.
We'll see.
Be careful. And good luck!
[TAO grunts]
[BOTH grunting]
You blocked my Death Punch,
with your knee?
Yep, it's all I need!
Get it, "kneed?"
[TAO yells]
[BOTH grunting]
This is the exact opposite
of their last fight.
Huh?
[TAO growls]
[GOKU grunts]
[TAO groans]
[TAO growls]
Now... it's my turn!
No way. I'm just starting
to get warmed up.
[GOKU yells]
[TAO yells]
[GOKU grunts]
[BOTH grunt]
[GOKU groans]
Look out!
[GOKU yelps]
That's right. Come and get me!
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU screaming]
[GOKU groans]
Oh, my head! Oh, man!
[TAO cackles]
[GOKU growls]
[TAO yells]
[GOKU yells]
[KRILLIN]
3,856...
3,857...
3,858...
3,859...
3,860.
Hey, break time.
It's afternoon tea.
Ah, thank you Launch.
Krillin, you care
to wet your whistle?
Yes...
Bulma, would you like some tea?
You've been working on this
non-stop since last night.
[ROSHI] Hm. What do you
call that thing anyway?
Hm. See, it's a
scouting plane for Goku.
I'm almost finished.
A scouting plane?
For Goku?
Yes. I've even
included a multi-task
processing chip so
it can track him down
and record whatever
it is he's doing.
How's it gonna
track him down?
We don't even know
where to start looking.
This machine can cover
a lot of ground, really fast.
And I've enhanced it with
a brand new Dragon Radar.
The Radar will get
a fix on his position
and then all we have to do
is send the scouting plane
out to him!
Wow! You're a whiz,
Bulma. That's great!
[BULMA giggles] Well, I've still
got some tweaking to do.
But it should work.
You've made some
pretty big improvements,
that's for sure.
Heh. You've got talent, kid, and
it's filling out very nicely.
[BULMA]
Ugh! Dirty old man!
The only machine of mine
you've ever shown
interest in is this Microband.
For obvious reasons!
You pervert.
You really ought to be
ashamed of yourself!
Bulma, why are you
so mad at Master Roshi?
[BULMA] Oh come on! You mean
you never figured it out?!
When this was his,
he kept pestering you
to take a bath because
all he wanted--
Look! It's Goku!
[BULMA, KRILLIN, LAUNCH]
Huh?
I mean, uh, Goku Two
and his mother.
I named 'em myself.
[BULMA, KRILLIN, LAUNCH groan]
[BOTH grunting]
[TAO groans]
[GOKU yells]
[TAO groaning]
[GOKU grunting
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU growls]
[TAO groans]
[GOKU grunts]
That's the second suit
you've destroyed.
Do you have any idea how
difficult it's going to be
to find another decent tailor?
You should worry about
your fighting, not your looks.
You dare question my abilities?!
Well! Then taste my Dodon Ray!
[GOKU growls]
Be careful, Goku!
[GOKU] Go ahead!
I'm ready for you this time!
Dodon!
[TAO growling]
[GOKU grunts]
[TAO gasps]
[UPA gasps]
That burned.
It's impossible. No one has
ever withstood that attack...
It can't hurt me anymore.
Just like my Kamehameha Wave
didn't work on you last time.
I guess we're even.
[UPA]
Yeah! You did it!
Dream on!
A capsule?
[GOKU screams]
[BOTH grunting]
[GOKU panting]
[TOA grunts]
[UPA gasps]
[TAO laughs]
Don't worry, boy.
I'm just going to take
a little off the top!
[UPA grunts]
[BOTH grunting]
[UPA]
Goku, catch!
[UPA grunts]
My Power Pole, thanks!
[GOKU grunts]
[TAO yells]
[BOTH yelling]
[TAO yelps]
[UPA giggles]
I don't need a weapon
to defeat you.
No, you need a miracle!
Now hand over the
Dragon Ball while I still
have some patience,
and I might let you live.
Do as I say!
No! The Dragon Balls
are mine, not yours.
So either you give me back
the ones you stole,
or I'll take them by force.
Ugh. Don't be such a fool.
You're just a child.
Why do you want these stupid
things so badly anyway?
Because only the Dragon Balls
can fix the damage you've done.
Upa!
Yeah?
I made a promise
to bring back your father.
Do you trust me?
Yes. I believe in you, Goku!
Well, your friend is in
for a big disappointment.
[GOKU growls]
[TAO thinking] I never thought
I'd suffer the insult
of having to bargain
with a child.
How humiliating! Look at him!
Standing there as if
he were my equal.
He'd be nothing more than
a heap of flesh right now
if he hadn't drunk
that cursed Sacred Water!
Wait! That's it! If the
Sacred Water could empower
that worm, imagine what
it would do for me!
I would be invincible!
Hm. Are you just gonna
stand there or what?
Hm? You should be grateful
for these last few moments
of peace before I take
what little life you've lived.
[laughs]
Let's get on with it.
Upa!
[UPA gasps]
You monster!
I'll get you for this!
[BOTH]
Huh?
[TAO cackling]
No one escapes the
ravages of battle, tiny!
Unfortunately ours will
have to wait for now,
while I take a trip up
your precious Tower.
I'm feeling a bit thirsty.
Go ahead and drink all you want.
But you'll have to
come back down sometime,
and I'll be waiting.
[NARRATOR]
And so, Mercenary Tao climbs
Korin's Tower in search
of the Sacred Water,
hoping it will
increase his already
phenomenal fighting strength.
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile, Goku and Upa
are forced to wait helplessly
for the fight of the
century to continue...
And continue it will,
in the next
action-packed episode
of Dragon Ball.