[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball,
Krillin opposed Chiaotzu
in the third match
of the quarter-finals.
Yeah, Krillin. Good job!
[NARRATOR] The pair seemed
to be evenly matched
until Chiaotzu summoned
the Dodon Ray,
a powerful force
of lethal energy,
which he unleashed upon
Krillin with reckless abandon.
[CHIAOTZU]
Dodon!
[KRILLIN yelps]
[NARRATOR]
Tien made a startling discovery
when he learned that
Goku was responsible
for the demise of Tao,
younger brother of Master Shen.
The Crane Hermit
plotted his revenge
against Goku and his friends,
starting with Krillin,
urging Chiaotzu to
destroy him in the ring.
[KRILLIN]
Ka, Me...
[NARRATOR]
To counter the Dodon Wave,
Krillin decided to try his
hand at the Kamehameha Wave,
much to the dismay of his
peers and Jackie Chun,
who feared Krillin was not
ready for such power.
We're about to find out.
[KRILLIN]
Ka, Me...
Hm?
[ROSHI growls]
Brash child!
The Kamehameha Wave
is a dangerous weapon!
You're not ready to use it!
Dodon!
Ha, Me,
[KRILLIN growling]
Krillin, you'll die!
[SHEN growls]
Kill him!
Wave!
[CROWD gasps
[GOKU gasps]
Oh no!
That's it!
[CHIAOTZU]
He's...
...gone!
Really?
Huh?
Ha!
[gasping]
[CHIAOTZU screaming]
It worked!
[CROWD gasping]
Look at him go! Yeah, Krillin!
Chiaotzu!
[CROWD gasping, screaming]
[CHIAOTZU grunting]
Aw! Give me a break!
You tellin' me after
that he's still floating!
[ROSHI] I must admit I'm
impressed by Krillin's strength.
It has improved a great deal.
I wish the same held
true for his patience.
If he had bothered to learn
the Kamehameha Wave properly,
Chiaotzu would be
dust right now.
[CHIAOTZU grunting, panting]
[KRILLIN growls]
[CHIAOTZU pants]
[TIEN] I didn't think a student
of Roshi's was capable
of such skill. He dodged
and attacked within seconds.
[BULMA] Whoa! It's not that
often that I'm surprised,
but I didn't think Krillin
was that strong.
Hm? Contestants,
please keep fighting.
The match is still in session.
[CHIAOTZU]
It's rare I do this,
but for you I'll use
my special technique.
Special?
Most Excellent. You know
what's coming next.
Oh yes, this fight
won't last much longer.
[KRILLIN yells]
[CHIAOTZU yells]
[KRILLIN grunts]
[KRILLIN groans] That's not
special! I can do that.
[KRILLIN growls, grunts]
[KRILLIN groans]
Krillin!
[KRILLIN growls]
And they say I'm hard-headed!
[CHIAOTZU grunts]
Bombs away!
Krillin, look out!
[KRILLIN laughs]
Too slow, pal! You missed me!
[KRILLIN yelps]
[KRILLIN growls]
[CROWD murmuring]
Boy has a high
tolerance for pain.
[CHIAOTZU humming]
Good boy. Stay calm,
focus on your target,
and annihilate him.
I won't let you down, Master.
Dodge him, Krillin!
[KRILLIN grunting]
[SHEN growls]
Sorry, but you'll have to
come up with something
a lot better than that.
Lucky. Next time Chiaotzu
won't play so nice.
Ha! It's my turn!
[KRILLIN, CHIAOTZU grunting]
Way to go, Krillin! Hit him!
[GROUP laughing]
[KRILLIN yelling]
[CHIAOTZU grunts]
[KRILLIN grunting]
[CHIAOTZU chuckles]
[KRILLIN groaning]
What's wrong with your stomach?
How many special techniques
does Chiaotzu have?
[SHEN]
That's it. Now you've got him!
Concentrate! Don't push
him out of the ring.
Kill him! Make him suffer!
Let my vengeance begin!
[KRILLIN groaning]
I haven't felt this bad since...
When was the last
time Launch cooked?
[KRILLIN]
Oh, man!
[KRILLIN screams]
[CHIAOTZU cackling]
[KRILLIN groaning]
My stomach feels
like it's on fire!
Krillin, get back up!
You can't give up now!
Ha! Your encouragement
is amusing, but futile.
Why give the boy false hope?
Chiaotzu will destroy him,
but his demise
will be on your hands.
[SHEN] For the death
of my brother, Tao!
[SHEN]
Krillin has a strong will.
Pity, he would have
made a fine pupil.
But he's too
headstrong, impatient.
Much like Tao...
I tried to train him,
mold his natural
aptitude for combat.
But I was too young and
arrogant to temper his ego.
He couldn't stand to be
anything less than number one.
And he certainly didn't care
for the "I told you so's"
of an older brother.
I should have treated him more
like a student than a friend...
If only I would have
had more time!
[SHEN] Our similar gifts
eventually drove us apart.
I must admit, I was jealous
of his phenomenal strength.
It all came so easy to him.
Our relationship
became adversarial.
Even in the quiet times,
we were at odds.
The tension built so thick,
that one day all it took
was a bowl of spilled rice
to break our fragile alliance.
The last time we spoke
together was in anger.
[SHEN growls]
[KRILLIN groaning]
[KRILLIN grunting]
[CHIAOTZU cackles]
[CROWD murmuring]
[PUAR whimpers]
Oh, Krillin.
This is becoming embarrassing.
[KRILLIN grunting]
[KRILLIN groans]
[YAMCHA gasps]
It was a dream. I hope
Krillin's all right.
[CHIAOTZU cackling]
[KRILLIN, CHIAOTZU grunting]
[KRILLIN grunting]
Stop kicking!
Are you afraid of
getting your hands dirty?
[CHIAOTZU cackling]
[KRILLIN]
That's it!
He doesn't use his hands
to fight because he can't.
He needs them to
control his powers!
[KRILLIN]
You think you're clever, huh?
[CHIAOTZU]
Well, I'm no genius.
But I'm smart enough
to know you're stalling.
[KRILLIN]
What's three plus four?
Huh?
Come on, that was an easy one!
You've gotta think
faster than that!
Let's see...
One, three. two--
Wrong, seven!
Huh?
Here's your other five!
[CHIAOTZU groans]
[TIEN, SHEN gasp]
Now's your chance, Krillin!
He's right.
[KRILLIN yells]
[CHIAOTZU grunts]
[KRILLIN groans]
[CHIAOTZU cackles]
Nice work, Chiaotzu.
Seems that pest is a
glutton for punishment.
[CHIAOTZU cackles]
[KRILLIN groans]
I may have trouble counting,
but one thing's for sure...
My ten beats your five!
16 plus 27?
Huh? Uh?
Nine minus one?!
[CHIAOTZU whimpering]
[KRILLIN yells]
[CHIAOTZU groans]
[SHEN, TIEN gasp]
[SUPERVISOR] The winner
by a knock-out is Krillin!
[CROWD cheers]
The answer is eight!
[GOKU giggles]
Yay! Yeah!
Great job.
[KRILLIN laughs]
[ROSHI] I think Krillin enjoys
the crowds' adulation for him
more than the victory itself.
[CROWD cheering]
[TIEN growls]
Chiaotzu, how could you
disappoint me like that?
I was counting on you!
[GOKU, KRILLIN giggling]
Who would have ever guessed
a fighter needed mathematics!
That's wonderful news.
Congratulations. And thanks.
Sure. See, Chiaotzu is
what you'd call...
...slow. And I'm a genius!
132,000,000 plus 904,203,000?
Uh-- um...
Uh oh.
[BULMA]
1,036,203,000.
Maybe I'm not a genius,
but I still won.
[ALL laughing]
[SHEN]
Quickly, now. Two plus one?
Uh, uh, three! Three.
Nine minus six?
Well, uh...
Three, yes? Three?
No fingers!
Count with your head,
not with your hands!
[snoring]
[SHEN grunting]
[GOKU snoring]
Huh? Are you a dream?
[GOKU yells]
[ROSHI gasps]
What's all the racket about?
[KRILLIN grunts]
Who's there?!
Hey, wait, you're--
[GOKU]
Stop!
[ROSHI yells]
[KRILLIN] Goku!
Krillin, don't jump!
Has everyone forgotten
how to use a door!
[ROSHI yelps]
[KRILLIN]
Goku!
Which way did he go?
I think he was a ninja.
[KRILLIN groans]
He moves fast.
I know your scent.
I've smelled it
somewhere before.
[KRILLIN grunting]
Hey! You're the--
[KRILLIN]
The Crane Hermit!
Why did you attack
me back there?!
[SHEN growls]
My motive is obvious!
You murdered my brother!
Not on purpose. He attacked.
I defended myself.
Tao is dead.
I don't care how it happened.
You're still going to pay!
[GOKU] Krillin, remember that
game Master Roshi taught us?
Right. You're it.
[SHEN grunts]
[GOKU yells]
[ALL grunting]
[GOKU grunting]
[SHEN]
Tien Shinhan!
Tien? I don't remember
inviting you.
My apologies, Master.
But I didn't want
you to kill Goku.
[SHEN]
Explain.
With all due respect, sir,
this shouldn't happen here.
No one wants vengeance
for this crime more than I.
But there is no satisfaction
in killing Goku here.
A quick death is
too good for him.
He deserves to suffer
as we do now.
What did you have in mind?
Tao was slain by Goku's hand,
but Master Roshi guided it.
He should watch his
pupil die in the ring.
broken and publicly humiliated.
Your heart is
cold and ruthless...
It warms my own. Proceed.
I am honored, Master.
And you...
The next time we fight,
it will be for Tao's honor.
I'll fight. But it's not about
Tao. This one's for Yamcha!
Whatever gets you there.
Just don't lose any matches
between now and then.
I'll do my best.
[NARRATOR]
With their challenge set,
the showdown between
Goku and Tien has raised
the tournament to
a whole new level.
It's not just about
winning the title anymore.
It's about survival.
Next time on Dragon Ball!