[growls] You really think
that you can beat me!?
[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
[PICCOLO JR.]
Just be quiet!
[NARRATOR]
Ravaged and weary,
Goku continued his
fight against Junior
in the final match of the
World Martial Arts Tournament.
But it was clear to all,
this battle would determine
more than the new champion.
It would decide
the fate of mankind!
[GOKU]
Ah... Hm...
[NARRATOR] Goku's maneuver
left Junior seriously wounded,
but far from defeated.
The creature was determined
to destroy its foe at any cost.
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[grunts]
[yelps]
[roaring]
[PICCOLO JR. groans]
[GOKU gasps]
[PICCOLO JR.]
You can't hurt me...
Nothing you say...
or do can stop my power!
I am invincible! You will be
the first to witness my destiny!
[grunts, groans]
[NARRATOR]
Goku watched in horror
as Junior's screams brought the
eerie promise of a new threat.
[GOKU gasps]
Get out of here! Get out now!
It's not safe here! Leave!
Move it! Get as far away
from here as you possibly can!
[PICCOLO JR. groaning]
[groaning continues]
[BOTH whimper]
[ALL scream]
[PICCOLO JR. groaning]
[whimpers]
--[BOTH gasp]
--[PICCOLO JR groaning]
[gasps]
[groaning]
[groaning continues]
[YAMCHA, BULMA yelp]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU thinking]
I've never seen so much power
summoned at one time!
[groaning]
Ahh...
[GOKU thinking]
He must be getting desperate
to go to such extremes!
[PICCOLO JR. groaning]
[PICCOLO JR. pants]
[PICCOLO JR. roars]
[BOTH sputter]
[ROSHI] Junior seems to
be absorbing our energy,
making himself stronger!
[sputters]
It seems that Junior is using
some sort of mysterious power
that drains the energy
from everything it its path!
Somehow it strengthens his own
body and weakens his opponent!
The audience has left,
you idiot!
What are you all doing?
You have to leave!
Didn't you hear me?!
Get out of here! Hurry!
You have to get off this island!
Run as far away as you can!
[whimpering]
[CHICHI] I'm not leaving
without you, Goku!
Just go!
[grunts]
I'll hold him!
[gasping]
Go--
Goku, listen, you can't stay
here! You must come with us!
I know how much the
tournament means to you,
but you have to turn away!
Give up before it's too late!
There's no more time!
Ah!
--[LAUNCH growls]
--[OOLANG whimpers]
[OOLANG yelps]
[groaning]
[grunting]
[groaning continues]
[grunts]
[GOKU]
Uhh?
[ALL screaming]
[PICCOLO JR. groaning]
[GOKU grunts]
[screams]
[groaning]
[ALL screaming]
[gasping]
[sputtering]
[PICCOLO JR. groans]
Uhh?
Ah! What happened?
Look at his body!
[BOTH]
Uh?
Ah!
[PICCOLO JR. groaning]
[PICCOLO JR. laughing]
This is it! Take cover!
[TIEN grunts]
[TIEN] I've got to save
my friends! Tri-beam!
Everybody take shelter in this
hole! It's our only chance.
It won't do Goku any good
if we don't survive!
--[KRILLIN whimpers]
--He's right!
Hurry!
Wait up!
[whimpers]
[BULMA]
Go!
[OOLANG]
Help me!
[PUAR screams]
--[YAMCHA pants]
--[CHICHI yelps]
What about Goku?!
[YAMCHA grunts]
[YACHA]
ChiChi, come on, we have to go!
Goku can take care
of himself! Come on!
--Let's go!
--[OOLANG whimpering]
[CHICHI yelps]
Goku, you gotta
get outta there?!
No!
Idiot... You can't fathom
the power you're up against...
If you had any brains, you'd be
on your knees begging for mercy!
No way... Get ready to lose!
Flee, Goku... Now!
[LAUNCH]
You're in danger! Move it!
[LAUNCH grunts]
Oh...
[LAUNCH]
Hello?!
You're going to die if
you don't get in the hole!
--[LAUNCH] Move!
--[KAMI gasps]
[LAUNCH grunts]
There's nothing more
to see! Get in there!
[PICCOLO JR. groans]
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
Conceited punk...
I will enjoy breaking you!
[gasps]
[PICCOLO JR. roars]
[GOKU grunts]
[roaring]
--[PICCOLO JR. roars]
--[GOKU grunts]
[roaring continues]
[GOKU screams]
[PICCOLO JR. roaring]
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[growls]
[laughs]
I have won!
[KRILLIN groans]
[screams]
G-Goku?
I don't see him...
[screams]
Goku!
[groans]
[gasps]
[PICCOLO JR. sputters]
Surprised to see me?
You'll have to be
stronger than that, Junior!
Ahh... You're... here!
But that's impossible!
You should be dust!
[ALL whimpering, groaning]
He's alive! Goku's alive!
What?!
It's a miracle!
Goku!
[BOTH groaning]
Good ol' Goku!
--[LAUNCH] Keep fighting!
--[CHICHI] Goku!
[TIEN]
Nice dodge, Goku! Keep it up!
--[ALL cheering]
--[KRILLIN] He's alive!
[PICCOLO JR. gasping]
[GOKU laughs]
Get over here, if you're
ready for more!
Uh... no! No! No!
[PICCOLO JR. whimpers]
[PICCOLO JR.]
It's not fair!
[YAMCHA]
He's sweatin', Goku! Come on!
--[KRILLIN] Woohoo! Yeah, Goku!
--[CHICHI] All right, Goku!
Amazing! He took
that blast head-on
and yet he doesn't even
look singed. Unbelievable!
That's Goku! He
always bounces back!
You've used every
dirty trick in the book!
But you can't get rid of me. I'm
still here and I'm going to win!
[PICCOLO JR. grunts]
[GOKU]
Hmm.
Okay... It's time
to finish this!
[yelling]
Uh... Uh-oh!
I really think this
is gonna hurt!
[GOKU laughs]
A lot!
[growls]
[yelling]
--[PICCOLO Jr. gasps]
--[GOKU grunts]
[PICCOLO JR. groans]
--[GOKU grunts, yelling]
--[PICCOLO JR. grunting]
[groans]
Nice one!
[yelling]
[PICCOLO JR. groans]
[cheering, laughing]
That one hurt.
[PICCOLO JR. screams, groans]
[GOKU grunts]
Kaa..
Mee...
Haa...
[screams]
Incoming!
[ALL scream]
[screams]
Haa!
[PICCOLO JR. screams]
[ALL screaming]
[CHICHI whimpers]
[sputtering]
[GOKU grunts]
[sighs]
[TIEN, LAUNCH groan]
[CHICHI whimpers]
[KRILLIN]
Uh?
[GOKU] Hey! Now might be a
good time to start counting!
[ANNOUNCER]
Huh? Oh, yes!
[ANNOUNCER pants]
I don't know why he's
even wasting his breath.
This means Goku's the...
Winner! You won!
[BOTH groan]
[BOTH laugh]
[ANNOUNCER sputters]
[ANNOUNCER] Oh my! Oh!
Oh my! He's not moving!
Do you think-- I mean, is he--
Oh. Do you think he
could possibly be...?
--[ANNOUNCER sputters]
--No way...
He's not that vulnerable...
Besides...
--You're right...
--[LAUNCH] Huh?
I'm still alive. And that
means, so is Junior...
He's asleep. Might I suggest you
start counting before he awakes?
Uh... oh, sure...
Excuse me, I have to count...
[ANNOUNCER clears throat]
And...
One... two...
three... four... five!
And six!
[ALL]
Seven!
[BOTH]
And eight!
[laughs]
[ALL]
Nine!
[roars]
Uhh?
--[ANNOUNCER sputters]
--[GOKU groans]
[screaming]
[GOKU groaning]
[grunts]
[groaning, laughing]
[ANNOUNCER sputters]
[ALL gasping]
[groaning]
[coughs]
[screams]
No! Goku's hurt!
--[YAMCHA, PUAR scream]
--Goku!
[groaning]
[panting]
[growling]
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[laughing]
[GOKU groans]
Huh? Hanging on till
the bitter end...
How considerate.
[laughs]
[groaning]
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
Your time is up...
End of game...
You made a good run of
it, but now it's over.
--[KRILLIN sputters]
--You monster!
No... No!
[gasps]
[groaning]
[growls]
For the crimes committed
against King Piccolo,
it's my honor to serve justice!
--[PICCOLO JR. roars]
--[GOKU screams]
--[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[TIEN]
Leave him alone!
[growls]
[PICCOLO JR.]
Back off!
[PICCOLO JR. roars]
[KRILLIN, YAMCHA, TIEN scream]
[growls]
[PICCOLO JR.] This doesn't
concern you... Stay out of it!
[YAMCHA, KRILLIN gasping]
Coward! If you hurt him,
you'll answer to me!
[CHICHI gasps]
Goku's in danger. We have
to find a way to save him!
Oh, please!
If anything happens
to him, I'd just--
Call off the match!
Do something!
[whimpers]
[whimpering]
[gasps]
--[PICCOLO JR. growls]
--[GOKU groans]
Huh?
[groaning]
[ALL gasping]
[gasps]
[sighs]
[groaning]
[GOKU] Good thing you aim
as bad as you fight.
You missed my vital organs.
All of them?!
--[ALL gasping]
--[BULMA] Poor, Goku.
[PICCOLO JR. gasping]
You were supposed to die!
[GOKU laughs]
[GOKU]
I'm glad to disappoint you...
Looks like the match
isn't over... yet!
[whimpers]
--[GOKU laughs]
--[PICCOLO JR. growls]
Fine... But victory
will still be mine!
[growls]
Ehh... We'll see.
[laughs]
[NARRATOR]
Despite his injuries,
Goku has managed
to stay in the fight.
But how much punishment
can his body withstand?
As the two warriors
prepare to battle once more,
which outcome awaits Goku...
Victory or defeat?
To find out, don't miss the
next action-packed episode
of Dragon Ball!