[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball,
Goku and his friends fought
Fortuneteller Baba's forces
as they attempted
to learn the location
of the last Dragon Ball.
While Puar and Upa were able
to defeat Fangs, the Vampire,
Yamcha found it nearly
impossible to oppose
the next challenger,
an invisible man.
Yet Krillin had a plan,
which involved sending Goku
after Master Roshi and Bulma.
[GOKU]
Master Roshi!
Where is everybody?
Excuse me, have you
seen Master Roshi?
If you-- ow!
Happen to see him-- ow!
Will you please-- ow!
Let me know?
[GOKU]
There they are!
Bulma! Master Roshi!
Please slow down! Wait up!
[LAUNCH]
It's Goku!
[OOLONG]
Why's he back so soon?
And why aren't the
other guys with him?
I wonder if he forgot
to take something?
[ROSHI]
What's up, Goku?
[GOKU]
Krillin told me to come get you.
Forget it! We're not
getting mixed up
in your silly adventures!
Yeah! That's right!
Sorry Bulma, but we
don't have much time!
[OOLONG, BULMA,
ROSHI, LAUNCH yell]
[GOKU]
Let's go!
[BULMA, ROSHI screaming]
[OOLONG growls]
[LAUNCH, OOLONG screaming]
[LAUNCH]
Oolong, do something!
[OOLONG]
What?! I'm a pig! I can't fly!
[LAUNCH, OOLONG screaming]
Pull up!
A-Ah-choo!
[OOLONG]
Oh-whoa! We're gonna die!
[LAUNCH]
Alright!
[LAUNCH grunts]
I thought I was dead.
Well, if you're disappointed,
I can certainly
arrange something.
No, no, I'm fine!
[OOLONG] You tell me
what I can do for you.
[LAUNCH]
Nothin'!
[OOLONG]
O-Okay, backing off!
Yamcha!
[YAMCHA gurnting]
That's it. Talk to me with
your movements. I'm all ears.
[YAMCHA grunts]
[YAMCHA yelling]
[SEE-THROUGH]
Ow!
Ha! It worked!
Every time you move,
you turn into my
invisible punching bag!
[PUAR]
You've got him now, Yamcha!
[YAMCHA]
Hm...
[SEE-THROUGH laughing] You think
you're pretty smart, huh?
Let's see how good your
hearing really is.
[BABA cackles] ♪ Oh, Listen up
and listen well. ♪
♪ I have a tale to tell! ♪
♪ Baba, Baba is my name,
Telling fortunes is my game. ♪
♪ If it's lost and
can't be found, ♪
♪ I'm the friend
you need around. ♪
♪ Solving mysteries
by the pond, ♪
♪ I'll turn your
frown upside down! ♪
♪ Look under a rock,
search a waterfall, ♪
♪ Why waste all that time?
Just ask my crystal ball! ♪
[YAMCHA groans]
[PUAR, UPA, KRILLIN gasp]
[YAMCHA groaning]
Keep moving! Don't stand still!
[YAMCHA grunting, groaning]
♪ You can pay
or you can fight, ♪
♪ Either way the
price is right! ♪
♪ This song is from me... ♪
[YAMCHA groaning]
[KRILLIN] Come on, Goku.
You'd better get here soon.
Otherwise, there won't
be anything left to save!
[YAMCHA groaning]
I can't hear him coming
with all of Baba's racket.
[BABA cackles]
I know! Go. invisible guy!
[UPA, PUAR]
Huh?
Hey! We're rooting
for Yamcha, remember?!
Stop, Krillin!
Yeah, invisible! Win!
[SEE-THROUGH laughing]
Thank you!
[YAMCHA grunting,
SEE-THROUGH groaning]
That's more like it!
Great trick, Krillin!
Go invisible!
I like your hat!
[SEE-THROUGH]
Oh, stop it! Ow!
[SEE-THROUGH groaning]
[KRILLIN, UPA, PUAR laughing]
See-Through, you idiot!
They're playing to your vanity!
Don't answer them!
[SEE-THROUGH]
Yes, ma'am.
[YAMCHA grunting,
SEE-THROUGH groaning]
[BABA]
Your words betray you!
Silence is your
best weapon. Use it!
[footsteps]
[YAMCHA groans]
There. That's much better.
[SEE-THROUGH grunting,
YAMCHA groaning]
Tell us how cool you are!
Say something!
See-through, speak!
Ha! You're just wasting
your breath, kids.
That trick has been played out.
[YAMCHA groaning]
[SEE-THROUGH grunting,
YAMCHA groaning]
[KRILLIN thinking] Yamcha's
getting creamed out there.
We need Goku!
[BULMA]
Goku, would you slow down.
My arm is about to
fall off! Slow down!
Are you listening to me?
Where are you taking us?
Answer me! I don't
have time for this!
And neither do I!
I'm a busy man!
There's a new
exercise video at home
that is in desperate
need of my attention!
Don't worry, Master.
We're almost there.
[SEE-THROUGH grunts,
YAMCHA groans]
♪ Baba, Baba,
that's my name! ♪
♪ Telling fortunes
is my game! ♪
♪ If it's lost and
can't be found... ♪
I don't know what
hurts more, getting beaten
by an invisible man, or
listening to your awful voice.
[BABA cackles] I can make
the pain end right now.
Just give up.
What, and miss the
next verse? No way.
[GOKU]
Krillin!
[ROSHI, BULMA screaming,
GOKU laughing]
[GOKU]
I'm back!
Well, it's about time!
Hm? What's this?
[ROSHI, BULMA grunt]
Alright, somebody had
better start talking now!
What is going on,
and why have I been
dragged into the middle of it?!
Nice feather. What's this about?
I know how much you
like games, Master Roshi.
I just wanted you to come
watch Yamcha. That's all.
[ROSHI, BULMA]
Huh?
[YAMCHA groaning]
You brought me here
to watch Yamcha dance.
I don't know what
you're up to, Yamcha,
but this is not my
definition of a good time!
[YAMCHA groaning]
[KRILLIN laughs] I promise I'll
explain everything in a second.
Just stand right here, okay?
And Master Roshi,
if you could stand right
over here for a second.
Yamcha is no king
of dance but any view
is better than this.
[KRILLIN]
Not from where I'm standing.
Alright! Master Roshi,
please give me
your undivided attention.
Eh? Hm. Don't get pushy.
This had better be good.
Now here they come.
We're only gonna
get one shot at this!
[YAMCHA groaning]
Okay! Now!
[ROSHI yelps]
[SEE-THROUGH groaning]
Huh?
[SEE-THROUGH] What is this?
I'm-I'm completely covered!
[YAMCHA]
Oh yeah... like a target.
No.
--[GROUP cheering]
--[GOKU] Wow! He's small.
Get 'em, Yamcha!
[YAMCHA chuckles]
It's my turn!
[BABA growls]
[YAMCHA yells]
Wolf Fang Fist!
[SEE-THROUGH yelping,
YAMCHA grunting]
[UPA laughs]
[YAMCHA grunting,
SEE-THROUGH groaning]
[SEE-THROUGH groans]
[GOKU, KRILLIN laughing]
[PUAR laughs]
[SEE-THROUGH]
I quit. Mama was right.
I'm not cut out
for show business.
[YAMCHA sighs]
Yeah!
[ALL cheering]
[BULMA grumbles]
Yay! Yay!
[BULMA grunts]
Normally I deplore violence,
but in your case,
I'll make an exception!
I understand you're upset
but I just want you
to know one thing...
I love you.
[BULMA yells]
[KRILLIN groans]
Boy, you've got some nerve,
pulling a crazy stunt like that!
Forgive me, Master.
I was just trying
to help Yamcha.
[ROSHI] It was reckless.
And I loved every minute of it.
[KRILLIN giggles]
[BULMA grumbles]
Your team is clever...
But that won't save you
from my remaining forces.
[YAMCHA sighs]
Huh?
Bulma, Master Roshi.
I didn't know you were coming.
Neither did we.
Huh. This is a strange setup
for a fortuneteller. Krillin?
Hm?
[BULMA]
Is this Fortune Teller Baba's?
[KRILLIN]
That's right.
I see. Well, if her
business is telling fortunes,
then why does she have you
guys fighting in an arena?
Uh, actually Baba is doing
us a big favor here.
You see, normally it costs a lot
of money to use her services.
So... she takes
it out of your hide?
That's a bargain.
A-A-Ah-choo!
If you can't afford
to pay her fee,
she gives you the option of
battling her five fighters.
If you can defeat them all,
she'll tell your
fortune for free.
Yep. My sister is a
shrewd businesswoman.
[KRILLIN, BULMA]
Huh?
Huh? Hey, what do you
mean by sister?
[ROSHI]
I mean Baba is my older sister.
[ALL]
Baba is your sister?!
You look alike,
especially the beard.
That's not funny, Goku.
Okay, this is weird. Ugh.
But of course that
does explain
why she lives in
the middle of a desert.
Touché.
Well, look who showed up.
[BABA] We could have
used you last week when
we moved mother. And you
missed my birthday again.
Happy Birthday.
Master Roshi...
Since you and Baba
are related, maybe you could
put in a good word for us,
and she could tell
our fortune without
any more fighting.
That's right. Family helps
each other out.
No more fighting
sounds fine with me.
That sounds great!
[GOKU]
Mm-hm!
Are you kidding me?
For family, I charge double.
What? You would refuse
your own brother?
You bet.
Hey, sounds good to me.
This is great for my training.
Then let's get on with it.
For our third match, we're going
to need a change of scenery.
[BABA]
Follow me.
[YAMCHA]
Sure.
[BULMA sighs] I can't believe,
in my life, this is normal.
[ROSHI]
So, uh, how 'bout
loaning your little
brother some cash?
You still haven't paid back
the last money I let you borrow.
Ten zeni isn't much,
but with 30 years interest,
I could buy myself
a new crystal ball!
Darn... I was hoping you
had forgotten about that.
I never forget.
Especially money I lend
to dead-beat brothers.
Sure. Check's in the mail.
How old are you anyway?
It's not polite to ask
a lady her age.
[GOKU]
Right. So, how old are you?
[BABA gasps] Why, I never!
Who do you think you are?
You should learn some manners!
Goku happens to be
one of my pupils.
That's right!
Well, that explains it.
What's your name?
[UPA] I'm known as Upa.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, Upa! Yeah,
I've heard about you.
In fact, you're the reason Goku
is looking for the Dragon Balls.
He hopes to revive
your father, right?
Uh-huh.
Upa, listen. I wouldn't
get too chummy with Bulma.
She changes temperature real
quick, if you know what I mean.
--Quick!
--[UPA] Huh?
Take that back, runt!
[KRILLIN]
See what I mean.
[GOKU]
Boy, this place is huge!
[BABA]
This way.
[YAMCHA] Where exactly
am I going to be fighting?
[ROSHI]
In the Devil's Toilet.
Whoa! That doesn't
sound good at all...
[YAMCHA]
What is it?
Do you have any advice
you can give me?
[ROSHI laughs]
Yeah sure... If I were you,
I wouldn't fall in.
Oh, well thanks
for the warning.
[ROSHI]
Don't mention it.
The fighters must enter
through this door.
Alright.
[BABA] The rest of you
climb the stairs.
You'll find seats at the top.
Goku, stay with me.
[GOKU]
Okay.
[BABA]
Wait a minute. Let's go in here.
[BULMA]
Where are Goku and Baba?
[KRILLIN] They were right
ahead of us a minute ago.
[ROSHI] Don't worry.
We'll see them at the match.
My sister loves to
pull tricks like this.
[GOKU] That shiny thing up
there is as bright as a star!
This place is beautiful.
[BABA] It's not much,
but it's home.
[BABA] You can take
this seat right here.
[GOKU]
Okay.
[GOKU sniffing]
Something smells wonderful!
[BABA chuckles] Indeed.
See-Through! The first course!
[SEE-THROUGH]
Certainly.
[GOKU]
This looks delicious!
Yes! Go ahead, dig in.
Thank you so much!
Oh, this is creepy...
[YAMCHA] I don't even wanna know
where she got all these bones.
[ROSHI grunting]
[BULMA] I guess an elevator
would have upset the décor.
How many more steps are there?
I stopped counting at 1,000.
[BABA]
How is it?
[GOKU]
Great!
[GOKU yelps]
[GOKU grunting]
[SEE-THROUGH groans]
Ha!
[BABA groans]
[SEE-THROUGH groans]
Did you know you have
a hole in your ceiling?
Oh boy, am I hungry!
The kid's reflexes are amazing!
I hate to admit it
but I think my brother
finally did something right.
[YAMCHA groans]
Great. Tongues for a bridge.
Why am I not surprised.
[YAMCHA]
Now that is just vile!
[ALL gasp]
[ROSHI] That's the toilet...
It smells worse than it looks.
[BULMA]
Ew! How disgusting!
[PUAR]
Yuck!
Yamcha, look.
Huh? Oh!
[KRILLIN]
What's he doing?
If he falls in, he's done for.
[BULMA]
Yamcha!
Hey!
Goku's back!
[BULMA] Where have you
been all this time?
Eating!
Goku, there's something
called poison!
I wouldn't eat anything
in present company.
Give me some credit!
Even I have standards...
What do you think of
your new surroundings?
It makes a cemetery look cozy.
[BABA]
That will be the next stop
for whoever falls into the pot.
That's not good.
There is only one way
that I can personally
guarantee your safety.
Yeah! Let me guess, you want
each of us to donate an organ?!
Sounds tempting.
But no, I want Goku!
[ALL gasping]
N-Not Goku!
Right-o!
[GOKU] Uh... What's wrong?
What do you want me for?
With your abilities,
you will be a prize addition
to my team of fighters!
She's joking, right?
Tell me your sister
has a sense of humor.
I'm sorry I brought
you kids into this.
Yamcha can win.
Trust me, Master.
[ROSHI grunts]
Don't be a fool. This is
a fight you cannot win.
Here comes Yamcha!
[ALL gasp]
What is he doing? Is he nuts?!
He won't fight alone!
Hm?
Goku.
I am the reason
we're all here, Master.
I have to fight.
Mm-hm. I understand.
Now go show them
what you're made of.
Yes, sir. I won't let you down.
Good luck.
Good luck, my friend.
[GOKU]
Hm!
[BABA cackles]
So eager to die.
[NARRATOR]
Goku has refused Baba's offer
and chosen to fight...
But in this arena,
losing means certain death.
And what of Yamcha's fate?
Which of Fortune Teller Baba's
evil henchmen
must he battle next?
[NARRATOR]
To find out, don't miss the next
astounding episode
of Dragon Ball!