[BULMA, KRILLIN grunting]
[BULMA]
What in the world?
[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
Bulma and Krillin
discovered the key
to unlocking their
wildest dreams!
Huh?
[BULMA]
Some treasure!
This could be big trouble!
[KRILLIN]
Yeah!
[BULMA, KRILLIN]
Huh?
[high-pitched squeak]
[BULMA gasps]
[KRILLIN, BULMA]
Ooh!
[NARRATOR]
At last, the pirate's treasure
was within their grasp...
The revelry was
short-lived, however,
as danger reared its
ugly head once more.
[BULMA] You know what this
means, don't you?
[KRILLIN] What?
[BULMA] We're rich!
[BLUE] I'm afraid that
you're both mistaken!
That treasure belongs
to the Red Ribbon Army!
[KRILLIN]
Uh oh...
[NARRATOR] General Blue
challenged Krillin for control
of the prize. But thanks to his
training with Master Roshi,
Krillin was somewhat
less than intimidated.
It didn't take long
for Blue to realize
that he would need
more than tough talk
to get the young
fighter to back down!
[KRILLIN growls]
[BLUE yells]
[KRILLIN, BLUE grunting]
[BLUE grunts]
[KRILLIN groans]
[BULMA screams]
[BLUE growling]
[KRILLIN whimpering]
[BULMA whimpers]
I can't budge! He did
something with his eyes!
[BLUE cackles]
[NARRATOR] Paralyzed by
General Blue's psychic powers,
Krillin was unable
to defend himself.
[BLUE cackling]
[BLUE grunts]
[KRILLIN groaning]
[BLUE growls]
[KRILLIN groans]
[KRILLIN groaning]
[BLUE] I know that hurt! Don't
worry! It'll all be over soon!
[BLUE cackling]
Goku...
[BULMA screams]
[BLUE yells]
[NARRATOR] It looked like
the end for Krillin.
But at the last possible moment,
Goku burst onto the scene
to give General Blue
a new challenger to face!
[GOKU]
Krillin! Are you okay?
[BULMA pants]
[KRILLIN groans]
Hey! Stop picking on
my friends and deal with me,
you big bully!
[BLUE laughs]
Don't you fret.
You won't get left out,
little boy, I promise you that.
[BLUE] There's plenty
of room on the floor,
next to your egghead chum!
Stop talking and fight already!
[BLUE laughs] You're in that
much of a hurry to die?
[GOKU]
I'm not afraid of you!
[BLUE]
Really?
Well, tell me...
Are you afraid of this?
[BLUE grunting]
Yes, I can see your bottom lip
quivering with fear, little one.
No matter. The end is here.
Oh yeah? You look
like a big balloon.
[BLUE]
You insubordinate twerp!
You dare to mock me?!
[BLUE growling]
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uhh...
Hey! What's that up
there on the ceiling?
[GOKU]
Huh?
[BLUE grunts]
[GOKU groans]
[BLUE laughs]
Goku?!
[BULMA]
Goku! Goku, I'm so sorry!
I was trying to
divert his attention
so you could whack him!
[BLUE laughs]
Thanks, little girl,
--but I'll take it from here!
--[BULMA] Stop!
[GOKU grunts]
[BLUE grunts]
Ah!
[BLUE] You can run,
but you're still going to die!
[BLUE, GOKU grunting]
Now it's over! Ha!
Whoa!
[BLUE laughing]
[GOKU grunts]
[BLUE groans]
[BLUE whimpers]
You insolent runt...!
You actually struck me!
[GOKU] Get used to it,
I'm just getting started!
[BLUE grunts]
[GOKU grunts]
[BLUE groans]
[BLUE yelps]
[GOKU grunts]
[BLUE groans]
[GOKU laughs] Boy, you sure
do kiss the ground a lot.
That was amazing!
Goku seems even
stronger than he was
during the
martial arts tournament.
Well, that's what you get
for picking on people...
[BLUE growling]
My tooth is loose...
My tooth is loose!
[BLUE]
You should not have done that.
You are a thorn in my side...
Time to pluck you out!
[GOKU grunts]
[BLUE growling]
Oh...
[BULMA]
No! Goku, snap out of it!
Goku! Listen to me!
Don't look at his eyes!
Don't look at him!
Goku, he's got some
kind of strange power
that paralyzes you!
He did it to Krillin!
[GOKU yelps]
[GOKU]
I can't move my arms!
My whole body is frozen!
What did you do to me?
Oh, Goku.
[GOKU grunting]
[BLUE laughs]
[GOKU, KRILLIN grunting]
Have something to say?
You're mumbling. Speak up.
I'm not afraid of you!
Fine. Now this might
sting a little bit.
[GOKU groaning]
Stay with me. We have
a long way to go.
[GOKU groaning]
[BLUE laughs]
Relax. You look a bit stiff...
You should enjoy life
while you have it.
Get up! Wha--?
[BLUE] I'm getting
bored with your torso.
Let's try the head.
[BULMA screams]
[BULMA screaming]
[BLUE gasps]
[KRILLIN gasps]
Lousy weather we're having...
And just when we were
beginning to have fun.
Oh well, I guess we'll have to
go to the abridged version.
[GOKU yelps]
Alright kids,
here's how this works.
Now, I'm only gonna say
this once, so pay attention.
You tell me where
the Dragon Ball is
and I don't blow his head off.
[BULMA gasps]
Start talking.
[GOKU yelps]
Wait! Okay. I'll tell you
what you want to know.
According to my radar,
the Dragon Ball
is in that pool over there.
[BLUE laughs]
Extraordinary...
That is the last place I
would have thought to look.
[GOKU whimpers]
The Red Ribbon Army
thanks you for your cooperation.
Say goodbye to your friend.
He must be going.
No! You can't hurt him!
I-I told you where
the Dragon Ball is!
Let him go!
You promised!
I did?
Well, I guess I lied.
Well. Bye, bye!
[BULMA screams]
How can he survive
a gunshot?! He can't!
He may be strong but
he's only human...!
He'll shoot me next. I know it!
How did I get into this mess?!
It's not fair! Just look at me!
I'm too beautiful to die!
Nice to see you care.
[GOKU grunting]
Open wide!
[BULMA screams]
[KRILLIN gasps]
[GOKU grunting]
[BLUE screaming]
Hey, I can move again!
That's great! Goku, quick!
Now's your chance!
Get him while he's distracted.
Kick him once
in the head for me!
Why are you scared?
It's just a mouse!
That wasn't a mouse!
Did you see the
size of its tail?!
I hate rodents!
That mouse saved me.
Stop crying and fight fair!
[BLUE] Fairness is the
last resort of the weak!
[BLUE growls]
[GOKU yells]
[BLUE yelps]
My eyes! Oh, you brat!
I'm not a brat!
[BLUE groaning]
[BULMA, KRILLIN cheering]
[GOKU laughs]
[ALL gasp]
[BULMA, KRILLIN gasp]
[KRILLIN, BULMA gasping]
[BULMA, KRILLIN scream]
Let's get outta here!
This place is falling apart!
Ooh...
[BULMA gasps]
[BULMA panting]
[KRILLIN yells]
[BULMA screams]
[KRILLIN, GOKU]
Bulma!
[BULMA grunting]
[GOKU] It's a good thing
you know how to climb.
[KRILLIN] We thought you
were a goner for sure!
I would have been if I would've
waited for you two to help!
[KRILLIN]
Check it out guys!
I can't believe we did it!
We found the treasure!
It's all ours!
[BULMA]
What good's a treasure
if we're not around
to enjoy it?! Let's go!
[GOKU]
What about the Dragon Ball?!
Like I said before, it's at
the bottom of the pool.
But there's no time
to get it now! Come on!
Goku! Come on!
You guys go ahead.
I'll catch up.
I have to go after
the Dragon Ball.
It might be my grandpa's.
[BULMA gasps]
No! Goku, wait!
I don't believe it!
There's nothing we can do!
Come on, we'll meet him outside!
[KRILLIN, BULMA gasp]
[KRILLIN, BULMA yelping]
[BULMA] We shouldn't
be far from the sub!
[KRILLIN] Let's hope the
submarine is still there!
[BULMA] If it's not,
we've got a long way to swim!
[BULMA, KRILLIN screaming]
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU]
Where are you?!
Come on! It's gotta be here!
[BULMA, KRILLIN screaming]
[KRILLIN]
Bulma, I'm getting a cramp!
[BULMA] Move it or you're gonna
be a permanent resident here!
[BULMA, KRILLIN scream]
Are you okay?!
[KRILLIN] Yeah, I think so.
What about the submarine?
I don't know.
I think it's still intact!
[KRILLIN] Great! How are we
supposed to get to it, huh?
We'll be crushed by rubble!
We can do it!
If we stay here,
we're goners for sure!
So buck up and follow my lead!
[BULMA] Quick, untie us.
I'll get the engine started!
What about Goku?
He's been gone a long time!
Not here.
Empty.
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU] Oh no! What if that
mean guy fell on top of it?
Hey! Mousy!
[GOKU giggles, groans]
Boy, I've been looking
everywhere for you!
We'd better get
out of this place!
Come on, you can ride with me,
little guy! Here goes!
[BLUE whimpering]
[BLUE]
Oh!
The legend is reality!
It's magnificent!
Enough riches to forge a
kingdom! And it's all mine!
All... mine!
[BLUE cackling]
I am invincible!
Huh?
[BLUE screams]
It's running!
Fuel level is fine.
We're ready to go!
--And not a moment too soon.
--[KRILLIN] Move it, Goku!
That building's
about to collapse!
[KRILLIN]
Goku!
[GOKU grunting]
[BULMA]
This is insane!
Why'd he have to go
after that stupid ball?!
It's not gonna do
him any good dead!
Oh! Stop talking like he's
not going to make it out!
He'll be fine!
And how do you
know that, huh?
We barely made it out alive
and we were running
as fast as we could.
Goku wasn't going to leave
without that Dragon Ball.
[KRILLIN growls]
Fine...
So what if it were you in there?
I'd expect you to make
the same decision
I'm having to make right now!
[KRILLIN whimpers]
We're leaving. Now.
I wish there was another
option, but there's not.
If Goku were here,
he'd say the same thing.
[GOKU grunting]
[NARRATOR] Can Goku escape
the crumbling fortress in time?
Will Bulma and Krillin really
leave their friend behind?
For those answers and more,
stay tuned for the next
thrilling episode
of Dragon Ball!