[CROWD cheers]
[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball,
the crowds gathered from
far and wide to witness
the spectacle of the World
Martial Arts Tournament.
And what a spectacle it was!
Krillin kick-started the action
by knocking the wind out
of the foul Bacterian.
Next, Yamcha displayed
his finest fighting moves,
but fell at the
hands of Jackie Chun.
Nam used his
disciplined fighting style
to combat the feminine
wiles of Ranfan.
And Goku stunned the crowd
by toppling the
Monster Beast Giran!
[NARRATOR] Krillin attacked
Jackie Chun in the semifinals,
but was unable to penetrate
the old man's defenses.
And Goku's raw
strength proved to be
more than Nam could handle,
despite his finest efforts,
[NARRATOR] Now,
only two competitors remain,
and the final match to
determine the new World Champion
will pit Goku's youthful
enthusiasm against the age
and experience of Jackie Chun.
But, little does Goku realize,
the man he's about to fight
is in fact none other
than Master Roshi,
who has cleverly
concealed his identity
to put his pupil
to the ultimate test.
[OOLONG] Oh! Pardon me!
'Scuse me! Comin' through!
Hey Oolong,
any luck finding Master Roshi?
Uh uh... I... couldn't
get anywhere in this crowd.
I just can't believe
he'd miss this fight...
He's got to be here somewhere...
Now...!
Let's have a quick word
with our two finalists
before this match
gets underway...
What do you say?
[ANNOUNCER]
Goku, could you tell us a little
about your strategy
going into this bout?
Huh? My... strada-what?
Your... strategy.
That is... your plans
for winning the fight?
Oh, I don't know.
I guess... my stra-je-dy
is to do my best!
Well then...
There you have it...!
A boy of few words indeed...!
But I guess you don't
have to say much
when you've made it all
the way to the finals!
[CROWD cheering]
Now it's time,
to talk to our next
competitor, Jackie Chun,
and I'm certain
this fighting veteran
is going to have plenty to say!
[ANNOUNCER] Jackie, what
are your plans for this match?
Jackie...?
Mister Chun...?
[snoring]
Uh... Well he, he seems
to be sleeping right now.
Ha, ha, ha, ha...
Just like a true master...
Extremely relaxed
before the big fight.
Ha ha ha ha.
[YAMCHA] You know, Krillin?
Now that I'm sure that
old guy isn't Master Roshi,
I think Goku actually has
a chance of winning this thing.
[KRILLIN] Maybe...
But, that "old guy"
beat the two of us
like a couple of chumps...!
I'm not so sure...
Here we go...
That's my cue...
Let the match... begin!!
Oh! Jackie Chun has...
taken the offensive!
He's looking for
another quick victory!
Oh no! Just like that!
He's out?!
And he can't use the
Flying Nimbus this time!
Foolish boy...!
If I've told him once,
I've told him a thousand times!
Never let your guard down!
"Danger is the nosey next
door neighbor of Security!"
If he'd just remembered that,
he might not've
lost so quickly...
Well, this is bad...
What do I do now?
[JACKIE CHUN cackles]
[ANNOUNCER] It would seem
Jackie Chun has done it again!
Hey, what'd you expect?
Despite his advanced age,
this seasoned martial artist...
continues to amaze!
In what may be record time,
he's managed to defeat
yet another opponent
with a minimum of effort!
It's what I do.
Ohhh, he lost the match...
Guess that old man
really knows his stuff.
Goku never had a chance...
[BLUE HAT] Look!
[DOG] What's that?!
Huh? What? What's happening?
Haaaa? Huh?
Hm...? Wha?
Hmm? Oh... Hahahaha.
[CROWD cheers]
[JACKIE CHUN] Hm?
Hey! It's Goku!
Yay! I knew he couldn't lose!
Wha... bu... He's flying!
[chuckles]
[CROWD cheers]
Goku!
He's coming back!
That... boy!
[ANNOUNCER}
Ladies and Gentlemen,
I can hardly believe my eyes...!
Ho-ho-ho!
Is there no end to this
youngster's resourcefulness?
Goku's using his tail
to fly like a helicopter,
back into the ring!
[GOKU] Hello again!
[JACKIE CHUN]
Why you little... You were out!
Nyaaaaah!
You're pretty arrogant
for someone who almost lost...!
That tail's all that saved you!
Not really.
I could have flown back
with a Kamehameha
Wave like you did...
But I thought it'd be good
to save that for later.
[JACKIE CHUN] Hmph!
Quit kidding yourself son!
That technique
is far to difficult
for a child to perform!
You can't do it.
Yes I can!
[JACKIE CHUN thinking]
Hoo! Arrogant, I tell you...
Well, we'll see about that!
Are you so sure of
your Kamehameha Waves
that you'd try one against me,
the man who invented them?
You invented?
But I always thought
the Kamehameha Wave
was Master Roshi's trick...
Uhhh...
Well, of course it is...
I mean, how silly!
Of course he did it first!
Then, if he did it first,
why'd you say you invented them?
Uh...
My Kamehameha Waves are,
well uh, they're different!
How so?
Kid.
Has anyone ever told you that
you ask way too many questions?!
Uh... Uh....
[JACKIE CHUN] Why, it's uh...
It's perfectly
obvious, isn't it?
First... I balance!
Then... I stretch!
Next I focus my entire body...
With some mild aerobics!
Like I said... Different.
Huh...?
[JACKIE CHUN]
Ka... Me... Ha... Me...
[GOKU] Ka... Me... Ha... Me...
[JACKIE CHUN] Haaa!!!
[GOKU] Haaa!!!
It's not just me.
That was really scary, right?
[panting]
Why I... never...
See, I told you!
Ha ha ha! I can do it!
Amazing...!
In a day...
he's learned a move that
took me fifty years to master...
[CROWD cheers]
You're the best, Goku!
Keep it up, kid!
You got'im!
[GOKU chuckles]
Remember this day, folks!
This may be the
only time in your life
you'll see two masters
of the legendary
Kamehameha Wave
in the same arena!
The first is Jackie Chun,
and the second is this
amazing, amazing boy, Goku!
[JACKIE CHUN thinking]
Yes... Goku is amazing!
I really didn't expect
him to do this well...
No matter.
It'll all be over
with my next attack...
[ANNOUNCER] Now,
let the match continue!
So far these two incredible
finalists have fought to a draw,
but keep your eyes open,
because at some point
that's gotta change!
Only one of them can be named
the Champion of the World!
This is fun!
What should we try next?
Fun is it...?
Well, it's too bad
playtime's over...! Ha!
This again?
Don't you know
any better tricks?
You've done this one already!
Now, which one
is the real one?
[GOKU] Here!!
[JACKIE CHUN] I'm sorry...
Were you looking for me?
Huh?!
Oh, Goku!!
The Double After-Image!
Heh heh... Never fails...
Hey...! Don't you
have a job to do?
Oh, right! Sorry!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Sorry to put your lights
out like that, Goku,
but it had...
to end sometime...
[ANNOUNCER] Eight...!.
Ni--Oh!!
Why, of all the...
How does he do it?!
All right..
Now it's my turn!
You little copy cat!
Think you can use
my own trick on me--do you...?
Well it's not going to work!
Hmph!
Just as I thought--a
double after-image!
[JACKIE CHUN] Not to worry...
Heh heh... I know right
where to find you...
[GOKU] Here I am!
The Triple After-image!
I made that up myself...!
You like it?
New rule.
No hitting your
teacher in the head.
What?
What do you mean?
You're not my teacher...
My teacher's Master Roshi!
Of course he is...!
I knew that!
Just got a little confused...
[GOKU thinking] That's twice
he's confused himself
with Master Roshi...
What...? What is it?
Why are you looking
at me like that?
[GOKU] I got it!
I figured it out...!
You're Master Roshi's brother!
Huh...? Phew... Ha!
You caught me!
We're family all right!
Oooh...
That explains
why you look like him!
[JACKIE CHUN]
Uh, Yeah, he he...
eh, but I'm not
actually his brother...
Here, look... You see...?
I'm his cousin!
[GOKU] Huh?
[JACKIE CHUN] Hm?
Wha...?
Bu, eh... I... well... uh...
Well I am, you know. Really.
Hahahaha.
But--this is no time
to be laughing...
We have a match to finish.
What are you doing?
Uh... What's the matter...?
You okay?
[ANNOUNCER] Oh!
And Jackie Chun is staggering
wildly about the ring...!
Either he's a little punch-drunk
from that last blow to the head,
or he's been taking a few too
many pulls off the ol' flask,
if you know what I mean...
Are you all right?
Ow! What'd you
do that for?
Hey, are you crazy?
Is that...
Don't be fooled Goku...!
He's using the
Drunken Boxing Technique!
He's only pretending
to be tipsy!
Tipsy?
He, he, he!
You know, 'Tipsy'!
Tanked! Looped! Schnockered!
I know... Drunken Boxing!
I recognize it now...!
That was one of...
my grandpa's specialties...
I wonder how he knows it?
[ANNOUNCER] Look at this!
It seems there may
be some method
to Jackie's madness after all!
Ha ha! Everybody dance!
[ANNOUNCER] Then again--
he could just be
out of his gourd...
[ANNOUNCER] Uh oh!
Looks like Goku's having
trouble staying on his feet!
Having some trouble, Goku...?
Yes, it's hard to Drunken Box...
if you've never
been drunk before!
Oh. Oh no.
Come on, kid...
Hang in there...
Uh oh!
Last call...!
Everybody go home...!
Time to go...!
[JACKIE CHUN] Wait...
You know I didn't mean that...
literally, right?
Hey... are... are you... crying?
[monkey noises]
What are you doing?!
Come on! Stop goofing around!
[JACKIE CHUN] I thought we...
agreed no hitting in the head!
What're you trying
to do to me...?
Crazy Monkey Technique!
Oooh! There you go, kid!
Give it to 'im good, Goku!
Goku's gonna win!
I never had a doubt!
[ANNOUNCER] Once again,
the tide of this Championship
bout has turned!
Goku's wild "monkey" attacks
have given him the advantage...!
It looks like Jackie Chun
has an uphill battle
to fight if he hopes
to regain control!
Oh, I'm not out of this yet...
In fact, I've already won...
You have?
[ANNOUNCER] What's this?
Jackie Chun has just
named himself the winner!
[ANNOUNCER]
But let's watch and see
if he has the moves
to back up his claim!
Don't be surprised
if this fighting master
still has a few fearsome
tricks up his sleeve!
[GOKU] Huh?
[ANNOUNCER] Uh oh!
This doesn't look good for Goku!
Jackie's gathering the
energy for his next attack,
which may be the
only one he'll need
to win this match and
become World Champion!
[NARRATOR] Jackie Chun,
the disguised Master Roshi,
has reached into his
bag of fighting techniques
and pulled out a
powerful finishing move!
Can Goku withstand
the coming attack?
Find out--next time
on Dragon Ball!