[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
The 22nd World
Martial Arts Tournament
came down to the final match:
Goku versus Tien Shinhan.
In the beginning,
the fight was balanced.
That is, until Goku
found himself
in a vulnerable position,
of which Tien took full
advantage, using his Dodon Ray.
[NARRATOR] Goku recovered and
launched into a counter-attack
using his proven
disappearing technique.
However, Tien was ready for him
and responded with
furious force...
Goku was defenseless
as his opponent
subjected him to a
hailstorm of punches
that left the young warrior
battered and bruised.
[NARRATOR] Goku appeared
to be down for the count.
Worse, his fate was in the hands
of his ruthless opponent.
Can Goku recover in time,
or will Tien Shinhan satisfy
his thirst for revenge
and win the tournament?
The answer is moments away!
Don't die on me yet.
I've got a special technique
I've been saving just for you.
This could turn out
to be the shortest finale
in the tournament's
long history.
What Tien Shinhan will do
next is anyone's guess,
though I'll wager it
won't bode well for Goku.
Um, is he about
to do what I think?
[SHEN cackles] Hopefully.
It is his favorite technique.
Aww, wake up, Goku.
Poor Goku.
He'll pull through. Don't worry.
Really?!
That looks painful.
Come on, you've got
tougher skin that that!
[cackles]
The Volleyball Technique!
[laughs]
It looks like Tien's
unusual technique...
...is exactly what it says.
He's toying with Goku
like a volleyball,
and setting him up for a spike!
[yells]
[grunting]
[yelling continues]
Get ready... Spike!
--No!
--[CROWD gasping]
[GOKU groans]
[KRILLIN, ROSHI gasp]
[SHEN cackles]
Great!
[MAN] This match better last
longer than my popcorn.
[ANNOUNCER whimpers]
Is he breathing?!
Goku!
Get up.
[TIEN]
Yamcha's here. Good.
--[CROWD cheers]
--What?! No way.
Incredibly, Goku is
on his feet again!
Impossible!
--[KRILLIN] Oh!
--[ROSHI sighs]
Goku, don't frighten us, okay!
Next time get up sooner!
That kid's tough as nails!
Get 'em, Goku!
Well, it's nothing
short of miraculous
that Goku is even alive,
let alone standing, after
such brutal punishment!
That was interesting,
but I don't think
I enjoy being the ball.
Well, you're resilient.
Stupid, but resilient.
You're not very nice,
but you are strong.
I guess it would be
safe from here on out
if I used my full strength.
[laughs]
Let me guess...
You've been holding back
out of concern for my safety.
Yeah, but now I'll fight normal.
[TIEN gasps]
N-Normal!?
Does that word apply to Goku?
Whenever I fight in a match,
I have to watch myself
so I don't get carried away.
I call it my battle strength.
I'll tell ya what...
The goal here is for you to die.
How that happens,
I really don't care.
So you have fun with your
little battle strength
and then I'll kill you.
Fine. You can try.
I won't have to try.
It's too easy.
What? Eh, get ready.
Here comes round two.
[TIEN groaning]
[GOKU grunts]
[TIEN groans]
[TIEN yelps]
[GOKU]
Ka...
--Wow, Goku is on a roll
--[GOKU] Me...
as he prepares to dazzle us
with his Kamehameha Wave,
the signature technique of
the Turtle Hermit school.
Ha...
Me...
Hold on.
In a bizarre shift in strategy,
Goku has withdrawn
his technique,
giving Tien Shinhan
time to recover.
This may well go down as the
turning point in the battle.
[KRILLIN, ROSHI gasp]
[TIEN groaning]
That's what I call
battle strength.
[laughs]
Thank you. That was the
most exhilarating rush...
I haven't felt this alive in a
long time. It feels wonderful!
So, what you're saying is
you like getting beat up?
I don't get it.
Why would Goku pass up
the perfect opportunity
to defeat him?
It just doesn't make any sense.
[YAMCHA] Goku had
a good reason... I hope.
[gasps]
Finally we have an
interesting battle.
Tien is an excellent opponent.
[PUAR, OOLONG]
What!?
All right, I've indulged you
long enough. It's time to pay.
I don't think so.
Tension in the ring is high...
Despite the extraordinary
toll this fight has taken
on its opponents,
neither seems to be showing
any sign of fatigue.
Boy, Goku made a huge mistake
by stopping his Kamehameha Wave.
Did he really? Look closer.
There is a very fine line
that distinguishes
ineptitude from strategy.
Huh?
[ROSHI] If Goku had followed
through with his plan,
Tien Shinhan would
have dodged the wave...
Goku would have wasted energy
and left himself vulnerable.
You're great, Tien.
[cackles]
Tien has that look in his eye.
Nothing can save Goku now!
[yells]
[KRILLIN]
Oh! Wow!
Rarely have we seen
fighters display
such an unrelenting fury!
Goku and Tien Shinhan are taking
this fight to a whole new level.
Everything is to the extreme.
Why, if an ordinary man was
to be on the receiving end
of one of those punches,
he'd probably never wake up!
Watch Goku... His breathing.
Uh, what?
It's calm.
Throughout that exertion
he never lost his breath once.
Oh...
All eyes are glued to the fight,
and one can't help but wonder...
What awesome technique
will we see next?
[GOKU]
Hm?
[yells]
[KRILLIN] They're fighting
so fast, it's like a blur.
[ROSHI]
Maybe you need glasses.
The pace at which these two
are fighting is staggering.
This may be the world's
record for speed combat!
It's a good thing there aren't
any rules inside the ring.
I don't think our judges
could see clearly enough
to enforce them!
Give him a left, Goku!
Now a right!
--Yeah! That's it! Clobber him!
--[OOLONG grunting] Ow! Ah!
[ANNOUNCER] Goku has taken
command of the fight
with an explosive offensive!
He's pushing Tien to the edge of
the ring. There's no more room!
Haaa!
Yeah! Pin him down, Goku! Huh?
What a rebound!
Tien Shinhan deftly avoided
expulsion from the ring
and has taken a decisive lead
in his bid to overtake Goku!
Don't stop. Keep punching!
[ANNOUNCER] That's what I
call a divided offense!
Goku has split into... 1, 2,
3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9... 10 Gokus!
You whelp. I can't be fooled
by optical illusions.
But you'll learn.
Ah-yah!
--[GOKU] Gotcha!
--[TIEN] Huh?
Now who's seeing double?!
Goku! Look out!
[KRILLIN, ROSHI yelp]
[ALL gasp]
Tien, no!
[CROWD gasping, murmuring]
Yeah!
[OOLONG growls]
--[BULMA giggles]
--[YAMCHA grunting]
Easy, Bulma.
[ANNOUNCER] Spectacular! I don't
think a single person here
would label that stunt as
anything less than
extraordinary!
Goku's success with the
Mirror-Image Technique
has left Tien face down!
I guess there's a first
time for everything.
[TIEN grunting]
[gasps]
It's... not over.
I thought you were knocked out!
Not again! What's this
guy made of?!
He's tough.
Fools, Tien would never
go down that easy.
You idiot! You think
your infantile abilities
can defeat me? Me?!
You're hardly even a challenge!
I don't know. It looked like
you were having to
fight pretty hard.
You dare to mock me?!
Then prepare for my wrath!
Fine!
Ha, ha, ha!
Say, it appears there's still
fight left in this match!
Cover your eyes, everyone,
because Tien is at it again!
Solar Flare!
[yells]
[grunting]
[CROWD gasping]
Doesn't get any brighter!
[TIEN]
Wanna bet?!
[TIEN yells]
[cackles, yells]
[TIEN groans]
Whoa! Now there's something
you don't see every day!
Goku should be seeing stars
right about now, but the blast
looks to have had
no effect on him.
In fact, it's Tien who
looks out of sorts.
What...? How... did...
you survive?
[GOKU giggles]
See? Sunglasses!
But... Sunglasses?!
Where did you get them!?
Borrowed.
[ANNOUNCER] Tien has collapsed!
It seems all but certain
that Goku will be
claiming this match!
Tien Shinhan!
[ROSHI] Hey! What happened?!
Where did my--
--[ANNOUNCER] One...
--But I don't understand...
How could Goku even
--[ANNOUNCER] Two...
--see Tien to fight?
--Three...
--How am I supposed to know?
--Four...
--What happened, Yamcha?
He improvised.
[YAMCHA] He knew the
Sun Technique would have
the same blinding effect
that it did on Jacky Chun,
so he borrowed
Master Roshi's sunglasses.
The tinted lenses allowed him
to see Tien's approach.
Therefore, it was easy
for Goku to track
Tien's movements and
block his assault.
Wow...
Thank you, Master Roshi.
These helped.
--[ANNOUNCER] Five...
--You're welcome.
Quick thinking.
I wish I would've
--[ANNOUNCER] Six...
--thought of it.
[ANNOUNCER]
Seven...
[growls]
Goku!
Ow! That hurt!
You made my ears ring!
This is getting old!
Give up now...
If you know what's
good for you.
Leave him alone, you big bully!
Oh?
[YAMCHA, BULMA]
Uh...
My... sunglasses.
[SHEN thinking] Tien had better
get it right this time.
I want that brat to suffer!
[SHEN thinking] If I could,
I'd get on that stage
and ring your
little neck myself!
Ah!
You may not like me, but I'm not
giving up for you or anybody!
Whatever!
[ROSHI]
Hm?
Forgive me for staring, Master.
I've never seen you
without your glasses before.
[ROSHI]
What difference does it make?
None. It's just your
eyes look familiar.
As if I've seen them
somewhere before.
U-Uh, yes. I-I get that a lot.
I'm certain... But where?
If you focused your attention on
the match instead of my eyes,
you might actually
learn something!
Yes... Master!
[yells]
[grunts]
[GOKU groans]
[KRILLIN, ROSHI gasp]
Tien Shinhan hits Goku
with a powerful right punch!
Goku!
[gasping]
Not fair!
So what.
[cackles]
[NARRATOR] Whatever mysterious
force has taken hold of Goku,
it's left him powerless
against Tien's attack.
Will he regain his strength
before it's too late?
Or will Tien be victorious?
Find out on the next
action-packed episode
of Dragon Ball!