[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball,
Goku continued his perilous
assent of Muscle Tower.
And a heated battle
against Major Metallitron
left the metal
monster terminated.
Murasaki proved to be a
dangerous adversary
as he turned the
tower's third floor
into a treacherous
obstacle course.
But Goku was up
to the challenge.
In the end, the tricky
ninja got the point.
[NARRATOR] Goku also met the
peaceful Android Number 8,
who befriended the young
warrior and became his ally.
But greater danger
still lay ahead.
Goku made a shocking discovery
when he encountered
the evil monster, Buyon.
The creature was
incredibly strong--
Even strong enough to withstand
Goku's mighty Kamehameha Wave!
The future looked
grim for our hero
until he got some fresh air
and discovered the
creature didn't like the cold.
In fact, once exposed,
Buyon fell to pieces...
literally!
[NARRATOR] Now, only one enemy
remains: General White!
This is your last
chance, mister!
Let the village chief go now!
[GOKU] Give me
the village chief.
[WHITE] You didn't say "please".
[WHITE growls]
"Please" give me back the
Village Chief right now!
[WHITE] Not if you got on
your knees and begged.
[WHITE growls]
I don't wanna hurt you...
but I will if I have to!
Hah!
I guess I have no choice
but to surrender...
You obviously have me
at a disadvantage...
I'm probably crazy for
saying this but--
Guess I'll risk it.
Okay! I tried it the nice way.
You asked for it!
[WHITE] Hmph.
Violence isn't the answer.
We must talk through
our problems.
We are men, not monsters.
[WHITE] Shut up!
[NUMBER 8 grunts]
Are you okay?
Hah! Weak simpleton.
Can you hear me? Eighter?!
[NUMBER NUMBER 8] Please, don't
fight--Note: Goku will cut Eight
off around "fight"
[GOKU] It's okay.
[WHITE] No way this brat has any
energy left after fighting
Buyon.
[WHITE] You want some pain?
[GOKU] Fine!
[NUMBER 8] Watch out for his
left hook!
[WHITE] You think that's funny?!
[WHITE] Look!
[NUMBER 8]
[WHITE] Take that.
[GOKU] Hey, that tickles, stop
it!
[GOKU] My turn.
[GOKU] Had enough yet?
[WHITE] This child is much too
strong.
[WHITE] Gotcha!
[GOKU] I don't feel so good.
[WHITE] I caught the lamb...
[NUMBER 8] Please stop hurting
him...
[WHITE] Stop talking!
[NUMBER 8] Goku.
[WHITE] Don't go to sleep on
me...
[GOKU] So tired.
[WHITE] Get ready.
[NUMBER 8] Goku!
[NUMBER 8] Goku?!
[WHITE] I really love kids.
[NUMBER 8] Don't get up, Goku.
[GOKU] That was a mean trick.
[GOKU] Try...
[WHITE] But how...
[NUMBER 8] No, Goku!
[NUMBER 8] You've won...
[GOKU] Not yet...
[GOKU] Look at him!
[NUMBER 8] Maybe.
[NUMBER 8] Goku, you're better
than that.
[GOKU] You're right...
[GOKU] Hey!
[WHITE] Perfect.
[GOKU] What's so funny?
[WHITE] Of course.
[WHITE] I accept defeat...
[GOKU] Great...
[WHITE] This way.
[GOKU] You're doing the right
thing...
[VILLAGE CHIEF] Strange...
[WHITE] Get out...
[VILLAGE CHIEF] I'm free?
[VILLAGE CHIEF] Are you the one
responsible for this?
[GOKU] Yep!
[VILLAGE CHIEF] You did?
[VILLAGE CHIEF] I'm going home!
[VILLAGE CHIEF] You defeated the
General all by yourself?
[GOKU] This is Eighter.
[NUMBER 8]
[VILLAGE CHIEF] Thank you.
[GOKU] You won't have to worry
anymore...
[VILLAGE CHIEF] That's
marvelous!
[GOKU] Well...
[VILLAGE CHIEF] Great!
[NUMBER 8] Finally we can laugh
again!
[WHITE] Don't anyone move a
single muscle!
[VILLAGE CHIEF] Let me go!
[GOKU] Don't hurt him.
[WHITE] That's up to you!
[VILLAGE CHIEF]
[WHITE] Don't try anything
heroic and he'll be just fine...
[GOKU] Let him go!
[NUMBER 8] Please, General.
[WHITE] Watch me leave or watch
him die...
[GOKU] You won't get away with
this, I promise you that!
[WHITE] So...
[WHITE] You do understand what
dead means, right!
[WHITE] Take one more step...
[VILLAGE CHIEF] UNCUT:Kill him!
[VILLAGE CHIEF] UNCUT:Do it now,
boy!
[GOKU] But what--
[VILLAGE CHIEF] Think about the
village!
[GOKU] Really?
[GOKU] Okay, I'll do it to save
your village.
[WHITE] UNCUT:This isn't a joke!
[GOKU] He's not afraid of you
and neither am I!
[VILLAGE CHIEF] No need to be
hasty.
[VILLAGE CHIEF] Returning to my
village alive certainly has its
advantages.
[WHITE] He doesn't want to die.
[VILLAGE CHIEF] No I, uh, I
guess not.
[WHITE] So...
[NUMBER 8] Wait!
[NUMBER 8] Have mercy, General.
[WHITE] Spare me!
[WHITE] I gave you a place in
this army and now I find that my
destroyer is a daisy.
[WHITE] Your pleas of compassion
make me sick.
[NUMBER 8] Please, listen--
[WHITE] You're a traitor...
[WHITE] Actually, there is
another way.
[NUMBER 8] Really?
[WHITE] Yes.
[WHITE] I know it's difficult.
[GOKU] Leave him alone!
[NUMBER 8] Please, don't make me
do this.
[WHITE] Come on!
[NUMBER 8] No...
[GOKU] Eighter.
[WHITE] Eight.
[GOKU] That's enough!
[GOKU] Stop picking on him!
[GOKU] I'm not scared of you!
[WHITE] Okay...
[WHITE] Do it!
[GOKU] Fine!
[WHITE] Move!
[GOKU] Okay!
[WHITE] You die.
[NUMBER 8] No!
[WHITE] Stupid little lamb!
[NUMBER 8] Goku!
[WHITE] Say hello to oblivion!
[WHITE] You want me?
[NUMBER 8] You're not going to
cause any more pain, General!
[WHITE] Stop!
[WHITE] Don't touch me!
[WHITE] Why aren't you working?!
[NUMBER 8] It's your turn to
suffer...
[NUMBER 8] Goku!
[NUMBER 8] Oh, Goku.
[VILLAGE CHIEF] Come on boy!
[GOKU] I'm fine...
[NUMBER 8] You're alive!
[GOKU] You okay?
[NUMBER 8] I'm fine, Goku.
[GOKU] Good.
[GOKU] Eighter, what's an
android?
[NUMBER 8] It's a robot that
looks human, but inside it's
still a machine.
[GOKU] So I'm a human...
[NUMBER 8] That's the nicest
thing anyone's said to me.
[VILLAGE CHIEF] The sun is
shining on a new day.
[NUMBER 8] Wait.
[NUMBER 8] Wait here.
[VILLAGE CHIEF] Come on!
[NUMBER 8] It's Eighter.
[VILLAGE CHIEF] Oh sorry, big
fella.
[NUMBER 8] It's okay.
[VILLAGE CHIEF] Well, sure beats
fireworks.
[SUNO] Smells great.
[SUNO] There's somebody here!
[SUNO] Come look!
[NUMBER 8] How are you feeling,
Goku?
[GOKU] Yes.
[NUMBER 8] Goku!
[GOKU] I am dying...
[VILLAGE CHIEF] We're here!
[SUNO] It's the Village Chief...
[FATHER] That's the chief.
[MOTHER] No!
[SUNO] Why isn't Goku with them?
[SUNO] It's Goku!
[SUNO] Oh, Goku.
[GOKU] These taste great!