[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball.
Goku was eager
to begin training for
the World Martial
Arts Tournament
and Mr. Popo was there to see
that he stuck to his program.
Even though the tournament
was three years away,
Goku was put through the paces
by a very special doll
that Mr. Popo
had designed himself.
And it was clear that Goku
had a lot of work to do.
[POPO] It's as I've
told you before, dear boy.
Your speed and skill are
matched evenly with the doll,
only you haven't finished
your mind training.
[NARRATOR] Taking Mr.
Popo's advice to heart,
Goku came out swinging,
but he still had a tough time
toppling his overly
animated opponent.
[NARRATOR] Luckily time
was still on their side,
and Goku could rest up
before he began his next
strenuous training session.
[GOKU snoring]
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, Yamcha,
Tien, Chiaotzu, and Krillin
were on their way
to Korin's Tower
in the hope that
they could improve
their own fighting skills.
Does this mean
that Goku's friends will become
his most fearsome competition?
[tribal music playing]
So this Korin tower,
does it really exist?
It has to exist. That's where
Goku's training right now.
And I guarantee
he's gotten a lot stronger
since undertaking this burden.
Goku's even stronger? Really?
Be patient. You'll see, Krillin.
We'll have a better idea
of where the tower is
once we get over this mountain.
Perhaps the people in the
area can show us the way.
[distant animal howling]
[KRILLIN moaning]
Tien?
What's goin' on?
[YAMCHA]
Uh.
[CHIAOTZU]
Huh?
Do you hear it?
Hear what?
[TIEN]
Drums, crying,
singing and shouting,
many voices...
...coming from the forest.
Uh... Unh-uh.
Hm. I don't hear it.
How 'bout you?
Hello?!
What's wrong Chiaotzu?
Uh!
I guess he must
still be asleep.
Or he hears some animals.
It's horrible.
[BOTH gasp]
It's something bad. Horrible.
Uh.
Hey, stop trying to
scare us, would ya?
It's not like this place isn't
creepy enough on its own.
Let's all go back to sleep.
You were imagining
things, that's all.
[YAMCHA chuckles]
[TIEN]
Hmmm...
[tribal music plays]
[music continues]
[GOKU groans]
[yawns]
What are we going
to do today, Popo?
I'll be your
training partner today
if that's all right with you?
Are you sure?
Mhm.
All right then,
I hope you're ready.
I won't be beaten as
easily as last time ya know.
No, not that.
We're not going to fight.
But. What do you mean?
You and I are going
to play hide and seek.
What's hide and seek?
[GOKU]
Uh...
First you go and hide
and I'll try and catch you.
You can go anywhere you like.
Do you understand?
Okay. But this game
sounds kinda crazy to me.
How are you going to find
me with that blindfold on?
How about you hide and
find out what happens?
Ready?
Mhmmm!
Uh, what's wrong, Popo?
[POPO] I'm trying to
pick up the spiritual energy
emanating from your body.
[POPO]
Hmm...
Aah!
[GOKU laughing]
--[GOKU giggling]
--[POPO grunting]
Uuuaaah!
[grunting]
[GOKU]
I won't let him catch me.
[POPO grunts]
--[GOKU yells]
--[POPO chuckles]
[GOKU hollering]
[yells]
[groans]
[POPO chuckles]
[chuckles]
[birds chirping]
It won't be too much
longer before we're
on the other side
of this mountain.
Yes.
I hope we find a village
somewhere soon
so we can have a hot meal and
sleep in a soft bed again.
He-heh. And if we're lucky
we'll meet
some pretty girls.
Yeah, in your dreams.
Ha! I'll go find 'em! He-heh!
[laughs]
Huh?
[yells]
[BOTH gasp]
[TIEN, YAMCHA grunt]
[TIEN grunts]
[YAMCHA]
Huh?
These don't look like
pretty girls to me.
[GIRL VOICE]
Where did you come from?
[giggles]
[KRILLIN]
Whew!
That's more like it.
[chuckles nervously]
[BOTH chuckle]
Here for the festival? Welcome!
What? You're having
a festival? That's great!
[laughing]
[CHILDREN laughing]
Once a year the entire village
gets together for this festival
to celebrate the mountain
that protects us.
You thank the mountain?
[GIRL]
Yes. Up there.
The mountain spirit protects
our village from danger.
That's why we give thanks.
[WOMAN humming]
Umm... Umm...
[MEN]
Hum. Hum. Hum. Hum.
[WOMAN]
Mmm... Umm...
That statue represents
the mountain spirit.
Isn't it beautiful?!
Sure is somethin'.
The drums I heard last night
came from this village.
That was a ceremony.
Now I understand.
So that's what
all the noise was about.
Shh!
Hey. My name is Krillin.
Hi, Krillin. My name's Mint.
[KRILLIN]
What a beautiful name.
--[KRILLIN] Aah!
--[birds cawing]
--[BOTH gasp]
--[ALL gasp]
--[birds cawing]
[ALL gasp]
[hollers]
[GOKU grunts]
[laughs]
I gave him the slip.
[GOKU]
Uuh! Uh?
Mr. Popo?!
[yells]
[yelling]
You're too fast!
The game is over.
I believe I've caught you
my little friend.
But how did you know
what moves I was gonna make?
Oh, it was really
quite simple.
I could feel your spiritual
energy all around me.
Awww...
Now this time
try and find me.
[GOKU] I can't see
a thing with this on.
How am I ever going to find him?
Well Goku,
what are you waiting for?
Okay.
[POPO]
Yoohoo. I'm over here.
I'm right here.
[POPO] Stop guessing.
You must focus on my energy.
I can't see a thing.
How am I supposed to catch you?
You see. I can control
my spiritual energy.
But you cannot.
[GOKU]
Mm?
Most everyone generates
an aura when they move.
You should be able to
see it if you concentrate.
Concentrate?
Use your mind and try to focus.
My mind?
Ah!
[laughing]
Pardon my asking, but we're
looking for Korin Tower.
I don't suppose if you'd
know if it is um,
anywhere near here?
Korin Tower? No, I haven't
heard of that place.
Too bad.
I bet if you ask the village
elder he might know where it is.
[KRILLIN]
Mm!
[TIEN grunts]
What's wrong, Chiaotzu?
You look worried.
[CHIAOTZU]
Something is very wrong here.
[TIEN]
What is it?
Hey pal.
Don't just stand there,
come over here and have a drink.
[KRILLIN giggles]
[groans]
--[VILLAGERS cheering]
--[WRESTLER] I give up.
That's it! He's done
it again! Paol wins!
[cheering, clapping]
[PAOL laughing]
Yes, you're a true champion.
You're the best. Well done.
Thank you, sir.
Excuse me, Elder?
Yes, what is it Mint?
I'm sorry to disturb you, sir,
but these boys would
like to ask you something.
Yeah, sir.
Wait, the first rule
of festival day
is for everyone
to have a good time.
I insist that you sit
and enjoy yourselves.
Sounds good.
Thank you.
Hmmm...
Here. Drink up.
[KRILLIN] I'm still
a little young to drink.
It's home made rootbeer.
I made it with
my own special recipe.
Well okay. If it's rootbeer.
Ooh. Mm.
Where ya from, stranger?
I'm from somewhere back east.
Hey, that's where I'm from!
[laughing]
Are you a warrior too?
[laughs]
I train everyday and I'm one of
the most bestest
fighters in the world.
[MAN]
Enjoy the festival.
[PAOL] Judging from his eyes
I can tell this guy
is no ordinary man.
[TIEN grunts]
It seems to me that you've been
in a fight or two in your time.
Care to accept
my challenge for a match?
Yeah. Great.
This could be interesting.
Why don't you accept.
If you win, we'll grant you
anything you want
in the whole village.
But good luck.
I doubt that you'll win.
Sure. You're on.
Tien.
I'll be fine.
[KRILLIN]
Hold it. Me first.
Let me have a chance
to fight the big guy.
You know I can take him.
It's what I've been
training for.
[hiccups]
What's with him?
[chuckles] Little man, you're
in no condition to fight me.
I'm okay, I just
drank a lot of rootbeer.
[hiccups]
He'll be fine, big brother.
Ha!
Your brother?
[MINT]
Uh-huh.
[laughs]
Imagine that.
[BOTH chuckle]
[PAOL] Don't worry. I'll go
easy on you, small fry.
[KRILLIN] Whenever you're
ready, ya meathead.
[PAOL, KRILLIN grunt]
[JUDGE]
Ready! Begin!
[PAOL] Look at him. He doesn't
even have his guard up.
[KRILLIN] I can't believe
that I'm doing this.
[hiccups]
[PAOL yells]
That little fella is quite
a good fighter after all.
[moans]
[chuckles]
[PAOL groans]
[VILLAGERS cheering]
He's won!
[cheering, clapping]
You fought well. Good job.
Hey thanks, big brother.
Brother?
[laughs]
Quite a festival, isn't it?
By the way young man,
I believe there was something
you wanted to ask me?
Yes, there is.
[clucking]
[bellows]
[squealing]
Look. The mountain
is going to explode.
[VILLAGERS chattering]
Explode?
Is that what you said?
Yeah.
What he'd say?
The mountain will blow up?
What are you crazy?
The mountain spirit has
always protected our village.
It would never blow up on us.
But it will.
I think you're
making all this up.
How can you say such a terrible
thing on this of all days?
Are you sure, Chiaotzu?
I'm positive.
--[WOMAN] Ooh...!
--[MEN gasp]
[gasping]
Get ready. Here it comes!
Ah! Aah...!
[distant rumbling]
[VILLAGERS yelling]
[yelling]
Aah!
[grunting]
[ALL yelling]
The spirit of the mountain
is angry with all of us.
Please everyone, beg for
your family's safety.
[VILLAGERS clamoring]
We've got to get out of here!
There may be
a way to stop this.
What are you gonna do?
I'm going to try and change
the course of the lava.
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
But Tien, it's too--
I've got to try something
before it's too late.
It's the only chance we have.
We must save the village.
Right, I'll help you.
[CHIAOTZU]
Wait.
Hey.
No Krillin!
[chuckles]
Be careful!
They must be crazy.
[TIEN] I know it's risky,
but I've got to
stop that lava.
[NARRATOR]
Is Tien overestimating
his own strength once again?
And what about Yamcha,
Chiaotzu, and Krillin?
They should know that
running straight into
an active volcano
will be no picnic.
They're all heading
into red hot trouble
that they might not
come out of alive.
Don't miss the next Dragon Ball.