[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
The 23rd World Martial Arts
Tournament continued
when Junior provided
the crowd a spectacle,
as he took on Krillin
in the third match.
[NARRATOR] The fierce combat
took its toll on Krillin
as he struggled to defeat
his powerful foe.
Despite the odds,
Krillin's determination
kept him in the fight,
as he exhausted the
extent of his training,
including the Kamehameha Wave...
In the end,
Junior was victorious.
[NARRATOR] The fourth match
pitted the oddball,
Hero, against Yamcha.
No one took the fight seriously,
including the
experienced warrior,
until it was too late.
[YAMCHA groans]
Who are you?!
[NARRATOR]
Hero shocked everyone
as he dropped his
bumbling idiot routine
and revealed his true nature:
that of a cunning warrior.
[HERO] You were paying so much
attention to my theatrics,
you never realized the
subtle moves I was making...
Didn't your master
ever teach you,
that you should never judge
power by appearance?
[NARRATOR]
Though stunned, Yamcha quickly
regained his composure and
launched into an attack.
[CROWD cheering]
Wolf Fang Fist!
[HERO]
No, you don't.
--[HERO grunts]
--[YAMCHA groans]
[CROWD gasps]
What good are fists
without feet?
The wolf is left
licking his wounds.
[ANNOUNCER]
In a shocking turn of events,
the match has shifted
in Hero's favor
as Yamcha struggles
to recuperate
from a crushing blow to the leg
he injured in the
last tournament!
He didn't fool me.
[YAMCHA grunting]
[YAMCHA groans]
[YAMCHA groaning]
[grunts]
[gasping]
[KRILLIN thinking]
Hero fights like a master!
Yamcha!
What are you doing?
Come on! Quit playing!
[LAUNCH] Yeah, stop showin' off
and take the old man down!
I don't think it's up
to Yamcha at this point.
He got more than
he bargained for.
[HERO] Aww, you look spent.
Why don't you take a moment?
I don't mind.
[panting]
[yells]
[HERO]
I'm right here, little man.
[yelps]
[YAMCHA groans]
Not good.
[YAMCHA groaning]
[BULMA growls]
Yamcha can't be defeated
like this... Get up.
Save your words of pity
for someone else, old man.
Because, I don't need 'em.
You're absolutely right. What
you need is some good coaching.
It isn't easy to excel
when you're so far
out of your league...
I'm much stronger than you.
[whispering] Just between
you and me... a secret...
I'm not from around here.
Huh, okay... But that's not
much of a secret...
No one's from around here.
Least of all, you, my friend.
[HERO]
No, you don't understand.
I'm not talking
about this tournament.
I mean this planet.
I'm a visitor.
[YAMCHA] Oh, I see.
That explains the hair.
I wasn't aware that aliens
looked so... human.
Oh, this is just a vessel. What
you might call rented space.
I inhabit this body.
[YAMCHA]
Hm?
He's an alien!
He said that? I can't
hear a thing...
What's an alien doin'
at our tournament?
Right. Thanks for
the confession.
But I'm an
equal-opportunity fighter...
I've defeated opponents
from many species...
Wherever it is you call home,
be it here or outer space,
it has no bearing on the
outcome of this match.
Yeah, I know your kind...
Misdirection is your
weapon of choice
and you use it quite well...
They say, the most
brutal weapons
are the ones we can't see.
Those forged from within.
Fortunately, I have quite
an arsenal to pull from.
Please, allow me to show
you a demonstration...
I'm not sure there are words to
describe the damage one can do
with raw spirit energy.
[HERO]
Ooh, looks dangerous.
[YAMCHA]
For you, only the best!
Oh, well, don't go
to too much trouble.
[ANNOUNCER] Yamcha's assurance
seems to signal his victory,
but Hero is holding fast
for whatever his opponent
is about to unleash!
Yamcha's chosen a risky course.
[YAMCHA laughing]
[gasps]
Whoa! What's that?!
Ready for this?
Eh, well I, uh...
Spirit Ball...
Attack!
[yelps]
Ha!
[yelling]
[yelps]
[yells]
[growls]
Nice reflexes, Hero!
That depends on your
point of view...
That's some technique
you got there.
[laughs]
Keep your chin up. You sound
distressed, old man.
[yells]
[yelps]
--[BOTH gasp]
--Yamcha!
[ROSHI]
Ha, ha!
Yeah!
[YAMCHA]
Yeah! Ha, ha, ha!
See ya... space nerd!
[HERO growls]
[YAMCHA yells]
[YAMCHA groans]
[YAMCHA groaning]
[HERO]
Mind your step, young one.
[YAMCHA groans]
[CROWD screams]
Oh, Yamcha!
No!
[gasps]
Yamcha has fallen out of bounds.
Therefore, Hero wins the match.
Yay! Yamcha survived!
[groaning]
No!
Something's wrong...
Hero... Oh, no!
[yelps]
[GOKU]
I know who he is.
I've seen his true face!
I should've known he'd
find a way to be here!
[HERO] Whew! That was
a delightful surprise
you had in store for me.
Too bad you let your guard down.
Still, you left your
mark on this body.
[HERO]
Seriously, you're good.
Huh?
You're a skilled young man.
I think you could
show me a thing or two.
Are you kidding?! You won it!
Perhaps.
[BULMA] They're chatting away
like old they're old friends.
Now that our match is over,
I have to ask you.
Just who are you, really?
I've heard of losing graciously,
but this is ridiculous.
[HERO] You are full of
curiosity, aren't you?
I would be so
depressed right now.
Why should he be upset?
He fought well...
There's no shame in that.
Sure, life's great.
Yamcha did swell.
[ROSHI] Mm-hm. His form and
technique were astounding.
He's turned into a fine warrior.
[YAMCHA laughs]
[sighs] It would just be nice
to see someone besides Goku
make it to the finals.
Yamcha deserves a
shot at the title.
Ah. I know what you mean.
Yamcha always gets
the toughest opponents.
[BULMA thinking]
He'll always be my champion.
[YAMCHA]
I don't mean to be pushy.
I'd just appreciate
knowing the identity
of one of the greatest
opponents I've ever faced.
All will be revealed in time.
[GOKU]
I know you... Kami.
[CROWD cheering]
[JUDGE] Come on. Put your backs
into it. We don't have all day.
Be sure it's centered.
I despise crooked tiles.
[ANNOUNCER] The ring has
seen its share of abuse
during this tournament.
But it's a small price
to pay for the excitement
and extraordinary drama
as only the World Martial
Arts Society can deliver!
With repairs nearly complete,
it's time to welcome
our top four athletes
to the semi-finals.
They are Tien Shinhan,
Goku, Junior, and Hero.
I think it's safe to say,
without exaggeration,
that those four men are the
world's strongest fighters.
Roshi, you sound
like a commercial.
Maybe you should do
the announcements.
They certainly couldn't
get any worse.
Even as I speak,
each fighter is undergoing
special preparation
for the battle ahead.
You're sweating badly, Goku.
Oops, I think I... uh...
I appreciate your concern,
but really, that tickles.
[ANNOUNCER]
Attention semi-finalists
and audience alike.
It is now time for the
semi-finals to begin.
The first match will be
Tien Shinhan versus Goku...
At this time, will both fighters
please make their
way to the ring?
[CHICHI]
Goku? Have a good fight.
Thanks.
Uh, I don't think this match
is going to be pretty.
Interesting, I wonder
how far their training
and enlightenment
have progressed
since their last battle.
I just hope they
both survive this...
with all their teeth intact.
[growls]
Well, if they don't break
some bones, I will.
[yelps]
We don't need this aggravation.
[ANNOUNCER] The last fight these
two were in is now legendary.
That battle closed out
the previous tournament,
and brought new meaning
to the word stamina!
Tien Shinhan was the victor,
by a narrow margin...
Both men have endured
three years of
training since then,
so we can expect three times the
power, three times the danger,
and three times the excitement!
Get ready for some
serious fireworks folks!
Because when these
two titans clash,
there's no telling
what may happen.
I assume this is
going to be intense.
Of course.
[CROWD cheers]
Goku's looking pretty
serious this time.
Is Tien Shinhan as
strong as he looks?
He's tremendously strong.
Just you wait.
Unlike these dullards,
I'm not so easily impressed.
[HERO thinking] Those "dullards"
might surprise you.
I've been looking
forward to this...
To be honest, I really didn't
feel like I won last time.
[GOKU laughs]
[ANNOUNCER]
And now, let the match begin!
[BOTH grunting]
[ANNOUNCER] It looks like this
fight has taken flight!
[ALL gasp]
[yells]
Whoa! Using astounding force,
Tien Shinhan has
caught up to Goku,
and now the two are trading
punches in mid-air!
[CHICHI gasps]
Tien Shinhan! Goku!
[ANNOUNCER]
In a strange twist,
both opponents have
gone invisible.
But we can still hear their
eerie sounds of combat!
--[blows landing]
--[TIEN, GOKU grunting]
For humans, they're
oddly imaginative.
--[blows landing]
--[TIEN, GOKU grunting]
What?! Where did--?
--[blows landing]
--[TIEN, GOKU grunting]
Wow... They're moving so fast,
my ears can't keep up!
Yeah.
Is this a normal occurrence
around here? This is crazy.
[PICCOLO JR.]
Hm?
[TIEN, GOKU grunt]
Whoa! Tien Shinhan and
Goku are practically
at each other's throat!
[growling]
Come on! Tien Shinhan!
Take him down! Hurry!
[TIEN groans]
[yells]
[TIEN yells]
[gasps]
[GOKU] About time you
found me. Did ya get lost?
[panting]
[giggles]
[ANNOUNCER] It doesn't get any
more exciting than this, folks!
Goku and Tien Shinhan,
standing toe-to-toe in intense
combat. The way it looks now,
this match could go either way.
Let's just hope they
don't disappear again!
I disagree. One of them
clearly comes up short...
Tien Shinhan is facing
an uphill battle
if he thinks he can defeat
Goku with his usual tactics.
Despite all that running around,
he hasn't even lost his breath.
Clearly he has learned
to control his energy,
conserving just enough to
stay one step ahead of Tien.
Such power! If I weren't
wearing glasses,
I wouldn't believe my eyes!
[NARRATOR]
What malicious plot
dose Junior have
in store for Goku?
While Yamcha, Krillin, and
ChiChi watch with uncertainty,
Master Roshi remains convinced
that Goku will win the match.
Will his hunch be correct,
or will Tien over-power his
young opponent as before?
The answers to these
questions and many more
are waiting to be revealed
on the next action-packed
episode of Dragon Ball!