[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball...
Having successfully
conquered the Eastern City,
King Piccolo decided to mark
the anniversary of his rule
with the destruction
of a world sector.
Selected at random,
the monstrous invader
implemented a policy
to destroy one
of the 43 sectors each year.
The brutal news shocked
citizens across the globe
and sent a wave of
panic through Sector 28,
the first to receive
Piccolo's death sentence.
[PEOPLE screaming]
After enhancing his abilities
by drinking Ultra-Divine Water,
Goku rushes towards a
rematch with King Piccolo.
Meanwhile, Tien Shinhan,
having learned the deadly
Evil-Containment Wave,
set out for the Eastern City;
his mind beset with plans
of vengeance against Piccolo
for the deaths of
Master Roshi and Chiaotzu.
[TIEN grunts]
You're nothing. The only thing
big about you is your mouth.
I can give you a competitor
I know that you
will find a challenge.
[TIEN]
Uh...!
[NARRATOR] With that,
a new menace was born!
[PICCOLO gutteral gasps]
Drum, King Piccolo's
newest agent of terror.
[DRUM laughing intensely]
[car horns honking]
[distant sirens]
[car horns honking continue]
Come on! Drive or
get off the road!
Lousy rubber-neckers!
I could walk faster! Move it!
[WOMAN screams]
[car horns honking]
[PEOPLE screaming]
[busy tone]
All I'm getting
is a busy signal!
Maybe the lines
are crossed. Or, uh...
Or maybe the city's been
blasted away already!
Oolong!
[busy tone continues]
[MRS. BRIEF giggles]
How do I look, darling?
[giggles] Does this
dress go with my hair?
[DR. BRIEF] Yes, yes.
You look wonderful, dear.
You'll fit right in
with the panic.
You don't think the bow
is too overpowering, do you?
Let's go.
Don't rush! This isn't easy!
But we have to go!
Stop being selfish! I want to
look nice for our doomsday!
--[DR. BRIEF] Nobody cares--
--[phone ringing]
[dial tone]
I got a connection.
Oh, thank goodness!
Mother?! Huh?
Oh, Bulma, it's so good
to hear from you
after all this time.
You wouldn't believe
the stress I'm under.
[BULMA]
Mom, I need to--
[MRS. BRIEF] Everything is
topsy turvy around here,
and I don't have a single
outfit for the occasion!
And your father
isn't helping one bit!
[BULMA]
That's what I'm trying--
What a horrible ruler that
new guy is turning out to be!
Making such announcements
without allowing
adequate shopping time!
Well, I've got a thousand
things to do, dear.
Thanks for calling. Bye!
[BULMA]
But Mom!
[busy tone]
Yeah, I love you too, Mother.
[grunts]
[laughing]
[TIEN]
Ugh!
[PICCOLO]
Hmph!
Drum, why don't you teach
our conceited little visitor
a lesson in proper manners?
[TIEN] I don't have time
to mess with this pig!
I've got to get to Piccolo!
Ugh!
[DRUM laughs]
[TIEN] Just a little
further and I can use
the Evil Containment Wave!
[TIEN yells]
--[TIEN grunts]
--[DRUM chuckles]
What's wrong? I'm right here.
Can't you see me?
[TIEN grunting]
[DRUM] Where do you
think you're goin'?
Fine. If I have to
fight you first, so be it!
[yells]
Uh?
[TIEN yells]
--[TIEN groans]
--[DRUM chuckles]
[PIANO chuckles,
PICCOLO laughs intensely]
He's no match for my warrior.
[groans]
[DRUM]
Uh?
[yells]
Mm! Ooh.
[DRUM grunbles]
[chuckles]
That was a new experience.
Now it's my turn.
[laughs]
[TIEN grunts] I can't believe
his speed and strength!
He's virtually unstoppable,
and he's only
Piccolo's underling!
I'm wasting too much time
and energy on this
laughing buffoon!
I have to finish him quickly,
or I run the risk of
losing my opportunity
to attack King Piccolo!
[DRUM laughing]
[GOKU] King Piccolo's in for
a big surprise this time!
I'll win the fight
no matter what!
[distant gunfire]
[GOKU]
Mmm?
[SOLDIER A] Don't let him
get away! Over here!
[GIRL screams]
I know I've heard that
voice somewhere before!
[GIRL whimpers]
Daddy!
If one of you so much as harms
a hair on my daughter's head,
I'll kill you all!
We aren't interested
in your daughter.
What?
Then...
[SOLDIER A]
By order of King Piccolo,
we have been sent
to capture and destroy
every well known
martial artist.
You're the first on our list.
King Piccolo?!
What for?!
It's nothing personal, sir.
I disagree! Aaah!
[OX KING yelling]
[OX KING whimpers, grunts]
[grunts, yells]
[SOLDIER B] How many bullets
does it take to get one man?!
[laughs]
Stop it! Stop it!
[SOLDIERS yell]
[grunts]
Okay...
[chuckles]
[SOLDIER A laughs]
[yells]
Dad, watch out!
Clear out!
[SOLDIERS gasp, yell]
[yells]
So long!
[screams]
[OX KING]
Uuh!
Daddy?
Goku?! Goku!
[laughs]
[OX KING]
Thank you, my boy!
Oh, Goku, somehow I knew
you would come to our rescue!
You've grown a lot
since I last saw you.
Excuse me, children.
We're kinda busy.
You guys are working for
King Piccolo, aren't you?!
Yes, we are, but reluctantly.
Look, if we don't
obey his orders,
he'll destroy us as well.
You should do what's right,
not what you're told.
And don't worry
about Piccolo anymore,
because I am going
to destroy him!
[SOLDIER A] What can you do?
You're just a child.
He decimated half of my force.
You have no idea
how strong he is.
You're wrong. I will beat him!
Look kid, get outta the way!
We don't want to hurt you,
but we've got a job to do here!
[GOKU grunts]
[CHICHI grunts]
[SOLDIERS yell]
No matter what, I will succeed!
[LAUNCH]
Ah.
[chuckles intensely]
[LAUNCH]
Isn't it a beautiful sight?
Locked, loaded,
and ready for action!
[YAMCHA]
Okay.
[BULMA]
Mm?
[OOLONG grunts]
[BULMA] Yamcha.
Listen, this is dangerous.
Are you really going
to go through with it?
Sorry. I can't just sit here
and do nothing, Bulma.
Don't worry.
I can handle myself.
My leg is feeling alot better
and I can work with one
foot in a crunch, honest.
And I'll be along
for the ride as backup.
You could use an
ammunitions expert, right?
I'm coming, too. That's final!
Mhm.
[eerie music plays]
[DRUM laughs]
[TIEN grunts]
[PIANO chuckles]
[PICCOLO chuckles]
[DRUM laughs]
[TIEN yells]
--[DRUM laughs]
--[TIEN panting]
Sire, don't you think
it would be prudent
to leave for Sector 28 now?
We know the outcome
of this fight.
There's no need
to stick around.
Wait, not yet.
Uuh?!
Relax, Piano. There's always
time to enjoy a good slaughter.
[PIANO sighs]
[TIEN yells]
[TIEN groans]
[DRUM yells, laughs]
Aah!
--[DRUM laughs]
--[TIEN yells]
[panting]
[groans]
[DRUM chuckles]
[PICCOLO chuckles]
[DRUM laughing]
[grunts, yells]
[PIANO yelps]
Aah!
[DRUM sobbing]
[TIEN yells]
[gasps for air]
[PICCOLO grunts]
Why must I continually
deal with these human fools?
If it weren't for but a handful
of these annoying warriors,
this invasion
would be so pleasant.
There's nothing more aggravating
than an inferior adversary
who confuses pure luck
with prowess.
Heh.
[DRUM] Come on, kid.
Is that the best you can do?
--[TIEN gasps]
--[DRUM laughing]
Time to say bye bye!
Aah! Aaaah!
[TIEN yells, groans]
[groaning]
[GOKU]
I should be there soon!
[TIEN groans]
[PICCOLO chuckles]
--Time to go.
--Good.
[TIEN]
Piccolo!
I'm not done yet!
No! Not that! Not the jar!
Evil Containment Wave!
[yelling]
--[PICCOLO] No! No!
--[TIEN bellows]
--[PICCOLO yells]
No, not you!
[DRUM yells]
Fine! I'll just
finish him first!
[yells]
[DRUM yells]
[TIEN bellows]
[bellows]
[TIEN] Am I still alive?!
Is it possible?!
[PICCOLO chuckles]
It appears as though Drum's
interference with your
Evil Containment Wave
not only spared my life,
but yours as well.
Finish him off, and make
it as painful as possible.
Yes.
[chuckles]
[DRUM yells]
Aah!
[groans]
I... must be dreaming!
That... that runt!
Uh! Goku!
Oh, Tien Shinhan!
Great to see you!
Goku! You're really alive!
You're a persistent little worm.
Next time I beat you, I'll make
sure that you stay down.
I might surprise you!
Hey, wait! Something
about you is different!
Good of you to notice.
I've been rejuvenated.
Do you know what that means?
Let's just say I'm somewhere
between invincible and immortal.
[GOKU]
Hm!
Aah! Go! Goku, get away
while you still can!
[chcukles]
You're not
going anywhere, runt!
No one treats me like that
and gets away with it!
Exactly. Drum, teach these fools
a lesson they won't forget!
[DRUM laughs]
Goku, move!
He's faster than he looks!
[GOKU yells]
[DRUM groans]
[TIEN yells]
[PICCOLO yells]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[GOKU]
Hmm!
[TIEN]
His strength is phenomenal!
[NARRATOR]
Goku's increased strength
has caught everyone off guard.
But will it be enough
to bring down the juggernaut
that is King Piccolo?
Find out next time
on Dragon Ball!