[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball,
Junior grew larger
than life, literally.
Presenting Goku with the biggest
obstacle he had ever faced.
As he towered above the
arena, it was evident
that King Piccolo's offspring
was "junior" no more.
[PICCOLO JR. laughing]
[NARRATOR] His behemoth size
and lightning-fast speed
posed a double threat to Goku,
who barely avoided
being crushed.
--[GOKU groaning]
--[PICCOLO JR. grunting]
[NARRATOR] Just when Goku
thought he was gaining ground,
he got hit with a solid
dose of reality.
[NARRATOR] Though battered,
and nearly broken,
Goku continued to fight with
such unyielding determination
it surprised even Junior,
who was left floored.
[PICCOLO JR. groaning]
[PICCOLO JR.]
I hate you!
[GOKU laughs]
[GOKU]
Your size doesn't matter.
All it does is make
you a bigger target.
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
[PICCOLO JR.]
You think one lucky throw
is an accomplishment?
[GOKU gasps]
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
[NARRATOR]
Unwilling to back down,
Junior summoned all
of his rage and malice
until the unthinkable happened.
[YAMCHA]
Goku, come on. It's over!
[NARRATOR]
He got even bigger!
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
[GOKU gasps]
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[PICCOLO JR. growls, chuckles]
[laughs]
Goku, where's your
confidence now?!
[ANNOUNCER]
Given Junior's size,
one would be hard pressed
to call this a match.
In fact, this could quickly
turn into a slaughter!
Goku, move it!
Before you're flattened!
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[PICCOLO JR.] My fingernail
is bigger than your body!
Give up, runt!
Ha! It's you who should give up.
I've been waiting
for this moment.
Oh, waiting to die?
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU]
Ka... Me... Ha...
Me... Ha!
[screams]
[ALL]
Ah!
Goku went down his throat!
[gagging]
[KRILLIN]
He's crazy!
[TIEN] No, it's his best
chance to defeat him!
[KRILLIN]
You're both crazy!
[choking]
[ALL gasping]
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU grunts]
[PICCOLO JR. groans]
Uh?! Goku!
[gasping]
[GOKU]
Tien!
[gasping]
But this is...
Open it right, now!
Right!
Quick! Kami is locked
inside that bottle.
[groaning]
Stop it!
[gasps]
[BOTH yell]
[chuckles]
Good!
[KAMI groans]
[PICCOLO JR.]
You mettlesome twit!
You freed him!
[ANNOUNCER whimpers]
Now there are two Piccolos!
[ALL gasp]
[BULMA] Am I the only
one in the dark here?
How can there be
two of that thing?
You're Kami, aren't you?
[KAMI]
Uh-huh.
Hello. You picked an odd place
to take a nap. You're free.
Goku rescued you.
Goku?
Mm, uh!
[GOKU chuckles]
Ah, I see. The effects of
my wave were reversed on me.
[PICCOLO JR. growling]
That's better.
Are you feeling small?
Ah! Shut your mouth!
Calm down. The veins in your
forehead are about to explode.
You should try to relax.
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
[yells]
[ALL gasping]
They're gone.
Not even I can see them.
Wha--?!
[GOKU, PICCOLO JR. grunting]
They're in the sky!
[ALL gasp]
[GOKU groans, yells]
--[PICCOLO grunts]
--[GOKU groans]
[ALL gasp]
[gasps]
[GOKU groans]
Goku!
[CHICHI]
Ah!
Ka... Me...
Ha... Me...
[GOKU]
Ha!
[PICCOLO JR. gasps]
[GOKU yelling]
--[PICCOLO JR. screams]
--[GOKU grunts]
[PICCOLO JR. groans]
[ALL gasp]
What's he doing?
Amazing!
He used his feet for the wave!
[ROSHI]
An extraordinary maneuver
only the most disciplined
warriors can achieve,
but worth the effort, as it
frees one's hands for combat.
[PICCOLO JR. groaning]
[PICCOLO JR. grunting]
[GOKU gasps, screams]
[ALL gasp]
[GOKU screams]
[ALL yell]
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
[GOKU groans]
[KAMI gasps]
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
[GOKU grunting]
He caught me by
complete surprise!
[PICCOLO JR. growling]
No!
[GOKU grunts]
[PICCOLO JR. yells]
Ah!
--[PICCOLO JR. yells]
--[GOKU grunts]
[CHICHI, GOKU,
PICCOLO JR. scream]
Goku!
[BULMA]
Ah!
--[CHICHI screams]
--[BULMA gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[KAMI, PICCOLO JR. grunt]
[PICCOLO JR.] You are too old
and too weak to defeat me.
You should've stayed
in that bottle!
[KAMI]
You forget your place, Piccolo.
Goku, join me. Together
we will stop this fool!
[GOKU gasps]
No, Kami, don't interfere!
You can't!
[gasps]
[KAMI] What are you saying?
I'm here to help you.
The tournament's not over yet.
He's still my opponent.
I can't win unless I
defeat him by myself!
Is that so?
[KRILLIN]
Why are they talking?
The entire planet
could be destroyed
if Junior isn't defeated.
What is there to discuss?
Hm. Very little, I'm sure.
A true warrior does not
contemplate the fate
of the world, only the
strength of his enemy.
For him, nothing exists
beyond the battlefield.
He knows only victory or defeat.
Hit me! I owe you a free punch.
Hm? A free punch?
Yeah, hit me to make up for the
punch that Kami just blocked.
[GOKU]
What are you waiting for?!
Hit me so we can
continue the match!
Heh. If you insist on it.
[PICCOLO JR. grunts]
[GOKU yelps]
Oh, Goku!
[groaning] Sure am glad
they put a wall here.
[KRILLIN] Only Goku
could smile after that.
[ROSHI]
He's nothing if not honest.
[GOKU panting]
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
Should we ask for a time-out
so you can catch your breath?
[GOKU] No, but feel
free if you're tired.
It looks like... It looks
like your antenna are drooping.
Now Goku, before we proceed,
think this through
very carefully.
If we act now,
we can stop him together.
There may not be
a second chance.
Thanks for your concern,
but I've made my decision.
I have to defeat him alone.
It's just something I must do.
[KAMI sighs]
--[TIEN] Kami!
--[KAMI] Hm?
I know you mean well, but Goku
is an accomplished fighter.
He's saved the world
more than once.
Don't worry. Hm. We're a team.
If things get too bad,
we'll take out Junior together.
[PICCOLO JR. laughs] Good one.
Your friends are so loyal.
And foolish. A bunch
of inept weaklings
coming to the rescue of their
idol. I'd pay zeni to see that.
I'll show you inept!
[BULMA, CHICHI gasp]
You are way out of your league,
pretty boy, and you know it!
[TIEN growls]
We'll show him... Right?
I hate to admit it,
but Junior is correct.
Goku is the only one among us
who can keep up with
his tremendous speed.
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[PICCOLO JR.]
You idiot!
It took you this long to
realize my supremacy?!
[laughing]
Listen, Goku.
I still think you're making
the wrong decision,
going up against Junior
by yourself is folly,
but if you insist, do not
stop until he's exterminated.
--I will fall as well,
--[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
but you can resuscitate
me using the Dragon Balls.
Hm. I won't fail. Thank you
for your confidence, Kami.
[KAMI]
Mm.
[PICCOLOR JR.] Ha! You really
believe you'll win, don't you?
[laughs] Stop lying
to yourself. Ha!
Your threats don't worry me.
I've already seen
your best technique.
Not hardly. You haven't
seen anything yet.
[KAMI thinking]
Goku, such a strange young man.
His strength, it's unfathomable.
He seems to be getting
stronger and stronger
every time he fights.
His power has increased
to such a degree
that he's even surpassed me.
I didn't notice it until now.
If he's to become the
warrior I know he can be,
I have to give him the room to
grow. He must face Junior alone.
[PICCOLO JR.] Your arrogance,
it's astounding!
You really believe you
can beat me? Beat me!
Yes. Hm.
You fool! Are you so
simply so moronic,
so moronic that you
can't comprehend
the impossible odds before you?
I am infinitely stronger
than I was three years ago!
Three years is a long time,
and you're the fool if you think
I haven't changed as well.
[PICCOLO JR. growling]
Be quiet!
Uh?! Can't you come up
with anything new?!
Ah!
[yelps]
[GOKU yells]
Ka-Me-Ha-Me-Ha!
[laughing]
There's no use running away!
You'll never escape me!
[GOKU grunts]
We'll see about that!
What are you doing?!
You can't escape!
[grunts]
[screams]
[GOKU chuckles]
[GOKU grunting]
[ALL grunting]
[ALL sigh]
[TIEN]
Where's Goku?!
[ROSHI]
He's all right.
[PICCOLO JR. groans]
I don't believe it! He did it!
Look, Junior's hurt!
I didn't know it was possible
for someone to move like that.
[PICCOLO JR. groans]
Give up, Junior. You're wounded.
You can't fight like that.
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
[PICCOLO JR. grunts]
[gasps]
[ANNOUNCER squeals]
[ALL gasp]
[PICCOLO JR. groans]
[PICCOLO JR. yells]
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
[GOKU gasps]
He can grow his arm back?
Now that is scary!
[PICCOLO JR. grunts]
Just give up! You can't hurt me.
You can't stop my power!
I am invincible! You will be
the first to witness my destiny!
[PICCOLO JR. grunting]
[PICCOLO JR. yelling]
[GOKU gasps]
[gasps]
[PICCOLO JR. yelling]
Get out of here! Get out!
[ALL whimper]
[GOKU]
It's not safe here! Leave!
Move it! Get as far away
from here as you possibly can!
[NARRATOR]
What terrible technique
is Junior about to unleash?
Can anyone survive
his monstrous power?
[ALL gasp]
[PICCOLO JR. yelling, laughing]
[NARRATOR]
Get ready for the unbelievable!
Next time, on Dragon Ball!