[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball,
the tournament continued as
Chiaotzu pitted his Dodon Ray
against Krillin's Kamehameha
Wave. The result was a blast!
Yet Chiaotzu stopped Krillin
dead in his tracks with his
paralyzing power of thought.
It appeared Krillin
was done for,
until he turned the
tables on his foe,
proving you can't always
count on special powers
to win the day.
[CHIAOTZU]
My ten beats your five!
It's 16!
[CHIAOTZU gasps]
Nine minus one!
[CHIAOTZU whimpering]
[NARRATOR] A few good punches
and Chiaotzu's number was up!
[NARRATOR]
Krillin won the match.
However, Chiaotzu's defeat
did not sit well with Tien
or his Master, the Crane Hermit.
While Krillin
and Goku celebrated,
their enemies
plotted their demise.
[BULMA growls]
[PUAR whines]
[GOKU slurping]
Mm! Another helping please!
I'll see if we have more.
Take it easy, Goku.
You don't have to eat
everything at once, ya know.
Really? Why not?
You only have two hours
until your match.
It's not wise to fight
on a full stomach.
They call me a pig!
It's not funny.
It's embarrassing.
You're right. I shouldn't
eat everything at once.
I'll take a snack with me
in case I get hungry later.
[ALL groan]
[GOKU burps]
Delicious!
So, Who's your
opponent going to be
in the next match?
A refrigerator?
I think he's fightin'
someone named Pamphlet.
Sounds lame to me.
No, Pumpkin.
Pumpkin?
It's Pamput. He's awesome!
Haven't you ever
heard of him before?
[BULMA] You guys need
to get with the times.
[ROSHI]
Yes, I know Pamput.
He rose out of
obscurity last year.
Some say he's a fighting genius.
[bell ringing]
[ROSHI] He's participated
in all sorts of tournaments
and won every match
he's ever fought.
Really?
That's great.
He's not just an athlete.
He's also a big-time action
star in movies like Big Bikes,
Explosion 4, and Mutant Rage!
That one was my
personal favorite.
His headband was cool!
'Pistol Papas' was better.
Yeah, I'm sure you like them
for their intricate plot lines.
Nice straw, Oolong...
Stick it up your nose.
[ROSHI] Hey! This joint may
not have the best food,
but the, uh, view is great!
[CROWD murmuring]
Come on, one quote!
Move it!
[GUARD B]
No pictures!
We appreciate your enthusiasm,
ladies and gentlemen. But my
client is busy training today.
There will be no autographs.
[PAMPUT grunting]
[knocking]
[MANAGER]
It's me. Can ya open the door?
Huh?
[CROWD squealing]
[GUARD A]
Let's go, girls. Nothin' to see.
[MANAGER sighs]
They worship you... its love.
[PAMPUT]
They don't love me.
They love the movies
and the press.
They don't know the
first thing about me.
To them I'm nothing
but a product.
[MANAGER laughing]
What does it matter
as long as they buy it?
The name of this game is zeni!
[MANAGER] I'm glad to see you're
takin' this fight seriously.
I've got some interesting
news about your opponent.
[PAMPUT] I know, he came in
second at the last tournament.
[MANAGER]
Yes, but that's not all...
You see, according to
my research--
[PAMPUT]
I couldn't care less.
Of all my fights,
how many have I lost?
Uh...
[PAMPUT]
Exactly.
Now why don't you make
yourself useful and leave.
I like to sweat in private.
[MANAGER] Sure, Pamput, sure.
Whatever you say.
I just want you to look
your best, that's all.
I always do.
After all, I'm Pamput.
And my best is the best.
[ROSHI laughs] So, uh,
tell me what you like best
about the tournament.
[ROSHI]
I know what I like.
I don't really find
the fighting enjoyable.
I like the costumes.
[ROSHI]
Me too.
I feel a strong
sense of community
when I'm with the crowd.
[ROSHI]
I'll bet they do.
They have the best
ice cream cones.
I'm sure.
What about you, Mister?
Why do you like coming
to the tournament?
Hm? Actually, I'm a participant,
in a manner of speaking.
I have three pupils
that are competing.
Pupils?
That's right.
Hey, Krillin, Goku!
Come here for a second.
[GOKU, KRILLIN]
Yes, sir?
These are my pupils,
Krillin and Goku.
Oh, they're just so adorable,
I could eat 'em right up...
...with chocolate
and marshmallows!
[GOKU, KRILLIN]
Uh...
Oh, Goku! Who's your
hair stylist?
So cute!
[ROSHI laughs] Yes, they are
something, aren't they?
I trained them myself! Hm?
Look, it's so shiny!
Wow! He's got a tail!
Hey, wait a minute!
I thought we were talking
about me, not them.
[BIRTHA]
Precious!
So sweet!
Good luck!
[ROSHI growls]
Goku, Krillin!
[GOKU, KRILLIN]
Huh?
Since you two obviously
have so much idle time
on your hands, we'd better
make good use of it
and do some training!
[RUBY gasps]
[CANDY] Real training?!
[BIRTHA]
Can we come watch?
[GOKU, KRILLIN]
Uh...
[ROSHI growls]
[RUBY]
Go, Goku!
[CANDY]
Good luck, Krillin!
[BIRTHA] Go, Gramps,
we're pullin' for ya!
[ROSHI yelps] Alright, boys,
I may be wearing gloves,
but I'm going to
give it all I've got...
And I want you two
to do the same. Got it?!
[GOKU, KRILLIN]
Yes!
Goku, you'll be first up.
Right!
Go.
[GIRLS gasp]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU, ROSHI grunting]
Incredible.
Amazing!
Wow! Goku is so fast!
[MANAGER gulps]
[GOKU, ROSHI grunting]
[ROSHI] I didn't realize
how much Goku's strength
had increased until now.
I've sparred with him many
times, but it never hurt before.
[MANAGER] I've never seen
anyone move like that.
His speed, follow-through,
everything's perfect.
This kid is the real deal.
I wonder if he
has representation?
Oh! What am I saying?!
[GOKU grunting]
[MANAGER] Goku may be the
best fighter in the world,
but he doesn't sell
movie tickets or t-shirts.
With Pamput, the licensing
rights alone are worth millions!
The old man's strong, too.
Yeah, he sure is!
[GOKU grunting]
[ROSHI] Had enough yet?
Hey, cutie!
Eh?
[GOKU grunting]
[ROSHI groans]
Uh... Is that all
we're gonna do?
Yes. But only because
you have a match later on.
The next time, I won't
let you off so easy...
Krillin, now you're up.
Great!
Isn't he cute!
Just darling!
Just Krillin.
I'd still like to work out some.
I guess I'll go for a run.
Alright, but don't go too far.
There isn't much time.
[GOKU giggles]
[ROSHI] Ah--
[MANAGER] If Goku defeats
Pamput in the ring,
it could ruin everything.
I can't allow that to happen.
I have to protect my investment,
by any means necessary.
[CROWD murmuring]
Where's Launch?
She could be anywhere.
Just listen for gunshots.
[LAUNCH]
I'd like my ice cream today.
[GOKU panting, humming]
Faster!
I've got bad news, Goku.
Huh?
Right, read my lips. More!
Oh, sure.
Huh?
How's this?
Really? They changed location?
Sure. The tournament's now
at a different place.
What? You didn't get the memo?
[GOKU]
Memo?
I'm not surprised.
Clerical error.
That's why they sent me.
But you'd better hurry.
Hop in. I'll give you a lift.
[LAUNCH] Hey, Goku! Wait up!
[GOKU] Gee, thanks.
I don't know those other guys.
But they don't look too
friendly. You there! Stop!
Wait! What about my money?!
Here ya go. I'll trade ya.
[GOKU yawns]
Hello.
So, why did they change
the location anyway?
What?
Uh, something about losing
their building license.
Why don't ya just relax and
look out the window. Enjoy
I'm okay.
[MANAGER]
Not for long, kid.
Pamput's going to win without
ever breakin' a sweat!
[CROWD cheering]
[SHEN cackles]
What do you mean he's not here?!
No one's seen him.
He's been gone for 30 minutes.
Well, if he doesn't get
here soon, he'll lose the fight.
[GOKU snoring]
[MANAGER cackles]
We won!
[LAUNCH]
Pull over!
Don't you want your ice cream?
Can't ya hear me?!
Stop the car!
[LAUNCH] Goku, wake up!
[GOKU] Oh, hi Launch!
[LAUNCH] Are you alright?!
[GOKU] How are you?
Hey, why don't you tell your
new friends to pull over
so we can all be
introduced properly!
She's got ice cream!
[MANAGER] Wait. Lose her!
Quick, step on it!
[LAUNCH] Fine! You wanna
do this the hard way?!
You've got the right girl!
[GUARD A yelps]
[MANAGER]
Get her!
[GUARD A yells]
[GUARD B grunts]
[LAUNCH growls]
[GUARD B groans]
[GUARD A grunts]
[LAUNCH grunting]
[GUARD B groaning]
I hate to waste good food.
[MANAGER yelps] Please!
I bruise easy! I'm sorry!
I just wanted Pamput to win
the match, that's all!
[LAUNCH gasps]
What's going on?
[LAUNCH]
Goku, what were you doin'
gettin' in the car
with this slime?!
Can't ya tell he's dangerous?!
[GOKU] He said he would help
me get to the tournament.
[LAUNCH]
No, he wanted to keep you away!
It was a lie? What about
the memo thingy?
[MANAGER]
Please forgive me! I was a fool!
[LAUNCH]
Go on. Get outta here.
You've got a fight to catch.
[GOKU]
Right. Thank you, Launch!
[LAUNCH cackles]
[MANAGER whimeprs]
[LAUNCH] Alright, where do
you wanna hurt first?
Now your patience
is about to pay off!
As we begin the fourth match
in the quarterfinals!
Let's welcome our fighters.
First up, a man that
needs no introduction.
The one, the only, Pamput!
[CROWD cheers]
Huh?
Whoa!
[CROWD cheers]
What a show-off.
[KRILLIN] Is he here to fight
or sign autographs?
Isn't he fabulous?
Now this is embarrassing!
Whether he's
fighting in the ring
or on the big screen,
Pamput wears superstardom
like a crown. He's won a
plethora of championships
and if he wins
this one, he'll become
the strongest man in the world!
Well, I'm convinced Pamput
could win the tournament,
if he had a stunt-double.
Next we have the
second place winner
of the last tournament, Goku!
Huh?
Uh, it appears as though
Goku is missing.
What has that boy
gotten himself into?
Hurry up, Goku!
[GOKU grunting]
Please, I'm beggin' you,
don't tell anyone about this.
I'll be ruined!
Sure, but, sir,
who are you?
Uh...
Well, he's extremely late.
It's expected really.
I'm used to my
opponents running away.
Uh, due to Goku's
unexplained disappearance
and in accordance
with rule 2758-A
of the Tournament Guidelines,
the winner by forfeit
is our esteemed challenger--
[GOKU]
Wait! Wait!
I'm here! Sorry I'm late.
He's here.
[KRILLIN sighs]
Finally.
Goku cut it close,
but it looks like
he arrived just in time.
The match will proceed.
I'm sorry I kept you waiting.
If you were smart,
you would have stayed gone!
Folks, the tension in this ring
right now is thicker
than my hair gel!
You wanted a big fight?
Well, now you've got it!
[PAMPUT grunts]
Hey!
What's the matter,
kid, scared stiff?
Or am I just too fast for you?
Hm? Were you
stretching or punching,
'cause I couldn't tell.
What?!
You don't know who
you're dealing with.
I-It's not your fault.
You're just uneducated.
That's fine. In fact,
I'll bring you up to speed
with a little demonstration.
With your indulgence of course.
This is an odd request,
but you may proceed.
[PAMPUT grunts]
[PAMPUT yelling]
[PAMPUT grunting]
[PAMPUT yells]
[CROWD cheers]
He's so talented!
Just whose side
are you on, Bulma?
Goku's, of course!
Well, uh, maybe both.
We just had that
fixed yesterday.
[ROSHI] I can't complain.
He improved our view.
[PAMPUT]
Now you've witnessed my power,
and this is just a taste.
[GOKU]
Uh, okay.
You don't want seconds.
He talks like he's in a movie.
Yes, Krillin. A very bad movie.
And now without further delay,
it's time to start
the 4th match.
[CROWD cheers]
30 seconds...
You get 30 seconds of Pamput's
time before you go down.
[ANNOUNCER]
Keep your eyes peeled, folks.
Because with these
two wild warriors
going head-to-head,
anything is possible!
Ready, fighters, and begin!
[PAMPUT] Remember my hair
is off limits, so is my back.
I just had it waxed.
[PAMPUT yells]
[PAMPUT groaning]
[PAMPUT gasping, groaning]
[ANNOUNCER gasps] He's knocked
out! The winner is Goku!
[CROWD cheers]
[OOLONG] Goku, you did it!
Yay, Goku!
Pamput...
He's stronger in the movies.
Better looking, too.
[ANNOUNCER]
Who would have thought!
Pamput defeated with one punch!
Like I said, folks,
anything can happen.
And remember,
you saw it here first!
So much for the action hero.
Maybe he'll fight better
at the box office.
No, he's mistaken.
Pamput wasn't done in
with a single punch.
From what I saw, there were
three separate hits
by Goku's elbow.
[TIEN growls]
He's no ordinary fighter.
Indeed. I no longer have any
doubt that he killed Tao.
That's all I needed to hear.
Now I'm getting excited.
[GOKU laughs]
You were incredible, Goku!
And I knew you'd beat Pamput
from the beginning!
There was no doubt that
that overblown windbag
was going to pop
sooner or later!
He wasn't strong at all.
Anyone could have beat him.
[ROSHI laughs]
I don't think so...
Pamput may be a
self-absorbed, arrogant,
pain-in-the-neck,
but beneath the hair
and publicity stunts is
an exceptional fighter.
The reason he seemed weak
and ordinary to you
is because you are not.
[GOKU, KRILLIN]
Huh?
Both of you have proven
through your recent fights
that you have moved beyond the
limitations of ordinary men.
But, if we're stronger
than everyone else,
why did Yamcha, who's as good
as we are, lose his match?
And I myself had a
hard time beating Chiaotzu.
You're not the only
ones with an edge.
In fact, Tien and Chiaotzu enjoy
the same advantages as you.
[ROSHI]
Maybe more.
[TIEN]
Your days are numbered, Goku,
and anyone who stands in my way!
[NARRATOR]
Don't miss the action
on the next episode
of Dragon Ball!