[NARRATOR] The sensational
World Martial Arts Tournament
has ended with Jackie Chun
capturing the win from Goku.
Our hero has no idea that
his opponent was really
Master Roshi in disguise,
or of the exciting
adventure that lies ahead!
[YAMCHA] So, are you up
for a second helping
of training on
Master Roshi's island?
You bet!
Now hold on!
Let's not get
ahead of ourselves.
You boys have
earned a break
before we begin the
next phase of training.
It's time you
learned some lessons
from the greatest
scholar of all: Life!
Really?
[ROSHI] Um-hum
Great, then I'm gonna go
find my Grandpa's
Four-Star Dragon Ball!
Huh?
What's the rush?
There's plenty of time.
Are you sure you
wanna start looking now?
Mm-hmm.
Wait a minute!
What in the world
is a Dragon Ball?
It's a magical ball
my grandpa gave me.
Oh.
Mmmm... Maybe you should take
someone should go with you...
I'll have the flying nimbus
to keep me company.
[OOLONG] Goku! He's right.
You going out
alone is a bad idea.
It's too scary!
It'll be an adventure!
I'm sure Krillin
would love to go!
Uh...? Actually,
Master, I was looking
forward to going with
you to your island
so we could start training
for the next tournament.
Hmm?!
Look, kid, what do I have
to do, spell it out for you?
I need you to leave! Scram!
You're cramping my style!
In the next tournament
I want to score big!
So do I.
[ROSHI thinking]
More than you'll ever know.
I can see it now.
Cocktails at sunset.
A gorgeous gal, Launch!
[ROSHI thinking] Yes!
Nice dress, big blue
eyes, big ohh--ha!
Total hottie captivated
by my rugged good looks!
And not another soul around...
Oh, well.
I guess there goes that
little slice of heaven.
Where are you going?
Uh...
I guess the rest of us
will go back to West City.
Yeah, that'll be fun.
A nice relaxing drive
across the desert.
Yeah, there you go kids.
Get out there and see the world.
Master?
Yes?! What?
Does that box have
my things inside of it?
Yes, and it's called a suitcase.
Wow! A suitcase...
I'll never get used
to all this great stuff!
You really need
to get out more...
This trip'll do you good.
Boy, sure are a lot
of magazines in here!
[ROSHI] Uhh...
You better get a move on, kid!
Yep!
Nimbus!
Hi there, Nimbus.
He flies on a cloud,
but he still goes
ga-ga over a suitcase.
Mm-hm. Naïve.
[KRILLIN] Hey, Goku!
On second thought, you're
gonna need my help.
Thanks.
But you can't ride the
Nimbus cloud. Remember?
Oh yeah... Never mind.
The Dragon
Radar will guide you.
You do know how
to use it, right?
I'll figure it out.
Time to find my Dragon Ball!
Be careful!
Bye! Bye, bye!
[BULMA] Good luck, kid!
[PUAR] So long, then!
I kinda feel bad
letting him go all alone.
Something tells me
he'll be just fine!
[ROSHI] He's a special boy.
Mmmm! Very special.
Mm-hmm!
[NARRATOR] And so,
Goku must part company
with his friends as
he sets out in pursuit
of the Four-Star Dragon Ball.
The future is
unclear for our hero,
but one thing is certain:
the adventure has just begun!
[BULMA] Oh!
Are you trying to hit every
hole in the street or what?
[YAMCHA] Actually,
there is no street...
That's why it's
called off-road driving,
and I'm doing the best I can.
You can take the
wheel any time you want.
Oh-h, can I...?
Anything would be
better than this torture!
I've never seen
Bulma this upset.
She does seem
a bit irritable.
I am not upset, got it?!
This is me happy!
[OOLONG] Right. We can tell.
[BULMA] Be quiet!
Master Roshi
said he'd wait
for me right here
while I got my ice cream.
Is this a test?
Ah, Eureka!
Satin, lace, little straps! Ooh!
I betcha they have the
type you can eat, too.
Yeh-heh!
Roshi, behave yourself!
Hee-Hee-Hee!
Actually, I did promise myself
I'd get Launch a souvenir!
How can I help you?
Something wrong?
Well, uh...
I was wondering if
you'd help me, eh...
...test these undies out...
You know...
for quality control...
Sir, please!
I don't know what
to say to that!
I'll... buy several...
and who knows...
if I like what I see,
there might be a tip
in it for you, too!
Is--that--yes--or--no?!
Heh heh heh.
Ugh!
[ROSHI] Heh-heh-heh-heh!
[GOKU] Let's see... Got one!
Sure looks real far away!
[NAM'S BROTHER]
Did you do it, Nam?
Did you win the tournament?
Nuh-uh...
Then truly all is lost.
Not yet... I did get water!
We're saved!
Here it is!
A bit small.
Everybody stand back!
[shocked, surprised noises]
[VILLAGE ELDER] Praise you...
You have brought a
ray of hope to the people.
I am very grateful
to help my village,
but it is the tournament we must
thank for this prosperity...
You see... all seemed lost...
[NAM] After losing the match,
I fell into despair.
That is when I met Master Roshi.
It was he who gave me the
Dyno-cap which was empty.
He explained how it could
hold an abundance of water,
for there it was
plentiful and free.
You can fit vast quantities
of anything you want...
We are truly fortunate
to receive such a gift.
[NAM] I fear the
water I have brought
will not sustain us long...
It is most strange.
We have been through
droughts before,
but I do not remember
the river ever drying up.
[VILLAGE ELDER]
That's because it hasn't.
At least, not like this.
It is as if the desert inhaled
the river in one breath.
I've never seen anything
quite like this occur.
Perhaps there is some problem
upstream, at the source.
Like what?
You mean something unnatural?
There's no telling.
To be honest with you,
I'm just grasping at straws.
In all my life, I've never
seen the village hit this bad.
It's almost like we're being
punished for some misdeed.
Don't let it get
you down, my boy.
All we need is a miracle.
Is such a thing possible?
Hm-mm. Anything's possible.
Just look at the Roaming Lake.
A Roaming Lake...?
Can this be?
When I was a child,
my father told me the story
of a nearby village crippled
by a terrible drought.
One day, a lake moved
across the ground
and settled at the
base of the village.
It quenched their thirst,
fed their crops,
then left as quietly as it came.
I will find it.
If this Roaming Lake exists,
I will lead it to our village.
Tell the people their
suffering will soon end,
for I will not
return without it.
Whew!
I will not tire.
Huh?
[NAM] My turn!
I call upon...
...the Aerial Attack!!!
Swift as lightning!
Loud as thund--Huh?
Well, guess who's
coming to dinner?
Let go, now!
Water... Need some water...
Hey!!
Wow! Big Puddle!
Ahh! Yeah... this is great!
[NAM] Unhand me, bird brain!
Huh?
C'mon, put me down,
you stupid bird!
You're going to make me mad!
I've got to make you go!
I've got to get
water for my people!
It's Nam!
Nimbus!! Go!
Faster!!
[NAM] Oh, Goku!
[GOKU] Don't worry.
I'll get you down! Hang on!
I am hanging on!
How did this happen?
My village needs more water.
I was searching
along the riverbed,
when this beast captured me!
I'll help!
Drop him off, now!
Do I look like a taxi service?!
Hey, you should watch
where you swing that tail.
You almost knocked me down!
If you don't leave me alone,
I'll do more than that!
This piece of meat
is my dinner, kid,
but now that I look at him,
he is kind of scrawny.
I'm sure I'll have
room for dessert!
Power Pole extend!
You're a bad bird!
That sure was a big mean bird.
With sharp claws!
Ah! Stop it! What
are you doing?!
Oh, you are a boy!
Yes, yes, I am!
Sorry, it's hard
to tell sometimes.
You can check me if you want!
[NAM] No.
Just so you know,
the people in my village
greet others by
shaking hands. Period.
Too bad someone forgot
to pack extra gasoline.
A shame it won't
run on good looks.
I'd keep it going forever.
Okay, look...
we can't just sit here.
I know, you could change into
an umbrella and
give us some shade
Oh, joy!
Don't listen to him.
I'll bet he doesn't even know
how to change into an umbrella.
Oh yes I do.
I went to the same Shape-
Shifting School you did, Puar.
Until you got expelled
in the first semester
for stealing
the teacher's papers!
Don't you ever stop talking?
Fine, I'll do it!!!
Hey, how about a fan?
This is much better.
[YAMCHA] It sure beats
baking in the sun.
Yep.. that's me...
bacon in the sun!
[NAM] I appreciate
your assistance Goku.
With this flying cloud
we can survey the river
and keep a look-out for the
Roaming Lake at the same time.
[GOKU] How far
does the river go?
[NAM] Far...
Very Far...
[NARRATOR]
Braving the harsh elements,
Goku and Nam eventually discover
a section of the river with
water and lush vegetation.
The green trees and blue
water offer a stark contrast
to the rest of the
desolate landscape.
It is a sight to behold
for the weary travelers.
But what lies beyond
is even more astonishing.
Un-believable...!
[NAM] The water flow is
being choked by that dam.
Who could be
responsible for this?
Set us down my friend,
so we can investigate.
Hey, those guys look familiar!
How can these beasts
horde so much water?
I will ask whomever leads
them to set the river free.
Okay!
The dam stays put, got it?!
[NAM] I do not understand
your resistance to this!
It is completely unacceptable!
How can you lay claim
to that which rightfully
belongs to everyone?!
You can no sooner own the
water than the sky above us!
Would you be so quick to
open the dam if you owned it?
My friend doesn't
understand you.
He only speaks the
language of money!
My village is poor.
We have nothing to
offer but our gratitude.
Then we have nothing to give.
Please, I beg you.
Yes, you're good at that!
Please, my people
are dying of thirst!
If they are thirsty,
let them drink the sand...
You little insect!
Tear him apart!
Heh-heh! What's this, your pet?
If you want him,
you gotta go through me!
Oh yeah? Sounds fun.
Let's introduce this runt
to the meaning of pain!
What the heck was that?
Wha--
Uh, hey boss.
You're Goku...
Uh... Hey! It's Giran!
This little pip-squeak
knows you?
This "little pip-squeak"
is the one who beat me
in the tournament...
so show him some respect!
I remember you
from the tour-r-na-m-en-t.
You're not still sore about
losing the match are you?
I was humiliated!
But that has nothing to do with
the dam you want to destroy.
It is a magnificent structure,
built long before any of us.
I would be happy to release
the water, but I can't.
The dam is impossible to break
because it is held together
by Merry-go-round Gum.
It is very much...
...unbreakable.
Then I have failed
my entire village!
I can break the dam for you!
You think so?
Well, sure... I'll try to.
Ka...
me...
ha...
HAA!
He really did it!
So much for the
Merry-go-round Gum.
You did it!
That was fun!
Hahahahaha!
[GIRAN] You are one amazing kid.
[GOKU] This is great!
Now we can all
go swimming, yeah!
Thanks to you, there are
many things we can do now.
This will be a
day long remembered.
[BULMA] Darn it!
Just when I was
starting to feel tanned!
Well, I hope
everyone is happy!
Once again,
I sacrifice my own comfort
and safety for the group,
and what thanks do I get?
I get dropped on my keister!
I'm a mess.
I've got sand in places
I didn't even know I had places!
It's okay, cheer up!
This storm caught
us all by surprise.
You did a good job.
It's not easy to do.
Too bad you got expelled
or you might have learned
how to concentrate and
hold a shape for
more than five minutes.
How about I concentrate
on busting your... Ahhh!
[YAMCHA] Come on! Hurry!
We have to get inside the car!
This storm is getting
worse by the minute!
[VILLAGE MAN] It's over.
The desert has robbed us
of our last hope for salvation.
Whoa!
[GOKU] Oohh!
It's that big puddle!
[NAM] The Roaming Lake!
It does exist!
I never thought I'd see
the day my father's
words would come
to pass before my very eyes!
Tonight we have
been smiled upon.
It's beautiful.
Yes. This has
been a day of miracles.
It has brought us you, Goku!
Huh?
Oh no!
[YAMCHA] South City.
I don't believe it.
The storm blew us right
back were we started.
I need a vacation!
I need a bath!
[NARRATOR] As the day
draws to a close,
our hero has a
lot to smile about.
By finding the Roaming Lake,
he has helped
to secure the future
for Nam and his village.
Now he flies on towards
his next exciting adventure
as the search for the
Four-Star Dragon Ball continues.