[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
Goku challenged
Tambourine to a rematch,
running circles around his foe.
Tambourine didn't stand a chance
as Goku struck with a vengeance.
Nothing Tambourine did seemed
to have an effect on Goku.
Now it's your turn to feel
the same pain you gave Krillin!
Realizing he couldn't win,
Tambourine fled,
but Goku gave chase, and with
help from his Kamehameha Wave,
made the monster see the light!
[NARRATOR]
Through a psychic link,
King Piccolo felt Tambourine's
destruction by Goku.
Distraught, the evil
overlord vowed revenge.
[PICCOLO] I don't know who is
responsible for this outrage,
but I will personally see
to their destruction
for interfering with my plans!
The dragon radar shows the
fifth ball is around this area.
[ROSHI] Hmmm...
This could very well
be the same one
that King Piccolo's subordinate
took away from Krillin.
Take us down. Let's say hi.
[TIEN thinking] What is it
about the Evil Containment Wave
that frightens Master Roshi?!
Why is he so adamant
about not using a technique
that's been proven to
incapacitate King Piccolo?!
I have to see it, just once in
my life. I must know its power!
[ROSHI] Tien, what's the
matter with you?!
What? Uh, nothing.
Nothing at all.
It's here!
What?!
[YAJIROBE] What are you talking
about? Another Dragon Ball?
[GOKU] It's close!
[YAJIROBE] Goku!
I don't see anything.
[GOKU] Above!
What is that thing? It's huge!
[MAI] King Piccolo, we have
arrived at our destination.
Wow! Who is King Piccolo?
No, no Mai! That's the switch
for the exterior speaker!
Oh no!
King Piccolo,
I'm sorry to disturb you,
but you asked to be notified
as soon as we arrived.
Very good.
That name, King Piccolo, I think
I've heard it somewhere before.
King Picco-whatever-you-call-him
sounds like he must be the
leader of all the monsters
who've been after
the Dragon Balls!
If I remember correctly,
I've heard his name
mentioned in my village.
I believe it was in a
story I was told once.
I remember!
Here Goku. You can have it.
It's all yours. Take it!
Really? But I thought
you wanted to keep it?
[YAJIROBE laughing]
It's yours now!
Bu--But Yajirobe, the leader
might taste best of all.
Oh, I'm stuffed.
I couldn't eat another bite!
[belches]
No room!
But just a minute
ago you were starving.
I-I lost my appetite. Bye!
Wonder what's gotten into him?
Oh well!
Ah, look at the ground.
There's somebody down there.
He must be the one who
killed Cymbal and Tambourine.
Give me just a moment
to land the plane
and you can destroy him!
No, don't bother.
It won't be necessary.
[terrified gasp]
No... Anyone but him!
[PILAF] It's impossible!
He's supposed to be dead!
Who is it?
Who else?! It's that same brat
who always keeps me
away from the Dragon Balls!
He always gets in my way!
He ruins every one of my plans!
So this little child
is responsible
for killing
Tambourine and Cymbal?
Both Cymbal and
Tambourine fell in disgrace...
If that little worm
had anything to do
with their demise...
I am not so weak that
I cannot deal with a child!
But Your Majesty,
it's too dangerous!
[PIANO laughing devilishly]
That human doesn't
stand a chance.
His majesty's power
is unequaled!
Come here!
Hey! Are you the
ruler of those monsters?
One of them killed
my friend Krillin
and stole my Dragon Ball!
That's me.
I see you have another Dragon
Ball hanging around your neck.
I was right about you!
Animal! You're just as
responsible for Krillin's death!
Can you forgive me?
[laughing]
You are unbelievable.
What's so funny?!
[chuckles]
You are.
I thought I was looking
for a great warrior,
and now I find it is you
who has killed two
of my greatest soldiers.
That's right, and you're
going to follow them.
But first, you are
going to give me back
my grandpa's Dragon Ball!
We will see.
[YAJIROBE] That face!
He-He looks mean.
It must be King Piccolo.
He's come to
destroy us!
[PICCOLO laughing]
You poor simpleton.
You don't have a single
clue who I am, do you?
I am the abomination that
haunts your nightmares.
Soon you will call me master!
That's not going to happen!
It never fails.
For some reason, every time
I meet a Martial Artist
I have this incredible
urge to destroy them.
Even one as tiny
and pathetic as you!
I might surprise you!
Bye, Goku. Nice knowing you.
You'll pay for all the pain
you've caused my friends!
He's quick!
Yah!
[shocked gasps]
Smooth! Good one, Goku!
But watch out!
If that's the King Piccolo
I've heard of, this isn't over.
That kid's gonna win.
It's time to get out of here!
Sire! What are we gonna do?!
Calm down.
We can't!
Did you really think
his majesty could be beat?
He's just getting warmed up.
[chuckling]
[YAJIROBE] It's a trap, Goku.
Don't fall into it.
You're putting up
a good fight,
but any minute now
he's gonna strike back.
I was right.
Here he comes again.
What you did was unprecedented.
I had no idea
I could be knocked down!
You're good.
It's obvious my minions were no
match for your level of skill.
You are the reason
I have exterminated
the Martial Arts Society.
Anyone with
your level of skill...
...deserves to be terminated.
You have such great strength.
I shall do my absolute
best to try to keep up.
This is only the beginning.
Let's go! I've been waiting for
this moment a very long time!
[chuckling]
Wh-What is going on?!
I can't move!
[radar beeping]
[beeping quickens]
It might be--
[straining]
Just a little further!
[continues straining]
[frantic gasping]
[yells]
[ROSHI] Ow!
[CHIAOTZU] Master Roshi!
[TIEN] Are you all right?!
Oh no, it's gone!
Now, let's try this once more.
[yelling]
[chuckling]
Nice. You're still alive.
I was hoping this
would last a good while.
I'm... feeling fine.
[GOKU grunts]
What's wrong?
No witty comeback?
Let go!
[yelling]
[GOKU yelling]
You'll pay! You lousy human!
[yelling]
So you still have some
fight left in you after all.
[PICCOLO yelling]
No Goku, don't come towards me!
[chuckling]
[PICCOLO laughing]
That's what I
call entertainment!
What's the matter? Have you
used up all your energy?
Tough luck!
We're just getting started, boy!
Your pain will be exquisite!
[groaning in pain]
It's over!
You're tougher than I thought,
but it doesn't
make any difference,
you big meany!
I'm still gonna destroy you!
[laughing]
Your misplaced
confidence is refreshing!
[PICCOLO]
Though I find this amusing,
you must know--
There is no escape.
The only choice left is how
you will meet your demise.
No!
Well, despite your shortcomings,
you are a defiant one!
It's been a long time
since I've seen
that kind of spark
in someone's eye!
I'm fortunate... I'm stronger!
Growl, human!
Bahahahaha!
No!
Ka... me... ha...
[GOKU] ...me...
[PICCOLO thinking] Wait! That's
not the Evil Containment Wave!
...ha!
Ha! Got 'em!
That was a direct hit!
It's about time
we said goodbye, boy.
Funny, you don't look heroic.
[NARRATOR] It appears Goku is
quickly running out of options.
Alone and without
a usable technique,
can Goku defend himself
against the mighty King Piccolo?
Or is this really the end?
Find out next time,
on Dragon Ball!