[NARRATOR] Previously on Dragon
Ball, Emperor Pilaf succeeded in
uniting the seven magic
Dragon Balls, and now prepares
to summon the Eternal
Dragon to grant his wish
to rule the world.
Come forth, Dragon!
I call upon you
to grant my wish!
[NARRATOR] Little does the
Emperor know, two of our heroes
have taken flight in an attempt
to thwart his diabolical plans.
[PUAR] Come on, Oolong!
We have to hurry!
[OOLONG] How fast do
you think a pig can fly?
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, the rest
of the team watches helplessly
from above, trapped within the
confines of their prison cell.
C'mon, Puar!
You're our only hope now!
You can do it, Oolong!
[GOKU] What's
going on, you guys?!
I can't see!
Eternal Dragon!
Arise!
[NARRATOR] At last, the Eternal
Dragon has risen from its
slumber within the fiery core of
the Earth. And It seems nothing
can prevent Emperor
Pilaf from fulfilling
his desire for world domination!
[NARRATOR] Hurry, Oolong!
Hurry, Puar!
The fate of the
world is in your hands!
We're too late, Oolong.
The dragon's already here!
Now what are we going to do?!
We can't just stand
here and watch!
Oh, we have no choice!
Hey, let me see!
I can't believe it...
It's the most beautiful
thing I've ever seen!
[PILAF] At last, my greatest
dreams are finally coming true!
Soon the whole world
will be at my beck and call!
[laughing]
[cheering]
[whimpering]
[GOKU] Wow, he's huge!
[DRAGON] Who has summoned me?
Uh, that would be me. I did.
Tell me your wish.
[DRAGON] But beware,
for it will come true.
We've got to do something!
We can't just let the
whole world go to ruin!
[DRAGON] Speak!
Do something, you stupid pig!
I hope he ate already!
Alright, then. I'm ready.
Whoa, this is it guys!
He's about to make his wish!
[YAMCHA] Now I'll
never get a date!
[BULMA] My boyfriend!
[PILAF] Uh, I wish for, uh...
Ka-me-ha-me-ha!
[GOKU] Darn, that didn't work!
Kamehamehas make me hungry...
But, I'm not gonna give up yet!
Ka-me-ha--!
[DRAGON] You try my patience!
I'm sorry!
It just that I've
never done this before...
[DRAGON] Make a wish!
[DRAGON] Now!
[PILAF] Yes, of course!
[PILAF] My wish... how
silly of me... my wish!
I'm a coward!
I don't want to be a hero!
I don't want to save
the day! This stinks!
And these boxers are chafing!
Uh... I would
like to have supreme...
...me-ha!
I want to have the world--
[OOLONG] The world's most
comfortable pair of ultra-soft--
underwear!
Huh?
[snickering]
I think that little
pervert just saved the world!
Maybe he's not such
a coward after all!
You dolt!
[DRAGON] Your wish
has been granted.
[whimpering]
All of the Dragon
Balls just flew away!
That's what happens when
the dragon grants a wish.
The balls are spread
all over the earth again.
What? That means the
Dragon Ball Grandpa gave me
to remember him by is gone!
[snickering]
[PILAF] Seize him!
I want that
pig for dinner!
[PILAF] The others
have escaped too!
I want them all!
Exterminate! Exterminate!
[OOLONG] Hey, let's go, Puar!
We can take those two!
[guns firing]
Or not!
Goku?!
[BULMA] What are you doing?
I'm too hungry
to go anywhere.
[BULMA] You're too hungry?!
You're gonna be too
dead to go anywhere if
you don't move it! C'mon!
Shu, they're heading
toward the north face!
I'll call my dog police!
We've gotta find
Yamcha and the others.
You wanna find
those whiney goofballs,
go right ahead. I've already
saved the world once today.
I feel like I've
done my civic duty.
You mean you're
just going to leave your
two friends behind?!
Let's get outta here!
Try thinking
positive for a change!
And run faster,
you're falling behind!
Think positive, huh?!
Fine, it doesn't work.
Snap out of it, Goku!
I'm too hungry...
Here they come!
[YAMCHA] Dinner time, Goku!
Yum-yum!
Looks like I'm
on clean-up duty.
Wolf Fang Fist!
C'mon!
Let's get out of
this stinkin' dog kennel!
Power Pole, extend!
They're... they're...
they're gaining on us!
Don't worry, I'm
an expert at running away!
Power Pole, extend!
All right, so
maybe it wasn't graceful, but
at least I got us
away from the dogs.
You know, we could
just change into
birds and fly out of here.
This is just great, Goku!
So how do you think we're going
to get over to that window, huh?
I dunno.
Now he tells us!
You ready, Puar?
Okay, let's go!
[screaming]
Ow, now that smarts!
Oh, great, more dogs!
I need some food, bad.
[MAI and SHU] Attack!
[SHU] Alright, drop that mutt!
[BULMA] Yamcha?
[growling]
[maniacal laughter]
I bet even Goku can't
blast a hole this time!
It's made of some weird metal.
No big deal. Look!
There's no ceiling!
Yes there is.
It's probably made of glass.
It can't be
harder than my head.
Just watch this!
And from the looks
of it--tempered glass.
Well, I'm not giving up.
First, we're gonna get out
of here, then we're gonna find
all seven Dragon Balls again.
There won't be any
Dragon Balls for a year.
What do you mean?!
Yeah, what gives?
It's all part of the legend.
Once the Eternal Dragon grants
a wish and the Dragon
Balls are scattered across the
earth again, they become inert
for a full year. In other words,
you won't even be able to
tell they're Dragon Balls.
They'll just look
like round stones...
Are... are you... serious?
Yikes, that's harsh.
I can't believe it...
Now I have to be shy
around women for another year!
[BULMA] And I have to wait
another year for a boyfriend...
[PILAF] Is this on? I wouldn't
worry your pretty, little heads
over what's going to
happen a year from now!
You're all going to
be terminated tomorrow!
I hope you're enjoying
your accommodations because
I personally designed
the cell you're in! I call
it my Easy Bake Office!
[PILAF] I wanted to see how hot
I could make a room by absorbing
all of the sun's rays!
It's pleasant in there now,
but just wait until the sun
comes up! Then,
get ready to broil!
I'm going to roast you alive
and enjoy every minute of it!
That fiend!
We've got to get out of here!
Oh, now my skin's
gonna dry up,
and I'm gonna get
premature wrinkles!
At least you'll die with a tan!
Oh, yeah, that's right.
I'll be dead!
I don't wanna die,
I'm too young!
I am, too!
[wailing]
I can't die now!
Oh no, oh no, oh no!
I'm hungry.
[PILAF] They kind of remind
me of those little goldfish
I used to have.
And they'll die just as quickly.
[blows landing]
[GOKU] Ka-me-ha-me-ha!
[GOKU] Ha!
--Come on you guys!
--You can do it!
That's right, struggle! Do you
two idiots really think you
can break through three solid
feet of my super-special steel?!
He's right, it's not gonna work.
We're stuck here.
Sleep well, and I'll wake
you up early for toast!
[laughing]
[SHU] Carefully, sire.
[PILAF] Ahh, there.
That's it, see?
Sometimes it's the small
accomplishments in life that
--have to suffice.
--[SHU] So true.
Of course, if it wasn't
for those kids, I'd be
ruling the world right now!
But come sunrise,
they'll all be french-fried!
Uh?
You think he'd at least
give us a last request...
Well, I have a last request!
Oolong, will you
please shut up?!
Request denied, glamour girl!
[PUAR] Ohh...
[OOLONG] Hey, Puar,
what are you doing up there?
Nothing, just watching the moon.
How can you watch the moon?
Aren't you
worried about tomorrow?!
Yeah, but that's why
I'm looking at the moon:
It's soothing. Look
how full it is tonight.
Doesn't it make you
feel all warm and fuzzy?
I'm a pig,
I am warm and fuzzy!
A full moon?
Did you guys know that
a terrible monster comes
out when the moon is full?
Oh, come on Goku,
you're making that up!
There's no such thing. You
should put that imagination
to better use and figure out
a way to get us out of here!
But I'm not making it up,
Bulma!
My Grandpa was trampled
to death by that monster!
What? Gohan, the
supreme martial arts master?
That's gotta be one
big, savage monster.
Yeah.
It destroyed our house
and crushed all of our trees.
[OOLONG] What did
it look like, Goku?
I'm not really sure,
I slept through the whole thing.
[OOLONG] What? How could you
sleep if a huge monster was
fighting your grandpa
and wrecking your house?
[GOKU] I don't know.
The last thing I remember was
Grandpa warning me about the
full moon and how I should
never, ever look at it.
Of course, that didn't have
anything to do with the
monster. Grandpa was always
saying these really strange
things, and every--
[GOKU] Hey, what
are you guys doing?
Oh, nothing.
Hey, Goku?
Can I ask you a
little something?
Sure.
[BULMA] The night your
grandfather was killed, did you
happen to look at the full moon?
[GOKU] Well. I think I did.
Just before I fell asleep. Why?
I'm getting a
little nervous...
You're not the only one...
I had a feeling that
Goku wasn't just an ordinary
kid, I think I was right.
I'm at a loss here,
Yamcha.
How do we find out for sure?
How do you find
out what for sure?
I guess we could make
him look at the moon,
then there wouldn't
be any doubts at all!
That's true...
But what if he...
What if he does
turn into a monster?
We'd end up just
like his grandpa!
Yeah, that'd be a lot of fun.
Let's not chance it.
It's far too dangerous.
I'm with you!
Goku, be very careful
not to look at the moon!
[BULMA] It's right above you!
[GOKU] Huh?
Huh.
[GOKU] I don't see what
the big deal is?
Are you okay, Goku?
Of course I am!
You had us
scared there, kid!
Phew!
I knew it was
just a coincidence.
I'd suggest we run,
but I wouldn't know where!
Goku, stop it,
this isn't funny!
[YAMCHA] I don't
think he's joking!
[growling]
[screaming]
[roaring]
[rumbling]
[SHU] Oh, I hate it when
Pilaf starts snoring like this.
[MAI] It feels
like an earthquake.
[SHU] That's ridiculous!
[APE GOKU roaring]
[NARRATOR] Will Goku
return to his normal self?
Or will he unknowingly be
responsible for the destruction
of Bulma, Yamcha, and
the others? Find out next
time, on Dragon Ball!
[roaring]