[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
Goku was attacked by Red's
former right-hand man.
Armed with his battle-suit,
the dastardly villain
hoped to destroy
the young fighter
in his first official task
as the self-appointed new
leader of the Red Ribbon Army.
[GOKU]
Hey! Who turned out the lights?!
Let me go! Let me go!
[STAFF OFFICER laughs] It's time
to throw out the trash!
[GOKU groans, screams]
Can't this thing go
any faster, Yamcha?
Goku does need our help.
I can't believe he tried to
fight the Army by himself.
If you ask me,
he deserves what he gets!
Oolong! You better take
that back right this minute!
[PUAR] You're not helping
Goku by fighting each other!
I know. Why don't we
all play a little game?
The first person that
says another word
gets shot in the face!
[ROSHI whimpers]
[beeping]
[GOKU groaning]
[STAFF OFFICER cackles]
This is going to hurt, a lot.
[STAFF OFFICER]
Your meddling days are over.
[STAFF OFFICER cackles]
[STAFF OFFICER cackling]
Victory, victory!
[SOLDIER A]
Huh?
[SOLDIERS grunting]
[SOLDIERS]
Huh?
[SOLDIERS laugh]
[SOLDIERS murmuring]
[STAFF OFFICER]
Victory!
[SOLDIERS cheer]
[STAFF OFFICER]
I did it! I've won!
Victory! All hail me!
All hail me! I've won! Victory!
Time to give those guys a
taste of their own medicine.
[SOLDIER gasp, scream]
[GOKU yells]
The boy's death is quite
an accomplishment,
though it would
have been flawless
if I could have recovered
his Dragon Balls.
[knocking]
Nyahhh!
It's impossible!
[GOKU]
Hello.
[STAFF OFFICER growls]
[GOKU giggles]
You look silly.
[STAFF OFFICER grunting]
I'll get you.
[GOKU screams]
That thing can fly pretty fast.
[STAFF OFFICER]
What is that kid made of?
He won't stop coming!
[STAFF OFFICER]
Alright then...
A little gift from me to you,
troublemaker. Enjoy!
That's kinda strange.
I wonder why he's
turning upside down?
[SOLDIER A, SOLDIER B]
Huh?
[BOTH scream]
[SOLDIER B gasps]
Is he nuts?!
No way out this time. Bye!
--[SOLDIER B screams]
--[SOLDIER A] Run!
[SOLDIERS screaming]
[GOKU]
What's that?!
That doesn't look friendly!
[GOKU grunts]
It's coming back!
No! No-no-no!
Come on!
[STAFF OFFICER yelps]
[ALL screaming]
[BULMA]
Yamcha! Hey!
[YAMCHA]
A missile hit the mountaintop!
I hope Goku wasn't
anywhere near it!
[OOLONG] If he was,
I'm sure he didn't feel much.
[BULMA growls]
Why did you bring flowers
to a battle, anyway, moron!?
Because it's not a battle.
It's a funeral.
[PUAR, TURTLE gasp]
[YAMCHA gasps]
Hang on, everybody.
I'm takin' us down.
[ROSHI] Uh-oh! Here comes
more turbulence!
[ROSHI laughing]
[BULMA grunts]
[BULMA]
Behave yourself!
[TURTLE groans]
[GOKU]
Whoa! I don't believe it.
The whole top of
the mountain is gone!
It's time to be a
great leader and retreat.
But I will return,
mark my words!
You haven't seen the last of
Officer, I mean Commander Black!
[GOKU]
Hey! Where are you going?
I'm not letting you
get away that easy...
It's payback time!
[GOKU yelling,
STAFF OFFICER gasps]
This is for all my friends!
[STAFF OFFICER screams]
Eject! Eject!
There's got to be
a way out of here!
This model has everything...
...but a parachute!
Flying Nimbus!
[YAMCHA] No one could have
survived that, not even Goku.
His fight is over.
Gee, the optimism around
here is just overwhelming.
Sure are a lot of
people down there.
Look at those cowards run.
Those cowards are
armed to the teeth.
So why are they running
away from their own base?
Maybe they're not leaving.
Maybe they decided
to come after us.
We can't fight a single plane,
let alone an entire army.
You're right, Bulma.
If we're takin' a break,
then I'm takin' a nap.
Anyone care to be
my snuggle buddy?
This is a high-performance,
automatic weapon. It fires 100
rounds in less than 10 seconds.
Any questions?!
[ROSHI whimpers]
[DEMON CAT shrieks]
Ah! Hang on, Upa.
Just one more Dragon Ball and
I can wish your father back.
And with the radar
to show me the way,
I should find it
in no time at all!
[GOKU]
Hm...
Weird...
Is it broke?
[YAMCHA gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[YAMCHA]
We're here.
Welcome to the home base
of the Red Ribbon Army.
Goku! Hang on, we're coming!
I'll set us down right here.
Why so far away?
From here we're lookin'
at a good two-hour walk
to get to the base, at least.
Hey, I could land
on their doorstep,
if you wanna get caught.
He's right.
Yep.
Sorry, Launch, it seems
you're outnumbered.
We'll land here and sneak in
the back door. It'll be safer.
[LAUNCH growls]
[YAMCHA grunts]
Alright, everyone,
grab your gear
and leave your fear.
We're here for Goku!
Now, hold on there, General.
We can't just charge in there
like bulls. We need a plan.
Oh, yeah, I, uh...
I say we eat first,
and plan later.
Sure, we'll have ham.
Aw, that's not even
the least bit funny!
Who's laughing, oink boy?
I love bacon! Oh, quit your
whining, you big baby!
I'm so sick of hearing
you complain!
[OOLONG]
Hey, if you don't wanna listen
to the voice of reason, fine.
But I'm tellin' you
this is a bad idea.
I say we go in
there blastin',
and whoever's left standin'
after the bullets fly, wins.
Uh, yeah. That sounds real sane.
Everyone stop
arguing and focus.
We're here to help Goku.
[ROSHI] We have to set aside
our petty differences
and work together as a team.
And we need a solid plan.
Okay, I'm in.
I'm listenin'.
[BULMA]
Yamcha, what do you think
our chances are, realistically?
Well, let's see what
Master Roshi has to say first.
[ROSHI]
Hm...
There is one idea
that comes to mind,
but it's not easy.
It's very dangerous
and requires precise timing.
Yeah. Think you could
expand on that?
Come on, out with it, old man.
[ROSHI]
Hm... Mm-hm. Hm...
[ROSHI] I think we can
sneak past the guards,
but we'll need a distraction.
That'll be Bulma, who'll pretend
to be looking for a date
Good one!
What's wrong with you!
I'm not serious.
It doesn't seem
right playing games
when Goku could be in trouble.
Look, maybe one of us should
go in first and scout the area.
Okay... but, who?
The one nobody likes.
[OOLONG growls]
Oldest!
No, biggest ears.
[OOLONG growls]
Fewest teeth!
Smallest--
[BULMA growls]
Grow up, you two!
[BOTH sigh]
Your ears aren't
really that big.
[KRILLIN gasps]
Uh, hey guys...
We've got company!
[ALL gasp]
Run for your lives!
[ROSHI]
Everyone to the woods!
[YAMCHA]
Go!
Wait! What about the airplane?
They'll spot it for sure!
Yamcha! There's no time!
Thanks, Puar, let's hope
they didn't see it!
Master Roshi,
that looks like Goku!
I don't believe it! It is Goku!
[GOKU] It's not working...
This isn't good.
These things sure do break easy.
I'd better go to Master Roshi's
house and ask Bulma to fix it.
The only problem is,
I don't know how to get back.
[GROUP cheering]
[GOKU]
Hm?
Uh...
Whew! It's really him.
Thank goodness he's alive!
[ALL cheering]
Oh! Hello! Oh boy,
am I glad to see you guys!
He looks happy for someone
who's been fighting an army.
I guess we were wrong.
Maybe he didn't
fight anyone at all.
Is something wrong?
Nothing. We just thought
you were dead, that's all.
We heard that you
decided to attack
the entire Red Ribbon Army
all by yourself.
Thought you might
need some help.
Wow! That's amazing.
How'd you guys know all of that?
This stinks.
He's not even wounded!
You're a smart kid.
I figured you wouldn't do
something as foolish as that.
[GOKU]
Huh?
But I did attack
the Red Ribbon Army.
I beat the whole bunch
and I managed to get
six of the Dragon Balls!
[ALL gasp]
[KRILLIN]
Y-Y-You mean you beat
every single soldier in
the Red Ribbon Army...
...all alone?!
Yeah! Well, not everyone.
Some of them ran away.
Puar, go scout out the base.
Search for any sign of life.
Uh, right!
Oh!
Yamcha the base is deserted!
The entire base?!
That's unbelievable!
Goku, do you think after this
you could show me a few tips?
It was easy
once I got started.
I can see the headlines now.
Evil Army Defeated by Child.
It's just one army!
A-Ah-choo!
Silly goose, how are
we going to have
a picnic without any food?
[ALL]
Huh?
[PUAR] Let's take a walk. I'll
fill you in on all the details.
I've seen a lot, but I've
never heard of anyone
accomplishing what you just did.
[GOKU] See Master,
I'm a lot stronger now.
Just like you, I climbed
up Korin's Tower.
What?! You made it to
the top? Of Korin's tower?!
[GOKU giggles]
[GOKU] I heard whoever drank
Master Korin's sacred water
would gain increased strength.
So, I asked him
if I could have some.
He agreed...
[GOKU]
So, it's all right then?
[GOKU] ...but only if I could
take it from him first.
[GOKU]
It took a while, but I did it!
You consumed
Korin's sacred water?
Yes!
I see... That would
certainly explain
your increased strength.
I'm here for the sacred water.
[ROSHI] That boy's
ability is astounding.
It took me three years
to reach the same goal.
And to think I used
to brag about that.
[KRILLIN]
What are you guys talkin' about?
Hey, if Korin was in
the Red Ribbon Army,
what would he be?
Um... I don't know...
A general maybe?
Ha ha! No silly, everybody
knows he'd be a kernel!
[ALL groan]
Uh, get it? Kor-in, corn!
Work with me, folks!
Excuse me, Bulma?
Uh, yes.
The Dragon Radar won't work.
I think it's broken...
Can you fix it?
Broken?
Why are you looking for
another Dragon Ball anyway?
I thought all you
were interested in
was your grandpa's 4-star ball.
I found Grandpa's ball,
but I need all seven
if I'm going to help
Upa and his father.
[BORA] What are you doing?
You nearly hit us!
Well, that's the idea...
I'm a hit man.
[BORA screams]
Here, have your spear.
[UPA gasps]
[BORA groans]
[GOKU] I felt responsible
for what happened to Bora
since the killer was
really after me.
So I promised Upa
I would ask the Dragon
to revive his father.
[PUAR]
Aw! Goku... You're swell.
I'll need to run a few tests,
but I think I can fix it.
You'll have to wait till we
get back to Roshi's house.
All my tools are there.
Thanks, Bulma!
[BULMA]
Goku really impressed me today.
[YAMCHA]
No kidding! He's a strong boy.
[BULMA] Not his strength.
His heart. He genuinely cares.
Strong? Yamcha, he's darn
near invincible!
You think he's unstoppable?!
[ROSHI laughs] I think Goku
has demonstrated abilities
that go far beyond
his years and training.
Let's be clear.
He didn't just hurt the
Red Ribbon Army, he crushed it!
When one little boy can
cripple a deadly empire,
with its superior
firepower and resources,
I not only think the word
invincible applies,
I think he defines it.
They're right above me.
[ROSHI] Personally,
I would have tried a more
diplomatic approach.
But hey, I can't fly
on a cloud either.
[ROSHI laughs] They'll be
talking about that one
for a while. He may very
well be stronger than me.
Hey, Roshi, is this
your subtle way
of informing me that I
need additional training
if I plan to beat
Goku at next year's
Martial Arts Tournament?
Did I say subtle?
[KRILLIN yelps]
In that case, I might
as well tag along
and help him find
the last Dragon Ball...
Yeah. He deserves the pleasure
of my company, and besides,
maybe some of that
invincibility of his
will eventually rub off on me.
Good idea. I think I'll join ya.
Just one more
Dragon Ball, Upa...
And then you'll have your
father back again. I promise.
[NARRATOR]
As Goku flies off to retrieve
the last Dragon Ball,
one can only imagine
the adventure that awaits
and the danger...
It all becomes a reality,
next time on Dragon Ball!