[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball...
Danger descended upon the
normally tranquil land of Korin.
[UPA] My Daddy!
[NARRATOR] Bora, protector
of this sacred land,
found himself locked
in a bitter struggle
with the ruthless
Mercenary Tao.
[BORA yells]
Here, have your spear.
[NARRATOR] Goku
looked on in horror
as the fight took a
sudden, deadly turn.
But by the time he moved in to
help, it was already too late...
[NARRATOR] Bora has
paid the ultimate price
to protect his land
and defend Goku.
Now Goku is determined
to avenge his sacrifice.
But will he be any match for the
Red Ribbon Army's hired thug?
Mercenary Tao gets down to
business in today's episode
of Dragon Ball!
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU growls]
[TAO chuckles]
[UPA gasps]
[GOKU groans]
That's all?
Piece of cake.
Goku?
[GOKU growls]
I'm not... done yet!
[TAO] I see. You're a
glutton for punishment.
[GOKU yells]
Amateur!
[GOKU grunts]
[TAO chuckles]
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU screams]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU yells]
[TAO] Hmmm...
[GOKU grunts]
Settle down, boy.
Oww!
[bones crack]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU shouts]
[UPA gasps]
Goku, no!
[TAO] Hmm...
[GOKU wails]
[GOKU screams]
Well, the boy at least takes
a better beating than most.
[GOKU groans]
[TAO] Hm?!
[groaning continues]
[TAO growls]
[GOKU cries]
[TAO gasps]
Hey! Ouch!
[UPA gasps]
So... you're back on your feet.
I would advise against that.
That hurt!
[GOKU growls]
My turn.
Ka...
me...
ha...
meee...
--[TAO gasps]
--Haaa!
[TAO grunts]
[UPA grunts]
[TAO growls]
Uhh...?
You ruined... my outfit!
You're still standing?!
Dodon Ray!
[GOKU yells]
[UPA gasps]
[yelling continues]
[TAO] Hmm.
[UPA whimpers]
[GOKU rasps]
So this is what the
army wants so badly?
Whatever. I guess
my work is done here.
But... before I go back
I must have new clothes,
thanks to him!
[TAO] That robe was
custom made too...
[UPA growls]
Now...
Hey! How could you
do that to my daddy?!
Ahh!
[UPA yells]
[UPA wails]
[TAO laughs]
You should thank me for
letting you live, little boy.
[UPA cries]
[RED chuckles]
It would seem that
Tao has everything
well under
control now.
[STAFF OFFICER] Wait a moment.
Something strange is happening.
[RED gasps]
What d'ya mean?!
Look at the radar.
Only three of the
Dragon Balls are moving.
Apparently this one is
still in the land of Korin.
Here's the ball we currently
have in our possession.
But the three that are in motion
are heading in the
wrong direction.
Where that man going?
What's he up to?!
[CHUBBY DRUNK gulps]
[BOTH warble]
[BOTH] Huh?
[CROWD murmurs]
[CHILDREN gasp]
What happened to you...?
Yeah, what's the matter,
big guy...? Did you get blasted?
I'm telling ya, man.
You look like something
the camel drug in.
[guffawing]
Hey, can't you talk?
Did you get hit on the noggin'?
Y-You got amnesia?
Or maybe you're just senile.
[TAO growls]
[BOTH] Huh?!
Hu-Huh...?
Fine then. I guess you want
me to rearrange your face!
Hrmph!
[CHUBBY DRUNK] Be quiet!
He didn't mean that.
And why not?
[CHUBBY DRUNK whimpers]
[CHUBBY DRUNK] Because...
[whimpering continues]
Take a good look at his face!
Eh, what about it?
[CHUBBY DRUNK]
It's Mercenary Tao!
Uhh...
You are drunk!
This guy looks nuthin'
like Namecary--
[TALL DRUNK gasps]
[TALL DRUNK]
Uh, wait a second...
It is him...! M-Mercenary Tao!
[CROWD gasps]
[BABY wails]
[CROWD murmurs]
I need a garment made.
Somebody show me
where to find a tailor!
[MAN A] His shop is over there!
I want it to look
exactly like this;
every stitch, every
detail, everything!
[TAILOR] O-kay.
Come back in ten days.
[TAO growls]
No, you have, mmm... three.
Three days?!
That's impossible, sir.
Oh, you'll find a way.
Now I need
something to wear.
This'll do.
Oh, yes. Make
yourself at home.
Now... get started.
I have a schedule to keep.
Yes, I've heard
about your work.
Now that I think about it,
three days is plenty!
Please... call me if
you need anything.
Anything at all!
[TAO] Where's your telephone?
Oh! It's right over here!
[SOLDIER A] Commander Red!
Mercenary Tao on line one.
Tao, where have you been?!
How did it go?
Did you take care of
the boy nuisance?
[TAO] Of course.
Everything you asked.
I've had to stop
on a bit of an errand,
but I'll be there in a
few days to deliver your prize
and collect my fee.
[RED] The brat's
really gone, huh?
That's right.
And I accept cash only.
Yeah, I got it!
Now are you absolutely sure
you've collected all
four of the Dragon Balls?
[TAO] What?!
There are only three!
One short! Check the boy's body.
He probably had one of the
Dragon Balls in his clothing.
Right. Well, we can
take it from here...
He's no longer a threat,
so I'll just send a man
to retrieve the ball.
I mean, how difficult could
that possibly be now?
[TAO] Great.
See you in a few days.
We'll see you then, Tao.
That's a relief.
Everything's in place.
That man is certainly
worth the fee.
Oh, Daddy...
I wish I had been
strong enough to help...
I wish I could have
saved Goku, too...
[UPA whimpers]
Huh?
[UPA gasps]
It's amazing that such a
little child could have caused
the Red Ribbon Army
such enormous problems.
We were so careless.
Ha! Well, what d'ya know?!
--[GOKU grunts]
--[PILOT gasps]
[GOKU groans]
What do you want?
[PILOT grunts]
Hey!
Goku! You're alive!
[GOKU grunts]
My Grandpa's ball!
Having it in your shirt like
that must have protected you!
I think it saved your life!
[GOKU gasps]
[shotgun cocks]
[BOTH gasp]
Yah!
[shotgun firing]
[shotgun cocks]
[shot fires]
[GOKU groans]
Didn't get me!
[PILOT gasps]
[engine starts]
[GOKU growls]
[PILOT] Headquarters!
Come in, Headquarters!
Can you hear me?! Anyone?!
[MAN B] This is headquarters.
This is urgent!
Hmm...?
[PILOT gasps]
Power Pole extend!
[PILOT screams]
[MAN B] This is headquarters!
Do you copy?
We've lost communication!
What?!
[RED growls]
Not again...
[GOKU] Hmm..
Grandpa...
I guess your still looking
out after me, aren't you?
[GOKU sighs] I'm really sorry
I couldn't help your dad...
[UPA] It's... It's not
your fault, Goku.
[UPA sniffs]
[GOKU] Why does it
have to be this way...?
Now Upa's all alone,
just like I was...
Oh, Grandpa, can't you
tell me what to do...?
There's got to be
some way I can help...
Wait! Upa! If I can collect
all of the Dragon Balls
I think I can bring
your father back to life!
What?! Can you really do that?!
I think so!
If I find all seven, I can have
any wish that I want!
But remember? The bad man
that hurt my father
took your bag with
the other Dragon Balls.
That's right! He sure did!
Dodon--!
Well, the next time I see him,
I'll just have to
take them back!
Then I'll only need three more!
That guy is really
strong, though...
I'm going to have to find
some way to beat him!
[UPA sighs]
[GOKU] I just don't know
what to do...
[UPA gasps]
[GOKU growls]
My Kamehameha wave didn't
even leave a scratch!
I've got to use something else!
[UPA] Why don't you try
to climb Korin tower?
What? Uhh...
Hmm...
Oh, I think you
can make it, Goku!
That's right.
If I climb all the way to
the top, I'll get to drink
the water that'll make
me super strong, won't I?
If the stories are true.
I wish I could ride
my Nimbus up there.
But I have to make it all the
way up by myself, don't I?
[UPA]
Yes, that is the only rule.
[GOKU] Hmm...
Ha-ha! Okay,
I'd better get going!
Then good luck, and be careful!
I bet that Tao guy will come
back to get my Dragon Ball,
so you should find
somewhere safe
to hide until I get back, okay?
I won't be long.
Watch your step!
I believe in you, Goku...
You can do it...
[phone ringing]
[TAO] Hm?!
[RED] This is Commander Red.
What do you want?
Listen...
[TAO growls]
[TAO] Yes?
[RED] I think that that
kid may still be alive.
[TAO] What?! That's impossible!
I told you I took care
of him, Commander!
Well, something strange
is going on over there.
I want you to go and
check it out immediately!
I'll be available
again in three days.
Call me then.
[RED] That will be too late!
I want you to go right now!
You can't order me!
I'm not one of
your little soldiers
[RED growls]
Is he going to
look into it?
[growling continues]
[GOKU sighs]
[GOKU gasps]
I can't even see the top yet!
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU screams]
[GOKU sighs]
[UPA whimpers]
[GOKU pants]
Oh, it's way past
my dinner time...
--[stomach growls]
--I'm so hungry!
[GOKU] I think I'll
just take a little nap...
[GOKU snores]
I hope I'm almost there...
[GOKU groans]
I-I'm so tir-ed!
[UPA] You can do it, Goku!
[TAO] That's it? Piece of cake.
That's it! I will never give up!
No matter what I'm gonna
make it to the top!
[NARRATOR] Goku continues
his perilous ascent
to the top of Korin Tower.
But what mysteries
await him at the summit?
You'll have to
tune in to find out!
Don't miss the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball!