[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
Desperate to defeat Hero, Yamcha
launched his ultimate weapon,
a missile of pure spirit energy.
[HERO yelps]
[NARRATOR] Though his adversary
deftly dodged the bullet,
he wasn't expecting
a second volley.
[YAMCHA]
Yeah! See ya, space nerd!
[NARRATOR] However, Yamcha
got a surprise of his own.
[YAMCHA yells]
[NARRATOR]
Yamcha's defeat made it clear
that Hero was much more
than he appeared.
[NARRATOR]
Fight after fight, warriors fell
as the World Martial Arts
Tournament continued.
Until at last, only two
contestants remained
in the semi-final round,
Tien Shinhan...
...and Goku.
[CROWD cheers]
[GOKU growls]
[BOTH grunt]
[NARRATOR] Junior, anxious
to engage Goku in battle,
watched intently as both
fighters continued to dazzle
each other and the audience
in a spectacular show
of martial arts savvy.
[yells]
[blows landing,
BOTH grunting]
[TIEN yells]
[TIEN growls]
[GOKU yells]
[TIEN shouts]
[yells]
[CROWD cheers]
I never knew your hard
head could be so painful.
The best weapons are those
your opponent least expects.
Get ready!
[gasps]
[TIEN yells]
[yells]
[GOKU laughs]
[BOTH grunting, growling]
[TIEN grunts]
[BOTH growl]
[BOTH grunting]
It appears this fight
will be decided
by who has the
strongest will to win!
[gasping]
[TIEN bellows]
Goku!
[CROWD gasping]
[cheering]
The crowd seems entertained,
but they wouldn't
know a good fight
if it kicked them in the head.
If this is Goku's best,
I'll bury him.
Well done. I'm amazed
by your level of skill.
You were already near
perfection three years ago.
Now, even that word
seems inadequate
to describe your talents.
Thanks, but you should really
save that praise for yourself.
You're powerful!
Thank you, Goku. But seriously,
there's one skill
I've improved upon
that even you
can't keep up with.
Huh?
And it so happens to be
the most important tool
in a successful attack.
And that is...
the skill of speed!
[TIEN yells]
[GOKU growls]
--[gasping]
--Oh, there they go again.
[ROSHI growls]
[ANNOUNCER]
Once more, Goku and Tien Shinhan
take their battle to the skies!
[GOKU]
Where...?
Haah!
Gotcha!
[TIEN] Your eyes are
still working, Goku!
That's good!
I'm impressed!
I'm moving at terrific speeds,
and yet, you're
still tracking me!
But, just because
you can see me,
doesn't necessarily
mean you know
where I am or what I'm doing!
--[GOKU gasps]
--[TIEN yells]
[GOKU screams]
[ANNOUNCER]
Look out below!
One of the contestants
is falling fast!
From this announcer's
vantage point,
it looks like the
plunging player is Goku!
And chasing close behind
is Tien Shinhan!
Haah!
Hyaah! Haah!
Huh?!
[growls, yells]
Yeah! Nice kicking,
Tien Shinhan!
[ROSHI growls]
[TIEN growls]
[TIEN growling]
[blows landing]
[ANNOUNCER] Tien Shinhan
continues his relentless attack,
which is obviously
wearing Goku down!
But it would seem that this
fight is far from over!
[TIEN yelling]
[yells]
--[gasps]
--[TIEN yells]
--Goku!
--He'll fall out of the ring!
Goku is heading straight
out-of-bounds!
[CROWD cheering]
[ALL sigh]
You caught me by surprise!
I can tell you're not going
to make this one easy on me.
Would you really want
me to? I doubt it.
I don't envy your position.
Anyone who hopes to defeat me
had better first
ask for a miracle.
Yeah, you are a challenge.
I hate to state the obvious,
but we both know I'll win.
[TIEN] I'm not bragging.
It's just a fact.
Your body is slower than mine
and that will be your undoing.
I appreciate
your concern. It's true.
I'm nowhere near as fast
as I would like to be.
What?! Goku moves
at the speed of light,
yet he thinks he's slow?!
That's Goku for you.
He has never been normal.
[CHICHI sighs] That's my Goku.
Isn't he wonderful?
Goku, it's time
to end this. Ready?
Ah, just a minute, please.
Huh?
Before we continue, I need to
shed some of these clothes.
Ah?
Suit yourself.
If you're going to lose,
you might as well
be comfortable.
I can tell you've trained
hard these last three years.
Glad you noticed.
I came here to win.
Whew! The heat is
beginning to take its toll
on the fighters,
especially Goku.
He obviously hopes
to find some relief
by relieving himself
of his uniform,
an unusual solution,
but then these two titans
aren't your everyday warriors.
The speed with which they hurl
themselves around the ring
is nothing short of outrageous.
One could hardly hope to catch
but a glimpse of the action,
short of slowing down
time itself!
At this point,
it's anyone's guess
as to which one
will go the distance.
Well, I'll be.
He's taking that thing off.
Now this should be interesting.
[gasps]
There's a sight! Goku struggling
to take off a t-shirt?
Maybe the heat
has gotten to him.
[sighs]
I don't think that's
a normal t-shirt.
[crash]
[gasps]
Hey!
[TIEN] Goku, do you mind if
I take a look at your shirt?
What? Sure.
[TIEN gasps]
What is this?!
[ROSHI]
Hm?!
[CROWD gasping]
[TIEN grunts]
Why is Tien acting so strangely?
Think. How many times have
you seen him wear a shirt?
[growls]
Goku, this thing weighs a ton!
Have you been wearing it
through the entire tournament?!
Yep, Kami told me to.
It was part of my training.
[gasps]
[GOKU] It's not much different
than Master Roshi's style.
He wore a big turtle
shell to gain strength.
It's pretty much
the same principle here.
Your wrist bands as well...
and your boots!
Could... you continue the fight?
This is a tournament.
[KRILLIN]
What are you guys doing?
Don't worry about this stuff.
We'll take care of it.
Thanks, Krillin.
I appreciate it.
Come on, Tien.
You guys have to keep fighting.
Here, give me that.
Hey! What the-- What is this?!
[grunts]
It's really heavy!
This is unlike any shirt
I've ever seen before!
[GOKU laughs]
I don't see how you managed to
walk in these lead boots,
let alone fight!
It wasn't easy. Each of those
boots weigh 20 kilos.
My feet have never felt so sore!
[TIEN thinking]
I don't believe this guy.
He'll do anything
to get stronger.
This-- This is impossible! Good
thing there's no water around!
Ah! I'd say I'm holding
about a hundred kilos!
Are you kidding?!
A hundred kilos?!
--[ANNOUNCER whimpers]
--[CROWD gasping]
It took me a long time to be
able to handle that much weight.
In the beginning, I struggled
to carry even a few rocks.
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU yelling]
But it was all worth it.
Now that I'm not
carrying around that weight,
I feel light as a feather!
[growls]
[CROWD gasping]
No, lighter than a
feather! It's great!
[GOKU giggles]
Goku just keeps amazing me.
I thought there was
no surprise left...
...but a hundred kilos?!
That's just crazy!
[gasps]
Well, I'm all
warmed up. Let's go!
Impressive! I've never
known you to show off.
You think you're
strong enough to defeat me?
Then let's go! Ready?
Yeah!
Here we go, ladies and
gentlemen! The fight is back on!
The crowd's expecting
greatness from you.
Don't hold back,
because I won't!
[TIEN yells]
Goku, I would congratulate
you on your increased speed,
were it not such a shame.
All that training, and yet,
I'm still one step ahead of you!
Are you sure about that?
Huh?
[giggles]
This belt does
belong to you, right?
[gasps]
[CROWD cheers, laughs]
[giggles]
What's going on here?!
This can't be happening!
You stole my belt
right from under me?!
[GOKU]
Yup.
You have to feel pity
for Tien Shinhan,
as Goku further
demonstrates his speed
by removing the
blushing baldy's belt!
[JUNIOR thinking]
Hmph. Quick.
[CHICHI gasps]
[TIEN thinking]
Doesn't make sense!
No matter how fast he moved,
I should have seen it!
[TIEN yells]
[TIEN]
Hmph.
I was wrong. I allowed
my arrogance to blind me.
I have never known a man
or beast that can move
as swift as you.
But if you think that gift alone
will aid you, you are mistaken.
Tien Shinhan will
fall before no man.
[yells]
--[CROWD laughs]
--[TIEN chuckles sheepishly]
[laughing, gasping]
Here. You might have better
luck if you get dressed.
[TIEN growls]
[TIEN] I don't need your help!
You've done enough already!
[TIEN gasps]
[TIEN]
Just you wait!
I have yet to play my best card!
[OOLONG laughs]
Oww!
Stop laughing!
What did you mean when you said
"playing your best card"?
Are you planning to use the
volleyball technique again?
Or the Tribeam?
No. I want to defeat you, not
blow you into a million pieces.
Besides, with that
incredible speed of yours,
you'd probably just dodge
the blast anyway.
What I have in mind
isn't quite as destructive
as the Tribeam,
but it's enough--
I'm not worried. Try it.
[TIEN snarls]
You will not
fend off this attack!
[GOKU]
Hmph.
Tien sounds serious.
He wouldn't do anything
to hurt Goku, would he?
That depends.
I wanna know what technique
Tien has up his sleeve.
--[TIEN yells]
--[GOKU yells]
[ROSHI] I don't know
if I can handle this...
After their last battle...
...who knows what
mind-boggling concoctions
those boys are cooking up!
My biggest mistake was assuming
that my exceptional sight
would be enough to
catch your movements...
These eyes have failed.
So if three will not win me this
fight, then I shall use twelve!
[GOKU]
Hm?
[TIEN]
They will see you fall!
Uh, twelve eyes?
[PICCOLO JR. thinking]
That's it. Make your move!
I'm sorry. But this is
the way it has to be!
[TIEN growls]
[NARRATOR]
What did Tien mean by 12 eyes?
To what length will
he go to avoid defeat,
and in the end,
what price will Goku pay?
[GOKU gasps]
[NARRATOR] What is to come?
You won't believe your own eyes.
Next time on Dragon Ball!