[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
Goku's search led him
to the land of Korin,
where he discovered Captain
Yellow of the Red Ribbon Army
in the midst of another scheme
to steal a Dragon Ball.
[BORA] What's that?
[NARRATOR] Goku quickly sent
the despicable captain's plans
into a tailspin, and
made some new friends
with a daring rescue
on the Flying Nimbus.
[GOKU chuckles]
Hel-lo!
[NARRATOR] His good deeds
did not go unrewarded.
[GOKU]
The Four-Star Dragon Ball!
I can't believe I finally found
my Grandpa's Dragon Ball!
[GOKU giggles]
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
at Red Ribbon headquarters,
plans were being made to cut
Goku's celebration short!
[RED] Listen up, Yellow!
[NARRATOR] Fed up with the
repeated failure of his men,
Commander Red has called in
some outside help;
The world's most
notorious assassin...
[TAO] I'm Mercenary Tao.
[GUARDS gasp]
Um, General?
Welcome back!
Hmph!
[GUARD A gasps]
Don't give me your
false sentiments.
You were all glad
to be rid of me.
So, save it.
[GUARD A] Excuse me,
sir! Forgive me!
Thanks for meeting me,
Mercenary Tao.
We have this situation--
One thing before
we get started...
I must tell you my
fee is very expensive.
Ah, I can assure you,
if you complete our mission,
we will pay you handsomely.
Then my going rate...
...is ten billion a head.
Ten... billion apiece?
[TAO] Did I stutter?
Though, I am having a
special 20th anniversary sale.
For a limited time only,
you get a quality slaying
at a bargain price.
All services are
fifty percent off.
[RED gasps]
You heard right.
A measly five...
billion... zeni.
That's... reasonable.
How can we be
sure, though...
that you are who
you say you are?
Would you like to try me out?
Oh, no, that
won't be necessary.
[knocking at door]
Who is it?
[BLUE] General Blue!
[RED growls]
He's back?
Come in!
I have returned to duty, sir.
How could you come back here?
Well, it was quite a hassle.
I was forced to steal
a plane and a car and--
[RED] That's not what I meant!
You failed to get the
Dragon Ball from the kid...
And you have the nerve to
come here empty handed?
[BLUE gasps]
But he's... tricky...
I don't need your excuses.
But, Commander,
I was able to confiscate
the Dragon Radar from him.
[STAFF OFFICER gasps]
Here it is!
It easily hones in on the
Dragon Ball's location,
and it's extremely
accurate, too.
It's smaller
than I expected.
It'll take me no time to
secure all the Dragon Balls
with this little device. Ha, ha!
[RED chuckles]
[RED] A good find,
I'll give you that...
But...
if I recall, your assignment
was to get the Dragon Balls.
[BLUE gulps]
[RED] You know how
it works around here.
Those who cannot achieve
results are punished.
And severely...
[BLUE whimpers]
N-No...!
[RED] However, since you've been
of some value to us in the past,
I'll give you a chance
to save yourself.
How?
I will be willing to let you
live if you fight Mercenary Tao
here and defeat him.
Mercenary Tao?
[TAO] Mm-hmm...
[STAFF OFFICER] Ah...
So, what d'ya think?
You in?
Yes!
Thank you for the
opportunity, Commander.
[BLUE chuckles]
So the ball holds
special power.
Now I understand why the army
was so determined to acquire it.
But I don't really care
about the wishes
or anything like that.
I was only looking
for this Dragon Ball
because it belonged
to my grandpa.
[BORA] Oh... Good.
You have few wants.
That's fortunate.
Daddy, what do you
mean by that?
You see, son...
Too many desires can
drive a person mad...
I was wondering.
What is that big pole sticking
out of the ground for?
The tower...
It is a sacred symbol
of my people.
To our tribe, it is a very
important and honored landmark.
We call it the Korin Tower.
[BORA] I learned of the
legend from my grandfather
when I was Upa's age.
It is a story that has been
told for many generations...
[BORA] But still we wait,
after all this time,
for the arrival of someone
who can pass the test...
[GOKU] What do you
mean? What test?
[BORA] It is said that
if any person can climb
to the top of this
tower unaided,
he will find the great noble
guardian waiting for him there.
[BORA] The guardian will
then give him a cup
of cold water to drink...
[BORA] And with that single sip,
the climber's abilities
will increase dramatically.
[GOKU] Really?
[BORA] As incredible
as it sounds,
my people have always
believed it to be true.
[GOKU] So if I climbed
all the way up there,
I'd get a lot
stronger, right?
Have you ever tried it?
Once when I was young.
But I couldn't make it
all the way to the top.
Anyway, no one has ever been
successful in the attempt.
But...
I heard that a long time ago
one person did make it
A compelling story,
but only... a myth.
It's so... gigantic!
[GOKU] So, why do you live here?
Because of the tower...
My family has been guarding
it for generations.
It is our ancestral duty.
It is my job.
I am the protector of the land.
Oh... I see...
Do you think it would be okay if
I took my Nimbus to the top?
So you're the world
famous assassin,
the one they call
Mercenary Tao?
Do you want
my autograph?
[BLUE laughs]
Well, aren't you amusing...?
I suppose I'll have to put
an end to your arrogance.
I don't work for free.
This will cost you.
Understand?
[RED] That's fine...
Let's get on with the show!
You should have a weapon
handy, you know, just in case.
[TAO] Hmph!
I won't even need
my hands and feet.
I'll just use my
tongue to beat you.
I wouldn't count on it.
[BLUE chuckles]
Begin!
[BLUE yells]
Heh... Not bad!
Now... try this!
[BLUE growls]
[growling continues]
[BLUE chuckles]
Well, how do you like
being paralyzed?
[BLUE grunts]
[bones crack]
[BLUE gasps]
[TAO sighs]
Excuse me.
What was that?
Impossible!
[BOTH gasp]
General Blue's finishing
move is completely useless!
It's astounding!
[TAO] Hmmm...
[BLUE yells]
[BLUE grunts]
[BOTH gasp]
[BLUE whimpers]
[TAO] Mmm...
I'd say you've got
that problem licked!
[RED] He... killed...
him with... one strike!
[STAFF OFFICER]
I can't believe it...!
He definitely lives up
to his reputation!
Now.
Since playtime is over,
why don't you tell me about
the real target so I
can finally get to work?
So he's just a little boy.
Yes, technically speaking,
but he's no ordinary kid.
He's incredibly strong.
Well... it doesn't
really matter.
I will annihilate
any man, woman, or child
as long as the price is right.
[STAFF OFFICER]
You're a good man.
By the way, after you
eliminate the boy, search him.
He will have in his
possession four special balls.
They're called Dragon Balls,
and they're very valuable.
You are to bring
those back to me.
They look just like this.
[TAO] Mmm...
That's going to cost you extra.
No problem.
In fact if anyone
gets in your way,
just do away with
them, too. We'll pay.
Very well...
But any extra killings
are twice the price...
[RED gasps]
This place, "Korin".
It's about 1400 miles to
the northeast, is it not?
I'll have the jet prepared
for you right away.
That's not necessary...
It'll take too long by airplane.
Huh?!
[TAO] Mmm... Hmm...
Would it be possible for me to
borrow this column from you?
Uh, what d'ya want...
uh, with that pillar?
[TAO] Mmm...
[BOTH] Uhh...
[BOTH gasp]
[TAO] Let's see... 1400 miles.
I should be back
in about 30 minutes.
Huh...?
[TAO laughs]
Amazing...
T hat Tao is simply amazing.
[RED laughs]
After all this time, the Dragon
Balls are going to be mine!
[GOKU] Huh?
[GOKU giggles]
Wow! That sure smells good!
[GOKU chuckles]
[GOKU slurps]
[UPA laughs]
Have as much as you want.
Thank you!
[UPA laughs]
[GOKU] This is great!
I'll be better at everything
once I go up there!
Do not get your hopes up,
my young friend...
It may only be a legend.
[GOKU] Oh...
I want to try it anyway!
[UPA] But you're
already strong!
I'm not the strongest though,
so it's still worth the chance!
Yeah! It's definitely
worth it to be the best!
[GOKU chuckles]
Perhaps, but, it will
not be an easy task.
Have a lot of people
tried to climb the tower?
Besides you?
Yes. There are many
who have attempted it.
[GOKU] Oh...
But... they all have failed.
[GOKU] Ohh...
The tower is much taller
than you imagine.
It takes many
days to scale it.
Those who try often eat
their provisions too soon,
and fall off from
weakness and hunger...
Those who attempt the climb
by plane fare no better.
Oh? How come?
They run out of fuel,
before they ever seen the top...
It's that far away?
[BORA] So you see,
those who defy the rules,
or who attempt the
climb unprepared
do not generally
get a second chance.
Oh.
[UPA] Oh.
What's that, Daddy?
Huh?
That thing... in the sky!
[GOKU] I can see a person on it.
[GOKU yells]
Watch out!
[BORA] Hang on!
[GOKU yells]
Pleased to kill you.
[BORA] What are you doing?!
You nearly hit us!
[TAO] Hmph.
Well, that's the idea...
I'm a hit man.
Huh? A hit man?
Whoever you are, your kind
is not welcome in Korin.
[TAO] The name is Tao.
And I won't be staying long.
I've simply come for the boy.
[BORA] What?
But I don't know you, do I?
Why did you come to see me?
The Red Ribbon Army has sent me
here to tie up some loose ends.
[GOKU growls] Red Ribbon?!
Yes. You're getting
in the way of their hunt
for the "Dragon Balls",
so you must be destroyed.
[GOKU growls] Again?!
They won't quit!
[UPA gasps]
Daddy, help him!
Please don't let them hurt Goku!
Now wait a minute.
That boy you are threatening
saved my son's life.
If you have come here
looking for a fight,
you will have to
deal with me first!
[TAO growls]
It's alright!
I think I can handle him!
It is my obligation to protect
this land from enemies.
Now, Son, stay back.
Okay!
[TAO chuckles]
What a fool!
Why would you choose
to take the fall?
Enough talk!
Daddy! Be careful!
[TAO] Hmm...
I'll bet you fancy
yourself a trained fighter.
Let's see if you
can handle this.
[BORA gasps]
Wh-What?!
[BORA growls]
[TAO] What's the matter?
Is it stuck? That's too bad.
[BORA grunts]
[BOTH gasp]
[grunting continues]
Let's try something
else... shall we?
[BORA grunts]
Hey! My Daddy!
Still stuck? That's okay,
I'll move it for you.
[BORA grunts]
[BOTH gasp]
[TAO chuckles]
[BORA yells]
Here, have your spear!
Nim-bus!
Daaad!
[BORA grunts]
[GOKU gasps
UPA gasps]
[TAO chuckles]
[GOKU gasps]
[BORA grunts]
[UPA cries]
[UPA] Daddy! Please
don't go, Daddy!
[UPA wails]
[GOKU growls]
[TAO] You're next, little one.
[GOKU snarls]
That's it!
[GOKU growls]
[NARRATOR] It would seem that
Mercenary Tao's reputation
as the world's most
dangerous assassin
has not been exaggerated.
Now, this cold and
calculating villain
has set his steely
gaze on our hero.
Goku faces the greatest
challenge of his life,
on the next heart-stopping
episode of Dragon Ball.