[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball...
In an effort to recover
the stolen Dragon Balls
and Dragon Radar, Goku pursued
the wily General Blue
through the skies
on his Flying Nimbus!
In the end, the high-speed
aerial chase crash-landed
them both in a bizarre place
known as Penguin Village.
There, with the help
of some new friends,
Goku was able to recover
the four magic balls,
but Blue managed to escape
with the Radar!
Luckily, a local scientist,
Sembei Norimaki,
was able to help him
construct a new one,
thus enabling our hero to
once again resume his quest.
Almost there.
Maybe this next one will finally
be my grandpa's Dragon Ball.
Ah! What I wouldn't give
for some conditioner.
This heat is absolutely
murdering my hair!
It's that little runt's fault
that I'm stranded
out here like this.
I promise, he is going to pay
for every single split-end!
[knocking]
Enter!
[STAFF OFFICER]
Excuse me, Commander,
but the boy has been
tracked traveling west,
just as you expected.
[RED]
Hmm...
Right into the hands
of Captain Yellow...
That reminds me,
has he been able to locate
the Dragon Ball yet?
No sir, he's had
quite a few setbacks.
Well, that figures...
Enough! I've had it with
all these silly games!
Buffoons!
They've been diggin' here
for days now, and no results!
[beeping]
What you want?
[SOLDIER A]
Captain Yellow, sir!
We have located the Dragon Ball.
I'm looking at it right now!
[YELLOW]
Where is it?
[SOLDIER A] It's down
there, sir. Just below us.
[YELLOW]
I don't see anything.
[SOLDIER A] Look closer to
the edge of the crater, sir.
It's there!
Well how about that?
Stop the presses!
Ya done somethin'
right for once!
[SOLDIER A] I don't know how
we're going to retrieve it--
[YELLOW]
The helicopter, imbecile!
We take the helicopter
into the volcano!
[SOLDIER A]
Yes, sir!
[UPA] I'm gonna grow up and
catch all the fish in the ocean!
[BORA] Son, you should not
take more than you need.
If you respect nature, she will
always take care of you.
Oh...
[UPA] Yay! That was so fast!
Oh, Daddy, you're the best!
[BIG FISH growls]
[UPA] Huh?
[BORA growls]
[BIG FISH growls]
[UPA screams]
Noooo!
[BIG FISH groans]
[UPA]
Dady!
Do not cry. We were
never in any danger.
We live under the
watchful eye of the Guardian.
[BORA] We must thank him
for protecting us from harm.
[SOLDIER IN HEAT SUIT] I have
it. Now get me outta here!
Come on...
[SOLDIERS screaming]
[PILOT screams]
Everyone away from
here right now!
[UPA gasps]
[UPA]
W-What's happening?
Mount Kana has been disturbed.
Something is wrong.
[BORA gasps]
[UPA yelps]
[BORA grunting]
[BORA panting, grunting]
Now, call back
headquarters and find out
exactly where the
Dragon Ball has gone!
[SOLDIER A]
Yes, Captain.
Calling base. Base come in.
Come in base.
[beeping]
West. The Dragon Ball
has moved approximately
five miles to the west.
[SOLDIER A]
Copy that!
Troops! Head west immediately!
It's over.
[UPA]
Daddy, are you okay?
Yes, no damage done.
[UPA]
Huh?
Ow!
[BORA]
Hm...
[UPA]
What is that thing?
I do not know.
I have never seen
such an object before.
Oh! It's so pretty!
Ugh! The jungle!
Won't be easy to find
a Dragon Ball in there.
Heh. Well, whatever.
This is as good a place
as any to set up camp.
Soldiers, prepare to land!
Huh?
Daddy! Those gigantic birds
are gonna land on us!
Those are not birds, little one.
Those are vehicles,
called helicopters.
Wow! I can't believe anyone
would live out here by choice.
[UPA whimpering]
[BORA]
Who are you?
[YELLOW]
Oh, yes. I'm Cap'in Yellow
of the Red Ribbon Army.
We'll be setting up our mobile
headquarters right here.
Here?
[YELLOW] Yep. And there's
plenty of work to go around,
so we can put a big fella
like you to good use.
No thanks.
[YELLOW growls]
[BORA]
You must leave.
This is no place for
people like you. Now, go!
[YELLOW growls]
I wasn't askin'
for your permission.
Captain Yellow, do you
see what's in his hand?
The Dragon Ball!
Now, hand it over,
ya painted peasant!
You will receive
nothing from me.
Whatever. Pulverize him!
[BORA grunting]
[BORA growls]
[GUY A] What the--?
[GUY B] No! No way!
Guns are but useless toys.
Get me my spear, Upa!
Sure, Dad!
[BORA grunts]
[YELLOW] Do you have any idea
who you're tangling with?!
Ya better turn over
the ball before you get hurt.
[BORA]
The ball is of no concern to me.
But this is sacred land,
and I am here to protect it.
You must pay for the
destruction you have caused.
Sacred land?!
You gotta be
kiddin' me, this dump?
[BORA]
It is the truth.
The guardian of our
people was born here,
and this beautiful monument
was built to honor him.
He still lives here still today,
high above us at
the top of the tower.
Leave here. Otherwise be
prepared to face my wrath.
[GUY C laughs]
Daddy, look out! Behind you!
[GUY C yelps]
[GUY C screams]
[YELLOW growls]
Men! Destroy 'im!
Looks like the Dragon Ball's
stopped moving, at least.
Don't you see?
Guns can't hurt me!
[BORA grunting]
[SOLDIERS groaning]
[YELLOW yelps]
[GUY F whimpering]
Good riddance.
Whoa! Daddy!
Stay here while I dispose
of these troublemakers.
[UPA]
Okay!
[UPA giggles]
[YELLOW]
Captain Yellow here.
Are you there headquarters?
Sir, Captain Yellow
sounds frantic.
He's calling on
the radio right now.
Captain? What?!
The men were overpowered
and only you could escape?
What happened to
the Dragon Ball?
[YELLOW] Well uh, w-we ran
into a little snag...
Enough with the excuses, Yellow!
Retrieve the Dragon Ball
at all costs!
It's more valuable to
this army than your life!
[YELLOW] Yes, sir. I-I
understand. I-I'll try harder.
[RED] Can't you handle
anything right?
[STAFF OFFICER]
Commander Red!
Here! Listen up, Yellow!
[YELLOW] Uh, he-hello,
Commander Red, sir.
You have exactly one hour.
That is 60 short minutes
to bring me the Dragon Ball
or else I'll be forced
to send in Tao.
Did you say Tao?
But sir, Mercenary Tao?
Isn't that a bit excessive?
[RED] Can it! I need the ball
and the kid eradicated
so I can complete my plans!
Of course if you fail,
Tao will exterminate you
along with whoever else
gets in his way.
Keep that in mind!
[YELLOW] I see. This guy,
the obstacle, he has a son.
I'll use the boy as a bargaining
chip to get the Dragon Ball
I bet Dad's gonna
be really hungry
when he gets back.
[UPA]
Daddy! Help me!
Oh no, Upa! Son?!
Hang on, kid.
Now where's your pop?
[BORA]
What do you want with my son?
Ah, there's your devoted dad!
Daddy!
Now, fool.
If you ever wanna see your
son back, give me the ball.
Just toss it right
to me. Understand?
[BORA]
That does it!
It seems he's got everything
under control this time.
We may have this
Dragon Ball in the bag,
but we still have
a problem: the kid.
[BEAR] Excuse me, sir, About
that. It looks like the boy
has almost reached
Captain Yellow's location.
Of course.
He's just in time...
...to mess things up!
[BORA] Here is your ball.
Come down here and get it.
[YELLOW]
No way, that's a trick.
You'll hurt me if I come
down there. Throw it to me.
No, I am true to my word.
I am not as despicable as you.
[GOKU] I should be
getting close to it now.
[UPA]
Help me!
Huh? What?
Throw it up here!
Hey, I've seen a symbol
like that before.
What's that?
I know! That plane belongs
to the Red Ribbon Army!
And just who might you be?
[GOKU grunts]
[YELLOW, UPA scream]
Upa!
[UPA screaming]
[GOKU laughs]
Hello!
[UPA panting]
We have lost contact, sir.
[RED growls]
You know what to do.
Poor kid. I kinda
feel sorry for him.
I'm sure Tao is going to
work him over pretty good.
And that's putting
it mildly, I would think.
I've heard of people
keeling over just because
Tao looked at them funny.
Imagine! What if he
actually used his fists...
[STAFF OFFICER chuckles]
[BORA]
Thank you for saving my son.
[GOKU]
Oh, you know, it was nothing.
No trouble at all really.
[UPA]
Thank you. You're nice!
[GOKU chuckles]
Oh! You have it! The
Dragon Ball! It's right there!
Please, can I see it?
Oh, you were looking
for the ball, too?
[GOKU]
One, two, three, four!
The Four-Star Dragon Ball!
I can't believe I finally found
my grandpa's Dragon Ball!
[BORA]
What is this Dragon Ball?
And why do so many
search for it?
[BLUE]
I'm home!
Hey, man. No trespassing
unless you want a bruising.
That's right, you just
keep pushing me, buddy!
[GUARD A groans]
[BLUE] How quickly they
forget when you're gone!
[DOG GUARD yelps]
General Blue!
Quit your blubbering
and open the gate.
At your service.
I am Mercenary Tao.
[NARRATOR] Goku has finally
succeeded in recovering
his grandfather's
Four-Star Ball.
But how long can he
hold on to it,
now that the Red Ribbon Army
has called in
the infamous Mercenary Tao
to take it away?
Find out, in the next
action-packed episode
of Dragon Ball!