[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball,
after a near fatal battle
with King Piccolo,
Goku retreated to
Korin's Tower to recuperate,
meeting some old
friends along the way.
Master Roshi attempted
to trap King Piccolo using
the Evil Containment Wave,
but was defeated.
King Piccolo realized his
dastardly ambition for power
by calling upon the Eternal
Dragon and wishing for youth.
[DRAGON]
As you wish.
[NARRATOR] Unfortunately for
all, his desire was granted.
Restored, the new King Piccolo
wasted no time implementing
his scheme of world domination.
He vowed to wreak
havoc across the globe.
[PIANO] Presently the world
is divided into 43 sectors.
Each sector is ruled by a king.
We are currently approaching
the Eastern City,
home of King Furry.
This is his sector,
as is the surrounding area,
also the north area,
which is covered with snow.
There's also a desert
and furthermore--
[PICCOLO]
Enough!
Eh?
Such a boring locale.
Let me show you something fun.
Oh!
[laughs]
Beautiful! Soon this
will be their reality.
Yes, sire.
--[alarm blaring]
--Huh?
[PIANO] Hm? We've arrived
at King's Castle.
Then, let's go. It's time
to take our first step
in creating a new world order.
[PICCOLO]
Huh?
I forgot to mention, sire,
today the town's
citizens are celebrating
their King's 20th term.
Good.
[PIANO] Or perhaps they knew
we were coming and decided
to start celebrating
your ascension early.
[PIANO, PICCOLO cackle]
[PICCOLO]
Maybe so!
[CROWD cheering]
[CHILD PANDA]
Here comes the car!
[PARADE MC]
Welcome, everyone!
Allow me to extend a big hello
from the citizens
of Eastern City
to everyone around the
world watching us today.
We're gathered here
for an amazing parade
commemorating King Furry's
20th term in office.
What makes this king so loved
and revered by his subjects
is his stellar political record,
highlighted by a dogged pursuit
of world prosperity and peace.
Oh, here he comes now!
You see him? Ah!
I can't believe it!
[PICCOLO] Let the little cretins
enjoy themselves while they can.
Soon enough, they will die.
[cackles]
[PICCOLO]
Shall we?
[UPA] Goku! Goku!
I missed you so much!
It is an honor. Welcome.
[GOKU laughs]
Do I look stronger?
Since you left, I've been taking
combat lessons from my father.
I'm gonna be a great
warrior, just like you!
[grunting]
[whimpers]
That's great, Upa. Boy,
you've become very strong.
Goku!
Are you hurt?
You are looking ill.
Is it serious? What's wrong?
[YAJIROBE]
He nearly got himself killed...
[BORA, UPA gasp]
...by a terrible monster
named King Piccolo.
Goku decided to try and
fight him all by himself.
It was a dumb thing to do.
Hey! I don't know who you are,
but you'd better stop
talking that way about Goku,
or you'll be sorry!
Quiet down before I step on you.
What did you say?!
Upa.
Aw , but Father!
Yajirobe is telling
the truth. I was beaten.
But no one can hurt you, Goku!
It is difficult to believe.
I came back
to see if Master Korin could
help improve my strength
like he did before.
You're going to
climb the tower!?
Mm-hm.
Sure am.
[BORA] Goku, why don't you
rest here a few days?
You'll never make it
with that wound.
[GOKU] Don't worry, Bora.
Yajirobe will take me there.
Uh--! Are you nuts!?
You're strong enough
to climb Korin's Tower.
Well, I appreciate
the vote of confidence,
but why do I have to do it?!
He's right, Goku! You don't
wanna rely on a guy like him!
Stay outta this, squirt!
[growls]
[grunts]
Heh. Nice teeth. Anyway,
it's none of my business.
I'm headed home, guys.
I don't wanna get involved
in anything dangerous.
I didn't come here for trouble.
I came here for food,
and since I'm obviously
not going to get any,
I'd be crazy just
to stand around here
listening to this
half-pint's insults.
You're a big coward!
[YAJIROBE]
I'll see ya around, Goku.
There's plenty of food.
It's up in the Tower.
[YAJIROBE]
Nice try, buddy.
I'm serious. Korin's food
is the best I've ever tasted.
He loves to feed people.
What kind of food?
Hm. Stuff like Senzu Beans.
Senzu? Strange name for beans.
I think it's delicious.
Did you just say delicious?
There must be more than
beans in those beans!
It's your job to hold on tight.
I can't help you if you fall.
Thanks a bunch.
Allow me to help
you on your way.
[UPA]
Huh?
The things I do for a
meal! Now you're positive
the food's up there, right?!
Of course I am.
Be safe. Hold onto his hair.
Ready to go?
Thank you.
Can we get going?
Good luck! Safe trip!
[yells]
Ow! My hands!
[yelps]
[YAJIROBE] We flew all that way,
and we still can't see the top!
[GOKU]
I can smell those beans.
I hope there's some
left when we get there.
Nobody's eatin' my beans!
All that I see before me
is now mine. Not too bad.
Hey! Hold it!
[groans]
Freeze Mister!
[GUARD C] All units to Gate 3!
Emergency! Emergency!
[TIEN] Please, forgive me. I
wish I were with you right now.
[yells]
--[plane humming]
--[gasps]
[BULMA] We're here.
This is where the Dragon Balls
were last spotted.
[LAUNCH]
Hurry up! I wanna check it out.
Wait. Let me circle
around the perimeter.
There could be enemies
lurking we don't know about.
Well, I've got a better idea.
Let's fly over and
keep heading south.
Staying here is suicide!
What's that?!
[BULMA, PUAR, OOLONG,
YAMCHA, LAUNCH] Tien Shinhan!
And that's Master beside him!
Master Roshi!
How could this have
happened to them?!
Chiaotzu...
Tien Shinhan!
We're the only ones left.
We have to work together to
defeat Piccolo. Tien Shinhan?!
I'm sorry, Yamcha. There is
something I must do, alone.
It's the only way.
[gasps]
I will learn the secret of
the Evil Containment Wave.
[YAMCHA]
No, it's too dangerous!
[TIEN] I must destroy that
monster, no matter the cost.
That's why I was spared.
You can't go alone!
I'll learn it with you!
No. That's not an option.
It's impossible to learn this
wave unless you've witnessed it
first hand, as I have.
No, Tien!
[TIEN] Don't argue with me.
My mind is set.
I have nothing left to lose.
[BULMA]
Will we ever see him again?
[TIEN thinking]
Goodbye my friends.
What a man.
As long as I draw breath,
I pledge to you that I
will guide our fair domain
under the principles of truth,
justice, and harmony
amongst all living things!
[GUARD C]
Halt! You are trespassing!
[GUARDS scream]
[PARADE MC]
To honor the King,
girls from all
parts of the world
have gathered to present
him bouquets of flowers.
First we have Cactus,
from the desert land.
[KING]
Welcome.
Thank you. I am honored to
receive such beautiful flowers,
and I accept them
as a symbol of peace.
Where is Suno? Is she there yet?
What was it like meeting him?
We shook hands.
He smiled. What a king!
Wow! How wonderful!
I can't wait till it's my turn!
What?
[GUARD D]
What should we do, sir?
Stay calm. Roll out the
battle tanks of the 5th brigade
to the square at
Gate 2, just in case!
And be quick!
[GUARD D]
Yes, sir!
[COMMANDER] We must preserve
the peace at all cost.
[GUARD C] Stop! I repeat,
this is your last warning!
Ready! Fire!
[GUARDS scream]
Nice reception.
[PARADE MC]
Next up, Suno,
representative of the
northern village, Jingle.
That's me!
[ROBOT NO. 8]
That's Suno! Look, she's on TV!
My little baby girl!
[cheering]
[booming]
[CROWD screaming]
[PICCOLO laughs]
[YAJIROBE panting]
I'm getting sick and tired
of climbing! This is insane.
I'm starving to death and
we still can't see the top!
We're almost there.
Yeah, sure! You've been
saying "we're almost there"
from the moment we started!
It's true.
Whatever! I don't wanna hear
anymore! Just stop talking!
[YAJIROBE] Come on, Yajirobe!
Let's go on a trip.
There'll be food!
Aren't you having fun?
[YAJIROBE] Oh sure! This is
great! I love climbing towers
with my bare hands!
[FATHER] Hey, what happened?
Where's the signal?
Suno.
[CROWD screaming]
[gasps]
[sobs]
[PICCOLO] Where is this king?
I've come all this way
to meet him.
I'm beginning to think
he's avoiding me.
I'm right here!
Sir! We've gotta
get you outta here!
I'm not going to hide
while that creature
wreaks havoc on the city.
The people are depending on me!
But, sir! It's my
place to protect you.
Let my men do their job.
You can't help the people if
you're not there to lead them.
[growls]
Huh?
I'll keep them busy while
you escape, your majesty.
Be quick!
[VC]
Hold it! You can't go in there.
Oh, are you the
welcoming committee?
Afraid not, I handle
the good-byes.
And you've worn out
your welcome.
You're fairly adept when
fighting against machines.
How about pure muscle,
you green freak!?
Ha! I thought you'd never ask.
But rather than fight,
why not work for me?
You could shine
my shoes, big boy.
[VC] Enough! Either you
surrender immediately,
or I'll do my worst!
[PICCOLO] Surrender?
Why should I surrender?
You're the one who's
losing all his men.
Before you die, tell me,
where is the king hiding?
[VC] Ugh! Forget the king.
Settle for my fist!
[VC grunting]
Oh, my! Is this how
we throw punches?
[groans]
Where is the king?
Where you'll never find him!
Heh. We'll see.
[VC groans]
[GUARDS yelp]
[GUARD E screams]
I hope you have
an answer for me.
[GUARD E]
I get paid by the hour!
[PIANO]
Sire!
These clowns were decoys.
The king is escaping
in his ship.
Leaving so soon?
[DOG] Too bad my
friends weren't here.
I know this
bloodhound who would've
taken that monster down.
This is the end.
There's nothing we can do.
We should've gone
to the movies instead.
Mommy, is there someone
who can stop the green man?
What about Daddy?
Isn't he stronger
than the green man?
Nobody's daddy is that strong.
[SUNO]
I know somebody.
I have a friend who I
know could defeat him.
Don't stop there. Who is it?
It's Goku.
Goku?
Goku, wherever you are, please
hear me. We need your help now.
Goku!
[YAJIROBE] Oh, wow! Goku,
look up! Is that the top?!
[snoring]
[YAJIROBE] You no-good, lousy...
How could you be sleeping
at a time like this?!
Wake up! Look! We're at the top!
[PICCOLO]
Going somewhere?
[NARRATOR] With the king of
Eastern City captured,
will King Piccolo make
good on his first conquest?
Goku has reached
the top of Korin Tower,
but can he hold out long enough
to see Master Korin himself?
Find out next time,
on Dragon Ball!