[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
[PICCOLO]
Now watch and learn...
You're about to see for yourself
how powerful I really am!
Come on! I'm ready
anytime you are!
[NARRATOR] Piccolo was
furious that Goku dared
to challenge him, so he
pulled out all the stops
and tried to clobber his
pint-sized opponent.
But the wily young hero proved
to be more than a handful.
Unfortunately, a well placed
punch sent Goku flying,
and it looked like
this battle was over
before it could
ever get started.
[NARRATOR]
With his competition crushed,
Piccolo now has free reign
over Eastern City
and that's got everyone
afraid for their lives.
[PICCOLO] Ha, ha. That's it!
He's gone! Ha, ha.
Good riddance, kid!
[NARRATOR]
Is Goku really gone?
Or is there a chance that
some miracle will happen
and he'll be able
to pull himself up
and face Piccolo one
more time? Stay tuned!
[gasping]
[PICCOLO chuckling]
If he was their best,
then I stand alone
as the most powerful
force on Earth! [laughs]
No, I can't let it end this way!
[chuckling]
My turn!
[GOKU]
Ka...
--No, it can't be...
--[GOKU] Me...
[TIEN]
Ah! Goku is that you?!
[GOKU]
Ha... Me...
That's impossible!
[GOKU growls]
Ahh!
What?!
Ha!
Nice try, but that
won't work on me!
Oh, yeah?!
Ah!
[screams]
[laughing] I gotcha!
[groaning]
A direct hit! He survived
the Kamehameha!
Hey! I couldn't have hurt you
that much! On your feet.
I'm just getting warmed up!
What are you, a monster?!
The only monster here is you!
This fight isn't over until
only one of us is left standing.
[growls]
Hear my words...
You won't be so lucky
this time! [laughs]
[GOKU]
Hmm.
[BOTH gasp]
King...
[chuckles]
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU groans]
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO screaming]
[GOKU yells]
[PICCOLO groans]
Incredible! Goku's even
more powerful than before!
Hang on! We'll be at the King's
castle in about ten minutes.
Do you think Tien could
hold out this long, Yamcha?
He must be okay. I haven't
heard any news about him
from West City, but if
there's any trouble
when we get there, I'm
joining in on the fight!
Uh. Have you gone bananas?
You know how tough Tien is!
How are you gonna help?
Huh?
Do you wanna bite?
No, I'm not hungry.
Huh?
[NEWSCASTER] Now a special
news bulletin from West City!
At this very moment, the
monster called Piccolo
is battling near
the King's castle!
Good! Piccolo is still there!
[BULMA] Uh. So, maybe we
should turn back now?
[YAMCHA]
Hm?
[BULMA sighs]
[GOKU growls]
[BOTH yelling]
[PICCOLO groaning]
Your highness, please.
Let's get out of here!
Now is a good time to go!
[KING]
I refuse to leave the castle!
But sir, something terrible
could happen to you!
You're in great danger
if you stay here!
I can't leave...
Listen to me.
The best thing for you to do
is leave the city immediately
and come back when it's safe.
This is the only
choice we have, sir!
Please, sir.
[KING]
Very well...
But what about all
those people out there?
I can't just leave them behind.
I wish there was something
I could do about this.
--[GOKU grunting]
--[PICCOLO yelling]
[panting]
Goku has the advantage!
Piccolo can be defeated!
[NEWSCASTER] It looks as
though two unidentified people
have surrounded Piccolo, and
at this time, there appears
to be an intense battle going
on inside the King's castle.
Two?
Did he say there
are two people?
I thought Tien was the
only one down there.
[NEWSCASTER] Here's a picture
taken by telephoto lens
of what's happening inside
the castle grounds.
We can't get any closer because
it would be too dangerous
for our camera crew. However,
I have some new information
on the two unidentified people.
One appears to be a young
man, a very bald young man.
And the other is a small boy.
A small boy?
Uh? Could it be him?
[NEWSCASTER] That is all the
information we can provide at
this time. Stay tuned for our
continuing up to the minute
coverage of the
War in West City.
Could it be?
[gasps] Goku?
[gasps]
[PICCOLO groans]
[chuckles]
[yells]
[groaning]
Ouch!
[laughing]
Without the use of that leg,
you can't avoid me much longer!
Ow! I only need one
leg to finish you!
[laughs] Really? That
I'd like to see!
Power Pole extend!
[gasps]
[GOKU]
Yah!
Goku? How could it be him?
It can't be him!
But no one saw him die.
Everyone just assumed
he was dead.
I mean, don't you remember
what Baba once told us?
[gasps]
He certainly is amazing...
I sense he'll be a great
hero of his time.
Huh. You're right.
I remember! It is Goku!
Then we don't have to worry
'cause he'll take
care of everything!
[YAMCHA] Yeah! Goku's
gonna to save the world!
[YAMCHA laughs]
[PICCOLO groaning]
Not bad for a kid, huh?
That staff is nothing
but a glorified crutch.
[PICCOLO growling]
I'll... show... you!
[PICCOLO groaning]
Uh. His body is growing!
[groaning continues]
Whoa! Look at him! It looks like
he's going to blow himself up!
[screaming]
[gasping]
[GOKU groans]
Power Pole!
Ha! Now your weakness
is exposed!
No! He can't move!
I have you now! [screams]
--[GOKU gasping]
--[screaming continues]
[humming]
Huh?!
[SUNO screaming]
--[screaming continues]
--[wind howling]
[static]
Hm? That's strange.
The picture's all broken up.
Look! Up there!
[BULMA]
Mm? Ah!
[YAMCHA]
What is that?
[BULMA] It looks like it's
coming from the King's castle!
[NUMBER 8]
Uh?!
[CHILDREN laughing]
[laughs]
Uh, Suno, are you okay?
[gasps]
[sighs]
Are you all right, Grandma?
Please wake up.
Dear...?
[GRANDMA chuckles]
Huh?
[gasping]
Oh my... That was
a really close one!
[KING] My castle...
The city... Gone!
[PICCOLO laughs]
[PICCOLO chuckles]
It is finished!
There is no one left to
stand against my power!
Wait! I feel his spirit!
No, it can't be!
I know I got him! There's
no way he could move!
[GOKU]
Yoo-hoo...
Up here!
[GOKU laughing]
[TIEN chuckles]
Your friend's heroics
shall prove to be in vain.
You saved me, Tien. Thanks!
[TIEN panting]
Hey Tien, what's
wrong? You okay?
Too bad...
He used up all his energy
helping you escape from me.
[PICCOLO laughs] Since
you can't move on your own,
--[PICCOLO laughs]
--[TIEN panting]
He's right. I'm exhausted.
I will send you away
from this world together!
Come on... let's go.
I'm ready... to fight... you!
Oh? Are you so stubborn?
The attack might not be as
powerful as the last one,
but that doesn't matter,
because it'll be strong enough
to destroy a little
brat like you!
You should've given
up a long time ago.
Now you're going to regret
the day we ever crossed paths.
[panting]
Goku...
[PICCOLO groaning]
Don't underestimate
my Explosive Wave!
Now's my chance!
I guess it's now or never!
[gasps]
[groaning]
Darn it! I couldn't hit him
hard enough because of my leg!
That's too bad! 'Cause
you're gonna pay for that!
[PICCOLO yells]
[GOKU groaning]
[yells]
[PICCOLO bellowing]
[BULMA, YAMCHA, LAUNCH
screaming]
Not again!
[PICCOLO gasping]
[PICCOLO panting]
That should solve
that little problem.
That's more like it!
I destroyed him.
--[GOKU] Anybody up there?!
--[PICCOLO screams]
[PICCOLO gasps]
I don't believe it!
No way you're gonna get
rid of me that easily!
[NARRATOR] With Goku proving
more of a match than expected,
which warrior will
have what it takes
to finish their most hated
opponent once and for all!?
Next time on Dragon Ball!