[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball,
the search for the
third Dragon Ball led Goku,
Bulma, and Krillin
into a secret port
constructed by pirates
centuries ago.
[NARRATOR] Though the pirates
had long since passed away,
they left behind
a dangerous legacy
to guard their precious booty!
A radical robot
of the killing kind!
Armed to the hilt,
this metal monster
was bent on ridding his lair
of the hapless intruders!
[ROBOT]
Yo, ho, ho.
[GOKU yelping]
[KRILLIN yelps]
[BULMA screams]
[KRILLIN grunts]
What a magnificent
little toy!
[NARRATOR] After a terrible
struggle, Goku was intent
on ending the battle
once and for all
by turning himself
into a human torpedo!
And in grand style,
he did just that!
It was the end of
one dangerous threat,
but another was just
around the corner!
General Blue of the
Red Ribbon Army was hot
on Bulma and Krillin's trail!
And as they were
unknowingly leading him
to the Dragon Ball,
the General was leading Goku
in the opposite direction!
[GOKU] Hey! Krillin must
have drawn that!
[NARRATOR]
Into the unknown they plunged,
oblivious of their plight!
While Goku journeyed
deeper and deeper
into the labyrinth!
[NARRATOR] Is it success that
awaits Bulma and Krillin?
Or an untimely end?
With every step,
Goku gets further away
from being able
to help his friends!
Stay tuned for more Dragon Ball!
[GOKU yelps]
Hmm? Whoa!
It might be best just to forget
about that Dragon Ball!
This is bad!
[GOKU] That ceiling is
going to cave in any minute!
[GOKU] I don't think we
should let Bulma fire cannons
when we're in
underwater caves anymore!
[GOKU]
We've got to get out of here!
Krillin! Bulma!
Hey! Bulma! Krillin!
Something's wrong!
I'm running at full speed and I
still can't catch up with them.
[GOKU gasps]
Wow! A dead end?
How can that be?
[GOKU yelps]
[GOKU yelling]
Huh? Hm?
[GOKU yelps]
[OCTOPUS cackling]
Groovy, baby!
[BULMA grunts]
[KRILLIN grunts]
[KRILLIN grunting]
Hmm?
[BULMA grunting]
[KRILLIN gasps]
[BULMA gasps]
[KRILLIN]
Wow!
[BULMA panting]
Huh? Ooh!
[KRILLIN]
Hey! Bulma, look! The treasure!
[BULMA]
Huh?
I don't believe it!
We did it! We actually made it!
[KRILLIN]
Yeah! This is great!
[KRILLIN, BULMA yelping]
[BULMA whimpers]
Krillin, he moved!
[KRILLIN]
I know! Ssshhh!
[KRILLIN yelps]
[BULMA gasps]
[BULMA]
What now?
[KRILLIN]
Don't move, Bulma! Stay still!
[OCTOPUS cackles]
Come to octo-papa, baby!
Huh?
[OCTOPUS moaning]
Hey! I know what you are!
[GOKU] All those legs!
Heh! You're a Spider!
[OCTOPUS]
I'm an octopus!
Oh! Nice meeting you!
Bye!
Uh-uhh...
[OCTOPUS cackles]
[OCTOPUS] You're not digging
the scene, sweetmeat!
You're my little octo-treat!
I am not!
[OCTOPUS cackles]
Don't be mad, baby!
It's just a little destiny!
Come to octo-daddy!
[GOKU grunting, giggling]
[OCTOPUS growls]
Look into my eyes!
[OCTOPUS] Gotcha!
[GOKU groans]
[BULMA, KRILLIN yelping]
[BLUMA whimpering]
[KRILLIN grunting]
[BULMA]
Krillin! Do something! Quick!
[KRILLIN]
Coming, Bulma!
[KRILLIN yelps]
What are you doing, Krillin?
Get up! Hurry!
[BULMA gasps]
I'll be quiet now!
[KRILLIN grunting]
[KRILLIN]
Bring it on!
[KRILLIN yelps]
[BULMA screams]
[GOKU groans]
[OCTOPUS cackling]
You're mean!
[GOKU yells]
Huh?
[OCTOPUS slurping]
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU laughing]
Whoa! Stop! That tickles!
Hey!
[OCTOPUS]
Yummy!
I'll bet you're packed
with flavor, aren't you?
[GOKU] Put me down!
You can't eat people!
[OCTOPUS cackles] For a
small guy, you talk pretty big!
[GOKU grunts]
Huh?
[KRILLIN chuckles]
Yeah! A bull's eye!
Now then! Let's see
what we've got here!
Hey! Krillin!
You'd better be careful!
[KRILLIN]
Don't worry!
If we can handle ol' ten arms up
there, we can handle anything!
Bingo!
Uh-oh...
[BULMA yelping]
[GOKU grunting]
[OCTOPUS cackles]
[OCTOPUS] Sorry! I like
to tenderize my meat!
No problem!
[OCTOPUS cackles]
Groovy!
Now come on in! It's chow time!
[OCTOPUS, GOKU grunting]
You wanna eat?
Here's a jawbreaker!
[OCTOPUS]
That's not my mouth you idiot!
This is!
Ew! Gross!
[KRILLIN yelling]
[BULMA]
Krillin!
[PIRATE laughing]
[BULMA]
Hmm?
He wasn't so tough!
[KRILLIN] Oh yeah?
Then why were you hiding
behind that rock?
[BULMA]
Wow! If you weren't so short,
he would've blown your head off!
I'm not short!
Not only are you short,
but you're shortsighted,
that's why you
almost got killed!
Huh?
You should know better
than to open the gold chest!
Duh! Right in the middle!
It was a set up!
Oh, and which chest would
a tall, brilliant person
like you have opened?
[BULMA]
Well, that dull one there!
No one would think
to open it first!
[KRILLIN]
Except a genius like you, right?
Exactly! Very perceptive!
[BULMA grunting]
[KRILLIN mimicking gunfire]
[BULMA screams]
Um, Bulma! Hey! That was me!
I know! Ugh!
[OCTOPUS] Take a look at
the entrance to your new pad!
It's jazzy, baby!
Yeah! Well, it's time
to die, small fry!
[GOKU] Wait! I want to
give you something first!
[OCTOPUS]
What's that, cat-daddy?
I'll show you! It's called
the Kamehameha Wave!
[OCTOPUS]
Show octa-papa!
Ka, Me, Ha, Me,
Haaaaa!
[OCTOPUS groaning]
[BULMA, KRILLIN grunting]
[BULMA]
What in the world?
Wow!
[BULMA]
What do you think it's to?
[KRILLIN]
I don't know!
Some treasure!
[GOKU]
Boy! It's steamy in here!
I wonder what roasted
octopus tastes like?
I'm starving!
Hey! It's not so bad!
It tastes a little like chicken!
What now? Do you
think it's to a door?
[KRILLIN] Well, there
aren't any doors in here!
[BULMA]
Yeah, good point.
Uh. Hey! Bulma?
[KRILLIN] Check it out!
That's gotta be it!
[BULMA]
Yeah! Good eye!
This could be big trouble!
[KRILLIN]
Yeah!
[KRILLIN] Ooh...
[BULMA] Huh.
[high-pitched squeak]
[BOTH]
Huh? Oh!
[BULMA]
Look how beautiful!
[KRILLIN] Wow!
[BULMA] It's incredible!
[KRILLIN]
Yeah!
[BULMA, KRILLIN giggling]
[BULMA] You know what
this means, don't you?
[KRILLIN]
What?
[BULMA]
We're rich! Yay!
[BLUE] I'm afraid that
you're both mistaken!
That treasure belongs
to the Red Ribbon Army!
Ah? No-good bullies!
[BLUE chuckles]
[BULMA sighs]
Hello! I'm Bulma!
Uh... Huh?
[BULMA giggling]
[BLUE disgusted grunting]
Ew! Don't touch me!
Ew! Ugh! Disgusting!
[KRILLIN, BULMA]
Huh?
You-You prude!
Funny, for a big guy,
you sure scare easy!
I doubt you'll
think I'm so funny
when you're dead!
You have a death wish,
don't you cue-ball!
[KRILLIN chuckles] Just 'cause
you're tall and muscle bound
doesn't mean I can't
stomp you, pal!
Oh! You think so, huh?
I know so!
[KRILLIN groaning]
[GOKU] Hmm?
[GOKU]
Huh? Whoa! What was that?
It sounded like Krillin!
That hurts! Uhh!
[BLUE cackles] What's that
you're wearing? A little diaper?
No! Don't fight!
I'm fine! He's just
a puffed up sissy!
Sissy, huh?
Well, bring it on, diaper man!
[KRILLIN yells]
[BLUE laughs]
[KRILLIN, BLUE grunting]
[BULMA screams]
Oh, no! That was Bulma!
[KRILLIN groaning]
You! That's it! You did it now!
[BLUE chuckling]
A girl scout could put up
a tougher fight than you!
Believe me, I know!
Oh yeah? We'll see about that!
Come on, then! Put 'em up now!
Gladly!
That's it, Krillin!
He's just a big wussy!
Show him who's boss!
[BLUE cackles]
[KRILLIN growls]
[BLUE]
Huh?
[KRILLIN grunts]
[BLUE yelps]
All right!
[BLUE whimpers]
You're through!
Give it up, sissy!
[BLUE whimpering]
Fool!
How could you kick
something so beautiful?
[BLUE gasps]
Oh, no!
Blood! Blood! Disgusting blood!
Huh?
[BLUE]
How-How could you?
That's-That's like
throwing a can of red paint
on the Mona Lisa!
[BLUE whimpers]
How could this happen to me?
This guy is strange!
[BLUE]
Murderer!
Huh?
[BLUE]
You killed my perfect looks!
For that, you must perish!
Come on, then!
Give it your best shot,
I dare you!
[BLUE growling]
[KRILLIN whimpering]
What's the deal?
Krillin? Are you okay?
[KRILLIN grunting]
I can't budge!
He did something with his eyes!
[BLUE]
What's wrong, little man?
Feeling a little stiff, eh?
[BLUE cackles] Maybe I should
have bothered to mention
my special power!
[KRILLIN whimpers]
Hey! No fair! He can't move!
Stop that! You're cheating!
You! Beast! Stop!
[BLUE]
What are you talking about?
You can't cheat in
a fight to the death!
Fool!
Whoever's alive at the end
of the battle is the winner,
and that's that!
[KRILLIN grunting]
Darn you!
[BLUE grunts]
[KRILLIN groans]
[KRILLIN groaning]
[BLUE grunting]
[KRILLIN groans]
[BULMA screams]
Krillin! No!
[BLUE chuckling]
I know that hurt!
Don't worry! It'll be over soon!
He's nuts! He's gonna
kill both of us!
This whole place
is falling apart!
I'd better finish
these two off quickly
so I can find that Dragon Ball!
All right!
Desperate times call
for desperate measures!
[BULMA]
Hey, there, military man!
You're muscles are like rock!
They're huge! How do you do it?
You're so buff!
I work out too!
[BULMA moaning]
Hoochie, coochie, cooo!
[BULMA]
You're such a super stud!
Do you want to
give me nightmares?
That is gross!
[BULMA gasps]
[BULMA] It's not working!
Think of something, fast!
All right, freeze!
I may be small but I'm
a trained Sumo Wrestler, pal!
Heh, heh, heh!
Will you stop wasting
my time with your nonsense!
Silly girl!
I would have perhaps let
you go, but now, sister...
...you're next.
[BLUE] I'll deal with you
as soon as I finish off
this little meddler here!
N-No!
[BLUE giggles]
Y-Yes!
Even though you're about to die,
you should be very
proud of yourself!
You're the first opponent
I've had that made me bleed!
Ho, ho, ho! Yes!
And unfortunately
for you, the last!
[BULMA]
No! Wait!
[BLUE]
Huh? Now what? Make it fast!
[BULMA growls]
You can't kill us!
You need our Dragon Balls!
Huh?
That's right! We've got two!
And you need them!
So, if you let us go,
they're yours!
I really appreciate the offer!
But I don't make deals
to get what I want!
I just take it!
Now! No more interruptions!
It's time to crack
this coconut wide open!
[KRILLIN whimpers]
Goku!
Be brave! Smile!
Krillin! No!
[BLUE yells]
Huh?
[BULMA]
Goku! Yes! You made it!
[GOKU]
Krillin! Are you okay?
Quick! Come down!
[BLUE whimpers]
Goku! He was about to kill us!
He works for the
Red Ribbon Army!
Take him out!
Red Ribbon, huh?
Ahh! Well, I'm glad
you've heard of us!
We've heard of you!
[GOKU]
You were able to beat Krillin?
Krillin? Oh, diapers! Of course!
I put him down easy enough.
Goku...
Now you're going down!
No one messes with my friends!
[BLUE cackling]
Put 'em up then!
[GOKU]
Hmm!
[BULMA gulps]
[BLUE chuckles]
[NARRATOR] As Goku squares off
against the dangerous
General Blue, the old
pirates' hideout
is caving in on top of them!
Time is running out!
Join us next time
on Dragon Ball!