[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball,
the battle between Mercenary Tao
and Tien Shinhan turned deadly
when Tao used a weapon
to make his point.
His intention was to
destroy his former student.
[TIEN] What respect I had for
you has now turned to pity.
You have no honor!
[NARRATOR] Fearing defeat, Tao
unleashed his ultimate weapon:
the Super Dodon Ray.
With Tien dead in his sights,
it appeared as though
Tao couldn't fail.
[TAO] Some things never
change, do they, Tien?!
Go ahead! I'm not afraid!
[TAO yells]
[yells]
[NARRATOR] To the assassin's
dismay, it didn't work.
[TAO]
I had you in my sights,
there's no way you
could have escaped!
[TAO groans]
[NARRATOR]
With one bone-crushing blow,
Tien not only
immobilized his adversary,
but proved his growth as
a warrior had far exceeded
that of his abusive
former instructor.
Meanwhile, Goku prepared
for the second match,
which pitted him
against a beautiful,
but mysterious female gladiator
known only as Anonymous.
[GOKU]
Mm?
[ANONYMOUS growls]
[CROWD gasping]
How could you?
So long as I live, I'll
never forgive you for this!
I don't understand.
We've never met.
I think you're mistaking
me for somebody else.
Don't be stupid!
You are Goku, aren't you?
Oh, poor Goku. Who is that girl?
She looks furious.
I'd give 5 bullets to know
what they're talkin' about.
She makes for a lovely warrior.
Not with that mouth.
That's right.
Little miss emotional
needs an attitude adjustment.
[ANONYMOUS growls]
It's time now. You may begin!
[ANONYMOUS yells]
--[ANONYMOUS grunting]
--[GOKU yelping]
[GOKU]
Have I ever met you before?
You really know how to
lay on the charm, don't you?
Of course we've met before!
[ANONYMOUS grunting]
[ANONYMOUS]
Are you that dense?
[ANONYMOUS] Or did I mean
that little to you?
So that's it. Goku and that girl
must have been friends once.
If you don't mind, could you
tell me what I forgot,
so I can remember?
[growls]
These two seem to be
arguing about something.
[ANONYMOUS] Have you forgotten
the promise you made as well?
Promise? Did I promise
you something?
That's right! Let me
jog your memory!
--[ANONYMOUS grunting]
--[GOKU yelping]
Whatever problem these two are
having, one thing's for certain.
She's a good fighter.
Her techniques resemble the
style of the turtle school.
[BULMA]
Oh.
How could that be?
I know you're angry, but tell
me what I promised you. Please?
[ANONYMOUS] You're serious?
You really can't remember?
Fine! I'll tell you
the promise you broke!
You said that I would be your
bride! You promised to marry me!
[ALL yelp]
Say what?!
[gasping]
[ANONYMOUS]
Hmph! I would think even you
could remember that one!
Ah... Uh?
[KRILLIN, YAMCHA gasping]
[GOKU whispering]
Hey Krillin, what's a bride?
[KRILLIN, YAMCHA groan]
[ANONYMOUS groans]
Please, tell me!
A bride?! Roughly translated,
it means your life is over!
Goku, a bride is a woman
who's about to be married!
[KRILLIN] I think my
definition is more accurate.
It's the woman you'll live
with for the rest of your life!
Live together? With you?! When
I said that, was I conscious?
[ANONYMOUS gasps]
How can I marry someone if
I don't even know their name?
Hmph!
I don't know what kind of
game you're playing,
but I'll be happy to tell you
my name, if you beat me!
[GOKU] Uh, ah! Perfect! Besides,
if we're going to be spending
the rest of our lives together,
it might be a good idea
if I knew what to call you.
Ha! Are you so sure you're
going to win? I'm not.
In fact, at the pace
you're fighting,
you'd be lucky if
you hit me once.
Goku, how thick can ya get?
It's obvious who she is.
You know who she is? Tell me.
You should pay more attention.
It's no great mystery.
Puar and Master Roshi
should know who she is.
[PUAR, BULMA gasp]
What?
I can't wait to
find out who you are!
Are you ready for my attack?
Hurry up, before I fall asleep.
[gasping]
[CROWD gasping]
[CROWD murmuring]
He's your student.
What just happened?
He clearly did not hit her.
Goku is no longer my student,
but he did something.
He stuck his hand out
at an incredible speed,
the force of which must
have created a shockwave
that threw Miss Anonymous
out of the ring.
[ANONYMOUS]
What happened? Ugh...
Just relax. Give it a second.
You'll be all right. I'm sorry.
That blast was designed to
knock you out of the ring,
not knock you out.
[PICCOLO JR.] How strange.
His powers are similar
to those of my own family.
I don't believe it. You
completely knocked me off guard.
Incredible!
[ANONYMOUS] I hardly
thought it was possible,
but you're even stronger
than I remember.
Well, uh, I won...
Will you tell me your name?
You're impossible. I'm the
Ox King's daughter, ChiChi.
[yelping]
It is ChiChi!
Exactly!
Wait a minute! You're ChiChi?!
Uh? Uh...
Oh, so you are a girl!
I really wasn't sure at first.
[screams] You jerk!
[CHICHI thinking]
That Goku has no manners at all!
But he sure is cute, and strong.
I was just wondering.
Are you ever
gonna think about
me again, Goku?
Uh, yeah, I think so.
Oh my, you're so funny.
Do you think you're ever gonna
think about me again, ChiChi?
[GOKU yelps]
I remember! I did say it!
It was back--back when
we were children,
that I told you
I wanted a bride.
I remember. I was there.
[sighs] But I... I don't
think you understand.
I thought bride meant
something to eat.
[sighs] Something to eat?
[BULMA, ,PUAR, OOLONG groan]
Then the promise you
made was a mistake?
Sometimes my brain doesn't
know what my mouth is saying.
Good thing my heart does.
Will you marry me?
Yes!
[ANNOUNCER] Goku has proposed
to Anonymous-- er-- ChiChi!
I've seen fighters join forces
before, but nothing like this!
[CROWD cheering]
Goku.
Why are you grabbing me?
[CROWD cheering]
Let's hear it for
Goku and ChiChi!
[ANNOUNCER]
These blissful youngsters
are the first opponents to
ever leave the ring as a couple.
Certainly, this is the
most surprising outcome
of any match in the
tournament's history.
[CHICHI]
How romantic!
I'm in love with you, Goku.
Love, what do you mean by that?
[CHICHI]
I'll show you.
[yelps]
Goku, have you lost all your
senses?! What are you doing?
[GOKU] ChiChi, please stop
squeezing my arm.
I can't walk with
you clinging to me.
[CHICHI]
Your shyness is adorable.
We're going to have a wonderful
future together, Goku.
Big family, lots of kids.
Kids?
Not too many, eight or nine.
Wait till you see the house
father has been building for us!
Oh, he wanted it
to be a surprise!
This is all happening so fast.
[CHICHI] I know. I wish
it could last forever!
[KRILLIN]
Um...
[CHICHI laughs]
You must be one
of Goku's friends!
I'm his fiancée, ChiChi.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah, uh, likewise!
[CHICHI]
Hello again, Yamcha.
[YAMCHA grunts nervously]
You know her, Yamcha?
Why didn't you say something?
You're a sweet person,
and I know you're fond of me.
But, I'm sorry.
Goku is my true love.
[BULMA gasps]
[BULMA]
What is she talking about?
[YAMCHA] If you really wanna
know the truth, my darling,
I'm in love with you.
Ever since I first set
eyes on you. Truly.
Wow! You're in love with me?
Are you telling me the truth?
Just look at my face.
Listen, this all just
a misunderstanding.
Enlighten us.
Bulma, please! It's not
what you're thinking.
When I met her, she was
just a little girl.
She was cute in a
sisterly sorta way.
She looked nothing like the
beautiful woman she is today.
Honest!
Oops! I shouldn't've said that.
Master Roshi, long time, no see!
You always were a
cantankerous old man.
[OOLONG chuckles]
Some of you I know quite well,
and some of you I've just met.
However, there is one thing
we all share in common:
a love for this wonderful man.
I'm so happy, I could pop!
I can't wait till we're married.
I'm going to be the best wife in
the world! Aren't you excited?
Uh, sure.
[CHICHI squeals] There's so
much to do. I'll be back!
Krillin.
Uh?
Your opponent in the next match
is no ordinary warrior.
Uh, how so?
Trust me. Keep your guard up.
Don't worry.
[LAUNCH]
Clear a path, people! Move!
It's time to leave
romance behind
and get back to the fighting!
Let's begin our third match.
Next up is Krillin and Junior!
[CROWD cheers]
Good luck, Krillin.
Thanks. I don't feel
much like fighting now.
What a show-off.
Ready?
Ready!
I'm waiting.
Attack at your leisure.
Oh, I'll attack. Don't worry.
And when I do, you'll wish you
had never entered this ring.
He's... powerful!
Yes, and very dangerous.
[PICCOLO JR.]
Say what you will, little man.
You're still a loser.
We'll see who loses!
[KRILLIN grunting]
Krillin has a new technique.
[yells]
That's it?
[gasps]
[chuckles]
--[KRILLIN yells]
--[gasps, groans]
[GOKU]
Incredible!
[ANNOUNCER]
Phenomenal!
Junior has regained
his composure
and now hovers
above the stadium!
You're not as pathetic as I
thought. This might be fun yet!
[PICCOLO JR. laughs]
[PICCOLO JR. yells]
Darn! I didn't damage him!
[ANNOUNCER] After an
exciting aerial assault,
both Krillin and Junior
have brought the battle
back to the ring!
--[BULMA gasping]
--[ROSHU] Hm...
[gasps]
[KRILLIN yells]
[PICCOLO JR.]
He doesn't give up!
[yelps]
--[PICCOLO JR. grunts]
--[KRILLIN screams]
Krillin!
He'll fall--
...out of bounds!
Loser!
[CROWD gasps]
[gasping]
[KRILLIN chuckles]
Amazing! He learned the
Hovering Space Trick!
Ha! Not bad, Krillin. Good work!
Nice, Krillin! When did
you master that move?
Yeah, way to go! Perfect!
I think I speak for
the entire audience
when I say how
unbelievable that was!
Just amazing!
[chuckles]
I must admit,
you've surprised me.
Your moves and
techniques are adequate
for such a limited mind.
I congratulate you.
Forgive my bias.
I see now that I can afford
to show you a little.
[KRILLIN] What do you mean?
A little of what?
[PICCOLO JR.]
Ha! My real power, unrestrained!
[KRILLIN laughs]
Real power? Okay. Let's see it.
[PICCOLO JR. growls]
Don't listen to him, Krillin!
He's boasting
because he's scared.
You can take him!
Bulma's right!
No! It's true. Krillin,
he's very dangerous!
Don't worry. I've got this!
[NARRATOR] What terrible power
is Junior about to unleash?
Krillin has a few
tricks of his own,
but will even
these new abilities
be enough to defeat
his mighty foe?
There's only one
way to find out.
Tune in for the next
action-extreme episode
of Dragon Ball!