[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball...
Goku successfully
obtained all seven
of the mystical Dragon Balls
and awoke the Eternal Dragon
for a very special wish:
The resurrection of his
good friend Upa's father...
Along the way, he managed
to defeat an assortment
of dastardly villains, including
Emperor Pilaf, Commander Red,
and the entire Red Ribbon Army.
In other words,
our hero has been busy.
Huh...?
--[laughs]
--[VILLAGER] No, child.
That isn't for you!
[cries]
How about a nice rock?
[crying continues]
Don't cry...
After the Feeding,
we'll be able to eat, too.
[crows cawing]
[GOKU laughs, yells]
[laughs]
[NARRATOR] At the
insistence of Master Roshi,
Goku has set out on
a training mission
with a new instructor: Life.
In hopes that the
young hero would discipline
his body as well as his mind,
the Turtle Hermit forbade
the use of the Nimbus Cloud
as transportation.
And so, we join Goku as he
continues his journey east.
[SNAKE screams]
Oops, sorry!
Uwuh-wuh-wuh!
[laughs]
[GOKU pants]
[GOKU groaning, panting]
[GOKU] Food...
[GOKU grunts]
I'm so hungry...
I can't feel my stomach.
[GIRL] Please!
We need your help.
My village is suffering!
[GOKU] Huh?
[GIRL] With your strength,
I know you could help us.
But you must come today.
[GIRL] Won't you please
help my village?
You are our only hope...
I brought money to pay you.
It's all we have.
[TIGER chuckles]
Very well.
I will help you.
Really?!
--[TIGER] No.
--Aw.
It's I who need you,
little girl...
--[GIRL gasps]
--...for my lunch!
[GIRL screams,
TIGER growls]
No! Please! If you're
hungry, I have food!
Here, have some
rice cakes! Take them!
Do I look like I eat
rice cakes?
[GIRL screams]
[TIGER growls]
Say, you wouldn't happen to have
any salt and pepper, would you?
[GIRL screams]
[GOKU] Excuse me...
Would you mind if
I ate these? I'm hungry.
[TIGER] Uhh...
[GIRL] Sure?
Thanks a lot.
[TIGER chuckles]
Stay right there.
I'll have plenty of
room for dessert.
[GOKU mumbles]
What's that?
You're not really
going to eat her, are you?
Don't talk with so much
food in your mouth!
Ahh...
Maybe I'll eat you... first.
[TIGER laughs]
--Yah!
--Ow!
[GOKU growls]
[GIRL screams]
[TIGER growls]
[grunts]
Ahh...
[chuckles]
That was amazing!
Thanks. Can I have
another rice cake?
I'm still hungry.
Your strength
can save my village.
Please come with me.
There isn't much time.
[GOKU] Uhh...
[CHAO] We'll feed you
anything you want, okay?
--We have to go now!
--Do they have lambchops?
Put the lamb chops
next to the rice cakes.
It's time. They should be
here any minute.
Yes, but... Chao
hasn't returned yet.
Your daughter is
strong and dependable.
It's unlikely that
she'd return without
completing her objective.
If she doesn't return before
attendance, we'll pay dearly.
[BOY A] They're here!
[BOTH gasp]
[FATHER] Is it Chao?
[No, the riders!
They're coming!
Mercy save us!
[WOMAN B screams]
Get the elderly and
children out of sight, quickly!
[VILLAGERS screaming]
[HEADMAN thinking]
They've arrived early!
We're not prepared.
Chao, where are you?!
[chuckles]
[engine revving]
[KIDS gasp]
[PLAGUE] I don't know which
smells better, the food...
or your fear.
[laughs]
[screaming]
[tires squealing]
[CHAO] They are both monsters.
We call them Plague...
and Terror.
For that is what they are to us.
They have been tormenting our
village since before I was born.
[GOKU slurps]
[CHAO] To appease them,
my elders created the Feeding,
a monthly ritual where they
come and take our food
and water, leaving us with
barely enough to survive.
[GOKU] That's mean.
I'll defeat them.
Is that all you need?
Are you kidding? That's a lot!
In return, this money is yours.
The villagers took up
a collection.
Uh, no thank you...
This sort of thing is exactly
what my master wants me to do.
It will help my training.
Thank you so much!
I'm sorry. I haven't
even asked your name.
My name is Goku. How about you?
I'm Chao. It's a
pleasure to-- Look out!
[CHAO screams]
[BOTH scream]
[GOKU laughs,
CHAO screams]
[BOTH grunt]
You okay?
Is this the path?
Yeah, sure, sort of.
I think you just
discovered a short cut.
Great!
[GOKU laughs]
[GOKU] It's kind of
scary in here.
[CHAO] It used to
be beautiful,
but that was before the drought.
This was my
favorite place to visit.
Back then, these bare trees
were covered with fresh
Ranpha flowers.
Seeing them at full-bloom
is breathtaking.
[CHAO sighs]
Their fragrance is so sweet,
you almost wish it were
possible to eat the air.
[groans]
[CHAO] But all that's
gone now...
Maybe they'll return someday.
[TERROR belches]
[HEADMAN] Does the feast
meet with your approval?
[FATHER whimpers]
[TERROR slurps]
Hardly.
I've eaten garbage that
tastes better than this!
Look at it!
What kind of a fool would
find this slop palatable?! Huh?!
[TERROR] The food tastes fine.
Oh?
[chuckles]
[TERROR] It's the tribute
I find lacking.
Explain it to them.
We came here expecting a feast.
What you provided was
little more than a snack!
The dishes on this table are
half of what we had last month.
Where's the chocolate cake?!
[FATHER] We've yielded
fewer crops this year
due to the drought.
Surely you can understand that.
I don't want your excuses...
But I will take your share
of the food supply.
No, that's impossible!
We can't give you our food.
Our families would
starve to death!
[FATHER] Leave him alone!
[PLAGUE chuckles,
HEADMAN whimpers]
Tell me, grandpa,
what good is food
if your belly is full of holes?
I don't think I'm
getting through to him.
Maybe we should use him
as an example.
No, wait...
Why waste the bullets when
we can just use the Gourd?
Excellent idea! Bring it out.
Let's take attendance!
Go!
[gasping]
You heard the man.
Gather your miserable hides
in the courtyard.
It's attendance time, and
you know what that means--
Did you hear what I said?!
Move, you insolent dogs!
It's time you faced the Gourd!
[PLAGUE laughs]
[bell rings]
[CHAO] There! Oh no!
[FATHER] Everyone! Gather in
the courtyard for attendance!
Quickly, please!
Not good!
Chao, what is attendance?
[CHAO] There's no time!
Come on, we've got to hurry!
[VILLAGERS screaming]
[CHAO] Papa!
[BOTH gasp]
--Chao!
--Just in time!
You're back!
I think I found someone
who can help us.
Oh, who?
Come here. I want you
to meet my father...
This is Goku.
But he's just a boy.
[HEADMAN] A baby.
Goku is strong, really.
I've seen him fight.
[glass shatters,
gasping]
Peasants, your
attention, please...
You wouldn't want to miss
hearing your name called.
[PLAGUE] When I call your name,
a simple "here" will suffice.
Don't get creative.
[chuckles]
[coughs]
--Bulka!
--Heeere!
Eh... Salli.
[SALLI] Here.
--[PLAGUE] Pino!
--[PINO] Here...
Louder, runt!
--Pino!
--[PINO] Here!
[PLAGUE] Jo!
Chao, I don't understand
what's going on.
Why is he calling out
their names like that?
Look over there.
Do you see that gourd?
[GOKU] What's a gourd?
[CHAO] It's a
hard-shelled fruit.
Like a melon.
Anyway, if someone's
name is called
and they don't
answer right away--
[PLAGUE] Chao!
Uh, here!
[PLAGUE] Mm...
That was a close one.
--Temjin!
--[TEMJIN] Here!
What happens if you
don't answer right away?
You'll be swallowed
by the gourd.
[CHAO] The gourd
releases a powerful mist
that can swallow a man whole.
[CHAO] Once inside, the
victim's life force is drained,
creating a potion that can be
consumed by another person.
[CHAO] We believe
it is the source
of Plague and Terror's strength.
--[PLAGUE] Renchi!
--[RENCHI] Here.
--[PLAGUE] Varbar!
--[VARBAR] Here!
--[PLAGUE] Foochi?
--[FOOCHI] Here.
There, that one. The boy.
Woman, what's his name?
No wait! My son, he can't speak.
He's a newborn.
He's only two weeks old!
Quiet! What's his name?
[MOTHER] No! It's no--
No isn't a name. Speak up!
This is intolerable!
You know he can't say anything.
Leave her baby alone.
Old man, you just
sealed his fate.
--Now, for the last time...
--[MOTHER cries]
His name!
His name is Chency.
[VILLAGERS gasp]
Chency won't be harmed...
You have nothing to worry about,
as long as he says
his name when called.
[grunts]
[CHAO screams,
GOKU growls]
[MOTHER sobs] No...
--Chenc--
--[GOKU] Stop it!
Eh?
What is your name, boy?!
[GOKU] Goku.
Goku?
Goo-goo, Gheg,
Goo-woo, Goup...
You won't find me in that book.
I came here to defeat you.
[laughs]
You're here to defeat us?
That's a good one!
Looks like you arrived
30 years too--
[PLAGUE screams]
[grunts]
Huh?!
[PLAGUE yells]
[GOKU grunts]
--Yaaay!
--[VILLAGERS gasp]
Good work, Goku!
[PLAGUE growls] Die!
[grunts]
[gasps]
That's impossible!
You shouldn't pick on
these people.
They haven't done
anything to you.
--[TERROR] Wait.
--What's wrong?!
That's useless... This boy
deserves a worthy challenge.
[VILLAGERS gasp]
Let's see how well
you fair against Steel.
Okay.
[TERROR yells]
[GOKU yells]
[BOTH grunting]
--[grunts]
--Are you all right?!
Quickly, grab the gourd.
Right!
--[FATHER gasps]
--Bad idea.
Papa!
[PLAGUE] Here!
[TERROR growls]
[GOKU yells]
The gourd!
Your strength
will be mine! Goku!
{BOTH gasp]
[TERROR chuckles,
GOKU yells]
[growls, gasps]
[chuckles]
[GOKU grunts]
[CHAO screams]
[GOKU] Nooo!
[VILLAGERS gasp]
[GOKU] The gourd
must have swallowed me
because I didn't answer.
[GOKU groans]
[TERROR laughs]
Do we have any more
heroes in the audience?
There's plenty of room!
All is lost.
[TERROR &amp; PLAGUE laugh]
[TERROR] This calls
for a celebration!
I can dance better than that!
You call this entertainment?!
As long as they
have that gourd,
we must submit to their will,
but I'm afraid it's going to
cost our village dearly.
[PLAGUE] I said I wanted my
bread extra toasted!
And where is that
chocolate cake?!
[CHAO] Goku...
Ka...
Me...
Ha...
Me.. ha!
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU] I guess I'm going to be
in here longer than I thought.
I've... got to go!
There's no more time.
I can't wait any longer!
I sure hope there's
nobody down there...
That should be
long enough, I think.
He's had plenty of time
to hit the bottom.
[GOKU] Haaa... Whaa... Hey!
[PLAGUE chuckles]
Good, he's dissolved...
It's been a long time
since I took my last drink.
Uhh...
[TERROR gasps]
[GOKU chuckles]
Goku!
How did you escape?!
[TERROR growls]
I'm back. Let's finish
what we started!
[PLAGUE] All right, little boy!
[TERROR yells]
I've got it!
[PLAGUE grunts]
[GOKU] Let's take attendance.
[chuckles]
--[GOKU] Let's take attendance!
--[BOTH gasp]
Alright, Terror!
Ah... Here!
[GOKU] Plague!
H-Here!
I can't hear you.
--Terror. Terror!
--H-Here!
Plague! Terror! Plague! Terror!
--Here! Here!
[chuckles]
[BOTH chuckle]
Plague, Plague, Terror, Plague,
Plague, Plague, Terror,
Terror, Terror, Plague,
Plague, Terror...
--Here! H-Here! Here!
--Here, here! Here!
[BOTH sigh]
[chuckles]
[VILLAGERS chuckle]
[BOTH squeal]
Wait! I answered four times.
No, three plus one is--
Have mercy...
I thought I had
trouble counting.
Sorry, guys,
you just couldn't keep up.
[BOTH yell]
[BOTH whimper]
Have pity!
Not the mist!
Have a nice trip.
[BOTH yell]
[BOTH scream]
[GOKU laughs]
That's that!
[VILLAGERS cheer]
--You did it!
--We're free!
[cheering continues]
Oh, Goku! Thank you! Thank you!
[TERROR] Please let us out.
We swear we'll be good!
Do you promise not to bother
the villagers any more?
[PLAGUE] Yes, yes, we promise!
[TERROR] Please help us!
I'm afraid of the dark!
[VILLAGERS laugh]
That's funny.
[GOKU laughs]
[CHAO gasps]
[gasping]
[BOTH] It's rain!
[VILLAGERS gasp, cheer]
[grunting]
Come on! Concentrate.
Put your backs into it!
Right!
[FATHER] You have to finish
that field before lunch.
Yes, sir!
[CHAO] You'll eat
the amount that you plant!
Yeah!
You have to work hard
to get your share around here,
and you boys are way behind!
[FATHER] Mm-hmm!
[grunting]
[BOTH groan]
[CHAO] Bye!
[VILLAGERS cheer]
[GOKU laughs]
[CHAO laughs,
VILLAGERS cheer]
--[GOKU] So long!
--[CHILDREN laugh]
[NARRATOR] Having liberated
Chao and her village,
Goku continues his journey
for self-improvement.
But no matter what
adventure lies ahead,
the young warrior
will never forget this day.
It has taught him that
no weapon or adversary
is stronger than
the human spirit.
For true strength
comes from within...
Join us again for the next
exciting episode of Dragon Ball!