I got ya!
[GOKU laughs]
[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball,
Goku began his
three-year training
for the next World Martial
Arts Tournament,
making good on
his pledge to Popo.
[POPO] One cannot
describe sight to the blind.
You'll have to
stumble upon it yourself.
[NARRATOR] A pledge that
forced him to undertake
the most rigorous
training of his life.
Goku was more than
happy to pay the price
for the revival of his friends.
However, the dangerous trials
he faced took their toll.
[GOKU squeals]
[NARRATOR] Popo and the Guardian
of the Earth watched with glee
as Goku bravely endured
his electrifying challenge.
It seemed as though he had
bested his shocking adversary.
Until...
[GOKU groans]
I'll never give up...
One way or another,
I'll find a way to move faster
than the lightning...
[GOKU groans]
[gasps]
Finally, you've awakened.
[GOKU]
Uh... Uhh...
What happened?
You've been asleep
for three whole days.
That long?
Everything seems okay, but I...
I could have sworn
I was struck by lightning.
Yes, yes you were, in fact.
But you recovered quickly.
That's great!
That lightning won't hit me
again. I'll beat it this time!
Maybe later. But today, we're
going to try something else.
No lightning?
Come, follow me.
Uhh...
Ohh.
This place again?
There is only one way
to guarantee success
against the lightning.
You must shed all that you are
and become blank, like the sky.
If you want success,
do what I say.
To understand fully, you must
first journey into the woods.
I get it! There's someone in
the woods I have to fight!
Is that it, Popo?
I have told you all that I can.
You must go into the woods
and see for yourself.
He's strong, right?
This is going to be a
great challenge! Yes! Yes!
[POPO laughs]
[POPO]
Now, are you ready?
[GOKU]
Mm-hm!
Ah, ha, ha, ha, ha.
[GOKU yells]
There's no end!
It's a bottomless swamp!
[GOKU]
Ka... Me... Ha... Me... Ha!
Ohh...
I sure could use something
to eat. I'm starving.
There's no way I'll be
able to do any training
until I've eaten something.
It's food!
[GOKU laughs]
Perfect!
[GOKU]
That wasn't very nice!
Mmm...
It's all right now. I'm all dry.
Sorry about that.
I've been trapping rabbits
and wild boars for years.
But this was the first
time I've caught a human.
Your trap smelled delicious.
What's your name?
My name is Moose, and over
here is my wife, Éclair.
[GOKU laughs]
Hello, boy.
I'm Goku. Nice to meet you.
And now, let me
introduce you to my kids.
Children, come quick! Hurry!
[CHILDREN giggling]
Waugh!
You've got a lot of kids!
From the left, there's Cupcake.
[MOOSE]
Pudding.
Nice to meet you.
[MOOSE]
Donut.
Hi!
[MOOSE]
Jelly...
Welcome to our home.
[MOOSE]
...and Jam.
Hello, sir.
[MOOSE]
Creampuff.
My friends call me "Puff."
[MOOSE]
Cocoa, Cookie, and Crepe.
How do you do?
[GOKU laughs]
You have great names. I'm Goku.
[stomach growling]
[GOKU laughs]
[CHILDREN laugh]
Please eat supper with us today.
I'm afraid I don't have
any more steak,
but Grandpa will return
soon with lots of fish!
[GOKU]
Mmm!
Well, how about that!
Here he is now.
[CHILDREN laugh]
[KARINTO]
The fish were biting today.
[CHILDREN laugh]
Grandpa, Grandpa!
It's great that you're home.
I missed you so much!
[KARINTO chuckles]
Can we play cards, Grandpa?
[COCOA] Grandpa, you promised
to read the picture book.
[CHILDREN]
Please! Come on!
Easy, children.
We have a guest. Welcome.
We still have plenty of food.
Eat your fill.
I will. Thank you, sir!
So, tell us about your journey,
Goku. Why come into the woods?
I'm here because of a
promise I made to Mr. Popo.
Popo?
Popo? What a funny name!
[CREPE] No, it's not. Besides,
I know a squirrel named Poppy.
Crepe is right.
What a nice squirrel. He doesn't
like nuts, but he loves sugar.
Popo knows Poppy?
[CREPE]
No. I doubt it.
Ahh. Poppy has issues.
He broke a branch and
fell on Palepaw.
Poppy's on a diet,
just like Papa.
So you see, it's very doubtful
that Popo knows Poppy,
or Palepaw!
Who's Palepaw?
Hmm...
He's an angry squirrel.
With a mean face like this.
[JELLY laughs]
[GOKU]
No, this is a mean face!
[GOKU growls]
That's kind of what
Mr. Popo looks like,
only he has one tooth.
So does Poppy!
--[DONUT] Wait, you're thinking
--[CREPE] That's what we'll
--of Palepaw!
--call him, one-tooth Poppy!
I think P oppy is a
wonderful squirrel,
and he has a
beautiful coat of fur!
Whoever this Popo is,
I'll bet Poppy and Palepaw
could defeat him in a fight!
Popo's not the one
looking for a fight.
That's what I'm supposed to do!
I'm afraid the
only person around here
who likes to fight is Yaochun.
He's strong as an ox!
He lives up in the mountains,
about 5 miles north of here.
Goku, you're not seriously
thinking about visiting Yaochun?
[GOKU]
Mm-hm.
[JAM]
Y-You don't wanna do that.
He'd mop the floor
with you, honest!
It sounds like a
worthy challenge!
I'll say one thing
for you, little man,
you've got a lot of spunk
chasing after Yaochun!
[laughs]
Thanks. I guess Yaochun is
the reason Popo sent me here.
I can't wait to fight him!
Well, you won't find him alone.
I'll take you there
tomorrow when I go fishing.
--[GOKU laughs]
--[PUDDING, CUPCAKE giggle]
[GOKU, COCOA laugh]
--[GOKU grunts]
--[CREAMPUFF] Haah!
[ALL laugh]
[ALL grunting]
[CUPCAKE laughs]
[GOKU snores]
[DONUT groans]
[snoring continues]
This time I'll win for sure!
I hope we get to fight each
other in the tournament finals.
Yeah.
You guys are acting
like big shots,
but don't forget about me.
I've already died once.
That makes me unstoppable!
[YAMCHA]
But, Master, I don't understand.
[KRILLIN] But you've always
trained us for the tournament.
It's kinda your job.
Why won't you help us this time?
I do appreciate
your predicament,
but in case
you hadn't noticed,
I'm a little busy right now.
Does anybody have
a socket wrench?
Please, Master.
Can't you see we're desperate?
You're the only one here
who can give us guidance.
All right. There is
one thing I can tell you.
You boys will never
be a match for Goku
unless you change your routine.
Look, let me share with
you a little story.
It all started when
I was about your age.
I was brash and confident,
and I had a full head of hair!
I was even better
looking then, than I am now.
Anyway, I happened to run into
this lovely nurse named Iola,
who it turned out was in the
same book club
as my sister's
best friend's cousin.
Now that's serendipity.
Thank you, Master.
I think I can speak
for everyone here
when I say that
was most insightful.
Uh, yeah.
Thank you.
[ROSHI]
Mm-hmm.
That's why I'm here.
What a way to inspire!
[BULMA laughs]
Thank you.
Master, how can a young bald
guy ever meet beautiful girls?
Well, that skill
just comes naturally.
[ROSHI]
Eh, right boys? ...Right?
--[YAMCHA] Pardon.
--[TIEN] Excuse me, Master.
[GOKU]
Goodbye! Nice to meet you!
[GOKU laughs]
[CHILDREN laughing]
Goodbye! So long!
So, do you go fishing every day?
I sure do.
I leave home at the same time
and get back at the same time,
just like clock work.
No change in the last 60 years.
Wow! Sixty whole years?
That's a long time.
And a lot of fish!
[KARINTO laughs]
You've caught fish every
time you've gone out?
You better believe it,
and not just for my family
but the neighbors, too.
Even the bears
hit me up sometimes.
If it weren't for me,
the whole forest would starve!
[KARINTO laughs]
[BOTH laughing]
Here you are. Good luck.
Thank you.
[KARINTO]
You be careful.
And I hope you
catch a bunch of fish!
I'd be happy with the
load I caught yesterday.
[GOKU chuckles]
[KARINTO chuckles]
Bye!
[GOKU laughs]
[KARINTO]
Take care!
[GOKU]
That's got to be him.
Who are you?
My name is Goku. I'm looking
for Yaochun. Are you him?
I am.
Good. Will you please
fight with me?
What?
Are you serious about this,
little boy?
[GOKU]
Mm-hmm!
All right.
But I won't hold back.
[GOKU]
I'm ready!
[YAOCHUN]
Here I come!
[GOKU thinking] Weird! He's left
himself completely unguarded.
[YAOCHUN growls bellows]
--[GOKU yells]
--[YAOCHUN groans]
[YAOCHUN] I don't believe it.
I've been beat by a kid.
But I'm... faster
than lightning.
You are strong!
Are you serious? Are you
really faster than lightning?
Of course not! I just
say that to scare people.
Then you're not
the one. Oh well.
[GOKU thinking] If Popo didn't
send me here to fight Yaochun,
then who am I supposed to meet?
[GOKU thinking]
I wonder if there's even
a strong warrior around here.
[yawns]
[KARINTO]
Oh, so we meet again.
Hi, Karinto.
When did you get here?
Why are you so surprised?
This is the same rock
I sit on every morning.
But just a little while ago...
[KARINTO chuckles]
You must have been half asleep.
It doesn't really matter.
Care to try your luck?
Sure!
I've caught fish before,
but only with my bare hands.
I've never used a pole.
You're holding
the pole too tight.
You need to relax those
arms and take it easy.
Oh, like this?
That's better.
Remain calm like the water.
Take in a
deep breath. Now.
[KARINTO]
Exhale. Look to the sky.
[GOKU]
Huh?
[KARINTO]
Isn't it beautiful?
Oh, wow.
Keep looking up. Feel the
world around you. Concentrate.
I see what you mean. Wow!
Everything is so calm and quiet.
[KARINTO] What's wrong?
Having trouble keeping focus?
Close your eyes.
[KARINTO] Remain perfectly still
and concentrate on the sound
of the running water.
Soon you will feel its rhythm.
[KARINTO] The water sets
the pace for the fish.
Once you can feel its rhythm,
you will be one with your prey.
Don't rush it.
Relieve yourself of all anxiety.
The fish can sense your stress.
[KARINTO]
Once you've cleared your mind,
you will sense
the approaching fish
before it ever bites
the string. Focus.
Pull up!
--[GOKU laughs]
--It's a keeper!
[BOTH laugh]
By the way, did you find
the man you were looking for?
Yes. I did meet up with Yaochun.
But you did not find
what you were seeking.
[POPO] He still hasn't
learned anything.
I'm not sure I agree.
[GOKU]
I've got another one!
[GOKU laughs]
Leave some for tomorrow.
[KARINTO laughs]
[GOKU laughs]
[NARRATOR]
With a simple lesson,
Goku found joy and laughter
that had been in short supply
over the last three years.
Join us for more fun
and excitement,
next time on Dragon Ball!