[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball...
Master Roshi stumbled upon
the six-star Dragon Ball
as he continued his search along
with Tien Shinhan and Chiaotzu.
[ROSHI] Hey, it's the
six-star ball! We did it!
[NARRATOR]
King Piccolo tracked down Goku
and challenged him to battle
for the demise of his henchmen,
Cymbal and Tambourine.
You are the reason
I have exterminated
the Martial Arts Society.
You deserve to be terminated.
[NARRATOR]
Goku fought bravely,
but against
King Piccolo's might,
it wasn't enough.
As a last defense, Goku
used the Kamehameha Wave,
his most powerful technique.
[GOKU] ...Ha!
[NARRATOR] It didn't work.
It's about time
we said goodbye... Boy!
Rain.
[GOKU groaning]
[chuckling menacingly]
[GOKU yells]
For once, I'm glad I'm hiding.
[chuckling]
You... won't... win.
He has to have...
some... weakness.
I believe we've come to the part
where you're supposed to grovel
and beg for your pathetic life.
[groaning]
I'll never give in to you...
Never!
[chuckling]
All right... die!
Now is when it really gets good!
Uh oh!
Come on!
Let's see if you
can live through this!
Do it!
[yelling]
[yelling continues]
Goku's gonna get creamed!
[GOKU yelling]
[screaming]
So this is the best that
the human race has to offer?
The boy's heart is cold...
It is over.
[laughing]
[laughing continues]
It's so nice to see him
in good spirits again.
Oh wow! He's truly amazing!
You can say that again!
Good show, Your Majesty!
Vengeance is most refreshing.
It's what keeps up my youthful
appearance. Our friends await.
Yes.
I think we've
given them enough time
to collect the rest
of our Dragon Balls.
[PICCOLO laughs]
[PILAF]
Excuse me...
[PILAF laughing nervously]
Once rejuvenated,
will he be stronger?
Yes. What you've just witnessed
will seem weak by comparison.
[YAJIROBE] I thought
he'd never leave...
I didn't think
anyone could kill Goku.
I guess there's always
someone more powerful somewhere.
I'm sorry things had
to end this way, Goku.
I'm sorry
I couldn't help you.
But you will receive
a hero's burial.
Is it possible?!
[heart beating]
Wait! I--I think
I hear something!
Come on, come on! Goku! Wake up!
[coughing]
Need... water.
Hang on!
That's it. Take your time.
I still can't believe it!
I mean, that fight was brutal!
I can't believe you're alive!
I didn't think anyone could
survive against King Piccolo!
I was no match for him... He--He
defeated me like I was nothing!
Don't be so hard
on yourself, Goku.
No one else could
have done any better.
King Piccolo isn't
your everyday fighter.
Yajirobe, have you ever
heard of Korin Tower?
Korin Tower? Never heard of it.
I trained there once before.
Listen, I have to
ask you a big favor.
Do you think you
could take me to it?
My muscles seem kinda stuck, but
I think I know who can help me.
Sounds like a strange
place to find a doctor.
Sure. No problem. I'll take
you anywhere you wanna go.
Under one condition,
you gotta feed me.
[laughing]
That ball has to be
around here somewhere.
[CHIAOTZU] I found it!
With that one we have five.
That leaves us with only
two more balls to get,
and we know where one is--
With King Piccolo.
We had better stay on our guard.
What's the matter?
Is something wrong?!
[ROSHI]
Well, we don't have to worry
about finding those two balls.
According to the radar,
they're together,
and headed straight for us!
That has to be King Piccolo!
He means to destroy us!
[radar beeping]
Your Majesty,
the other five Dragon Balls
are headed straight for us!
[laughing]
How thoughtful of them
to deliver my prize...
This day has been fruitful.
It has seen the end of my enemy
and soon I will possess
all seven Dragon Balls!
[laughing]
All right, we're on
an intercept course.
[TIEN thinking]
That fiend! He's mine!
Let me make one thing clear.
We have no chance
of defeating King Piccolo
with hand to hand combat.
We must get his Dragon Balls and
call upon the Eternal Dragon.
It will be the
Dragon's privilege
to remove Piccolo
from this world.
Yes, sir.
[ROSHI] Tien, take us down
between those two boulders.
That's as good a place
as any to make our stand.
I admire your courage,
but it was foolish for you
to go up against
King Piccolo by yourself.
I'm surprised, Yajirobe.
You didn't even lend me a hand.
Of course I didn't!
I like you Goku, but not
as much as I like living.
[YAJIROBE]
Do I keep going straight?
[GOKU] A little to the left.
[YAJIROBE] A little?
What kind of direction is that?
I like your car.
It sure is nice and fast.
Yeah, it's pretty neat,
all right. I stole it.
Just in case you're thinking
what I hope you're not,
I wouldn't go up against
King Piccolo again.
It's not wise to push your luck.
How... well do you know him?
Who is he?
Like I said, it's just
a story I heard as a kid...
A terrible tale
that gave me nightmares.
A long time ago,
King Piccolo used his power
to try and
take over the world.
Fortunately, a brave Martial
Artist--I forget his name--
but he was able
to stop the invasion...
Or that's the story...
I guess we know differently now.
Guess so... So, how did
the Martial Artist stop him?
I don't know, but I'll bet
it was spectacular,
whatever he did...
What's going to happen
once you put
all seven Dragon Balls together?
[GOKU]
The Eternal Dragon will appear
and make your
wish come true.
Whatever you want to
ask for is fine with him.
But you only get one wish.
Any wish you want? No way.
Yeah, it is true. A little
more to the left, please.
[YAJIROBE] If that is true, what
could someone as powerful
as King Piccolo
possibly ask for?
[GOKU]
Uh, a better personality? Heh.
Perfect... soon I will
have all seven Dragon Balls,
and my youth will
finally be restored!
[ROSHI] Yes! Right there,
see those two rocks?
That's where we'll land.
[TIEN]
What shall we do first?
[ROSHI] Capsulize the plane.
Get it out of sight.
Yes, Master.
[clears throat]
[CHIAOTZU] Oh!
Quickly, we can bury the
Dragon Balls in this hole.
Right.
Piccolo won't find them
so easily here,
and it might
just buy us some time.
[CHIAOTZU] There we go!
[ROSHI] All right, listen...
Chiaotzu, you hide
behind that rock over there...
Tien Shinhan and I will snatch
King Piccolo's Dragon Balls
while he's searching for ours.
[CHIAOTZU] Got it.
[ROSHI]
Once we secure the last two,
we'll throw them to Chiaotzu
who will bury them
with the other five
and call for
the Sacred Dragon.
All you have to say is,
"Come out, Dragon"
and tell him the wish.
Yes, sir.
All right?
Mm-hmm. Understood.
Ready? They should
be here at any moment...
Good luck. Now get going!
Ah! It appears they've
come to a complete stop.
They're just waiting.
[laughing]
Oh, they're not just waiting.
Our prey has set a trap. See,
they're trying to ambush us.
Let's play along, for now.
Wait.
They're here!
[ROSHI]
They're traveling by airship.
We have arrived, Your Majesty.
We are directly above
the Dragon Balls now.
Time to get the goodies.
[TIEN] There's a chance
they won't come down,
or what if King Piccolo decides
to keep his Dragon Balls
on board that ship?
Then we sneak aboard
and take them.
Besides, I'd like
to see the view.
[PILAF] I don't see any
movement down there.
That's because they're hiding...
So, they want to
play games, do they?
They're hoping we'll come down
so they can
steal our Dragon Balls.
I guess I should keep
these in a safe place.
I take it the ugly
green guy is King Piccolo.
It looks like he just
swallowed the Dragon Balls!
Maniacal fiend!
He's smarter than I remembered!
The only option for us now
is to knock him over
and pump those balls
out of his rotten hide!
We have to fight him
head on, Master Roshi.
That's what he
wants us to believe.
No, Tien,
you stay out of this.
No, Master Roshi!
I must fight Piccolo!
You won't do anything,
Tien Shinhan. That's an order.
But Master! You can't do this
to me! I have to fight him!
Don't tie my hands... Please!
I appreciate your
concern for my safety,
but I've taken steps
to protect myself,
including a
life-sustaining potion.
But you can't do it--Agh!
Master, you--
[ROSHI] I'm sorry to
have to do this, Tien.
It's better for you
to sleep through this one.
Too many lives
have been lost already.
Your dedication to
our cause is admirable.
But I must confess I didn't
take a life-sustaining potion.
Never touch the stuff myself.
Anyway, if I fail,
you'll be the only one left
to defeat that monster.
But only as a last ditch effort.
Your will is strong, but
your training is incomplete.
Tell Goku... I was proud.
Chiaotzu! Forget about
the maneuver we discussed.
I want you to stay hidden.
Do not come out until it's over,
no matter what happens!
Understood?
[CHIAOTZU]
Yes, Master. Okay!
Hey, look! There he is!
If you want the
Dragon Balls, Piccolo,
you'll have
to come down here!
Oh, so he knows my name.
He's done his homework.
I'm at a disadvantage.
Though I'm afraid
knowing my identity
and still putting forth
this challenge
doesn't say much
for his intelligence.
[PICCOLO]
Thank you for the invitation.
I look forward to your agony.
[NARRATOR] The duel
between Master and Majesty
has finally begun.
Can the Turtle Hermit
foil Piccolo's plans
for world domination
a second time?
Or will he be consumed by
the monster's awesome power?
Find out next time,
on Dragon Ball!