[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
[TIEN]
I no longer wish to kill you.
When the time comes, avoid it.
Huh?
The Tri Beam Cannon?!
Don't Tien, don't!
Tien Shinhan,
you mustn't do this!
[NARRATOR] Proving his desire
to win at all costs,
Tien called upon
the Tri Beam Cannon,
a lethal technique with
such fierce power,
it not only destroys the target,
but its master as well.
[TIEN]
Tri Beam!
Excitement turned to horror
as Tien's Tri Beam Cannon filled
the arena with blinding light.
Goku was consumed by
its deadly brilliance.
[CROWD screaming]
[panting]
[yelps]
[KRILLIN]
Where's the platform?!
[CROWD gasping]
[ANNOUNCER] Ladies and
gentlemen, please remain calm.
Everything is under control.
The fight will continue, uh,
assuming that we
can find the stage.
I was wrong to judge
my wave against this.
There's no comparison!
Where's... Where's Goku?!
[BULMA gasps]
[KRILLIN]
Goku! Goku, where are you?!
[ROSHI]
Hm... Hm?
[OOLONG] I hate to be the
pessimist, but I don't see
how anyone could
have survived that.
He's gone!
Hold on... He's not dead.
I can sense it.
Are you sure? Where?!
Goku is alive.
[panting]
[CHIAOTZU thinking] Where is he?
If he's not below, that means...
He's up!
[CROWD gasping]
I was right. It looks
like they both made it!
[ANNOUNCER] Yes, yes, it's true!
Both Goku and Tien
have survived the
Tri Beam Cannon!
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER]
It's a miracle Goku had time
to get free of the blast!
[laughs]
You made it.
You must have set a new record
for speed-jumping to
evade such destruction.
Powerful technique!
There's no way I
would've been prepared
to dodge if you
hadn't warned me.
Thank you.
[TIEN] Like I said before,
I didn't wanna kill you,
just knock you out of bounds.
As you plainly see...
I was quite successful.
[TIEN] There's no way you'll
win. Nothing to do now but fall.
And, since there's no
longer a stage to land on,
whoever touches
down first will lose.
It's as simple,
and perfect as that.
Lucky for me, I just happen
to know Sky Dancing.
I could stay
up here for hours.
Tien's little scheme worked.
Then it's over. Goku will lose.
Good work, Tien!
You haven't won yet.
I've still got one option.
Huh?
[GOKU growls]
With all my energy focused,
there's no telling
what I can do!
[TIEN gasps]
I think the thin air has
affected your brain.
You're defenseless up
here and you know it!
That last technique
took a lot out of you.
I guess we're even. Ready?
[TIEN gasps]
Ka... me...
You're joking! Don't you
ever get tired of that?!
Wait a minute! It looks
like Goku is preparing
to use his Kamehameha Wave!
[YAMCHA gasps]
You can't be serious...
That's your last effort?
The Kamehameha Wave
won't do you any good,
not at this altitude!
[laughs]
Ha...
Bad move, Goku. There's no
guarantee it will work.
But, Master, you've always
said Goku is extraordinary.
Maybe he can do
something special.
No, no. This has nothing
to do with Goku's ability.
It's just a simple fact. That
wave is useless against Tien.
No... But then...
It's impossible... Goku lost.
Me...
[TIEN]
Give it up. You're beaten.
Don't do it!
He's about to shoot!
[GOKU]
Ha!
[yelps]
I may be slower in
the air, but so are you!
He's crazy!
What are you doing!?
[TIEN groans]
[ALL gasping]
[OOLONG]
Ouch!
--[KRILLIN] Alright!
--[ROSHI] That's it!
Goku has used the
Kamehameha Wave
to propel himself like a rocket,
directly at Tien Shinhan!
[yells]
Oh, no!
That was a perfect hit!
I think Tien's unconscious.
That means Goku will win.
Not so fast... It's not over
until they touch ground.
Goku's efforts may
have been in vain.
Both opponents are falling fast.
There's no telling which of them
is going to hit
the ground first!
I must have used all of my
energy on that last wave.
I can hardly move a muscle!
If you'll excuse me...
[ANNOUNCER] They're both
falling neck-and-neck.
At this point, it's too early
to tell who will hit first.
Though, Goku seems to
be at a disadvantage.
Ka... me... ha... me... ha!
[ANNOUNCER] Despite a lack
of energy, Goku has managed
another Kamehameha Wave.
Though barely creating
a spark, it appears
to have slowed his
descent considerably.
[ALL]
Yeah!
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[GOKU yelps]
[DRIVER yells]
[TIEN groans]
[tires screech
[whimpers]
[gasps]
[ANNOUNCER]
I-It's over, folks!
I'm hovering above
the city streets where
both opponents have
finally landed.
In what can only be
described as bad timing,
Goku lost his advantage when he
collided with a delivery truck,
sending him bouncing
to the pavement
a split second before Tien!
Our new tournament
champion is Tien Shinhan!
[CROWD gasping]
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER] Once again,
we have an official winner.
The Champion of the 22nd World
Martial Arts Tournament
is Tien Shinhan!
Let's catch up with our champion
and get his reaction...
Um, while Tien
collects his thoughts,
let's hear from Goku on
his incredible, uh, loss.
Well, we'll get reactions from
our winner and loser soon...
Uh, maybe... I hope.
Goku!
Let's go. Goku needs
his friends.
Yes, you're right.
[LAUNCH] The number one
leader in crowd control.
[LAUNCH] Move it, twinkle toes!
Yo! Watch out, people,
we're comin' through!
Cool... It's an armed escort!
[CROWD cheering]
[GOKU grunting]
[KRILLIN laughs]
You look awful.
Krillin.
[grunts]
--[KRILLIN laughs]
--[CROWD roaring]
[CROWD cheering]
Cool landin', kid!
Cool hairstyle!
You did it!
I knew you'd win.
That was awesome!
[MAN]
Hooray for Tien Shinhan!
[CROWD cheers]
[gasps]
[ROSHI thinking] That's right.
All this noise is for you.
You've won.
I know cheering is a relatively
new response to you,
especially since you're
used to hearing screams.
But you'll get through it.
Adulation has a funny
way of growing on you.
So, how does it feel
to win-- the right way?
You should be proud of yourself.
I am. But be warned:
This new turn may bring with
it unexpected consequences.
People may actually
like you. Enjoy.
Master, I...
[GOKU laughs]
Uh-- Ah!
A champion should
be seen in style.
Relax, I'm your biggest fan.
[applause, cheering]
[laughs]
[ANNOUNCER]
See you in three, everybody!
And don't forget to
bring your sunglasses!
That was a
marvelous tournament.
Full of some thrilling fights.
I'm going to miss it very much.
The finale was close.
It's just bad luck, Goku.
If only you hadn't
been hit by that truck.
Aw, that's okay. I sure had fun!
[fabric rips]
[KRILLIN laughs]
[KRILLIN] You go through clothes
almost as fast as meals.
Don't worry.
You can wear mine.
Huh?
Goku, listen. I've been
thinking about it
and there's something
I want you to have.
[KRILLIN] Tien... That's your
prize money, isn't it?
Look, it's no big deal. I just
think you should take half.
We both know if you
hadn't hit that truck,
you would've won.
You are stronger.
No thanks.
I appreciate the offer,
but I wouldn't know what
to spend it on anyway.
Yeah, but--
[ROSHI laughs]
Tien, it's true.
Luck helped you win today.
But you shouldn't let that
discount your achievement.
In fact, luck and
strength go hand-in-hand.
And I learned a lot
from our fight.
[BULMA]
There you are.
[gasps]
[OOLONG]
Great match. Now let's go home.
You fought well... really.
Uh, thank you.
Sorry about your leg.
I did a lot of terrible things.
No big deal. Bones heal
just like everything else.
[gasps]
But at the next tournament,
I expect a rematch. Got it?!
Uh! Of course.
What will you do until then?
Three years is a long time.
Where will you go?
You're more than welcome
to stay with me,
though you'll have to put
up with Launch's cooking.
[LAUNCH]
I heard that!
I can tell ya like me, Tien.
Huh?
If you come to Roshi's island,
I'll be sure and take
care of you, but good!
I appreciate the offer.
Unfortunately, even
though Chiaotzu and I
went against Master Shen,
we were still members
of his school.
I don't think we're
allowed to switch...
We'll find a home. Somewhere.
[ROSHI]
As you wish.
Wait, if you come,
I promise not to cook.
[ROSHI] Tempting... But he's
made up his mind, Launch!
Well anyway, why don't we take
advantage of the local cuisine
and celebrate your
victory with a feast.
[ALL]
Sounds great!
One condition...
You allow me to treat.
[laughs]
Looks like you found a way to
spend half that zeni after all!
Wait!
What's the matter?
I forgot about my grandpa's
Dragon Ball and my Power Pole.
I left them both back at the
stadium. I'll be right back.
No, you stay here and have fun.
I'll go get 'em for you.
I know where they're at.
[GOKU] I should go. I'm the
one who forgot them.
[laughs] Don't be silly!
[GOKU]
Thanks, Krillin!
I'll be right back!
Okay!
Wait, Krillin!
[KRILLIN]
What is it?
Uh... See ya soon... Good luck.
[laughing]
[KRILLIN]
Save some for me!
[ROSHI]
Let's go.
[LAUNCH]
Ooh! I'm starvin'!
We've been waiting forever.
What's taking him so long?
I'm starving.
Even the pork looks tasty.
All those in favor, say dig in.
[ALL]
Dig in, dig in!
Goku, is there something
wrong with your food?
I'm not hungry.
I'll wait for Krillin.
[BULMA]
He probably got distracted
and lost track of time...
[BULMA]
Eat, Goku.
[GOKU]
Huh?
What's wrong with you?
[KRILLIN]
G-Goku!
Goku!
[LAUNCH]
Hey!
Goku!
What's up?!
Krillin!
[screams]
[GOKU]
Krillin!
No, no, Krillin.
I'm here! Wake up!
It was a monster!
I-It came through the window.
It took a little ball
and list of names
from the tournament.
It got away!
Krillin!
H-He's gone...
[GOKU]
He's gone.
It should've been me.
Please don't go.
[NARRATOR] What is the identity
of Krillin's killer,
and for what purpose
did it attack?
The plot thickens
next time, on Dragon Ball.