[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball,
the world's greatest
fighters vied
for the coveted title
of World Champion!
Krillin overcame the
foul smelling Bacterion!
Yamcha faught valiantly
against the old master
Jackie Chun, but to no avail!
Nam was perplexed
by the apparent fragileness
of Ranfan until he got the boot!
He came with closed
eyes and conquered!
[NARRATOR] Goku battled
the ruthless monster Giran
and managed to
tame the wild beast!
Then it was on to
the semi-finals
where Krillin and
Jackie fought it out.
Though Krillin had a
few tricks up his sleeve,
he was no match
for the wily veteran!
And now, Goku meets
Nam in the last semi-final bout!
[CROWD cheers]
Sausage on a stick,
hot peanuts, and cold sodas!
Get your hot sausage here.
Very tasty.
And cold sodas!
[ANNOUNCER]
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is the moment
you've all been waiting for!
[ANNOUNCER] The last semifinal
match is about to begin!
[ANNOUNCER] On this side
we have a man who has come
from a small village
and defied all the odds!
Nam!!
And over here we have
the amazingly young
and strong Goku!!
[ANNOUNCER] Which of
these men will go on
to fight Jackie Chun in the
finals for the World Title
and the grand prize of five
hundred-thousand zenni?
Hmm?! Five
hundred-thousand zenni!
[thinking] I must not forget! My
village! My people! My family!
[KID BROTHER]
Big brother I'm so thirsty...
[OLD MAN] Even the carrots
are too thirsty to survive...
The sun takes us all...
[NAM'S MOM]
Nam, the crops have failed
and there is no
money to buy water.
[thinking] My mother,
my brother, my people!
I will not forsake you!
I will win and return
with enough money
to buy all the water we need!
I promise!
Come on, Goku!
You're the one, kid!
Goku! You can do it,
you little wild man!
Alright! Here we go!
Let the match begin!
[GOKU] Hmm?!
[thinking] What should
my opening attack be?!
[thinking] Hey! I know!
I'll try the technique
that Jackie Chun
used to beat Krillin!
[chuckles]
Hm?!
Huh?!
Aaah!
Wow!
I can't believe he
saw that one coming!
I thought I had him!
Did you guys see
what Goku just did?!
He already
learned the technique
that you used to beat Krillin!
[CHUN] Mhmmm!
But Nam was able
to see him and react!
That's extraordinary as well!
[GOKU] Ow!
Here's my chance to end
this battle right now!
Whatd'ya think?!
Pretty handy, isn't it?! Yeah!
[NAM] I did not...
expect that...
[ANNOUNCER] Once again
Goku has saved himself
from defeat by using his tail!
Incredible!
I need an attack that
will throw him for a loop!
Huh?! He-he-hey!
I just thought of an attack
that I think you're
really going to like!
Huh?! What do you call it?!
Tornado!
What's... he doing?!
[NAM thinking]
The boy is spinning too fast!
No way to counter!
I can't even get near him!
Ah?! Oh no!
A-ahh!!
Huh?!
Uhhhhh! Oh, boy!
I think I'm going to puke!
[CROWD] Ohhhh!
I was certain
I had lost this match...
Fate has given me
another chance to win!
[GOKU] Uhhhh!
[NAM] That was a very
unpredictable attack
but it was the cause
of your own downfall.
[thinking] Now I must
end this battle,
but that tail is more
dangerous than a cobra!
There's only one way!!
The aerial attack!!
[ANNOUNCER] Look at him go!
Nam is way up there!
What a jump!
I'd say he's at
least four stories high!
Unbelievable!
I will strike like a
lightning bolt from the sky!
[NAM thinking] Young warrior!
I have no desire to harm you!
I do this only because it is
my duty to help my people!
Come on, kid!
You've got to move!
Goku!! Get up!
[GOKU] Uhh!
[NAM] Hmm?!
It's too late!
I must fulfill my destiny!
[GOKU] Uhhh!
[CROWD shocked gasps]
Forgive me!
[ANNOUNCER] Good heavens!
What a blow! Goku's out!
I think it's time
for you to count!
Huh? Oh! Right!
Oh, no! He's about
to start the countdown!
I'm afraid it's over anyway!
Nobody could get up
after being hit like that!
Aw, no Goku!
[ANNOUNCER] One!
[ANNOUNCER] Two!
[NAM] It is against
my way to harm any creature!
You will regain consciousness
in eight to ten days!
I think he's hurt pretty bad!
Please no!
[ANNOUNCER] Six!
[ANNOUNCER] Seven!
[ANNOUNCER] Eight!!
[ANNOUNCER] Nine!
[NAM] Hm?!
[ANNOUNCER] Te--Huh?!
[GOKU] Ahh, yaa!
Ow! That hurts!
Goku...
Alright!
That boy...
How does he do it?
My best attack... It failed!
[ANNOUNCER] If I hadn't
seen it with my own eyes,
I wouldn't believe it!
After being hit by a
pile-driving,
aerial attack from
four stories high,
Goku is back on his feet
and back in the match!!
Impossible!
No one can stay conscious
after my aerial attack!
Perhaps my execution
was in some way flawed...
That's it! It must be a fluke!
I can't afford any more errors!
My aim must be
perfect this time!
They're all counting on me!
Ahhh!
[ANNOUNCER] There he
goes again! Incredible!
Nam looks like
a rocket from here!
What a breathtaking ascent,
ladies and gentlemen!
He's going even higher
than the last time!
Ahhh! Well! Here goes!
[ANNOUNCER] And there goes Goku!
Now! I must not fail!
I must be bold and
sure, like thunder!
Huh?!
Oops! It looks
like I went too high!
He jumped even higher than me!
Wow! It's great up here!
It's a shame that
I have to beat ya!
Oh... no... you.. . don't!
[GOKU] It's nothing personal!
This is breath-taking!
They're actually fighting
each other in mid-air!
I've never seen
anything like this!
Goku and Nam are
conducting their match up
in the sky as if they had wings!
Look! They're coming
down! Right there!
[ANNOUNCER] Those aren't
ballistic missiles,
ladies and gentlemen!
Those are our semi-finalists!
Perfect! He's playing
right into my hands!
He'll land first,
and I'll hit him from above!
[GOKU] All right!
[ANNOUNCER] He won!
Nam is out of the ring!
Goku has won the match!
A twelve-year-old boy
has won the semi-finals
and is on his way to compete
for the World Championship!
Stupendous! I don't believe it!
This is fantastic!
No way, he did it!
Goku did it! Alright!
Yeah...! Ha ha...! Ha ha!
[CHUN thinking]
He's really good!
I'm starting to wonder
if I can beat him!
[ANNOUNCER]
What a fabulous match!
Alright!
Goku is now the
youngest fighter to make it
to the finals in the history
of the World Championships!
And what a match
that promises to be!
The young prodigy, Goku,
verses the seasoned
veteran, Jackie Chun!
[KRILLIN] Goku!
You did it! Wow! Alright!
Hey, kid!
Remember before you ever got
famous, I was your best buddy!
And I discovered him!
Me too!
Man!
Win or lose, Goku's already
made it in the history books!
I have to take
my hat off to the kid!
Yes! Indeed!
He's a remarkable young man!
To accomplish what
he's accomplished
at his age is
truly extraordinary!
[ANNOUNCER] Alright!
Nam is back on his feet!
Let's hear it for this
great semi-finalist!
Yeah! Yeah! What a fighter!
[GOKU and KRILLIN] Huh?!
[NAM] Good match!
[NAM] This is a match
that I will not soon forget!
It was an honor having
an opponent like you!
Thanks!
You're a great fighter!
[ANNOUNCER] This is
the most exciting tournament
I've ever seen at
the World Championships
and it's all boiled down
to two amazing fighters!
Jackie Chun and Goku!
And what a battle
this promises to be!
This final bout,
which will determine
the new Champion of the World,
will begin after
a brief intermission!
Are you okay?
Aren't you tired
from fighting with Nam?!
Naa, actually
I feel pretty good
except I could
use a little food!
I'm amazed at how
strong you've become, kid!
Yeah, I owe it all
to Master Roshi,
without his training,
I would have been knocked
out a long time ago!
Hey!
There's a good chance
that it's Master Roshi
that you're going to
be fighting in the final!
[GOKU] Huh?
[KRILLIN] Are you
still stuck on that?
[GOKU] Hm?
There is something
about him that reminds me
of Master Roshi,
but I don't know!
[YAMCHA] Sshhhh! Look!
[GOKU and KRILLIN]
Hmm?
[CHUN]
Oh, hello there! Nice day, huh?!
[whistles]
[CHUN] That was
a great match you fought!
Huh? Thanks!
Aren't you going
to hang around
and watch the final match?!
I'd like to but
I have some problems
that I need to address!
[thinking] I must return
to help find a solution!
But how can
I face my little brother
and the elders and my mother
without bringing back
any money for water?!
I failed!
[CHUN] Hey, Nam.
[NAM] Hm? Huh?
[CHUN] Here, catch!
[NAM] This is a Dyno-Cap,
isn't it?
[CHUN] Yes!
It's empty!
I think this is the kind
that's used just for storage!
Right! You can
fit vast quantities
of anything you
want in that capsule!
Food, building materials!
Nifty, huh?
A man could even transport
a small reservoir of water
single handedly
with that capsule!
Uhh...
How did you know
I'm in great need of water?
Minds are
just like books, Nam.
They're easy to
read if you know how.
[chuckles]
[NAM] What that
guy said is true!
You're Master Roshi!
Aren't you?!
[CHUN] Quiet!
Please! Shhh! There!
They can't find out my secret!
[GOKU] Yeah, I was fighting
Giran and it just grew back!
Isn't that great?!
[NAM] I don't understand!
Why are you keeping
your true identity secret?!
[CHUN]
You saw the three fighters
that I was trying to
get away from in there,
well, two of them have been
my students for some time!
The two little ones are mine!
The bald one's
name is Krillin!
The other one--the one going
to the finals--his name is Goku!
He's something else!
Goku has tremendous talent!
But I don't have
to tell you that!
You faught him yourself!
[NAM] Yes! He seems unbeatable!
[CHUN]
Yes! That's why I came!
To see to it that he doesn't
win this tournament!
You see, Goku and
Krillin are just boys!
All they're really
interested in is having fun!
To them the study of
Martial Arts is an amazing game!
They live to get stronger
and better at it in the hopes
that one day they'll be
able to hang with the best!
They have no idea
that they're already
at the pinnacle of the sport!
I'm afraid that if they knew,
they would lose interest!
Because if you're on the top,
then there's nothing
left to shoot for!
But if they think
there are guys out
there that are stronger
than they are like
Jackie Chun, for instance
Then they'll continue
to give it everything they have!
Training like the wild
animals they really are!
Totally carefree
and uninhibited!
Without a trace of ego!
So, Nam,
I don't want Goku and Krillin
to know how great
they really are!
That's why I came
to beat the pants off 'em!
What about your hair?!
How do you get it to stay
on your head like that?!
Believe it or not,
I glued it on!
It's working fine,
but it's itching like
there's no tomorrow!
The sacrifices
I make! Sheesh!
Thank you!
I'm honored that you
trusted me with your secret!
Please, take this
back if you would!
I appreciate it,
but I'm afraid that I won't
have occasion to use it!
[CHUN] Hmm?
You see, I was
counting on the prize money!
Without that, I have
no means to buy any water!
No money, huh?!
That's a shame!
But come with me,
I have something to show you!
[NAM] Huh?
[CHUN] Notice anything
unusual about that well?!
[NAM] There are
no money changers!
Right!
You see, in this region water's
not scarce it's abundant!
You can take all you want!
It's as free as the
air that we breathe!
Wha...?! It's free?!
[ANNOUNCER] May I have
your attention, please!
Will Jackie Chun and Goku
please report to the arena!
The final match
is about to begin!
Ahh, well! Here goes!
See ya later, Nam!
I'll never forget what you
did for me, Master Roshi!
Oops! I mean Jackie Chun!
I'll never forget it! Ever!
[CHUN] It was nothing!
Forget about it!
[CHUN] Wait a second!
I was wondering
if you'd be interested
in doing me a favor?!
Alright!
Here we go, folks!
The final bout
of this year's World
Martial Arts Championships!
And I can't think of
a more exciting match-up
than the one we have today!
[ANNOUNCER] Help me get
these fighters out here,
ladies and gentlemen!
Let's hear it for Goku,
he youngest finalist
in the history of the
World Championships,
and the amazing Jackie Chun!
[GOKU] I'm ready!
Good luck, Goku!
You're going to win this match!
I know! Thanks!
Don't let your pupil
beat you, Master Roshi!
Look!
How many times
do I have to tell you?
I'm not Roshi! Are you
deaf or something?!
Do you think
Master Roshi would have
a student in the finals and
not even show up to watch him?!
No! Of course not!
Wait! Isn't that him?
If I'm not mistaken,
that's Master Roshi in
the audience right there!
[YAMCHA] Yeah right!
Huh?! No way!
It's him! I don't believe it!
Gosh!
I guess I owe you an
apology, Mister Chun!
[CHUN] Actually,
you owe me several apologies!
[AANOUNCER]
One more time, folks!
Let's get these
fighters out here!
[ANNOUNCER] Hopefully,
Goku's not taking a nap!
[YAMCHA] Guys! I was wrong!
Master Chun isn't Jackie Roshi!
Yamcha?
Did someone
hit you on the head?!
[YAMCHA] Hmm?
[KRILLIN] Well I knew it!
Master Roshi doesn't get
involved in tournaments anymore!
He's a living legend!
[GOKU] Yeah, besides,
Master Roshi would
never use orange perfume,
I think he enjoys
smelling like the sea!
Goodbye!
[ANNOUNCER]
I think I see them coming!
Yes! Here they are!
The two finalists
fighting for the title
of World Champion,
Jackie Chun and Goku!
Well! Goku!
You seem to be in high spirits!
Yeah!
I'm thrilled about
fighting the mighty Jackie!
It's going to be a lot of fun!
[ROSHI thinking] Look at him!
So innocent and carefree!
And yet, so powerful and wild!
I'm going to have to
be serious for this one!
Only a fool would
take Goku lightly!
[ANNOUNCER]
I don't know about you, folks,
but I can't wait to see
how this one turns out!
Both of these fighters
have completely dominated
their opponents
throughout this tournament!
And now the inevitable clash
has arrived between Goku,
the young prodigy
of the Martial Arts,
and Jackie Chun,
whose experience is even
more deadly than his punch!
Here we go!
[NARRATOR] Join us next time,
for another exciting
episode of Dragon Ball.