[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball,
the last quarterfinal match
of the World Martial Arts
Championship began,
as Goku faced the monster Giran!
[NARRATOR]
Goku took the offensive,
and for a moment it
seemed the young warrior
would win with relative ease...
[NARRATOR] That is, until
Giran's Merry-go-round Gum
put Goku in a bind...!
The monster tried
to give Goku the toss,
but our hero was saved--
first, by the Flying
Nimbus, and next...
...by his tail?!
[NARRATOR] Yes!
Goku's tail suddenly grew back!
And along with it, his
strength grew, as well--
so much so that Giran decided
to raise the white flag...
Goku advances!
Now, the semi-finals begin!
[ANNOUNCER] No one's
ever thrown in the towel
in the quarterfinals!
This is unprecedented
in the history
of the World Championships!
[ANNOUNCER] And that's how
it all shakes down, folks!
Krillin will fight
Jackie Chun and Goku
will fight Nam
in the semi-finals!
But what's really
amazing is the age
and size of these
two semifinalists!
Take a look at these guys!
It's phenomenal!
And they're both
wearing the same outfits!
What's that mean? Stick around!
We're about to find out!
I can't believe that
Goku's tail grew back, you guys!
This could be a serious problem!
No kidding!
Imagine the damage he would do
if he transformed in the
middle of a city like this!
If that kid goes ape,
the whole planet's doomed!
Uhh... You've got a
tail on your back...
[GOKU] Mhmmm!
That's where tails grow, silly!
They'd look funny anywhere else!
Let me congratulate you both!
You two have such talent!
And at such a tender age!
It doesn't seem
possible, does it?!
So, Krillin I heard that
you're thirteen years old!
Goku, how old are you, son?!
Hm? What's this...?
Is it for me?
[KRILLIN] It's a mic, you dummy.
[GOKU] A mike-you?
[KRILLIN] A mic!
As in microphone!
You're supposed to talk into it!
I see! A joke!
What funny little guys! Yes!
Don't embarrass me like this...!
Just answer the question,
knucklehead! Hello?!
Question?!
Uhh... Oh! You want
to know how old I am!
Okay! Well, let's see!
Eight, nine, ten, eleven!
I know! I'm twelve!
What?! Wait a second, Goku...
I thought you were
older than me...
Yeah...! I know!
I used to think that
I was older than you, too!
But then Launch taught me
how to count past
ten with my fingers!
And I figured out that twelve
comes before thirteen!
Twelve, huh?!
I always thought he was a lot
closer to my age than that...!
Well It just goes to show you--
you think you know somebody...
So you're twelve!
And you have a tail!
That's pretty weird, man
Well, I guess we're both a
little bit strange, aren't we!
[KRILLIN] Hey, I'm older than
you so you better shut up!
[ANNOUNCER] Now, now, boys!
You should both be
very proud of yourselves!
Goku I must say,
it is a bit unusual
that you have a tail!
How'd that come about?!
See, told ya...!
That tail isn't exactly
normal, you know...!
In fact, I've never heard
of a person who had one!
Is it real?
Well how
'bout I just show you!
There! See!
Goku, are you crazy?!
Hm?! What's the matter!
Pull your pants up!
Uh, boys!
Let's stick to answering
the questions verbally!
Shall we?!
Oh, brother...
I guess Goku still
hasn't learned
the meaning of the word
'modesty', has he?
How embarrassing!
Now then!
You obviously
know each other, boys!
And you're dressed the same!
So you must train together!
Can you tell us about your
training and your master?!
We do regular stuff!
Like farming!
And delivering milk!
And since Master Roshi
trains us we wear big shells!
Did you say...
...Master... Roshi??
Whoa, man! No wonder!
Yeah, that explains everything!
Wow! This is
really unbelievable!
You mean... that you boys
are pupils of Master Roshi?!
Yep, first he told us that he
wasn't accepting any new pupils.
But he took us.
[ANNOUNCER] This is astounding!
Master Roshi is the
greatest Martial Arts expert
in the world!
What a treat!
Having two of his
students here today!
The Turtle Hermit's
fighting style is legendary...
And as old as he must be,
it's amazing he's still alive!
[YAMCHA] Hm?
[YAMCHA] Excuse me,
have you seen Master Roshi?!
[CHUN] 'Fraid not!
Is that so?!
Have you looked
in the mirror lately!
What?!
[YAMCHA] Look, there's
only one man your age
who could make it
into the semi-finals!
And when you showed up,
he disappeared!
You're him! You're Master Roshi!
So that's what you think.
Well, then,
I'll tell you the truth.
I am...
...Jackie Chun!
[ANNOUNCER] Krillin, your match
is coming up in just a minute!
What do you think of your
opponent, Jackie Chun?!
Well, he's old!
But he's strong!
Yes, I see.
You're a pupil of Master Roshi's
so is this going to be
an easy match for you?!
Easy?
Well, maybe But I haven't
had an easy match yet!
You can deny it all you want to!
But hey! What about your
weakness for the ladies?!
And your mustache and beard?!
And that silly laugh of yours?
If you won't admit it,
I'll prove it!
Huh?!
[ANNOUNCER] Will Jackie Chun
please report to the arena!
Well, that's me!
Yeah...
He's Master Roshi
all right, I'm sure of it!
Alright! Here he is!
Good! Now! Let's get
the semifinals underway!
Let the match...
[CHUN] Hey! Aren't
you going to interview me?!
Aren't you?
Oh. Uh, well there's no time.
[CHUN] Hm? Nonsense!
Give me that!
Hi!! I'm Jackie!!
Uh-one, uh-two!
Uh, one, two, three, four!
Ba, da, dada! Dedee, dee, dee!
How many of you ladies
out there love me?!!
Alright!!
Uh, bom, bom, bom, bom!
Ah, dee, dee, dee!
I know you ladies love me,
because I'm so studly, he-hee!
Uh, huh! Alright!
I know I'm causing a reaction!
But that's cause
I'm the main attraction!
Come on now, ladies,
can't you see--
that a Martial Artist's life
is the only life for meeeee?!
Hey!
Uh-one, two, three, four!
A bom, bom, bom!
A dee, dee, dee!
A Martial Artist's life is the
only life for me!
I've been a jumpin'
and a runnin' and that's no lie!
If I stay in one place
then I'm gonna die!
Oh yeah!
[BOTH] A bom, bom, bom!
A dee, dee, dee!
A Martial Artist's life
is the only life for me!
I said: A Martial Artist's
life is the only life for me!
[CHUN] Yeah! Peace
[GOKU] Yeah!!
[CHUN]
Here ya go! Thanks!
[ANNOUNCER] Well-uhh!
Now that the entertainment's
finished. Let the match begin!
[KRILLIN]
Ready or not! Here I come!
[CHUN] You've got some
power behind those punches!
Not too bad!
[CHUN]
Now, let's check your speed...
Huh?!
Uhh! That... That hit...!
I didn't... even see it!
What's wrong with
Krillin, guys?!
He's sitting down!
I don't know!
How can I beat
him if I can't see him?!
[GOKU] Hey, Krillin! Get up!
Look! He's fast!
Yeah?
So what? You are too!
Besides, I saw it!
You did?
Yeah! You can, too!
You've had the
same training as me!
[KRILLIN thinking]
Goku's right!
If he was able
to see that punch,
I should be able to see it, too!
Well, look who's back!
That was a slow punch!
Allow me to show you
one of my fast ones!
[KRILLIN thinking]
Either he's bluffing...
...or I'm a goner!
[KRILLIN] Uh, oh!
[CHUN] Haa!!
Whoa!
Ahh!
[CHUN] Mmm!
[KRILLIN] Hm!
Way to go!
I knew you could do it, Krillin!
Yeah!
[CHUN]
Mmm! Very impressive!
[ANNOUNCER]
I don't know about you folks,
but they moved so fast
that it was all
just a blur to me!
Now, that's what I call speed!
It's rare that I find a fighter
who can follow my movements!
It comes natural!
I was trained by the best!
Master Roshi is my teacher!
Let's see if your
master's training
can get you
through this next one!
Whenever you're ready!
Ah...
[ANNOUNCER]
Krillin's down!
I'm not sure what
just transpired!
But whatever it was,
it didn't agree with Krillin!
[ANNOUNCER] The judge is
signaling for a countdown!
This could be it!
Yikes! Ten seconds!
I don't think he can get up!
He's not moving!
[ANNOUNCER] One!!
[GOKU] Krillin!
[ANNOUNCER] Two!!
[GOKU] Come on!
You've got to get up!
You can do it!
[ANNOUNCER] Three!!
[GOKU] Krillin! Stand up!!
[ANNOUNCER] Four!!
[GOKU] Yeah! Great!
Come on, Krillin,
you're doing it!
He won't make it...
[ANNOUNCER] Six!!
[ANNOUNCER] Seven!!
[CHUN] Hm?!
[ANNOUNCER] Eight!!
[GOKU] Stand up!!
[ANNOUNCER] Nine!
[ANNOUNCER] Ten!
Wow!! He did it!
[ANNOUNCER] Krillin's up!
This match is still underway!
Yay!! Krillin! Alright!
[CHUN chuckles]
[CHUN thinking] Well,
I've got to hand it to the boy.
He's a lot stronger
than I was at his age...
[CHUN] Hmm?
Uhh... excuse me, Jackie!
But would you mind?
It's just that...
You're movements are so fast,
that nobody could
see what happened!
Would you mind
explaining it to us!
[CHUN]
Hm? Sure! Why not?! Yes!
The fans paid good
money for their tickets, so...
...they have a right to know!
Great! Thank you
very much, Jackie!
First I attacked!
Just like this! Hawww!!
That's when Krillin
countered with his own attack!
[ANNOUNCER]
Mm, hm! Mm, hm! I see!
Then, I attempted a kick!
But I saw the kick coming...
...so I dodged!
Then, I countered by going
for his face with a punch...
Just like this here!
Yuk! He spit at me!
I was so surprised that
I pulled my punch back!
While he was busy
dodging my spit,
I came at him with
a hard left! Like this!
[CHUN]
Then, he countered my spit
by blowing his nose at me!
It was then I realized
that this encounter
could get really ugly! Mm!
It looked like it was
going to be germ warfare!
But the Bacterion fight
got me ready for that! Yep!
I knew that!
I had to change tactics
but I was stumped!
Then it came!!
Rock, paper, scissors! Come on!
What?! No way!!
Oh, alright! Yeah! I know!
I should have stuck to
the germ warfare but I didn't!
[BOTH]
One Two! Three!
[KRILLIN] Uhh!
Scissors cuts paper! Ha!
[KRILLIN] Sure!
He won that round!
But I told him that
we should at least
do the best out
of three to decide!
Fooled you! Sucker!
The game was
only a distraction!
Hey?
Huh?!
Come over here and
give me a lift, would ya?!
U-Uhh, sure! A lift? Why not?!
Alright, then! Heave ho!
See! I jumped up
and kicked him! Haa!
Alright, let's go!
Take me over that way!
[ANNOUNCER] Y-Yes, sir!
Let's see now!
Oh, yeah! Like this!
Mm! Mm! Taw!!
[ANNOUNCER] E-Excuse me, Jackie!
Didn't you land
right about here?!
[CHUN] Mm, hm! Yes!
I landed perfectly,
just like this!
Hey, how about a
little help over here!
[ANNOUNCER] Right!
Alright!
Just pick me up
and I'll show you
what happened
after he kicked me!
[ANNOUNCER]
Mm! Yes! Okay! There!
Yes, that's it!
Except here I started
turning a flip!
Flip?
But I'm not sure I can do that!
[KRILLIN] What are you doing?!
Are you crazy?!
[ANNOUNCER]
Sorry, I didn't mean it!
My head hurt so bad that
I couldn't see straight,
but I still landed!
Yeah, that's the spot!
I landed right there!
But I couldn't keep it
together and I passed out!
Mm? Oh, yes!
We saw that part!
You mean all this happened
just in that brief instant?
[BOTH] Mmhmm!
Can you believe
the incredible talents
of these fighters?!
Yes! This is a
match for the ages...!
Sorry for interrupting
your fight, gentlemen!
Please continue!!
[KRILLIN] Uh, oh!
[KRILLIN] I'm not
so sure I can beat
this old geezer using
conventional means!
[KRILLIN thinking]
But I know his weakness!
I saw how he went
ga-ga over Ranfan!
It's time to use
my secret weapon!
[CHUN] Oh!
Heh heh heh! Yeahah!
Oh!! I've been had!
I did it!!
Kids! You just
can't trust them nowadays!
Wow! I don't believe it!
If I'm right, Krillin just
defeated Master Roshi!
Oh, my! There goes Jackie!
I hope he sends a postcard!
Unless he has wings,
it looks like Krillin's
heading to the finals!
Darn it!
I didn't think he'd
pull a stunt like that
Well! Here goes nothing!
Ka... me...
ha... me... haa!!
Ohhh!!
Haahh?!
Huh?!
[CROWD surprised noises]
Thank you very much!
Bu... I... Wh...
How did you do that?!
[PUAR] Th-That's...
not possible...! Is it?
[GOKU] Hey! Jackie!
Was that a Kamehameha Wave?
You betcha!
But I thought only
Master Roshi and Goku...
Oh, man!
[ANNOUNCER]
This is quite unexpected!
We just witnessed a
Kamehameha Wave, folks!
It was thought that
only Master Roshi
was capable of executing
this technique,
but apparently Jackie Chun
has mastered it as well!
[YAMCHA thinking]
Yes! I knew it!
That proves that he's Roshi!
You might be able to fool them,
but not me, old man!
Goku! What am I gonna do now?!
Beat him!
You can do it, Krillin!
So nice having
optimistic friends!
Too bad.
That was a great
trick you played on me.
If I was a normal man,
you would've won.
Tough luck there, kid.
[KRILLIN] Oh well...
I guess there's only
one thing left for me to do!
Foolish...
He's attacking wildly now...
Glad to see you're
still using your head...!
Good work!
You like that...?
Well how 'bout this!!
Krillin! Look out!
He's coming up behind you!
[ANNOUNCER]
Down! Krillin's down again!
One, two, three...
[CHUN] Count to
a thousand if you'd like.
He won't be getting
up for a while.
[ANNOUNCER] This could be it,
folks! He's not moving!
Wow... That was a...
great move...
Krillin attacked his after-image
while he snuck up from behind!
[ANNOUNCER] Eight!
I don't believe it!
[ANNOUNCER]
Ten! The match is over!
Jackie Chun is
advancing to the finals!
[GOKU] Hey, don't worry!
You tried! Right?!
He sure did. He faught well.
Yeah, he did extremely well!
Considering that his opponent
was the great Master Roshi!
[CHUN] Hm?!
Huh?
What do you mean?!
He's Jackie Chun!
Why do you keep saying that?!
Yamcha! What are
you talking about?!
You know that
Master Roshi's bald!
That does seem to pose
a problem, doesn't it?!
Unless it's a wig!
Wait! What are you doing?!
Eeeh! Let go!
It's real!
Well, of course it's real!
I get it now!
You've had hair
the whole time...!
You've just been covering
it up with a bald cap!
Well, how do we know
that you're not Master Roshi
wearing an ugly, rubber mask?
Okay!
You can say what
you want, but I know!
You're him!
You know...
There is kind of
a resemblance there!
[GOKU] Hm?
[sniffs]
He doesn't smell
like Master Roshi!
He kind of smells like oranges!
Eegads!
What's that?! Perfume?!
Oh, I've been
using this for years!
It's Cologne d'Orange!
Ladies love it!
Listen, buster!
You're pushing my limits!
I am who I am!
Got it?! Now back off!
[ANNOUNCER] May I have
your attention, please?
The second semi-final
match is about to begin!
Will Goku and Nam please
report to the arena!
Alright! It's our turn!
Awesome! Goku!
One more win and
you're in the finals!
You can do it!
Right! I'll do my best!
[CHUN] Hm?
That guy sure is serious.
[YAMCHA] Hm?
[ANNOUNCER]
Ladies and gentlemen,
our last semi-final bout
features Nam versus Goku!
Only one of these fighters
will advance to the finals!
It's sure to be
an amazing match!
[NARRATOR] Join us next time
for another exciting
episode of Dragon Ball!