[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
After meeting with
the mysterious Korin,
Goku learned that the only way
to defeat King Piccolo
was to find and drink
the dangerous
Ultra Divine Water.
[GOKU] I will go and find the
Divine Water and bring it back.
I guess this is where
I'll be going home. See ya.
[NARRATOR] Yajirobi decides to
take Goku as far as the mouth
of the Cave of Darkness
before going home.
But, the best laid plans of
mice and martial artists
seldom go as planned.
[DARKNESS cackles]
What a boring place.
[GOKU]
No Ultra Divine Water here.
Not over here, either.
[YAJIROBI] You really
think you have a chance
against King Piccolo?
Man, you're dumb.
[GOKU]
I have to try, don't I?
Didn't you say he killed
some of your friends?
Mm. My best friend,
Krillin and Master Roshi.
So why don't you just be
happy you're still alive...
...and get on with living.
[GOKU]
Huh?
This... is where
we say goodbye.
[GOKU]
Goodbye!
[GOKY] Oh! Tell Master
Korin that I'll find
the Ultra Divine Water
no matter what! Goodbye!
Goodbye, yourself, fool.
[GOKU]
Hm?
[footsteps tapping]
Master Roshi?
Yes. In the flesh, Goku.
[laughs]
Master...! You're still alive!
Beauty never dies. Heh.
So, what brings you here?
Oh... I forgot!
[laughs]
[ROSHI chuckles]
[GOKU] I'm looking for
the Ultra Divine Water
so I can defeat Piccolo.
Have you seen it here,
Master Roshi?
I have seen something.
[GOKU]
Really?!
Ha...! I can always
count on you!
Follow me.
[GOKU]
All right!
[YAJIROBI grunting]
[YAJIROBI thinking]
Stupid Goku! Leaves me
in the middle of nowhere
with no food or anything...
[YAJIROBI grunting]
[YAJIROBI thinking]
Scary monster. Looks delicious.
[YAJIROBI]
Come back, lunch!
Wait...
Come on, I wanna dip
ya in some gravy!
You're moving so fast!
[GOKU]
Ah, whoa!
Hey, wait for me!
[yelps]
[GOKU] How did you--?
I don't-- What in the--?
Come inside.
[ALL laughing]
[BULMA]
It's Goku!
[laughing continues]
[DARKNESS panting]
[ALL]
Cheers!
[YAMCHA] It's great to
see you again, Goku.
It's strange that
you're all here.
Master Roshi convinced us
that this is the best place
to hide from King Piccolo.
[PUAR] Oh, Goku, you just
have to stay with us here.
Um... Well, I still have
to find the Divine Water
to defeat Piccolo.
Uh?
Piccolo?
[ALL laugh]
That is the dumbest
thing I have ever heard.
[TURTLE]
Yeah, dumb!
[ROSHI] Only a fool
would take on Piccolo.
Plus, if you stay here, you'll
have perpetual existence.
What does that mean?
Goku, it means you'll
live forever.
Um...
Oh, hey, I have
got a great idea.
Why don't we stay down
here until Piccolo dies?
I mean, it has got
to happen sometime.
Yes, now that is perfect!
Can you imagine
how much training
we could do, Goku?
And when we finally leave here,
I will challenge you
at the World Martial
Arts Tournament.
That will be great, yes.
Wow! That sounds awesome!
I can not wait!
Yamcha... my money is on Goku!
[laughs]
--[ALL laugh]
--[GOKU] Uh... Uh...
What is the matter, Goku?
I think you all should
be ashamed of yourselves.
[ALL]
Huh?
Why is that?
You're all acting like
a bunch of cowards.
"Cowards"? Well, you have
got some nerve, pal!
Yes, how can you say such
things to your friends, Goku?
Well?
--Well?
All right, I've had enough!
[ROSHI]
Hmm...
[door creaks]
[ROSHI] Stop right there,
Goku... Since you insist
on seeking the water...
...then I will have to kill you!
[gasps]
[ROSHI grunting]
[GOKU gasping]
[grunts]
[yelps]
[yells]
[GOKU yelping]
[grunting, yelping]
Give up, Goku! You don't
stand a chance!
Never!
The Ultra Divine Water
is sacred!
It is not meant for humans!
Your presence defiles it!
You must leave this
holy place or die!
None of this is real
and you're not Roshi!
[ROSHI]
I'll show you real!
[GOKU groans]
[yelps]
[groans]
--[pants]
--[ROSHI] Real enough for you?
[ROSHI chuckles]
Real or not, I've had enough!
Hm?
[ROSHI yelps]
[GOKU grunting]
[growls]
[chuckles]
[YAJIROBI]
Gotcha!
You're coming with me, tasty!
[YAJIROBI laughs, yelps]
[screams]
[growls]
[YAJIROBI, GOKU groan]
[YAJIROBI yelping]
[GOKU grunting]
No! Not now!
[cackles]
[whimpering]
[GOKU] Please... let him go.
Your fight is with me!
[cackles]
[ROSHI]
Why don't you "let him go"?
[GOKU screams]
[yelps]
Nobody let go!
[ROSHI]
Save yourself, Goku.
Drop him and you
stand a chance.
Keep holding him,
and you both die.
Hey, Goku, who's your friend?
[GOKU grunts]
I will not let go!
[groans]
Happy landings.
That's it!
[grunting]
[ROSHI grunts]
[GOKU groans]
[yelps]
[groaning]
Come on! Stop wiggling
around up there!
[ROSHI]
Fool, just... let go.
[groans] I will not let go!
[growling]
[screams]
[yelps, groans]
I will not let go!
Goku, be still!
[GOKU grunting]
[ROSHI]
Hmm...
[GOKU grunting]
Eh?
[yelps]
Hold... together!
[YAJIROBI] This is your fault,
Goku! You killed me!
A-And on an empty stomach, too!
I'm too young to die!
I'm so tired of falling!
Look at that!
[yelps]
[BOTH whimpering]
Show your true self, you coward!
Come on! Who are you?
[DARKNESS] I am Darkness.
You have proven yourself worthy.
What is that...? See it?
[GOKU]
Is this the Ultra Divine Water?
[DARKNESS] The sacred liquid
is very dangerous...
One must be both mentally
and physically strong
to survive it...
For the unsuited...
it means certain death.
[GOKU, YAJIROBI gasp]
[whispering] Come on,
Goku... Let's leave!
But it will make
me stronger, right?
[DARKNESS]
It is uncertain.
[gasps]
[DARKNESS] The Ultra Divine
Water takes advantage
of special powers within you...
If you have no power,
nothing will change...
Only those with the special
power become stronger...
...the others will die.
Say... uh... Darkness...
How many people have
drank this water stuff?
[DARKNESS]
Thirteen.
And, uh, how many
people survived?
Uh, like six...?
Or... Or three?
[DARKNESS]
None survived.
[gasps]
None survived?
Hey, that's not fair...!
What kind of a chance
does that give us?
If no one survives it,
then it's just poison!
And there's nothing
special about
dying from poison, is there?!
I'll do it!
[grunts]
Are you nuts, Goku? I mean,
it's one thing to play the hero,
but drinking this stuff
is just plain suicide!
Then, I'll risk it.
Goku, please, I'm begging you.
For some dumb reason, you always
wanna do the right thing...
But I'm telling you, there is
nothing in that pot but poison.
You drink that stuff,
and you will die.
We'll see.
Let me taste it.
Just a little bit.
[yelps, gags]
I'm telling you...
that's poison!
Look Yajirobe, there is
nothing else that we can do!
[yelps]
[gulps]
[screams]
[YAJIROBI gasping]
[groaning]
Ah! Goku! Don't die!
[GOKU screams]
Ok, people, let's get
this in one.
[OOLONG laughs]
How can you be laughing
at a time like this?
Hey, this is my
favorite cartoon!
[OOLONG laughs]
[OOLONG]
Hey!
"Citizens, I come today
bearing important news.
This is a great,
joyous time of change."
Look, it's King Furry.
[KING] "This change will affect
us all in, uh, wonderful ways."
"I have proudly given my throne
over to the great King Piccolo."
[BULMA, YAMCHA, OOLONG]
What?!
Citizens! It's all lies!
King Piccolo is not
to be trusted!
Please, we must find a way to
stop him before it's too late!
[KING gagging]
Stick to the script, Furry.
[KING groans]
Show time. Ha, ha.
People of Earth, I am King
Piccolo and I am your new ruler.
[PICCOLO cackles]
You who bow down to me...
--[OOLONG, BULMA, YAMCHA gasp]
--Listen to that old windbag!
[PICCOLO]
In fact, you will find
that I will encourage your
freedom... every freedom.
By now, you all know
how powerful I am.
But what you may not know,
is what a loving king I can be.
So, my first decree will go
out to the ones I love the most.
And of course, that's
the criminal element.
We will begin by
eradicating the police,
those wicked people who would
stomp on your freedom
and put you in chains for
merely seeking the life
that you desire!
Theft, violence, murder...
Nothing will be illegal
in this grand new world.
Come out from the shadows!
Your new King
understands your pain.
[DOG]
All hail King Piccolo!
[PICCOLO] This is your time...
This is our time!
Order is dead and chaos reigns,
thus says King Piccolo!
This guy's a madman!
Uh... I don't know.
It doesn't sound that bad.
--[YAMCHA] Hm?
--[BULMA] Uh...
[GOKU screaming]
Come on, Goku,
you can fight it...
Just hang in there! Don't die!
[screaming continues]
[roars]
[gasps]
That... great power...
Could it be?
Do we dare even hope Goku
could be the one to survive
the trial of the
Ultra Divine Water?
[KORIN]
Could Goku really be the one?
G-Goku!
[NARRATOR] Has Goku tapped
into some special power,
or is this the end
of our brave hero?
Find out on the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball!