[BULMA screams]
[KRILLIN]
It's not fair!
[BULMA]
I'm too beautiful to die!
[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
[GOKU]
Ha!
[NARRATOR] Though our
heroes were unable to claim
the pirate's treasure, they did
not leave empty handed,
thanks to the diamond Bulma
grabbed during her escape.
[BULMA]
I got a souvenir.
[NARRATOR] The hefty jewel
created quite a stir
amongst the others,
especially Master Roshi.
[ROSHI] Are you insinuating
that I don't make
sound financial decisions?!
Yes.
[ROSHI]
Why you no good--!
[NARRATOR]
However, Launch's alter ego
proved that diamonds are
a bad-girl's best friend.
Hand it over before someone...
...gets hurt.
[ALL yelp]
Thanks.
[NARRATOR]
Just as the gang was recovering
from Launch's surprise attack,
General Blue decided
to drop by for a visit...
And he didn't come to
borrow a cup of sugar.
[ROSHI] Nooooo! That
diamond is mine! I want it!
Bring it back! It's not fair!
Bring me my diamond back!
[BLUE]
There's no need to get so upset.
Life is too short. Well,
at least yours is anyway.
[ROSHI]
What a beautiful sight!
Like little, white, soft cotton
balls stuck in the sky.
I'd like to pluck one down
and just bury my face in it!
I lost my dream
somewhere between
the ocean and the
bottom of this glass.
That's pretty deep.
But is that you talking
or just the fruit-punch?
[ROSHI]
She loves me not...
She loves me. She loves me not.
Goku, are you ready
for some time off?
Sure. After I find
Grandpa's four-star ball.
Suit yourself.
Me, I'm going home.
No more adventures...
Oh, which reminds me.
Can I borrow your airplane?
[ROSHI gasps]
[ROSHI]
Sure. If you don't mind
retrieving my diamond
from Launch first.
That's impossible!
I can't get the diamond back.
I need transportation.
We could always work out
another arrangement.
Forget about it!
[BLUE cackles]
[BLUE] Those amateurs
don't stand a chance
against my enhanced
mental capabilities.
[BLUE grunting]
[BLUE]
Live!
[BLUE grunts]
[GOKU sniffs] Hey, do you
smell something funny?
Sorry.
Oh yeah, I forgot.
You don't have a nose.
[KRILLIN growls]
I can take you to the shore,
but it might take me a while.
[BULMA growls] Great, I've been
reduced to traveling by turtle!
Oh, Master Roshi, will you keep
one more Dragon Ball for me?
Certainly.
I think we're
forgetting something...
Anyone holding these balls is a
target for the Red Ribbon Army.
I am a master warrior.
Any attack on me would be folly.
[ROSHI yelps]
[BULMA, KRILLIN scream]
[GOKU yelping]
[TURTLE yelps]
[BULMA, KRILLIN yelping]
[ROSHI yelping]
[BULMA yelps]
Master Roshi,
we're being attacked!
What are these things?!
I can't move!
[BLUE cackles]
[GOKU grunting]
I'll get us out!
[GOKU groans]
This is heavy...
[ROSHI]
Goku! What are you doing?!
[TURTLE gasps]
[GOKU gasps]
It's you!
[BULMA whimpers]
You can't be here!
You're dead!
[BLUE cackles]
Who are you?
[BLUE cackles] Someone you
should fear, old man.
[ROSHI]
You're not scary. You're sick.
[BLUE] On the contrary,
I've never felt better.
Ah, what a beautiful sight.
The Dragon Ball, like your
fate, is now in my hands.
[BULMA, KRILLIN screaming]
[BLUE sighs]
[BLUE] Now why do I get
the feeling there's something
you're not telling me?
Oh yes, the other Dragon Balls.
You do have more tucked
away somewhere, don't you?
Where are they?
Hm...
Ah! Yes!
[GOKU grunting]
No!
Hm. Mm-hm... Mm-hm!
Here.
[BLUE] Hm. Oh! Perfect.
They're even gift-wrapped.
[GOKU growling]
You maniac! Why in
the world are you
so interested in collecting
the Dragon Balls anyway?!
Who can say?
Commander Red's
purpose is his own.
I've simply been ordered
to retrieve them.
[BLUE]
But you needn't concern yourself
with any of this, my dear.
After all, what is there
really to worry about
when you're dead?
[BLUE cackles]
[BLUE] The explosive is set
to detonate in five minutes.
[BULMA yelps]
[BLUE] That should allow
plenty of time for you
to try and save
yourselves but...
...not enough to succeed.
Hm.
Hey wait! You don't
want to kill us!
I can help you find
the other Dragon Balls!
[KRILLIN]
Bulma! Have you lost your mind?
I don't need the help
of a little girl. Please!
How 'bout an old man?
Master Roshi!
Bye... Wish I could stick around
to watch but I'm late
to collect my reward.
[BLUE cackles]
[KRILLIN, BULMA whimpering]
[ticking]
[TURTLE yelps]
[KRILLIN whimpering]
[BULMA] Help me! Help me! Help!
[GOKU grunting]
Three minutes!
[ticking]
[KRILLIN]
[BULMA] This is it!
We're never gonna make it!
Master Roshi,
please do something!
You can save us, right?!
Well, there...
...is a technique
I haven't tried yet.
[KRILLIN]
You can do it, Master.
You've got two minutes.
[ticking]
[ROSHI grunting]
[ROSHI farts]
[ALL groan]
[BULMA grunts]
[ROSHI giggles]
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU gasps]
Hey, what's up in the sky?
It's Launch! That girl's got
some timing, doesn't she!
[ALL shouting]
[LAUNCH] Oh! I didn't know
we were having a party!
[ALL groaning]
[LAUNCH] Hey! You'll never
believe what I found.
Isn't it beautiful?
What do you think?
Hello! Earth to Launch!
There's a bomb!
We're gonna die!
Is this a new game?
Where'd you get the blue rope?
[BULMA]
Yeah, it's called Stay Alive!
Quick, grab the box and
throw it out of the house!
Why is there a clock
on the floor?
That's no clock, it's a
high-explosive bomb!
[LAUNCH grunting]
Oh no...
This house was spic
and span when I left
and I don't appreciate
things being left out.
Launch, I'm serious!
This is no joke!
Launch, there's no time.
Just untie me. Fast!
The rope is so tight.
There's this new invention.
It's called a knife!
[BULMA] We've got less than
a minute to live. No pressure.
[LAUNCH] This knife's a bit
dull but it's all I've got.
Faster!
We've only got ten seconds!
[GOKU] If you can just
get my tail loose!
[BULMA, ROSHI gasping]
Ah! Thank you!
[GOKU grunts]
[ALL grunting]
[GOKU laughs]
Nimbus!
[BULMA gasps]
Where are you going?
Be careful.
Don't worry. I'm going to
get the Dragon Balls back!
Go catch that twerp, Goku!
Make Roshi proud!
Of all the mean,
dirty tricks to pull.
I can't believe it. And
right here at lunch time!
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU gasps]
There's something up ahead.
It's gotta be him!
[BLUE cackles]
These Dragon Balls
will bare proof
of my genius to Commander Red
once and for all!
[beeping]
Who is this?
[BLUE]
You...!
But that's impossible!
How are you still alive!
[BLUE gasps]
Faster!
[BLUE growls]
Of all of the--
Go away!
[BLUE] I don't know
how you escaped,
but I won't make
the same mistake twice.
Let's see how fast
you can fly, little boy.
[GOKU growls]
[BLUE cackles]
Ah, what's the matter?
Having trouble keeping up?!
You're not getting
away that easy!
Faster, Nimbus, faster!
[GOKU yells]
[BLUE gasps]
[GOKU] Nyaaaaah!
[BLUE yelps]
Give me my Dragon Balls!
[BLUE growls]
Lousy kid!
[BLUE screams]
[GOKU grunting]
[BLUE yells]
The controls!
[GOKU yelps]
Oh no! The circuits
are all fried!
I'll have to make an
emergency landing!
[BLUE]
No! Where am I?
This isn't one of the
Red Ribbon Army territories!
[BLUE yelps]
[BLUE]
This doesn't make any sense!
I've never seen any place like
this on our navigational charts!
I'm not letting you
out of my sight!
[SUN laughs]
Penguin village time,
12 o'clock.
[ARALE giggling]
[PANDA, CROC]
Huh?
[ARALE giggling]
[GREEN, PINK, BLUE giggle]
Ooh...
[ARALE giggling]
[GATCHAN ONE,
GATCHAN TWO giggle]
[NEFISHIKI, RAT cheering]
[ARALE giggling]
Wee! Wee!
[SEMBEI laughs]
Hey there! Sembei Norimaki here!
Live for your enjoyment!
[AKANE laughs]
Huh?
Ah, spring break here I come!
So, have you guys thought about
what you're going
to do during vacation?
I'm looking forward to
practicing my kung fu.
I'm going to be productive
and try to get a part
time job so that I can
feed all of my cats.
You know what I'm
gonna do, Akane?
All of my homework!
Gee, sounds like a blast.
[SEMBEI laughing]
What are you doing?
And who are you
supposed to be talking to?
Huh? Why everyone, my dear girl.
It's been a long time since
I appeared on television.
It's nice to be seen, see?
Okay, Sembei,
time to get a grip...
The only person seeing
you should be a doctor,
as often as possible.
[SEMBEI groans]
You're standing in my light.
[aircraft humming]
[ALL] Huh?
What's that noise?
Okay then!
We'll be right back
after these messages!
[ALL giggling]
Oh?
What in the world is that?
[BOTH]
So fast!
Wow, what a pretty cloud.
This is impossible!
How can he keep up with
me riding on a cloud?!
[GOKU laughs]
Caught you!
So, you ready
to give up now?
[BLUE gasps]
[GOKU grunts] All right, you
asked for it! Power Pole extend!
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU gasps]
[ARALE]
Look! There they are again.
His persistence is incredible...
Ah. Perhaps running from
him isn't the answer.
[GOKU]
Maybe he's finally giving up.
[BLUE cackles]
That's close enough.
[GOKU growls]
You'll get a blast out of this!
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU screams]
No force in the world
can save you now!
[GOKU yelling]
[BLUE cackles]
[BLUE gasps]
[BLUE screaming]
Whoa...
[ALL gasp]
Bad man, but great fireworks!
[GOKU grunts]
[ALL gasp]
[GOKU]
Uh...
[ARALE] Hi!
[GATCHANS cheering]
Huh? Oh, hi!
[NARRATOR] It appears Goku
has made some new friends...
But who are they?
And what is this strange
land he has fallen upon?
There is more to
reveal on the next
fun-filled episode
of Dragon Ball!