[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball,
the World Martial Arts
Tournament advanced
to its final match,
with the young Goku fighting
against Jackie Chun,
who is actually
Goku's own teacher,
Master Roshi, in disguise!
[NARRATOR] The weathered
old man unleashed
a handful of crazy techniques,
but Goku matched him
with every step,
treating the entire fight
like a big round of play time!
[NARRATOR] This didn't
make the old man very happy...
He attacked Goku with
even more amazing moves!
[NARRATOR] His strategy didn't
work and Goku kept smiling.
Now, Jackie Chun
has mysteriously
announced his victory
with one more move...
[NARRATOR] As the earth's
most experienced fighter,
the old man clearly
has a huge arsenal
of techniques to choose from,
so what will this next
unbeatable move be?
Today on Dragon Ball.
You... are... so sleeeepy...
What'd you say...?
You... are... soooo tired...
[KRILLIN]
Huh??
What's... Happening?
When... you hear me sing...
Your eyelids will drop...
That's weird...
Your... a...sleep... boy...
Sleep...
Huh?!
He dozed off!
The "Sleepy-Boy" Technique.
Heh heh heh.
I win!
Hold on...
That was hypnotism...
You're supposed to use
martial arts in this tournament!
Ohhhh... Come on...
The "Sleepy Boy" is a
martial arts classic...!
Now just count to ten, will 'ya!
But, just think
of how the fans
are going to react if we end
the tournament this way...!
Kind of anticlimactic, you know?
Who cares
about the fans...!
It's the kid's own darn fault
for falling for
such a thing anyway.
Now start counting
or I'll "Sleepy Boy" you!
Oh gosh!
And one... And two...
[CROWD murmurs]
[ANNOUNCER] Um... Three...
He's going to sleep
his chance away!
Hey snap out of it Goku!
He's just an old kook!
[ANNOUNCER] Four...
They can yell all they want.
Goku won't wake up
until I tell him to myself.
[ANNOUNCER] Five!
Come on Goku...!
Just wake up!
You can sleep
when we get home!
[ANNOUNCER] Six!
[JACKIE CHUN thinking]
Finally over...
Fighting in disguise
might lack the glam,
but it was worth it...
[ANNOUNCER] Seven!
[JACKIE CHUN] With Goku thinking
there's someone out there
who can beat him, he'll keep
training to be stronger...
Just in case...
[ANNOUNCER] Eight!
Don't be a loser Goku!!
Oh, wait!
Goku...! Your dinner is ready!
Dinner?
[GOKU] Dinner? Where's Dinner?
I want dinner!
Is there some left for me?
[GOKU] Hello...? Dinner...?
Where's the dinner...!
Dinner? Hello?
[JACKIE CHUN]
That's impossible...!
That's the ticket Goku!
Just give us all a heart attack!
That was close!
Way to go Bulma...!
What a brain!
Hey, now, where's this
dinner I'm hearing about?
Don't be a goofball!
We're fighting, remember?
Goku...
We'll go and eat a
big dinner as soon as
you beat that
smelly Jackie Chun!
Okay!
[chuckles]
Then, I better hurry
and get this over with!
Why you...!
Disrespectful little rookie...!
Just try and finish this!
[GOKU] Janken... Rock!!
[GOKU] Scissors!
[GOKU] Paper!
Hey... that's funny...
My Janken attack
moves didn't work!
Of course not kid...
I'm an old pro...
at the Janken fighting pose!
Really...?
So did you know my grandpa?
Because it seems
like you know
every one of his
fighting moves...
Okay...
Let's play it one more time.
Fine...
But you know you're
gonna lose again!
Jan...
...Ken...
...Paper!!!
[ANNOUNCER] Oh my...!
Jackie Chun has gone down!
All right!!!
[ANNOUNCER] One!
[cheering]
Oh he got him!
Did you see it?
I love the way
winning feels!
Don't you, Oolong?!
[ANNOUNCER] Three...!
Four...! Five...!
[ANNOUNCER] Oh! He might get
up...! Six...!
Clever little runt...
Saying paper but
attacking with rock...
[ANNOUNCER] Seven!
[ANNOUNCER] He made it...!
Jackie Chun is
back in the fight!
That last nose blow
took a lot out of him,
but he's still swinging!
Gee...
Bulma, don't you think I should
take you out to dinner first?
What are you talking
about you pig?
Hey you were the one
clinging to me now...!
I thought it was special!
Oh save it for your dreams!
So here we are, folks!
Knee-deep into the
tournament's final match!
On the one hand is
Jackie Chun's experience
and superior technique...
And on the other,
the youthful energy of Goku!
[ANNOUNCER] The sun is sinking,
but this amazing fight
has yet to be settled!
Can the winner
prevail before night fall?!
Goku...! Stay strong!
You're so close kid!
Yeah! I can
practically smell it!
Is that so...?
[JACKIE CHUN thinking]
I have no choice...
but to use the technique...
[JACKIE CHUN thinking]
It's dangerous, but...
well... maybe
it won't kill him...
Now...
let's have some fun
before I go eat dinner...!
I'm sorry young man...
but you... have lost the fight.
What...? I have...?
I thought we weren't
done fighting yet!
Don't listen Goku...!
That geezer's just bluffing
cause he knows he can't
beat you any other way!
[growls] Hey!
Enough with the heckling!
I'll try to make it quick.
Huh?
I really don't like
using this technique...
It's an emergency attack
when nothing else works...
This is the second
time I've used it...
The first time was
on the great warrior Gohan,
your grandfather.
Wha...? So you
really did know him?
That's how you
know all his moves!
[ANNOUNCER] I don't know
if you could hear, folks.
Jackie Chun has just made
a strange declaration...!
According to him,
he's already won the fight!
[ANNOUNCER] But wait a second!
That's my call...!
What's he up to???
What is that?
It's... massive!
[ANNOUNCER]
Incredible...! Jackie Chun
is a walking encyclopedia
of fighting techniques...!
And from the looks of it,
this latest concoction
is a finishing move...!
[ANNOUNCER]
It certainly looks powerful,
but what we all must
be wondering is...
what exactly does it do?
[gasps]
Ah!
Huh?
Lightning Flash...
...Surprise Attack!!!
Oh!!
[GOKU screams]
Oh... He's gonna kill him!
[ANNOUNCER] Amazing...!
What a fight!
[KRILLIN]
What's happening Yamcha?!
[YAMCHA] I've heard
about this move!
It changes all the
energy in the body...
...into twenty thousand
volts of electricity!
[ANNOUNCER] Young Goku really
seems to be suffering...!
Is there any hope for him?!
Say that you give up...!
You'll die if you
don't say it quick!
No...! Not yet...!
I'm... still fighting!
Darn you...!
It's no time to be stubborn
when your life is at stake!
Ahhhhh!!!!
Goku!!
Just give up!
I'm... not... quitting...!
Please...! Don't be a fool!
Goku...
I... can't watch!
Oh... Throw in the towel Goku!
Give up, kid! Give up!
You did just fine!
But it's over now...
Please listen to us!
It's not worth it!
Okay...
I... guess I'll... say... it...
Yes...
Don't be ashamed Goku...
Not even Gohan
withstood it for this long...
I... give...
Goku!!
Goku!
Now... Goku!
Say that it's over!
Waaaaaahhh!!
What the--??
Oh no...! It's happening!
It's the full moon!
Goku... What are you doing?!
[roars]
[ANNOUNCER] Folks, I...
I have no idea what to say...!
That young Goku has transformed
himself into a gigantic ape...!
I've never even heard
of this fighting technique!
It's not a technique, pal!
It's the worst thing
that could possibly happen!
And... it's scary!
[roars]
But that was my
Lightning Flash Surprise...!
It's unbeatable!
[YAMCHA] Watch out!
[JACKIE CHUN]
He can't do that...!
I... I promise he can't!
[panicked screams]
[roars]
Ahh!
Oh...! Run away...!
I would get out of here
too but unfortunately...
I have to be referee...
How horrid!!!
Yeah...?!
You think you've got
it bad mister...?!
I can't run outside this ring
or I'll be disqualified!
[KRILLIN] Goku!
Come on buddy...!
You're taking this fight a bit
too far, don't you think?!
There's no use
trying to talk to him!
When Goku changes like that,
he loses all sense of himself!
He's just a big ape
with a sweet tooth
for tearing people's limbs off!
[KRILLIN] Oh... is that all?
Well then...
I'm afraid there's only one
way to take care of this...
Aaaaahh!
I can't let you
hurt people!
So are there any ways
to de-ape him?
I only know of one...
We have to cut off his tail...!
Hey, Puar!!!
I'm gonna try
to get behind him
and grab onto his tail...!
You change into scissors
and cut it off like last time!
I'll try!
Hey look...!
The old man seems to have
a game plan of his own!
Okay beast...!
Kamehameha, Maximum Power!
Oh no...!
Jackie thinks he has
to kill Goku to stop him!
Oh, you have to
stop him Yamcha...!
Tell him about Goku's tail!
[YAMCHA] Wait Jackie!
Ka...!!!
Me...!!!
No!!!
Ha...!!!
Wait!!!
Me...!!!
No!!!!
Ha!!!!!
Aaaa!
[screams]
[KRILLIN] G-Goku!!!
Hey... Where is he?
But he's just a kid...!
[sobs]
He can't be...!
You can't be...!
You can't be gone...! Goku!!!!!
Goku...
I'm sorry...
I... only did what
had to be done...
[KRILLIN] Goku!!!
Don't leave me!
[NARRATOR] To save the crowds
from the rampaging monster,
Jackie Chun has fired his
strongest Kamehameha Wave...!
And so, the young fighter
has been quieted by his own
disguised teacher...
[NARRATOR] But can it be true?
Is this really the end of Goku?
Find out next time
on Dragon Ball.
[KRILLIN] Goku!!!