[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball...
Goku and ChiChi
were taken by surprise
when her father's castle
went up in flames.
In a desperate attempt
to save his kingdom,
the Ox King sent Goku to
find the magical Bansho fan.
Fortuneteller Baba revealed
the instrument's location
was linked to an octagon
and pointed the pair
to a remote island, home of a
magical bird called Fire-Eater.
What they found was an egg.
The Fire-Eater
caught the attention
of another interested party:
none other than the King
of Schemes, Emperor Pilaf.
His plan to sell the egg
for profit was smashed
when its owner made
a surprise return.
Goku and ChiChi were
stunned to learn
the bird could not help them,
but watched in awe as its
offspring successfully hatched.
Both mother and chick
escaped the fiery volcano
and set out for
their new life together.
Meanwhile, Goku headed north
as his search for
the Bansho fan continued.
What a gorgeous mountain!
The way that old man
was talking,
I thought we were
headed for trouble.
[gasps]
Ah!
[BOTH screaming]
[CHICHI]
What's going on? Goku!
[CHICHI screams]
[WOMAN humming]
[GOKU, CHICHI screaming]
[WOMAN whimpering]
[WOMAN]
Oh... Oh... Oh.
[BOTH shivering]
It's... cold!
Who... are you?
My-My name is Go-ku!
Chi... Chi.
Fine. My friends
call me Octagon.
Oh. You look more oval to me.
Uh, did you say Octagon?
Baba's clue!
Yeah. That means the
Bansho fan must be here.
Oh!
We found it!
Yes!
[OCTAGON]
Foreigners.
I assume the two of you
tried to climb
Mt. Frappe together?
[GOKU] That's right.
Why, did we do something wrong?
If you took that girl with you,
you certainly did.
Women have been forbidden
to climb Mt. Frappe
since before I can remember.
[CHICHI]
Huh?
I don't understand.
[growls]
If a female gets near that
mountain, things turn ugly.
Oh?
You mean that horrible
snowstorm was because of me?
I provoked the mountain?
[OCTAGON]
Mhm-hmm.
[CHICHI sighs]
[OCTAGON]
Why should that bother you?
What business do you young
ones have with the mountain?
We were told that's where
we might find the Bansho Fan.
Ah?
The Bansho fan?
Yes. It can
extinguish any flame.
That's a tall claim. A fan?
You mean you've
never heard of it?
[OCTAGON] Yeah, here's your
word for the day: reality.
But how could you not know
about the fan? You're Octagon.
[OCTAGON]
Well...
Since Fortuneteller Baba was so
convinced the Bansho fan was
near an octagon, we naturally
assumed that meant you.
[laughs]
I said Octopus.
Sorry, all gums!
[GOKU, CHICHI groan]
[GOKU] If the fan isn't
on the mountain...
[CHICHI]
Where could it be?
Hmm. Cheer up. There's more than
one way to put out a fire.
It's true. You're not likely
to find a fan on that mountain,
but there is something that
will work just as well.
[GOKU]
What is it?
[CHICHI]
Please, tell us.
The snow on the mountain...
[OCTAGON] It is cold enough
to freeze even fire.
It's no fan, but...
Snow that can freeze fire?
Goku, if we can gather
enough and take it with us...
Right! Wait here. It'll
be faster if I go alone.
I'll be thinking about you.
Oh.
Ma'am, do you mind if I
borrow this for a while?
Sure.
[CHICHI]
Goku!
[laughs]
Nimbus!
Don't worry, I'll be back soon!
--[CHICHI] Good luck!
--[GOKU] Let's go!
[CHICHI laughing]
That young man is
your future husband?
Huh?
Yes. Isn't he just fabulous?
It takes more than...
smiles to make a marriage work.
Huh? Oh, I know what you mean.
I need to learn how to cook.
[OCTAGON]
Do you want to be a good wife?
Well, I certainly don't
wanna be a bad one!
[OCTAGON]
Good. Let's get started.
I have much to teach you.
[cackles]
Emperor Pilaf,
we are within range.
You may begin your scan
of the mountain.
[PILAF]
Hmm. There's no sign of them.
[SHU] What's the big deal
about this Bansho fan, anyway?
Given the effort they're
expending to find it,
this Bansho fan may be even more
valuable than the Dragon Balls!
That would be great.
Every time we go after
the Dragon Balls,
something bad happens.
[PILAF]
Hmm.
[ALL screaming]
The weather's affecting
our guidance system.
Everything is frozen!
[grunting]
[ALL screaming]
[GOKU thinking]
I hope the Ox King
can hold on awhile longer.
[PILAF]
Put your backs into it!
The only thing that will
keep us thawed is that ship!
[PILAF sneezes]
[shivering]
We have to salvage that ship. My
skin dries out in cold weather!
[GOKU]
Hey, guys.
[PILAF]
Uh?
What are you doing here?
[PILAF screams]
[PILAF]
Impossible!
--[MAI screams]
--[SHU] Emperor Pilaf!
--[PILAF screaming]
--[GOKU] What's wrong?
[PILAF screaming]
[PILAF] Now look what you've
done! It's all your fault!
--[GOKU] What?
--[MAI] Emperor, duck!
[screaming]
Oh, no!
[PILAF]
Huh?
Uh?
[BOTH gasping]
[gasping]
The flame, it's frozen!
Woohoo. It works!
The old lady was right!
We don't need the fan!
[OCTAGON] Lesson one: a clean
house makes for a happy home.
And you've got a lot of
happiness to clean here!
A cleaner's best
weapon is water.
Go through the woods,
pass two valleys,
and you'll come upon a lake.
There you'll find all
the water you need.
There's no water in the house?
No.
[PILAF laughing]
[PILAF]
A reunion. I'm so happy!
You didn't seem happy
inside the volcano.
Ah?
You didn't catch me at my best.
But here, I'm in my element.
Now, give me the Bansho fan!
Mai, Shu, attack!
[SHU]
Uh, we tried that before, sire.
[MAI] Do you have a plan
to defeat him, Emperor?
[PILAF]
No.
[MAI, SHU] What! Then how do
you expect us to win?
I haven't found the Bansho fan.
That's why I'm here.
That's too bad. Bye!
[yells]
[ALL]
Huh?
[ALL screaming]
[GOKU]
What's wrong?
Once more, attack!
[grunting]
Hey, you dropped this!
[ALL screaming]
[grunting]
Heh.
Just kidding!
[PILAF, MAI, SHU whimpering]
You look upset. Can I
help you with something?
Yes, you can.
Wait there a second.
[screaming]
Hold on.
[PILAF]
You trouble maker!
One of your friends
is a woman, right?
[PILAF] You moron!
This is all your fault!
That's why the storm is blowing.
[PILAF]
Why you! I--
Huh?
--[SHU] Huh?
--[PILAF]What did you say?
For some reason, the mountain
doesn't like women.
When one enters,
it causes a storm.
What? But that's ridiculous!
[sneezes]
Mai, come here.
[MAI]
Yes, sire?
[PILAF] I want you
to leave the mountain!
You can't be serious.
I said get off, right now!
[MAI screams]
Look! The sun!
[GOKU thinking]
Now, I can return!
[OX KING grunting]
[OX KING yelling]
[OX KING yells]
ChiChi, Goku! I could use
that Bansho fan right now!
Hurry!
[grunting]
[coughs]
[CHICHI groaning]
[screams]
[CHICHI thinking] I know
that old woman means well,
but this is ridiculous!
--[screams]
--[glass shattering]
[GOKU laughing]
[GOKU] This is easy! I should
have enough snow in no time!
[PILAF] Finally, we have him
in our sights! Ready?
Don't miss this time!
What if it freezes
up again, sire?
You fool! The storm
is over. Fire!
[GOKU]
Surprise!
[PILAF, SHU scream]
[GOKU] I didn't know
you guys were still here.
[PILAF]
Destroy him!
Emperor Pilaf, how could
you do that to me?
Mai! It's good to have you back!
It's time for plan R.
Comrades, on my mark, run!
[MAI, SHU yelling]
Huh?
Ma'am, I've brought
you some tea. Huh?
[OCTAGON]
Thank you.
[CHICHI] I had no idea
you kept bees in here.
[OCTAGON] Yes. Did you finish
cleaning the entire house?
Yes, I have.
Everything's spotless.
You get out of here.
Shoo! Shoo!
Oh.
That was fast. I'm impressed.
Now you can sweep the yard.
[CHICHI]
I didn't know you had a yard.
[OCTAGON] From this tree,
to the end of the woods.
All of it? The forest!
Get busy. Here.
The dustpan is in the back.
[GOKU thinking]
Hold on ChiChi. I'm on my way!
[CHICHI groaning]
[CHICHI]
This must be the dustpan.
Funny, it feels lighter.
I'd better hurry
before it melts!
[OCTAGON]
Oh! Wow! Ahh!
[OCTAGON thinking]
It's spotless!
Oh?
[OCTAGON]
My dishes!
[OCTAGON whimpering, screaming]
[CHICHI screams]
Huh?
[CHICHI screaming]
[grunting]
[screams]
What's all the--
This is some dustpan!
Wait a minute!
This isn't a dustpan.
I've seen it before!
Ma'am, this is it!
I found the Bansho fan!
[OCTAGON groaning]
Excuse me? What, that old thing?
I found it on the shore
a long time ago.
You silly old woman.
Whether you knew it or not,
you saved the Bansho fan!
Now I can rescue my father
and his kingdom! Oh!
I don't understand.
How did it melt so quickly?
Boy, ChiChi is gonna
be disappointed.
[CHICHI]
Goku!
Hmm?
Come quick, I've got
the Bansho fan!
[CHICHI] Hurry, let's get
back to the castle!
[GOKU]
All right!
[GOKU laughing]
That's fantastic!
Good work, ChiChi!
[SHU]
I'll take that!
[BOTH]
Hey!
--[GOKU growls]
--Who are you?
[laughing]
The person who always...
gets the last laugh.
[laughing]
Hey, give it!
[SHU] I'll return it, in pieces!
How many do you want?
[growls]
[laughing]
Emperor, the fan is
old and ordinary.
What value could it
possibly have?
You, female--
Yeah, what?
Um... tell me, why is this
pan so special to you?
[CHICHI]
It's a fan.
[PILAF] That's what
I said! What's it do?
[CHICHI]
Most people wave it.
[PILAF] Of course.
You heard her. Wave the fan.
Right!
[ALL screaming]
[whimpering]
[SHU yells]
The fan works.
Isn't it magnificent?
Yeah, it is. Let's go.
Thank you for all
you've given us.
Not so fast!
Take this with you.
[GOKU, CHICHI]
Huh?
It's a bottle.
Filled with honey from
my bees. A rare type...
Uh?
[OCTAGON] They build
octagon-shaped honeycombs.
Octagon, or octopus?
Consider it a gift. You did
a good job cleaning my house.
I'd use it sparingly, dear.
There are no refills.
It may just come in handy.
I will treasure it. I will.
Stay sweet.
[laughs]
[PILAF] Get off the mountain
and go find some help!
One of us has to be brave,
and it's not going to be me!
ChiChi! Goku!
I won't give up!
Nothing's going to prevent me
from seeing my daughter
wear this dress!
[yells]
Papa! We found the Bansho fan!
Hold on, we're coming!
[CROWD cheering]
Where have you been? You've
missed all the excitement!
[GOKU] Ox King! You'd better
grab hold of something sturdy.
Otherwise, you'll be blown away!
[OX KING]
I'm ready!
Do it now!
Okay!
[yelling]
[CROWD cheering]
It worked!
We did it!
It's over!
Goku, the flames
are still rising!
Fine! If it's a
fight you want,
I won't stop swinging until
every last flame is put out!
[yelling]
[GOKU grunting]
It's raining!
This will put the
fire out for sure!
[NARRATOR]
The villagers watch in horror
as the flames continue to rise.
[OX KING]
ChiChi!
Papa!
[NARRATOR]
With the Bansho fan doing little
against the mysterious fire,
will Goku be able to save
the Ox King's kingdom
before it burns to the ground?
Find out on the next sizzling
episode of Dragon Ball!