[wolves howl]
[thunder crashing]
[GOKU grunts]
[NARRATOR] Sometimes
you can feel as though
the weight of the world
is on your shoulders...
In Goku's case, it's true.
[NARRATOR] The pain he endures
is minimal compared
to the satisfaction he gets from
achieving yet another goal
of his self-imposed
life training;
a journey recommended by
Master Roshi in which his pupil
foregoes the more
traditional training routine
in favor of random,
real-world experiences:
All leading him to the next
World Martial Arts Tournament.
[GOKU grunts, whimpers]
[yells]
Looks like my tail
grew back just in time,
and stronger, too!
It won't break off again!
[GOKU chuckles, gasps]
[yells]
[groans]
I'm tired... and hungry.
Ah! There goes another one...
Huh...?
[chuckles]
[OLD WOMAN gasps]
Here.
[OLD WOMAN] Oh,
that was so kind. Thank you.
Sure. Is this place your home?
Yes.
Great.
Can you tell me if someone
really strong lives around here?
Someone strong?
Yes. I want to fight someone
who can challenge my skills.
There is one person
I can think of right away.
His name is Chin.
He lives in the city.
Master Chin? Great!
One last thing,
where is the city?
[OLD WOMAN] Follow this path
along the river.
It will lead you right to it.
I see. Thank you
for all your help.
[GOKU] Oohh...
So this is the city.
Boy, there sure are
a lot of people around.
[MAN] A fight! A fight!
This transgression
is inexcusable.
What's inexcusable
is your charge
that my son stole
your wallet, Dragon.
It's laughable!
Yeah, laughable!
Liar.
I know your gymnasium is
hurting for business, Chin,
but if you needed a handout,
you should have just asked.
Come on, kid,
you're going to the police.
[CHIN] Back!
Keep pushing!
Shokin, my son, get to safety.
Yes, father.
Now...
[PUPIL B yells]
[PUPIL A yells]
Aahh...
[BOTH] Huh?
[grunting]
[CROWD gasping]
[chuckles]
He's strong!
So... Care to join
your pupils, Dragon?
[DRAGON whimpers]
[CHIN grunts]
[coughs]
Father!
Aw, what's the matter?
Is the mighty Chin feeling
a bit under the weather?
Well, the Doctor is in,
and the prescription is pain!
Ah! That's my wallet!
Give it back!
Did you steal it from me?!
No, sir. It was just
lying on the ground.
Uh-huh. I told you
I didn't steal your wallet!
This proves nothing, boy!
You probably threw it down
out of fear once you stole it!
[GOKU] Excuse me...
Is it possible that you dropped
your own wallet by mistake?
My grandfather always told me
it wasn't nice to doubt people.
Well, I'm not a nice guy!
Especially to thieving little
brats who steal my wallet!
Uh. That's not a nice thing
for you to say.
I said be quiet!
[BOTH gasp]
[DRAGON growls]
[VILLAGERS gasping]
[GOKU chuckles]
You!
[growls]
[yells]
[MAN] Stop!
Ah! Brother...
Hello.
I apologize, sir, for my
brother's rude behavior.
Please forgive him.
Fine.
May I extend the same
sentiment to you?
Uh, yeah, sure.
He didn't do anything to me.
We're leaving.
Fool! Sick, old Chin
will fall tomorrow at the match,
in front of the king,
by my hand and no one else's!
Do you understand?!
Yes, sorry, Brother.
That was a brave thing you did,
standing up to Dragon.
Thanks... I'll bet
he's a tough opponent to defeat.
Says you. My father
could have beaten him easily.
Huh...
Mister Chin, it's a
pleasure to meet you.
Actually, you're the reason
I came to this village.
Um... Who are you and
what do you want?
My name is Goku...
An old lady told me you were
the strongest around.
I was hoping we could fight.
A runt like you could
never defeat my father...
He's not worth your time, Dad.
You don't have to fight him.
[CHIN] Hmm... Alright, boy.
I'll fight one match.
Yes! Thank you!
But Father!
Don't, Father. You can't.
You're not healthy.
Mind your tongue.
I don't need
the counsel of a child.
Ugh!
[CHIN] Are you ready?
Uh-huh!
[CHIN thinking] Hm. This child
may possess more skill
than I thought.
[BOTH grunt]
[CHIN yells]
[CHIN grunts, coughs]
Ah! Father!
[coughs]
Father, are you all right?!
You overdid it.
You need to rest, Father!
Why is he coughing like that?
Ngh! Why do you think?!
Because of you!
The old lady was right.
You are strong.
And a very good fighter.
[CHIN laughs]
You're not so bad yourself.
What is the name
of that trick you used?
The Phantom Star Technique.
My dad created it.
I never heard of that before.
Like its namesake, the
technique uses an energy
to project an image
that doesn't exist.
I never knew that.
Shokin... Patience.
You are not ready to
wield the Phantom Star.
Perhaps one day, but not now.
Goku has the discipline and
training to use it correctly.
I'm not sure what you said,
but it sounds a lot
like my Afterimage--
Technique...
Not many can use it.
That you can shows that
you have extraordinary skill.
Goku, I'm sorry.
The truth is I have
a very bad condition...
I've tried to maintain my health
for the King's Match but...
For a king?
Yes, sort of.
Each year, a fight is held
in the presence of our king...
Whoever wins the match
will be bestowed the title of
Master of Martial Arts.
I see. Who is your opponent?
Is he strong?
[CHIN] Sky Dragon.
You met him in town today.
He runs the Panther-Fang school
along with his oversized
brother, Rising Dragon.
Sky is a gifted fighter and
extremely powerful,
but he doesn't like competition.
Mine is the only other
martial arts school in town.
When it became popular, Sky
nearly ran me out of business
by persuading, threatening
most of my students
to join him instead.
If I defeat Sky and gain the
title of Master of Martial Arts,
there's a good chance I can
revive my Chin-Star School.
--[coughs]
--Ah! Father!
You need medicine!
Where do you find medicine?
I'll go get some
if you think it will help.
There's a place in the city--
[CHIN] No!
Uhh...
[CHIN] Rising Dragon
is a vengeful man.
If he sees you, there's no
telling what he'll do!
I'll be okay. He's just one man.
All the same, I'd rather
avoid any confrontation
with the Panther-Fang School...
The King doesn't like opponents
fighting before the match.
I understand...
If I run into anyone
from the school,
I won't start a fight.
Drinks! Bring me more drinks!
[SKY] Calm down, brother.
Drink your soup...
Your manners leave much
to be desired. More tea.
Yes, right away.
Hey! Kid, come here!
Watch out! You almost hit me!
[DRAGON laughs]
Next time I won't miss.
Let's finish what you started.
No, I can't fight you.
Suit yourself, thief.
Sky, remember that
punching bag
you were going to get me
for my birthday?
Don't bother. I just found one.
Let me pound him, Brother.
Happy birthday.
[DRAGON chuckles]
Sorry, I don't have
time for this.
I'm in a hurry.
[DRAGON grunts]
[yells]
Cut it out!
[grunting]
[DRAGON yells]
Huh?!
[laughs]
No one makes a fool of me!
[yells]
[chuckles] Bye-bye!
Somehow I don't think that's
what my brother had in mind.
Try me.
[blows landing,
GOKU grunting]
[GOKU] You're fast!
Where's that
carefree laughter now?
Come on, show me
some effort this time.
[GOKU grunts]
[blows landing,
GOKU grunting]
How pathetic. You're obviously
one of Chin's students.
[SKY laughs]
--[SKY] Brother, let's go.
--That wans't fun.
But at least I kept my promise.
I got Chin's medicine
and I didn't start that fight.
He's late. I knew
we couldn't trust him.
Hi. I'm back.
'Bout time. I was beginning
to worry. What happened?
I got the medicine.
I hope it's enough.
[grunting,
blows landing]
[SKY] Who's next?
What's the matter?
Am I still too great a challenge
for you weaklings?
Alright, I won't use
my legs either.
Let's go, anybody!
[yells]
[screams]
There is no doubt...
Tomorrow, I will destroy Chin
in front of everyone.
[SHOKIN grunts]
Sky Dragon isn't so tough.
Everyone thinks I'm just a kid,
but I know how to
take him down.
One day I will.
[SHOKIN grunts]
[sighs]
[yawns]
[SHOKIN] What are you
saying, father? [CHIN]
Sometimes knowing
when not to fight
is just as important. I know
it is difficult for you, Son,
but please try to understand.
I cannot fight
in this condition.
I must therefore
forfeit the match.
But the King will declare
Sky Dragon the Master.
I am well aware.
If there was anything I could do
to change that, I would.
You can... allow me
to fight in your place.
No!
Why don't you have
faith in me, father?
I'm ready. I know
I can beat him.
My word is final... No!
Please, father, I know--
Shokin! I said no!
[coughs]
I didn't mean to upset you!
[GOKU] How about me?
I'll fight against
Sky Dragon.
But Goku--
This has nothing to do with you,
so just stay out of it, okay?!
Look, I'm not trying
to interfere,
but I have experience fighting.
That's why I'm here.
Sky Dragon is a
deadly adversary.
I appreciate your concern,
but I wouldn't volunteer
if I didn't think I could win.
Besides, I'm in training
to compete
against the world's
toughest fighters...
I'll win.
Very well.
[GOKU] Thank you.
He's no bigger than me.
Sky is a devious fighter
who will do anything to win.
He has never lost a match.
I understand.
[SHOKIN] How can you trust a
stranger over your own son?!
If anyone's going to
replace you, it should be me!
I will not debate
with you, Shokin...
Your arrogance blinds you
to Goku's superior strength.
Where do you think
you're going?
To fix breakfast. I think
I have enough skill to do that.
Hey, how's it going?
Breakfast ready? I'm starving!
Just a minute. I'm almost done.
Ahhh... It smells delicious!
[slurps]
Ahh... Tastes great!
[SHOKIN thinking
One way or another,
I'm going to
be in that match.
[GOKU chuckles]
[gong crash]
[CROWD murmuring]
Wow! The King sure
has a big house.
I wonder how many rooms it has?
[GOKU laughs]
This is great!
--Look at that!
--So, Goku, how are you feeling?
Everything okay?
Sure. I'm fine. Why do you ask?
It's nothing.
[GOKU laughs]
[SHOKIN thinking] Oh no...
The match is about to start!
Is there something
troubling you, Shokin?
You don't seem like yourself.
No, sir.
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen,
to the King's Match.
This year the Panther-Fang
School vs. the Chin-Star School.
Presiding over the ceremonies,
King Wan-Tan and Queen Harumaki.
Please address your attention
to the center stage.
[KING laughs]
Start the match!
And now, the competitor
from both schools
will enter the arena
at this time!
[SHOKIN thinking] Oh no!
From the Panther-Fang
School, Sky Dragon!
[CROWD cheers]
Sky Dragon!
You're the champ!
Representing the
Chin-Star School, Goku!
What?! Who?
Hello, Mr. Dragon. Good luck.
Nonsense!
I signed up to fight Chin,
not some upstart brat!
According to rule sixty-three,
sub-paragraph thirty-seven A,
each team is allowed
one representative
of their choosing.
Either fight this boy
or forfeit the match.
[SKY] Very well...
But I do so under protest.
Let Chin hide
behind the rulebook!
The dispute is settled.
The match will continue until
one contestant either gives up
or loses consciousness...
Begin!
[gong crash]
[GOKU yells]
[SKY yells]
--[SKY grunts]
--[GOKU] Yaah!
[SKY yells]
[GOKU grunts]
I didn't think Goku
could move that fast.
He does have some skill.
Haah...
Before you get too proud,
taste the Panther-Cyclone Leg!
Haah...
[SKY laughs]
[SKY] You can't hide forever!
[GOKU grunts]
Now you're going--
[grunts]
Time-out!
What?!
Something's wrong
with my stomach.
I don't feel good.
What have I done?!
--[CROWD laughs]
--[SKY] Whatever stunt you're
trying to pull,
it's not going to work!
Either resume the fight
or forfeit!
[GOKU] I-I'm not kidding!
[JUDGE] You're holding up
the match! Let's go!
This might hurt.
[SKY grunts]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU] Yep, that hurt.
[SKY laughs]
[GOKU grunts]
[SHOKIN thinking] I thought
he'd quit when he got sick.
I never wanted this to happen.
[GOKU grunts]
End game, boy.
Goku, get up!
You can beat him!
Oops! Uhh...
This is...! No, Shokin!
Tell me you didn't.
[GOKU grunts]
[SKY] Are you going to try your
little After-Image trick again?!
You've already proven
that doesn't work on you.
--No, I've got something
--[SKY] Blah, blah, blah!
--better in mind.
--I'm going up and
you're going down!
Phantom-Star!
Haah!
Panther-Cyclone!
Ha-ah-ah!
[BOTH yell]
[SKY grunts]
[gasping]
--[CROWD cheers]
--Yeah! Woo-hoo! Yeah, Goku!
And the winner is Goku!
[ANGRY GUY A] Hey, move it!
[ANGRY GUY B]
You're blocking our view!
[CROWD cheers]
[CROWD chanting] Goku,
Goku, Goku, Goku!
[GOKU thinking] My stomach
is about to explode.
I shouldn't have eaten
that last rice cake!
[GOKU grunts, yells]
I bestow the title
Master of Martial Arts to Chin.
Congratulations.
You have robbed me
of my vengeance, Goku,
and for that I thank you.
In losing, I have learned there
is much I must atone for.
Perhaps as Master Chin's pupil,
I can start over.
Uh-hum.
Thank you.
Sure. I was glad
for the training.
The Phantom-Star technique
will help me a lot.
[SHOKIN whimpers] Goku...
[GOKU] Hm?
I, well, to tell the truth,
the soup I served you was--
I know what you're going to say
and I couldn't agree more.
That soup you made
was incredible!
Yeah, right.
[GOKU] Well, I better run.
Wait!
I thought you might
need something
for the long trip ahead
so I made this for you.
Oh...
Thank you for everything.
See ya later!
'Bye... Goodbye, Goku!
Take care!
[GOKU hums]
[GOKU] Hey!
Aah...!
Ooh! Delicious!
[NARRATOR]
Goku sets out in search
of his next training exercise.
Who or what will he find?
Don't miss the next incredible
episode of Dragon Ball!