[NARRATOR] In our last episode,
Goku and Bulma set out to
retrieve another Dragon Ball.
This one, however, proved to be
the most challenging yet,
as it resided
at the bottom of the ocean.
Unphased by this
monumental obstacle,
the pair paid a visit
to Master Roshi,
in hopes they might
borrow his submarine-jet.
Master Roshi agreed, in exchange
for Bulma's micro-band.
[NARRATOR] Goku and Bulma
received additional assistance
from Krillin,
who not only helped them
map out their target, but
decided to join them as well.
Together, the three explorers
face the mysterious unknown
that awaits them far below.
[BULMA] According to the radar,
we need to head south.
Mmm... About thirty miles.
You got it!
[exhales]
[knock, knock]
[STAFF OFFICER] Hm?
[RED] Enter.
[clears throat] Excuse me.
Commander,
General Blue has just sent in
his latest field report
regarding the island.
Apparently, it is
inhabited by an old man,
a young woman, and a turtle.
Old man? Hmm... Scientist!
Details are unknown.
You're probably right, sir.
This quite possibly
could be the same scientist
who built the sophisticated
radar for the boy.
[RED] Hrm. What is the
position of the Dragon Balls?
No change, sir.
Two are somewhere on the island
and one is in the ocean.
Tell General Blue to
invade the island immediately.
Get me those Dragon Balls
and the old man.
I want him taken alive.
Yes sir!
[RED chuckles]
Checkmate.
[chuckles]
[LAUNCH humming]
[LAUNCH] Hm?
[LAUNCH]
Hmmm... That's strange.
This is Bulma's bag.
She must have forgot it.
Aaah...
[LAUNCH] What are these?
[ROSHI laughs]
Now's my chance!
[humming]
Eeh! That was close!
This job takes stealth.
[chuckles]
[humming]
[laughs]
[ROSHI] All right! Let's get
down to business!
Now I'll finally
get what I deserve.
[laughing]
[BULMA] Okay, we should be
right above it.
Dive here.
[KRILLIN] Gotcha.
You mean we're really
going underneath the water
with this thing?
Yeah. That's the plan!
Wow, neat!
That's it, find the ball...
so I can steal it from you.
[laughs]
Roger. I'll tell
General Blue, immediately.
Gen--aah!
Aah!
Now, how many times will it
take until you've learned?
It is very difficult
to sneak up behind a general
and keep your teeth.
Sorry, General, urgent message.
[BLUE] Well? What is it?!
[SOLDIER A] Sir, we've received
official confirmation
from headquarters
regarding the boy's hideout.
According to radar reports,
the boy's Dragon Balls
are on that island
as we thought.
We've been ordered
to steal the Dragon Balls
and capture the old scientist
for questioning.
Everything is happening
as I had envisioned it...
[laughs]
That boy's days are
numbered... Attention!
Sir!
Divide the corps
into two units.
I will lead company A's
attack on the boy,
while you mobilize company B
and take the island.
Aside from the old man,
no prisoners.
[BLUE] Is that understood?!
Yes, sir!
Lieutenant. This army
requires its soldiers to move.
[BLUE] Lose some weight.
Yes, sir...
[GOKU] Wow! Everything
looks so beautiful!
Huh...
[GOKU] Bulma, why does
that big fish look so sad?
What's its name?
I don't know.
Be quiet, I'm trying to think.
Stop here, Krillin!
The radar shows it
should be right beneath us!
[KRILLIN] Right.
[GOKU] Where is it?
All I see down there
is a bunch of pretty fish.
[BULMA]
It's down there somewhere.
The radar doesn't lie.
Why don't you go look for it?
[GOKU] Okay.
Oh...
No wonder that fish is so sad.
All he can see is blue.
That's nice, bye. [chuckles]
[yells, laughs]
[KRILLIN]
What's the matter with Goku?
[laughing]
Uh?
[GOKU] This one must
be called a tickle fish.
[chuckles] Neat.
What are you doing?!
Stop goofing off!
Wow! How did your voice
get in my helmet?
[BULMA] Goku?!
Uh! Goku, what's going on?
Did you find it?
Uh...
Hey guys! Look at this!
It's the biggest crab
I've ever seen in my whole life!
[laughs]
Would you quit playing around
and find the Dragon Ball!
[BLUE]
We stand at the crossroads
between success and greatness.
Those who stand before me
represent the best that
the Red Ribbon Army
has to offer.
Your deeds
are already legendary.
But your actions today
will determine
how that legend is to be told.
[BLUE]
Find your enemy. Pluck him out.
And let his bones
pave the way to your glory!
[BLUE] Fail yourselves,
but never fail me.
[chuckles]
Bring me the old man.
For those who
help him, no mercy!
[BLUE] Now scramble!
[sirens]
[INTERCOM] All troops
report to battle stations!
All troops
Repeating! All trops report--
[BULMA] Any luck?! You should
be right on top of it.
[GOKU] Nothing here
but sea fish and coral.
This is strange.
Maybe the radar is acting up.
Uh. Guh.
[GOKU] Look! There's a
big crack in the ground.
It seems deep. Do you think
maybe the Dragon Ball
could have
dropped down inside of it?
[KRILLIN] Wait a minute!
Let me guide the submarine jet
down there and investigate.
[BULMA] If Goku's right,
this might be more difficult
than I thought. I need to
adjust the search grid
to compensate for
the depth differential.
[KRILLIN] Uh, yeah... O-Okay...
You mean, closer to the wall?
Yes. Closer to the wall, okay?
[beeping]
Goku, I... I think you're
gonna want to come see this.
I'd like to, but I
don't think I can fit...
I think we need the machine
you gave to Master Roshi,
the one that makes you smaller.
Uh! Wait... a... sec...
What's up?
[BULMA] Judging by
the shape of the ditch,
it looks like
it leads to something.
[gasps]
[BULMA]
I'll switch radar magnification
and see if I can't
get a better view.
[BULMA] There, see?!
It's a cave of some sort.
Maybe we can get inside!
It might lead
to the Dragon Ball!
We can go in there?
[BULMA] Come back to the sub
so we can check it out.
[sirens]
Start your engines!
[sirens continue]
[SOLDIER Z]
Attention all personnel--
secure stations
and prepare to dive!
I repeat, secure stations
[SOLDIER B] All hatches secure!
[SOLDIER B] All systems are go!
We're ready to dive!
Take us down.
So, what kind of
opposition are we looking at
once we reach the island, sir?
[chuckles]
[DOCK] Just a woman
and old man, so I hear.
[chuckles]
[ROSHI] Mmmm...
Eh! What in the world
is taking her so long?
Eh. Oh! She's here!
[LAUNCH humming]
[laughs]
[LAUNCH] Here we go.
Aah!
[yelling]
No! Stop! Wait!
[ROSHI yelling]
Launch! Stop! Aah! Wait!
This sucks! [yells]
Hello? Huh?
Sir, we have a visual
on the enemy submarine.
General, we have them
within weapons range.
Perfect.
Hold your fire, Captain,
but keep them
locked in your sights.
We'll just let them
lead us to the prize.
[BULMA] Go straight ahead
just a little farther.
We should see the entrance
just beyond this ridge...
There it is! We found it!
We're almost there!
General Blue, sir!
It appears that the enemy sub
is headed inside that cave.
[BLUE] That must be where
the Dragon Ball is hidden!
Ha-ha! Now,
blow them out of the water!
Aye, aye, sir!
Fire the torpedoes!
[SOLDIER F] Torpedoes away.
[ALL yell]
Sir, we missed.
No excuses.
Fire another round immediately!
[BULMA and GOKU wail]
What's going on?!
Oh no! Look!
There's another
submarine behind us!
They fired at us!
I don't think
they're too friendly!
There's only one group
mean enough to do this...
the Army!
Huh?!
Army? You don't mean the...
Red Ribbon Army?
That's them...
I know the Red Ribbon Army
has been looking for the Dragon
Balls just as hard as I have.
But they're much more
dangerous and mean about it.
[yells]
Mean?! I'd say trying
to blow us into fish food
borders on psychotic!
Why didn't you tell me
you were expecting company?
I never would have signed up
for this crazy mission!
Fire away!
They're firing on us again!
Okay, now would be
a good time to move!
Negative impact! I'm afraid
we missed them again, sir!
No, you missed them!
Soldier, execute this fool!
I grow tired of him!
Sir!
[SOLDIER C]
No, no, no, please! C'mon!
I've got a wife and
two cubs at home, man!
I gotta pay
the electric bill and--
[thud]
[BULMA] Faster!
We've gotta go faster!
[KRILLIN] I'm going!
[BULMA] Would it help
if I got out and pushed?!
At this point
I'm willing to try anything!
This is serious!
Why didn't you tell us
these guys were after you?!
No one ever asked me
about the Red Ribbon Army.
Ready torpedoes for launch.
We may be in luck.
The cave is getting narrow.
Faster! Hurry up! Just go!
[BULMA and KRILLIN yell, laugh]
[KRILLIN] We did it!
Their ship is too big
to follow us in here!
[laughs]
Those simple fools think
they've found a safe haven.
Prepare the escape pods!
We're going after them!
Engage!
[laughs] Idiots!
They are playing
right into my hands!
[laughs intensely]
[NARRATOR] Our heroes are well
on their way to discovering
the secret lying deep
within this mysterious cave.
All they have to do is
survive long enough to reach it.
Don't miss the next incredible
episode of Dragon Ball!