[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball,
Goku returned to Korin's Tower
following a near-fatal fight
with King Piccolo.
With help from friends,
Yajirobe and Bora,
Goku began the long climb
to see Master Korin
and regain his strength.
[NARRATOR] Using the power
of the Dragon Balls,
King Piccolo succeeded
in restoring his youth
and began anew his bid
to conquer the world,
one sector at a time.
First on his agenda
was King Furry's domain.
The frightened ruler
reluctantly fled for safety,
but it didn't take long for
the brutal invader to catch up.
[PICCOLO]
Going somewhere?
[PICCOLO cackles]
[PILOT]
I can't look.
[COMMANDER] Open your eyes!
You're a professional, Pilot!
[PILOT] Is there a big, green
monster standing on our ship?
[COMMANDER]
Yeah.
[PILOT]
Then, I'm flying blind!
[PILOT whimpers]
[COMMANDER growls]
[KING]
Hm...
[GUARD A]
I've got a positive lock.
Hold your fire!
[gasps]
No firing at the king's vessel!
The king is still
on board, soldier!
Right!
[COMMANDER, KING yelp]
[GUARDS yelping]
Well, well. I went searching
for a king and found a coward.
How dare you talk to the
king like that! You animal!
Wait your turn.
[gulps]
My name is King Piccolo
and you are hereby
relieved of your command.
I am your ruler now.
Not today, monster!
[gun barrel clicks]
[whimpers]
[PICCOLO] You must be
your king's first officer.
Sorry, I've already
got one of those.
[yelps]
No! No! No!
[KING] Stop it! Let him go
this instant! It's me you want!
Oh, that's true. Good point.
Wha--?
--[COMMANDER yelps]
--[PICCOLO] You're free to go.
[PICCOLO]
Bye.
No!
You are a monster!
I honored your last
request as King.
Do what you want with me.
I won't fight,
but leave my people alone!
Oh, how very touching.
A ruler, sacrificing himself
for his subjects.
However, you're hardly in a
position to plead for anything.
It's not you I want,
it's your kingdom.
There is one thing
you can do for me.
You are personally going
to make this announcement.
Tell your people
that the whole world
is now controled
by me, King Piccolo.
You are mad! I would never
help you enslave my people!
[PICCOLO] Mad? On the contrary,
I've never felt better.
I'm glad you disagree.
It gives me a chance to do this.
Wait! Uh, stop that!
What are you doing now?!
[PICCOLO grunting, cackling]
[PICCOLO]
Watch closely and witness
the price of your defiance!
[PICCOLO grunting, growling]
[KING, COMMANDER yelp]
[PICCOLO yells]
[sighs]
It's-It's all gone!
[RABBIT gasps]
[SUNO gasps]
[CROWD groaning]
[MAN coughing]
From the expression
on your face,
I can tell that you're
a visual learner.
But, this is a miniscule
example of my power.
I trust you won't need another.
Whether you're staring
at one crater
or an entire wasteland
is entirely up to you.
I can do this all day.
Very well. You win. Just stop
this senseless destruction.
[laughing]
[TURTLE]
Master Roshi!
I can't believe...
he was defeated.
I brought the extra
capsules just in case.
I didn't think I'd need them.
[YAMCHA grunts]
No!
Tien! Tien Shinhan! Tien, can
you hear me? This is Yamcha!
This is Tien Shinhan.
[YAMCHA]
Come back, please!
I'll master the Evil Containment
Wave and fight Piccolo with you.
Did you hear me?!
Don't do this alone!
Tien, listen! We'll collect
the Dragon Balls again!
That way we can bring Master
Roshi and Chiaotzu back to life.
That's not an option.
Once King Piccolo got what he
wanted from the Dragon Balls...
...he destroyed the Dragon.
[OOLONG, PUAR yelp]
Did he say--?
Destroyed!
[YAMCHA] Then there's no other
way but for us to fight!
Tien Shinhan?
Did you hear me?! Tien!
[beep]
[TIEN thinking]
If anyone else is going to die,
it will be me, and only me!
Well, so much for being Eternal.
This means Master will
never be able to return.
I wonder if we're ever
going to see Goku again.
He will come back, you'll see.
Goku is alive! I just know it!
I feel the same way
about it, Puar.
I mean, why call him Eternal
if he's not gonna be around?
That's just false advertising.
That's enough!
[PUAR, OOLONG, TURTLE scream]
This is no time for jokes,
you filthy pig!
[UPA] I wonder if Korin will
be able to help Goku get well?
[BORA] Perhaps it is
better that he didn't.
At least, not too soon.
What do you mean, Father?
Goku is a warrior.
As soon as he is well,
he will rejoin the fight.
[UPA]
Uh?
This new adversary is
strong enough to defeat Goku.
I do not think he will
be easy to eliminate,
even if Goku receives
additional training.
Poor Goku.
[YAJIROBI]
Just a little further...
Good ol' tower.
I can practically see
all that delicious food!
Look at it. It's so close, I can
almost touch it! I'm so hungry!
[YAJIROBI, GOKU yelp]
What happened?
Don't worry. Nothing's
going to stop us,
because nothing's going
to keep me from that food!
[YAJIROBI panting, grunting]
Finally!
[groans, pants]
I'm exhausted!
It was hard work.
Just rest a while.
[KORIN] You climbed all the way
up here with Goku on your back?
You must be very strong
and pretty stupid.
[GOKU] Hm? Master Korin,
it's great to see you again!
Whoa! That's Master Korin!?
Yo!
[GOKU]
Uh, listen Master, I--
Don't bother. I know, I know.
You know what happened to me?
You took a pretty nasty
beating from King Piccolo,
if I'm not mistaken.
That's right, but how
did you know, Master?
Oh, just because I live
above the world doesn't mean
I don't know what's
goin' on down there.
[gasps]
[YAJIROBI] You can't
see anything from here.
[KORIN] Because you're not
lookin' in the right place.
Huh?
Over there.
How's a jar gonna help see?
[yelps]
[YAJIROBI]
That's King Piccolo!
[PICCOLO] You work for me, now.
You will do my bidding.
[gasps] I will not help you
betray my people. Never!
Betray them?
[KING] I was elected
to preserve the peace.
So far, it doesn't look like
you're doing too good of a job.
[gasps]
[laughs]
In fact, one could say that
your peace is in pieces!
[laughs]
[YAJIROBI]
Uh, do you have another jar?
I don't like this one.
[KORIN] Goku, why did you come
here? What do you want me to do?
Don't you know?
You've already guessed
everything about King Piccolo.
Well, sort of.
He's a terrible monster!
Somebody has to defeat him!
I want to continue
my training with you.
[KORIN]
Hm...
Well, there's no sense in
training a body that's injured.
First thing's first.
You need energy.
Here we go! Catch!
Oh, thanks, Master. This
is a Senzu bean isn't it?
Hm? Ah! The beans!
What?! Senzu beans?!
These are the beans
you were talking about?!
That's them.
[YAJIROBI] You call this
special?! This is my reward?!
I can't believe I
went through all that
just for these lousy beans!
Well, I'm gonna get my fill!
Stupid beans!
[KORIN, GOKU gasp]
Risk my life all night!
[gags]
[grunting]
[GOKU giggles]
You're silly, Yajirobe!
You only need one bean.
They last for ten whole days.
[KORIN] Ha! Those beans sure
do the trick, don't they?
Now, you should be feelin'
better pretty soon.
[laughs]
I feel fantastic! Yeah!
[GOKU laughing, grunting]
[YAMCHA] I still can't
believe Master's gone.
[BULMA] Neither can I.
Just a short while ago,
he was sitting outside
on his favorite chair.
[sighs]
[TURTLE, PUAR sigh]
[gasps]
Yamcha?
Huh? Ah!
Is that who I think it is?!
[BULMA]
Master Roshi!
[TURTLE, PUAR gasp]
[YAMCHA]
Master!
[BULMA]
You're back!
Huh?
[BULMA, YAMCHA, PUAR growl]
Oolong, you lousy pig!
[sighs]
[TURTLE]
I thought the door would open
and Master Roshi
would walk through.
[ALL yelp]
Hey! Dinner!
[ALL groan]
Guys, there's too much food.
Oh...
Right.
I forgot and set a
place for Master Roshi.
Man! If only I were stronger!
Stop it! Tien will
defeat King Piccolo!
[growls]
[yells]
[yelps]
[TIEN grunts]
No, no! Focus! You can't
give into the anger.
Remember your goal!
[cackles]
[yells]
Now, I wanna make sure
we're absolutely clear here.
You want me to train you again?
Yes, Master Korin.
Just like the old days.
[GOKU]
Really!
Sorry, my boy.
But to be completely honest,
there's nothing left
for me to teach you.
Aw... What do you mean, nothing?
[KORIN grumbles] I know how
badly you want something new
to use against Piccolo,
but I'm all tapped out.
It's not like I gave ya a crash
course the first time around.
You mastered the master.
Still, that won't be enough.
Many great warriors
have tried what
you're attempting.
But he manages to kill everyone!
That monster even
killed Master Roshi.
What!? King Piccolo
killed Master Roshi!?
[KORIN]
Yes.
You-You mean I'll never
get to see him again,
just like my grandpa?!
Well, in these cases,
that's what normally happens.
Oh, no. But I never even
got to say goodbye.
[ROSHI] Well, hello there!
I'm the Turtle Hermit.
It's called the Flying Nimbus.
[GOKU] Whoa! Look, Bulma!
Isn't it neato?!
[grunts]
[yells]
If you boys want to
learn about martial arts,
you've got to go out
there and find me a date!
Hi!
[MERMAID]
Hi.
So what d'ya say
you and me go inside
and learn some more
about our species!
There's a lot more
to this training
than you boys might realize.
And there's so much more
to learn if you're
going to be ready for the
World Martial Arts Tournament.
[KRILLIN, GOKU, ROSHI]
1,2,1,2,1,2...
[ROSHI]
1,2,1,2...
1,2,1,2,1...
[laughs]
[GOKU growls] First Krillin,
and now Master Roshi?! Piccolo!
[growls]
[PICCOLO chuckles]
[laughs]
[GOKU]
I've got to stop him!
[KORIN] Hold it! You mustn't
face him in anger!
I have to fight him! He's taken
too many lives already!
Cool down and
listen for a minute.
If you seek him now,
he'll kill you.
I don't have a choice!
I'm not scared
and I'm not gonna
hide in a tower!
Well, if he's not
afraid of death,
I guess he could take a sip.
What?!
Ultra Divine Water.
Ultra Divine Water? Is that like
the Sacred Water I drank before?
That's for amateurs.
This is the real stuff.
[NARRATOR] What is Ultra Divine
Water, and what deadly secret
does it possess?
As Tien Shinhan desperately
tries to master
the Evil Containment Wave,
he must wrestle with the
same dilemma facing Goku.
To defeat King Piccolo, is he
willing to face his own demise?
Find out next time
on Dragon Ball!