[NARRATOR]
Last time on DragonBall...
[BULMA]
Faster! We've gotta go faster!
[KRILLIN] I'm going!
[BULMA] Would it help
if I got out and pushed?
They're firing at us again!
Okay, now would be
a good time to move!
[NARRATOR] The Red Ribbon Army
made their presence felt,
as they turned up the heat
on Goku, Bulma, and Krillin.
General Blue lead the attack,
which included sending troops
to Roshi's Island
to kidnap the master
and steal the two
Dragon Balls in his possession.
Goku and his friends
found safety in a cave
too narrow for the
large submarine to follow.
However, the resourceful
general was prepared
and continued the chase
in smaller vessels.
Hurry up, guys!
And whatever you do,
don't look back!
Oh my gosh!
They're still after us!
Only now they have two ships,
and they don't look happy!
Are you trying
to get us killed?!
Trust me, I don't
want to meet them either.
Did I mention
that they have torpedoes?
What are torpedoes?
Haven't you been
paying attention?
They're bombs!
They blow things up!
Oh, okay. So that's a torpedo!
It must be nice to live
in complete oblivion.
Which is about
what we're gonna be!
I'm trying!
I've got them in range, sir.
Shall we launch torpedoes?
Negative. We'd risk a cave-in.
Besides, you don't need to use
a torpedo to destroy a fly.
There's an easier solution.
Ram them into the cave wall!
[STAFF OFFICER] General Blue's
Company A is in pursuit
of the little boy
and the third Dragon Ball.
Captain Dock
is supervising the raid
on the island by Company B.
Our radar has a confirmed
lock on two Dragon Balls
[STAFF OFFICER] located within
the scientist's compound.
As you know, the old man
is accompanied by
a woman and a turtle,
which are believed to be
his only protection.
Yes, yes. General Blue
is a brilliant tactician.
I'm supposedly surrounded
by the best minds
[RED]
of every conceivable industry.
Yet I'm still chasing a child
for what should have been
in my possession months ago!
I understand, sir.
You understand nothing!
But make sure General Blue does.
I want that scientist
brought back to me alive,
at all costs...!
He is the key to our success.
Consider it done, sir.
[TURTLE yawns]
[LAUNCH hums]
[ROSHI] A beautiful day,
a beautiful girl
cooking me breakfast,
what more could
a hermit ask for?
Now if I could just
get some results from
this shrinking
contraption of Bulma's.
So far, the answer to my dreams
has given me
nothing but nightmares!
I've been flushed
down the toilet
and sucked up
by a vacuum cleaner!
Getting a bird's-eye view
of dust-bunnies
wasn't exactly
what I had in mind.
Well I've never
given up on anything
and I'm not about to start now!
[LAUNCH humming]
[ROSHI chuckles]
[laughing]
[LAUNCH] Ah, a hot bath!
[laughs]
[LAUNCH singing]
[ROSHI] Aah! Not attractive.
Control Roshi, control.
[singing]
Hey there, Launch!
Huh?
You've been working
so hard this morning.
Awe. Don't be silly.
I took the liberty of
drawing you a nice, hot bath.
Thanks, but I
have to finish cooking.
Cooking...?!
Nonsense, what you
need is a bath.
Here, I'll take care
of those eggs.
I-I'd rather--
[ROSHI] Hand it over!
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ahhhchoo!
[TURTLE] Aah...
Haaa! What are you
looking at, old-timer?!
[yells, groans]
[LAUNCH] Not so fast.
Mercy!
[LAUNCH] Who are you and
what do you think you're doing
here in my house?!
Speak up! I don't have all day!
What?! This is my house!
You're welcome to stay,
but I'm feelin' kinda sick.
[coughing]
See ya!
Hold it right there!
I'm on to you!
[ROSHI] It was all
innocent fun. Really! Heh.
What are you
talking about, old fool?
Stop your blabbering
and answer my question!
Now, are we roommates or not?
Huh? The two of us? Roommates?
Why... yes, we are.
Have I lived here long?
Long enough to call it home.
You like the salty air
and the warm climate
and you especially like those
soothing massages I give you.
Uh, daily!
A massage? Why would
I let anyone near me,
much less give me a massage?!
Launch, baby, you love 'em!
That's plausible I guess.
But why would you
go out of your way?
What do you get out of it?
Hey, that's what
friends are for.
[ROSHI laughing]
[LAUNCH chuckles]
Actually...
a massage sounds nice.
My shoulders
have been a bit stiff.
Ooh?!
But I'm warning you, Buster!
If you try any funny business,
I'll knock your block clean off!
[ROSHI] No! Of course not!
Perish the thought!
All right. Pay extra
attention to my upper back.
It's really sore.
[ROSHI] Roshi, you devil!
You still got it!
I'll have her eating from
the palm of my hand in no time!
[chuckles]
Okay, looks like the back
is in good shape.
[laughing]
[ROSHI] Easy does it!
[continues laughing]
[grunts]
[laughing]
I know your game, old man,
and I don't wanna play!
[yelling]
Okay, you win!
[ROSHI whimpers]
Hm!
By the sound of it,
I'd say my master is
up to his old tricks again.
Captain, we have
an ETA of five minutes.
All right men, listen up.
The circus is
coming into town in five!
You know the drill.
I want this one
strictly by the book.
[DOCK] Tonight is hoagie night
and we're not going to miss it!
[SOLDIERS] Yes sir!
[police sirens]
Where's the chow at?
I'm wasting away over here!
[ROSHI] Coming!
Eh, oh, oh, hot, ah, eh, hot!
Bon appétit!
Huh. Looks interesting.
What do you call it?
[ROSHI] Oh...
It's an old family recipe.
I call it dah-wha-la...
"Roshi Surprise!"
[ROSHI laughs nervously]
Well, then you've had
a long time to get it right.
Uuuh... Eeeh...
[LAUNCH] Bleh! Ugh!
[growls]
Does it need more salt?
You're the chef. You tell me.
Okay.
[yells]
What are you trying to do,
poison me?
You call that slop food?!
In case I forgot to mention it,
I'm allergic to garbage!
Give me another chance!
I make a mean soufflé!
[LAUNCH] Quiet! Something stinks
here and it's not the food!
I'll give you another massage!
You've given enough!
Now it's my turn.
[LAUNCH] Uh, uhhh, ahhh...
[sighs]
Ah! Ah! Ahhh! Ahhh...!
[LAUNCH] Aaahchoo!
[ROSHI and TURTLE sigh]
Roshi? What's wrong?
You look beat.
You certainly have a way
with the ladies, Master.
Well, I guess everyone
has their talents.
[chuckles nervously]
[BOTH] Huh?
Wow!
Are you expecting
any visitors today?
Nope. I don't know 'em.
[beep]
[chuckles]
I have them on screen
and in range, Captain.
Roger. Proceed with caution.
They may be up to something.
Roger.
Look's like
we have a lot of guests.
Good thing I made
plenty of soup.
[whimpers]
[chuckles]
Ensign, check the house.
Who are you? I paid my taxes.
[grunts]
Congratulations, Doctor.
You're just been recruited
by the Red Ribbon Army.
Doctor? That's a new one.
[laughs]
Don't play games...
We know who you are.
I wish I could say the same.
Uh. I, uh... I've never
had so many guests
on my island
with so much ammunition.
The Red Ribbon Army
is well supplied.
The Red Ribbon Army...?
Oh... I have
heard of you before.
We found the girl.
She was alone inside the house.
There doesn't appear to be any
booby-traps on the property.
Good.
You'll have to forgive me.
It took a moment to register
the title of your organization.
I've heard it called
so many different names.
You have a real reputation
for being cruel and unjust.
What?!
There's a ton. Like the
jerk patrol, the dirt-bags,
and my personal favorite,
the Red Ribbon Slime Balls.
Heh. That's nice...
In case you haven't noticed,
these dirt-bags,
as you call them,
have you out-numbered
and out-gunned.
Yup... And out-whipped.
That must come in handy
on training day.
It's not for my men...
It's for those
who oppose me, Doctor.
Now, let's dispense
with the pleasantries.
[DOCK] You will soon learn
that I am not a man
with whom to toy.
Hand over your
Dragon Balls immediately.
Yes, we know you have them.
Do it! Or suffer my wrath!
Uuh...
I guess he needs more practice.
Say, I didn't know
you had any Dragon Balls.
Maybe he's confused.
[DOCK] Silence!
[DOCK] There are three things
I want from you, Doctor!
The two Dragon Balls the kid
left in your possession,
which you undoubtedly have
hidden somewhere on this island,
[DOCK] and a radar to
track down the other balls,
like the one you made
for that little brat!
You think he left
Dragon Balls here?
Oh... The bag...
He left one behind.
Maybe... that's where they are.
Well, we'll soon find out!
Tear the house apart!
I want those Dragon Balls!
And I can see why.
You're obviously lacking
in the ball department.
That's it! I'm sick of
your mouth, old man!
Just remember,
you asked for this!
[DOCK grunting]
Hey...!
Felt the wind on that one!
[SOLDIER A] Captain,
he's just an ornery old man.
He can't fight anybody.
He probably can't even
walk without his cane.
That's true, Scout.
Whatever helps you
sleep at night, slick.
Next time I may not
be able to hold myself back.
[ROSHI groans]
Heh. I understand.
That's a lot to restrain.
Bring it on, gramps!
[yells]
[ROSHI laughs]
[SOLDIER D laughs]
[humming]
Is that all ya got?
Eh?
[SOLDIER D yells]
[SOLDIER B] Hold it, old man!
[SOLDIER B] Take another step
and she's history!
All right...
Settle down now...
Put the gun away.
I'm the one who's
giving orders here, not you!
So pay attention!
Roshi, help me!
[TURTLE] Launch, this will help.
[ROSHI] I'll do what you say.
I'm watching you, man!
Don't try anything funny!
Just stand still!
Ah... Ah... Ah... Ahh...
[LAUNCH] Achoo!
Hey! Watch it, sweetheart.
You don't want to
break my concentration.
I'll break
a lot more than that.
Trust me, sweetheart.
[yells]
[LAUNCH grunting]
Quit complaining,
you stupid ox!
At least I let you
keep your teeth.
--[LAUNCH grunts]
--[SOLDIER B groans]
[ROSHI] Launch, Launch!
He's not moving. You got him!
Come on, let's go in the house.
Ya big sissy!
Unbelievable.
She may be more frightening
than the Red Ribbon Army.
[ROSHI]
How about a nice hot bath?
[ROSHI] Hello.
Yes, sir?
[ROSHI]
Are you sure you wouldn't like
to join your friends?
[SOLDIER D] Eeh! N-No, sir.
I-I'm only in the reserves!
[BULMA] Come on, Krillin, step
on it! They're gaining on us!
[KRILLIN]
I hate back seat drivers!
[BLUE] Ram them!
[ALL yelling]
That's it! Hit them again!
Again! Yes!
Bash them against the wall!
[ALL yell]
[GOKU] Wow! What happened
to all the water?
[BULMA]
We're still in the ocean,
but this cave
has a pocket of air.
[GOKU] Lucky for us!
[BULMA] I wouldn't call it luck.
Those maniacs
are still after us.
Come on!
Lets get out of here!
[KRILLIN] They're here!
Hey guys, wait up!
Where in the world are we?
General! It looks like
those pesky kids
are trying to
make a run for it.
Get them and quickly!
[SEAL SOLDIER]
This is Alpha Leader, over...
It's for you, sir. It's
Captain Dock of Company B.
Captain. Report.
What?!
The whole company defeated?!
[BULMA screams] Stop!
What are you trying to do,
leave me behind?
Wait a minute.
Why are we running away?
Why can't we just...
talk this out?
No! They're not here to talk!
They have guns.
We have feet. So let's go!
[panting]
What's the matter?
What's wrong?
I'm going to talk to them.
Goku, I knew you were strange,
but I didn't know
you were crazy!
Do you have a
death wish or something?
[SEAL SOLDIER] Hold it!
Don't go any further.
Come on back!
Uh... Where are they going?
I don't understand...
How come they don't
wanna come down here
and talk to us?
Way to go! You did it, champ!
Now let's get out of here
before they decide to come back!
[KRILLIN]
Maybe Goku scared them off.
Or maybe they're going back
to get some reinforcements.
Let's get moving.
This is it for me.
No more adventures.
It seems we have
underestimated our enemy.
That is the fatal mistake our
predecessors made, I'm sure.
If we are to avoid their fate,
we must be careful.
[BALD SOLDIER] But sir, the
enemy is just a bunch of kids.
Yes, the same kids
that decimated
both Silver and White Corps.
Not to mention what
they did to Company B...
[BLUE] An entire company wiped
out by an old man and a girl,
who are known associates
of these kids!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
Do not think of them as
young, old, or by gender.
Simply know them as your enemy,
and all five will crumble
before this day is through.
Bulma, are you sure
this path will lead us
to wherever the
Dragon Ball is hiding?
Pretty sure. Unless the
Red Ribbon Army gets us first.
I don't see anybody
following us.
I can't see anything at all.
It's way too dark in here.
I know, we could
put Krillin up front!
His head could light the way.
That's not funny.
[GOKU] Hmmm.
[ALL gasp]
[laughs]
Neat! I didn't know there were
lights in the ocean!
There aren't.
These are electric lights.
Okay. Now I'm scared.
One thing's for certain,
we're not the first ones here.
These lights had
to put up by someone.
I just hope
they aren't still here.
[BALD SOLDIER]
Man, what is all this about?
Interesting. Electrical.
We are not inside a cave...
Someone has turned this
into a base of some sort.
Now why would they do that?
Strange. Who builds a base
at the bottom of the ocean?
[GOKU chuckles]
Hey! Look at me!
[screams]
Sounds frightening...
Soldier, check it out.
Yes, sir.
[SOLDIER F shrieks]
[GOKU laughing]
[KRILLIN and BULMA] Goku!
Gotcha!
You almost gave me a
heart attack, you little twerp!
Uh, Goku, where exactly
did you find that?
Next to that suit.
That's gross!
Wait! The skull!
The mark of the pirate.
This must be the place Master
Roshi was talking about.
The Pirate's
sunken treasure. It's here!
[BULMA yells]
[cannon fire]
[PIRATES commotion]
[BULMA squeals] All that gold
and jewelry and diamonds!
Oh, please let
there be diamonds!
He's a pirate?
[laughs] Yes! We did it!
We discovered
the pirate's treasure!
[BULMA]
Who needs the Dragon Balls?
We're rich! We're rich!
General, I have
a visual on the kids,
and you're not going to believe
what they've stumbled onto.
Are you telling me
that old tale is true?
That the fabled treasure exists!
And it's right here
in this cave!
Well done, soldier.
Get back here now.
I want a full report.
Ha-ha! We have just made the
greatest discovery of our age.
And the most lucrative...
Supreme Commander Red
will be most pleased.
[laughing]
[BULMA and KRILLIN]
Hip, hip hooray!
[NARRATOR] As Goku
and his friends rejoice
over the buried treasure
they hope to find,
a few mysteries still linger.
What happened to the pirates
who supposedly
secured this wealth?
Is their bounty
really hidden within the cave?
And if so, what danger awaits
those who attempt to claim it?
After all,
where there is treasure,
there are booby traps!
Our heroes deserve
a moment of joy,
but they should also beware,
General Blue will stop at
nothing to get what he wants.
Next time on Dragon Ball!