[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball:
Sergeant Major Murasaki
charged into action!
This tricky ninja
will stop at nothing
to prevent Goku from
rescuing the Village Chief.
The battle was fierce, but our
hero was up to the challenge.
He proved that you
should never underestimate
a boy and his pole,
especially when that boy
is Goku!
[NARRATOR]
Murasaki attacked using all
of the techniques
at his disposal,
but Goku was able
to handle every surprise
the ninja threw his way.
That wasn't fair!
You said you
didn't have a weapon!
[NARRATOR] Every surprise--
that is, except one.
[yells in pain]
[chuckling evilly]
[MURASAKI]
Wahahahahaha!
Now you know why they call me...
...the messenger of Death.
[laughing]
Yes...
That's what I call results.
[laughing evilly]
Huh?
[MURASAKI]
K-O! K-O! K-O!
[laughing]
[gasps]
[GOKU groaning]
Ow! Ow!
[incoherent babbling]
No more dirty tricks!
Now it's my turn!
Impossible...
No one could survive that
kind of blow to the head.
No one!
What are you trying to do to me?
Get back down on the ground
where you belong!
[yelling]
[high-pitched screaming]
Hey! Missed me!
[GOKU]
You better not be hiding again!
What took you so long?
Haha! Hoho! Ha!
Go ahead.
Take your best shot if you can.
Hey-ya!
Whoa!
[MURASAKI laughing]
I call that the
overturned mat trick!
Catch this one!
Hi-ya!
Wow...
[MURASAKI laughing]
What's the matter?
Out of stars?
Nope.
[MURASAKI]
No mat!
Oh! Ho!
Look at me! I'm deformed!
Oh, I knew I should have
shelled out the extra 25 Zenni
for the complete set, but no!
"When am I ever gonna
need six mats?" I said.
[MURASAKI] Well that's
the last time I buy...
[growling]
How will my village survive
without my guidance?
I must find a way
to return to them.
They need my help.
All right,
old timer, food's here.
Hey! Old man, are you deaf?
[VILLAGE CHIEF] I will not
eat while I am your prisoner.
Send the food to my people.
Fine. Let the rats have it.
What's with all the
noise I hear downstairs?
It's nothing.
There's some
little boy running around.
A little boy?
He sneaked in,
I guess to rescue you.
Don't worry.
He's probably in
a million pieces by now.
What?!
Why you--
Picking on an old man is
one thing, but a little child!
You are barbaric!
What if that were your own son?
What kind of an
army fights children?!
Let go of me, you old fool!
If he were my kid,
I wouldn't send him here
in the first place!
What's the matter? Aren't there
any men in your village?
[SOLDIER A]
Pathetic.
What am I going to do?
I've got to do something,
and quickly!
That poor little boy
is was--Huh?
Cocoa, my favorite!
Hey, wait! Wait!
Stop, will ya?
I don't have time for this!
[GOKU coughing]
[MURASAKI]
Let's see you follow me now.
[coughing]
See you on the other side, brat!
Neat shoes,
but what's the big deal?
I can just swim across.
Sure. That's a great idea, kid.
Dive right in!
If you wanna lose some weight...
Say, all your pounds!
See, this is a special pond,
full of piranhas!
Full of pajamas?
Are you deaf?
I said Piranha!
A voraciously carnivorous
tropical freshwater fish
of the genus Serrasalmus.
In other words, it's a little
fish with a big, big bite!
What's that? I can't hear what
you're saying. Speak up!
You--You little heathen!
You try my patience!
Fine!
[MURASAKI] Watch this!
[screaming]
[MURASAKI laughing]
Go ahead. Just try and
cross the pond. I dare you!
Okay!
Hi there.
I've got to be dreaming!
Boy, that was fun.
Why don't you try it?
Or do you want
to fight some more?
Hi-ya!
I am sick and tired of playing
silly games with you, boy!
This has got to stop!
So does this mean you
are ready to give up now?
That does it!
That is the
last straw, little boy!
You look a little upset.
I'm not upset.
Oh no, I'm way past upset.
I'm furious!
Oh. That's mad, right?
You're going
to learn what happens
when you push me too far!
Just remember little man,
you brought this on yourself.
Prepare!
[whistling]
What are you doing that for?
Now you will
understand what it means
to suffer the wrath
of the powerful ninja!
[GOKU] What's going on?
Now... separation!
How'd you do that?
[chuckling]
[MURASAKIS laughing tauntingly]
[GOKU]
Hey, there's four other yous!
Kill the boy.
[MURASAKIS] Kill the boy.
Kill the boy. Kill the boy.
Kill the boy.
Which one's the real one?
They all look alike.
I'm real, boy.
Okay, now I know
which one to fight.
You're the real one?
Lucky dodge.
That was pretty sneaky.
But now that I know
that it's really you,
I won't fall for
that trick again!
What's going on?
I don't know which one's real,
but they're all
trying to hurt me.
[MURASAKIS laughing tauntingly]
Now! Let's finish this runt!
This is serious!
He's sure been gone a long time.
Suno...
I'm worried.
It's natural to be scared, dear,
but everything's
going to be all right.
[rustling]
[gasp]
Father!
Hello, dear.
What's wrong, Suno?
[MOTHER] It's nothing. She's
just frightened by everything
that's been going on lately.
We all are.
Did you find
the Dragon Ball today?
No, not yet.
I'm worried about that
awful Muscle Tower, Father.
Have you heard
any news about it?
Has anyone been caught
inside or maybe escaped?
I've never mentioned that place.
Why would you ask about it?
A child?! By himself?!
Yes, Father,
but he's very strong!
In fact, he beat up two of those
Red Ribbon Army
soldiers right here!
We saw him do it!
Didn't we, mother?
Yes.
He's brave, too!
As soon as he heard,
he ran straight to Muscle Tower
to free the Village Chief!
But the danger is
too great to go alone!
There's some thing inside
the tower that isn't human!
[distant fighting]
[GOKU]
Whoa!
All right. I'd better
hide here for a while
until I can figure out
exactly what's going on.
Boy, he's really good.
He can make all of his other
hims do different things.
[MURASAKI D] Where did he go?!
[MURASAKI E]
He couldn't have gone far.
[MURASAKI D] Yes. He's got
to be around here somewhere.
[MURASAKI E] Let's split up
so we can cover more ground.
They're talking to each other!
But how is that possible?!
[MURASAKI] There he is!
[laughing tauntingly]
Don't leave.
Why, we're just getting started!
How can you make the fake
yous do all this stuff?
That's for me to know...
...and you to deal with,
if you live long enough.
[yelling]
[laughing menacingly]
Isn't it obvious? I'm the
one you've been fighting.
The eldest.
I am number two.
Three, that's me.
That makes me four.
Five! Five!
Formation! Haha!
We are the five
Murasaki brothers!
Oh boy!
And as you have seen,
all of us are very much real!
[gulp]
Yes. Now that
you know our secret,
prepare to meet your
demise at the hands of the
mighty Murasaki Ninjas!
Five against one doesn't
seem like a fair fight,
but I'm ready.
Two can play at this game.
Okay, which one of you
guys wants to go first?
You insolent child!
We will strike you down
together, as one!
[yelling]
Okay!
Here I am!
Look out behind you!
Stop hiding! Stop!
Hey!
[GOKU] Well that's
three down, two to go.
I don't believe it!
He knows how to do the
Afterimage trick for real!
Be quiet! Stop your whining
and concentrate on the battle!
Hurts... really hurts...
Now wait a minute!
Let's talk about this, okay?!
Next up, number one.
Monster?!
I've never actually seen it,
but I've heard the stories
of a living nightmare
that lurks somewhere
deep within Muscle Tower.
[FATHER] They say
sometimes, late at night,
you can hear
the creature moaning
as it searches
for its next victim.
[faint growling]
[FATHER] I'm afraid if a child
were trapped in that place,
it could not survive
such an abomination.
Let's pray that the boy
somehow finds his way out.
That's all we can
do for him right now.
Goku... he's lost!
Our thoughts go out
to this brave boy
and we hope he finds freedom
from the evil
that threatens him.
Boy, you sure like to run
a lot, don't you, number one?
I definitely need a raise!
Hey! Yoo-hoo!
Earth to Android Eight!
Wake up! It's your turn!
Destroy the boy!
Caught you!
[MURASAKI] Go and fight,
number eight! Annihilate!
[NARRATOR] It appears
the mysterious monster
of Muscle Tower
is actually an android!
But that doesn't
make it any less dangerous.
Whatever Android #8
has in store for our hero,
One thing is certain:
It doesn't look
happy to see him!
Can Goku overcome
his newest opponent?
Or will Murasaki
have the last laugh?
There's only
one way to find out...
Tune in next time for
another thrilling episode
of Dragon Ball!