[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball...
[GOKU] Hey, are
you listening?
[NARRATOR] Goku's first
visit to the frozen tundra
took a nasty turn as
his airplane nose-dived
into the thick snow below...
[NARRATOR] In this
unforgiving weather
and with the Red Ribbon Army
close at hand,
Goku would have been
a goner without the help
of a young girl named Suno,
who pulled our hero
by the heels
through the frozen wilderness,
toward the safety
of her nearby village.
You imbecile!
Stop wasting
my time and follow
that trail before
the snow covers it up!
[NARRATOR] General White's
troops widened their search,
their every resource
dedicated to finding Goku
and the Dragon Ball he carries.
But the falling snow served to
hinder the soldiers' progress,
and gave Goku
some much needed time
to recover from
his latest ordeal...
[GOKU snoring]
[NARRATOR] Suno and her mother
placed the unconscious boy
in front of a warm fire,
and did what else
they could to thaw him out.
Fortunately, they
didn't have to wait long
before their kind
efforts were rewarded.
[GOKU groans]
[SUNO gasps] I think
he's waking up!
[NARRATOR] And with the addition
of some extra clothes...
[GOKU giggles]
This feels great!
[NARRATOR] Goku was
soon back on his feet
and feeling better than ever.
[GOKU chuckles]
Don't worry about me...
I'll be fine.
[NARRATOR]
His energy fully restored,
Goku raced away from
Suno's house on a new mission.
Do you really think he can
defeat the army, Mother?
He thinks he can,
but so did your father.
[NARRATOR]
To show his thanks,
Goku promised to
rescue the village chief...
who is being held hostage
by the Red Ribbon Army
in their heavily
fortified Muscle Tower.
[GOKU yelling]
[WHITE laughing]
Power Pole extend!
[NARRATOR] Goku easily swept
aside the first wave of guards
and vaulted his way
onto the tower,
ready to face
the many dangers ahead.
Little does he know,
General White is
also ready for him.
[GOKU]
Hmm?
Well, I am impressed,
little lamb...
Come on up.
[WHITE] I'll be right
here waiting for you.
[WHITE laughs]
Come inside...
You'll catch
your death out here.
I was just hoping
I'd see Goku...
This place is huge.
The chief could be anywhere.
[WHITE]
I see you, intruder!
[GOKU]
Hmm?
[WHITE]
Welcome to Muscle Tower!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
[GOKU]
Huh?
Where are you?
I can't see you!
What's it to you?
You're the trespasser!
What do you want?
[GOKU] I came to take
the chief back to his village!
The chief? I see...
You've been sent here
to retrieve him, have you?
[WHITE] Well by all means,
come and get him.
Take the stairs all the way
to the top floor.
You'll find him there.
Ah, just be sure to watch
your step on the way up.
[WHITE laughing]
Thanks!
That's exactly what I'll do!
[door creaks open]
[door squeaks shut]
Huh?
Look, a kid!
You startled us, boy!
And we hate to be startled...
[MOHAWK MAN snickers]
Yeah... you're in for it!
[BEARD MAN]
General White, sir!
Want me to teach
this kid a lesson?
[WHITE] Yes. Education
is very important.
[BEARD MAN chuckles]
[knocking]
Who's there?
[MURASAKI]
Murasaki!
[WHITE]
Come in!
Come for the show?
[MURASAKI gasps]
Ahh!
[YELLOW HAIR]
Don't kill him too quick!
Yeah, it's important to
learn about sharing, kid.
So pay attention,
this is how it works.
You see, I'm gonna
pummel you first,
then I'll let the other
guys have a turn.
[GOKU]
Ha...
[BEARD MAN]
Oof!
[BEARD MAN groans]
Huh?
[YELLOW HAIR whimpers]
[DARK HAIR growls]
[DARK HAIR]
Why you little brat!
I'll pound you into mush!
I'll teach you!
[GOKU yells]
--[YELLOW HAIR yells]
--[GOKU] Hiyah!
[YELLOW HAIR groans]
[DARK HAIR huffing]
[GOKU]
Hmm...
[DARK HAIR growls]
--[GOKU] Hiyah!
--[DARK HAIR] Oof!
[DARK HAIR groans]
[gun clicks]
[GOKU]
Hmm.
Say good-bye!
B-bu-but... what the...
But I hit him...
where did he go?
--[MOHAWK MAN whimpers]
--[GOKU clears throat]
[GOKU] Hiii-ya!
[MOHAWK MAN grunts]
[WHITE and MURASAKI]
Hmm...
Whew, I'm starting
to work up a sweat.
[GOKU] Yeah...
This coat's gotta go.
[MURASAKI]
Did you see that?
The way he vaporized like that,
he's no normal boy.
I think I'm
beginning to understand
how he was able
to overpower Silver.
[MURASAKI]
He beat up Colonel Silver?
You don't think he can
make it up here, do you?
That is absolutely
impossible, sir.
No one has ever defeated
the third floor guard,
Major Metallitron...
But if by some chance
he makes it past him,
I'll be waiting
on the fourth floor.
[MURASAKI giggles]
I guess that'll
take care of him...
I sure would enjoy a crack
at the boy myself, though.
[WHITE] Metallitron,
you have company on the way.
Show him your
special hospitality.
[WHITE laughing]
Now, that's better.
[GOKU panting]
[MAJOR METALLITRON]
Stop, intruder.
[GOKU stammering]
Wow!
You're huge!
I am the guard
assigned to this floor.
You must get past me
to proceed upstairs.
You mean... a fight?
You wanna bet on how long
it takes Metallitron
to kill him?
[MURASAKI]
I'd put my money
on one, perhapas
two minutes, tops.
You're dead.
[GOKU whimpers]
[MAJOR METALLITRON grunts]
Where did he go?
[MURASAKI grunts]
[MAJOR METALLITRON grunts]
[GOKU chuckles]
[GOKU yells]
--[MAJOR METALLITRON gasps]
--[GOKU chuckles]
[MURASAKI and WHITE stammer]
[GOKU yells]
[MAJOR METALLITRON groans]
[WHITE and MURASAKI gasp]
[MAJOR METALLITRON grunts]
[GOKU]
Ha!
That was easy!
I bet I'll find
the chief in no time!
[GOKU]
Going up!
[GOKU grunts]
Going down.
[GOKU and MAJOR
METALLITRON grunting]
[grunting continues]
Oh, yeah, this is it!
[MAJOR METALLITRON growls]
[MAJOR METALLITRON
and GOKU grunting]
[GOKU growls]
[grunting continues]
Oh no!
Remarkable.
[MAJOR METALLITRON
and GOKU grunting]
[MAJOR METALLITRON growls]
That was pretty good,
but it's my turn now!
[GOKU panting]
[WHITE yells]
[GOKU yells]
[MAJOR METALLITRON groans]
[WHITE yells]
[GOKU] That got him.
[GOKU]
Hmm?
[GOKU whimpers]
[WHITE snickers]
Nice...
[MAJOR METALLITRON growls]
[GOKU whimpers]
[MAJOR METALLITRON grunts]
You're back?
But I knocked you out
with that last kick, didn't I?
[MAJOR METALLITRON grunts]
[GOKU yells]
--[MAJOR METALLITRON grunts]
--[GOKU groans]
[GOKU yells]
Oof!
[MAJOR METALLITRON snickers]
[WHITE giggles]
That's the end of that pest.
[MURASAKI] It took a bit
longer than two minutes.
Major Metallitron's
a little rusty, I guess.
[GOKU whimpers]
[MAJOR METALLITRON grunts]
Huh?
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU yells]
[MAJOR METALLITRON grunts]
[GOKU groans]
What is he, made of metal?
Ahh...!
That boy is hard-headed.
[WHITE chuckles]
But all I'd say
he's managed to do
is really tick off
the good major.
[GOKU grunting]
Not again!
[MAJOR METALLITRON]
I'm mad.
[GOKU]
Wow...
Have you ever thought about
fighting in the tournament?
[MAJOR METALLITRON growls]
[GOKU gasps]
[glass breaks]
[SUNO and SUNO's MOM gasp]
[SUNO] I hope nothing bad
has happened to Goku.
[MAJOR METALLITRON]
The end!
[WHITE laughing]
Metallitron blew him to pieces!
I must confess,
that robot is one
dangerous opponent...
I'm glad I didn't face him.
[WHITE]
Yes, this is the first time
I've seen him fight seriously.
Powerful stuff.
Whew, that was close!
[MAJOR METALLITRON]
Victory.
Victory... Victory...
What kind of move was that...?
He shot his
tongue out at me!
[GOKU]
Hm.
I wonder how he
gets it back in?
[tongue] Maybe he's
got two of them...
I dunno -- but oh well, as long
as we're showing tricks...
Hey!
[MAJOR METALLITRON]
Huh?
[GOKU taunting]
You missed me!
Impossible!
[WHITE]
How could he dodge that?
[MAJOR METALLITRON grunts]
[GOKU]
But you know what?
I'm sure not
gonna miss you!
[GOKU] Ka...
...me...
...ha...
[MAJOR METALLITRON yells]
[GOKU]
Ha!
[GOKU grunting]
[MAJOR METALLITRON yells]
[WHITE groans]
[GOKU]
Uh...
[electricity fizzles]
Oh no...
I only wanted to stop him!
I didn't want to make
his whole head come off!
[MURASAKI] What...
just happened down there?
[GOKU] You were
a really tough opponent.
Oh!
D-did I see his hand move?
[GOKU whimpers]
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU groans]
[WHITE chuckles]
That did it.
Very nice.
[GOKU groans]
[GOKU yelps]
He's still moving?!
[MAJOR METALLITRON]
Destroy.
Destroy....
[GOKU pants]
How's he doing this?
He's a monster!
[WHITE laughing]
Major Metallitron
is a robot, you fool!
Go Major!
To the end!
[MAJOR METALLITRON]
Destroy.
Destroy. Destroy. Destroy...!
[GOKU yelps]
[GOKU stammers]
[MAJOR METALLITRON]
Destroy...
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU yells]
[WHITE whimpers]
No!
[electricity fizzles]
[GOKU sighs]
[GOKU whimpers]
[GOKU growls]
[MAJOR METALLITRON]
Destroy.
[GOKU groans]
[MAJOR METALLITRON]
Destroy.
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU]
Uh... huh?
[WHITE and MURASAKI gasp]
[GOKU]
Oof!
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU] That's it!
I've had it with this fight!
[GOKU yelling]
[electricity fizzles]
[GOKU giggles]
[MAJOR METALLITRON]
Destroy.
Ugh, this guy is annoying me!
[GOKU growls]
[MAJOR METALLITRON]
Destroy...
Ka... me...
...ha...
...me...
[MAJOR METALLITRON
powering down]
Ha--uh??!
[GOKU]
Uh...
Huh?
Hiyah! Yah! Yah!
Uh...
Is it really over?
Get up, fool!
Get up!
Uh, I think his batteries
may have run out of juice.
His batteries?!
Well, I remember
they were changed
last spring sometime...
What a tough fight!
I hope there aren't any
more like him around here!
Hmmm...
It seems we
underestimated this boy.
Why are you still here?
Get to the fourth floor
and defend it!
[NARRATOR] Goku may have
beaten Major Metallitron,
but there's still
a long way to go
before he reaches
the top of the tower
and General White is
making sure there's plenty
to stand in his way!
Watch out, Goku!
Ninja Murasaki is coming!
[NARRATOR]
Back at the village,
as the air outside
fills with snow,
the air inside is
filled with worry!
Suno and her mother
hope against hope
that Goku will be
the first person to challenge
the Red Ribbon Army and escape
from Muscle Tower alive.
Can our hero possibly survive?
Find out in the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball!