[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball...
Goku was in hot pursuit
of the sinister General Blue,
who stole three Dragon Balls
from Master Roshi's island.
You'll get a blast out of this!
[NARRATOR] Unfortunately,
our hero fell victim
to the General's
dastardly trick.
But in the end, the evil villain
got his just deserts.
Bad man, but great fireworks.
[NARRATOR]
Goku landed in a strange place
known as Penguin Village,
where more adventure
awaits him - today!
Hi!
Huh? Oh, hi!
[SUN laughing]
Hello. What's your name?
I'm called Goku.
My name is Arale.
And this is Gatchan One and Two.
[GATCHANS cheering]
Wow, what strange little birds.
Would you like to come
play with us for a while?
That sounds like a lot of fun,
but I can't right now.
[GOKU]
I have to find the Dragon Balls.
Oh, and what is a Dragon Balls?
Hey Nimbus Cloud! Hurry back!
[GOKU grunts]
[ARALE, GACHANS gasp]
Cool! Hey, wait for me!
[ARALE]
Goku!
Huh?
[BLUE pants] I believe I owe
General White an apology.
I've never suffered
a task as difficult
as destroying that child.
[BLUE] Impossible! No one
could have survived that fall.
What is that kid made of?!
I could have sworn he crashed
somewhere around this mountain.
There it is!
But it doesn't look like
there's much left of the plane.
I hope the
Dragon Balls are safe.
[BLUE pants] What a nuisance!
He won't give up!
That little brat is
the bane of my existence.
He's not going to get
these Dragon Balls!
[BLUE grunts]
[GOKU] Nope, that's not it.
This is really strange.
There's no sign of
the balls anywhere.
Not a single one. Or the bag.
Everything's gone!
Including the bad man!
He must have gotten away
and taken the
Dragon Balls with him!
I know you're around
here somewhere!
[ARALE, GATCHANS cheering]
[ARALE giggles]
Gee, you guys are really fast.
Did you run all the way here?
Yes!
Incredible! You're as fast
as my Nimbus Cloud.
Maybe faster!
Who did you train with?
No one. I just like to run.
It's fun. You know,
you don't need this junk.
We have a playground.
I'm not here to play.
I'm looking for a bad man.
He took my Dragon Balls.
That's horrible.
Flying Nimbus!
I'd be happy to help
you look for your balls
if you need a hand.
Really? You wouldn't mind
doing that for me?
Sure. Would you mind giving
me a ride on your cloud?
Yeah, no problem.
If it lets you.
[ARALE grunts]
[ARALE giggles]
[GATCHANS giggle]
Whoa! You guys have
definitely been good.
Of course. Let's go.
You heard her. Let's go! Fly!
So, is this fun or what?
Yes!
[GATCHANS cheer]
Go Nimbus, go!
[ARALE]
Whoa!
Fly!
[GATCHANS, ARALE cheer]
[KIDS murmuring]
[BLUE]
Such a strange, backward place.
With one tank I could
conquer it in a day.
These simpletons would
think I was a god!
What have we here?
[KIDS]
Huh?
[KIDS whispering]
Hm?
[BLUE gasps]
[KIDS}
Bleh!
[BLUE grunting]
[KIDS giggling]
[BLUE]
Hmph!
Finally!
[BLUE]
Halt!
Hey, what's the big idea?!
Can't you see I'm
tryin' to drive here!
Stop whining.
Get out of the car.
What?! Why you little--
Nice pants you've
got there, pal.
[SOUR MAN laughs]
This should be fun.
All right, stranger.
I'm assuming you didn't
stop me for my autograph.
Hm. Wait here a moment.
I'll be right back.
I can tell this is
going to be a long day.
With the bite of a
sour prune I become...
...Sour Man! Incredibly
strong and regular.
Uh...
[SOUR MAN laughs]
Feel free to tremble.
For no one can resist
the might of Sour Man!
Perhaps. But I would lose
the bow tie if I were you.
What do you know about
being a superhero?!
Have you ever changed
clothes in a phone booth?!
Or spent hours combing your hair
just to get that perfect curl?!
Why, my dry-cleaning bill alone
would turn your hair white!
[SOUR MAN]
But let's cut to the chase.
Bear witness to the
awesome power that is me!
[SOUR MAN grunts]
[SOUR MAN whimpers]
Ha ha! There's plenty more
where that came from!
[BLUE chuckles]
[SOUR MAN grunting]
I do not wish
to harm you, stranger.
But if you do not
move out of my way,
I will be forced to
use extreme measures.
[SOUR MAN]
What do you think you're doing?!
Huh?
[BLUE chuckles]
[SOUR MAN sputters]
Ah ha ha... Well then,
okay, so, have you ever
thought about taking
a sidekick, sir?
I'm sure I could
free up my calendar.
I have plenty of lackeys.
What I need is transportation.
Ah, I understand.
What mode of travel
do you prefer?
I need something
that doesn't have feet.
Do you have an airplane?
Yes! An airplane would
be perfect, wouldn't it?!
Why didn't I think of that?!
[SOUR MAN laughs]
Actually, I don't.
Then perhaps you would
be so kind as to refer me
to someone who does.
Let's see now, who do
I know owns a plane?
Ah! Yes, I know!
Sembei Norimaki is who
you want to see, sir!
And where does this
Norimaki reside?
Yes, it's very simple.
Just head down this road
until you get to the sea.
Turn right, and his
house is on the left.
Nice car. You don't
mind if I use it.
Certainly. Certainly.
It's my privilege, sir.
Have a wonderful journey!
[SOUR MAN chuckles]
You can run, you fiendish rogue.
But Sour Man will still be here!
[KIDS giggling]
[alarm blaring]
[AKANE gasps]
Police! Pull your
vehicle over now!
Taro. What did I do this time?
That's Officer Soramame, miss.
And you were speeding.
Speeding! Didn't you see
how slow I was going?
Besides there's no one
on the road for miles.
Lucky for them.
In any case, there's no
excuse for speeding.
I have to issue you a ticket.
Please hand over your
license and registration.
Fine! But I'm telling
Mother what you did
to her flower garden.
Hey, look!
There's Akane and Taro!
Who?
[AKANE]
Hi, Arale.
Hi.
[AKANE]
And who is this?
I don't believe I've
ever seen you before.
[ARALE] He's just visiting.
His name is Goku.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
Is he a friend of yours?
[ARALE] Yes. We've been
having lots of fun.
Haven't we, Goku?
Yeah, you bet!
Hi. You were flyin' pretty fast.
Do you have a permit
for that cloud?
[ARALE] Akane here has
the coolest scooter in town.
My ride is nothing
compared to this beauty.
What do you call it?
It's called the Flying Nimbus.
It's neat-o! It even does tricks
and stuff. You should try it!
Would you mind? I've never
sat on a cloud before.
[GOKU] Sure. But you
should probably be careful--
[GOKU]
Nevermind.
Oww! What did I do wrong?
I don't know but it
must have been bad.
What?!
Only people with
clean minds and hearts
can ride aboard
the Nimbus Cloud.
[TARO giggling]
What are you laughing at?
You think this is funny?!
You're busted.
Oh yeah?! Then why
don't you try it?
Uh! My pleasure.
[AKANE laughs] Looks like your
star's a little tarnished, Taro.
I thought you were
supposed to be perfect.
But I'm the police?!
So a policeman is
someone who goes out
and tries to catch
the bad people?
That's our job, son.
I'm looking for
a bad person, too.
Maybe you've seen him.
Who? Is it someone
really dangerous,
like a bank robber?
I don't know,
but he's a member
of the Red Ribbon Army.
Did you say Red Ribbon Army?!
The Red Ribbon Army is
here in Penguin Village?
Yeah.
[TARO screams]
Uh...
What was that all about?
Taro?
The kid's gotta be mistaken.
It can't be true.
It's not true. There's no way
the Red Ribbon Army could
be in Penguin Village.
Believe me. The kid's
tellin' the truth.
I know it. They're here.
The Red Ribbon Army
is the most dangerous
criminal organization
on the planet.
What do they want with us?
I'm not sure.
It could be that they're
just passing through,
or, they may be planning
some sort of invasion.
[GARA, PAGOS]
An invasion?!
One thing is certain.
They didn't send one of
their soldiers out here
to help us meet this
month's ticket quota.
Come on! You stupid
piece of junk!
I just want to get
back to headquarters.
Oh, I could walk
faster than this!
[BLUE groans]
I said work! That's an order!
Huh? What's this?
[OBOTTCHA MAN]
Excuse me.
What's the matter with your car?
[BLUE] If I had to guess,
I would say it was broken.
Here, let me
take a look at it...
Oh, I see! This isn't so bad.
If you just connect this
wire and rotate that valve...
It'll just take a minute!
Hm... Ah!
[BLUE]
Such a kind and thoughtful boy.
He reminds me of...
...Samuel! My little brother.
Can it be that I've found
you after all these years?
I've missed you, little one.
--[BLUE gasps]
--See how easy that was.
It should work now.
Amazing! I can't believe it.
You have no idea what
this means to me!
It was my pleasure, sir.
I love automobiles.
Especially the vintage
models like yours.
You always did love to fix
things, didn't you, Samuel?
Sorry. You must have me
confused with someone else.
My name is Obottcha Man.
But you can call
me O.M. for short.
Everybody does. Well,
it was nice meeting you.
But I'd better be going now.
I'm late for a meeting. Goodbye!
No, wait! Samuel, come back!
Fool, when will you
realize your brother
is never coming back!
Focus on your mission!
[TARO screams]
Looks like I'm
about to trade up.
Hey, this might be him.
[BLUE chuckles]
I'll need to see your
license and registration.
I'm sorry, officer, well I
didn't carry them with me today.
Must have left 'em
in my other jacket.
Very well. Then you'll
need to come with us.
Stop! You're under arrest!
[BLUE chuckles]
[TARO screams]
[GARA, PAGOS scream]
[BLUE] So, what do you guys
do for fun around here?
Personally, I love to bowl.
[BLUE laughs]
[POLICE OFFICERS whimper]
Once again I'm in
need of an automobile.
Do you mind if I take yours?
Gladly, sir.
The keys are in the ignition!
[POLICE OFFICERS good-bying]
This is strange.
It's almost as if he
disappeared into thin air.
Oh, look. There's Taro!
[ARALE] Hey, Taro.
Are you okay? What happened?
It was terrible.
We tried to apprehend him,
but he's unstoppable.
So I was right.
The bad man is still alive!
Which way did he go?
Straight. Just
follow the sirens.
[GOKU]
Thanks for your help, policeman!
Hey, Goku! Wait for me!
[GOKU grunts]
Okay, you! I know you're
around here somewhere!
[BLUE laughs]
Missed me again.
[ARALE humming]
[ARALE yelps]
[ARALE] Ooh...
[GATCHANS] Ah!
[BLUE whimpers]
But I don't wanna go
to school today, Mummy.
Ah? Hello.
I don't suppose
you have a spare tire?
Are you hungry?
[GATCHANS munching]
Huh?
[BLUE whimpers]
[GATCHANS cooing]
Sorry about that. I'll find
you some more food.
I'm not hungry, thank you.
I don't think
I'll ever eat again.
Yoo-hoo? Yoo-hoo?
[ARALE]
Yum!
[BLUE whimpers]
What's the matter with you?!
Get that ugly thing
out of my face!
I don't know where it's been!
Zero fat. Tasty!
Do you have any idea
what you're holding?
It has a face! Get away from me!
All of you! You're all insane!
[ARALE] Maybe you'd like
to try a different flavor.
[BLUE yelps]
[GATCHANS] Yoo-hoo!
[ARALE, GATCHANS]
Ooh...
Yay!
Any luck finding that bad man?
Nothing yet. If I only
had a way to find him.
Hey, wait! I do have
something here I can use!
Bulma built this to find
the Dragon Balls...
and if he still has mine,
then wherever they are,
that's where he is too!
Oh no, it's broken again.
Oh...
I guess I'll have to
take it back home
and ask Bulma to repair it.
[ARALE]
Huh?
By the way, do you
know where we are?
No. But it's pretty.
Not here, this whole place!
I was chasing that
Red Ribbon guy so fast,
I didn't look where I was going.
Do you have any idea
how I can get back
to Master Roshi's island?
No, I sure don't.
Oh no. How can I
get the radar fixed
if I can't get home?
[ARALE]
Are you sure it's broken?
Yes.
Then that means
a doctor can fix it.
Really? Great! Do you
know where one lives?
Yep!
[GATCHANS]
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
[ARALE]
We're here!
What? What in the world is that?
[SEMBEI]
I've never seen that boy before.
Maybe it's a
long-lost relative...
Your side.
I have a cousin with a tail
but that doesn't look like her.
[ARALE]
There he is. He's the doctor.
Hey there-- I mean,
hello. How are you?
Fine. And you?
Goku, over there.
Are you his wife?
[ARALE] Sir, we were wondering
if you could repair this?
Okay. Your watch?
No, sir. It's a Dragon Radar.
Dragon Radar?
You hunt dragons
with this thing?
Dragon Balls.
There are seven in all and
the radar helps me find them.
That's fine...
But I need to know how
it works, what makes it tick.
I believe it works by
detecting the unique
energy signatures emitted
by certain objects.
Oh, yeah...
[SEMBEI] First I need
to get inside the machine
and make a diagnostic appraisal.
Its construction looks
simple enough.
[SEMBEI gasps]
What in the world is that?!
I've never seen
anything like this before!
Look at all the colors!
It's really high-tech!
Who could design such a thing?!
A girl named Bulma made it.
Huh? Girl?! You say
a little girl made this
complex machine?
That's impossible!
[ALL]
Ooh...
[NARRATOR]
Little does Goku know,
but the Dragon Balls
are coming to him,
as General Blue makes
his way to Sembei's house.
Can our hero stop
this one-man army?
Or will he wreak more
havoc on Penguin Village?
Find out on the next
episode of Dragon Ball!