[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball,
a damaged, but determined Goku,
summoned one, last
powerful punch,
and put a super
sized hole in Piccolo!
--[GOKU yelling]
--[PICCOLO groans]
[NARRATOR] This daring attack
sealed Piccolo's fate for good.
[GOKU]
I won!
[NARRATOR] But Piccolo wasn't
about to lose the battle
and just walk away.
He had something special to
leave behind for planet Earth.
[PICCOLO]
Good luck, my son.
Get revenge for my demise.
Destroy all of my enemies.
[groaning]
[NARRATOR] The defeated
demon went out with a bang,
and sent Goku into a tailspin.
Luckily, Yajirobe was there
to catch him before he hit
the ground. The battle was over,
but Goku soon learned
that his dearest friends
had become victims
of Piccolo's madness.
[GOKU]
What about Master Roshi?
Is it true he's gone?
[TIEN]
Yes, it's true.
And Chaiotzu as well.
[GOKU]
The Eternal Dragon?
[NARRATOR] With no way of
summoning the Eternal Dragon,
will Goku be forced to accept
the loss of his closest friends?
Bye.
See ya!
[groaning]
What, is that--?
[groans]
--[YAMCHA, BULMA grunt]
--[LAUNCH gasps]
It's a little too quiet here.
Yeah.
[BULMA]
I wonder what happened?
[YAMCHA]
I'm not sure.
We'd better move in
and get a closer look.
That looked a lot like Goku in
that air car that just flew by.
So do you think he beat Piccolo?
Shh. Come on, hurry up.
If he did win, then I wonder
what happened to Tien?
[LAUNCH gasps]
--[BULMA] Shh.
--[LAUNCH whimpering]
[screams]
[YAMCHA, BULMA gasp]
[TIEN groaning]
Is that Tien?
[LAUNCH, BULMA, YAMCHA cheering]
[BULMA]
It's really you.
Yes, I'm very happy
to see all of you again.
[groans]
I guess that Piccolo was a
pretty tough fighter, wasn't he?
He demolished a
whole city by himself.
And you won. Mm.
Good. Almost there.
That's great!
So Goku won the battle?
[TIEN sighs]
Yeah, you should have seen him.
I've got so much to tell you.
--Hi, T.V. Central?
--[REPORTER] Uh-huh.
I just wanna let you know
that the battle's over,
and everyone's all right!
[REPORTER] Are you serious?
It's really over?
[BULMA] That's right! He's been
defeated. Piccolo is dead!
[REPORTER]
But how can that be?
Who in the world is
powerful enough to do that?
[BULMA]
Well, let's just say good has
won out over evil once again!
[REPORTER] That's great, but I
need a name to tell the people.
Bye!
[REPORTER]
Wait! Hello?
Ladies and gentlemen,
Piccolo is gone.
He has been defeated!
There's nothing to worry about.
Eastern City, I mean the whole
world is safe once again.
[CROWD cheering]
Did you hear that?
Everything's gonna be all right.
It's over, we are free!
[BOTH gasp]
--[CROWD cheering]
--[LITTLE GIRL laughs]
[PILOT A] That's a big 10-4,
Piccolo is no more!
The battle is finally
over. We're free! Over.
[PILOT B] Copy that! I'll meet
you back at headquarters.
Over and out!
[CROWD cheering]
Without Piccolo around,
I can concentrate on all the
other bad guys around town.
--[WANTED MAN grunts]
--[POLICE OFFICER gasps]
You're just in time! I decided
to turn over a new leaf anyway.
Congratulations on behalf
of everyone, my king.
Thanks, but I believe we owe
everything to that little boy.
[NUMBER 8]
Hurray for Goku.
Thanks to him, the
world is safe again.
Mm. That's right.
He won!
Hear that? It must
mean Goku won.
Great! Thatta boy!
It's time to wake up,
Goku. We made it.
[groans]
[YAJIROBE]
We're at Master Korin's place.
Good to see you alive,
Goku. Nice work.
Master, I need your help.
Please, help me.
Hey, kiddo,
don't worry about it.
I'll take care of
all your wounds
until you are as good as new.
Uh? It's not that. Uh...
Huh?
I'm hungry.
[gasps]
No way! You mean he was
really that powerful out there?
It's true, even I'm
no match for him anymore.
As far as I can tell,
he must be the most
powerful guy in history.
I bet Krillin would have
somethin' to say about that,
if he were here now.
[sighs]
[ALL sigh]
I'm sure he'd be
jealous. Ya think?
That's 'cause he and Goku were
always trying to
out do each other.
Outgrow each other?
--[OOLONG] Huh?
--[TURTLE] Uh...
[BOTH laugh]
[ALL laugh]
You know, I sure wish
the dragon were around.
[OOLONG sighs]
[OOLONG]
Without him,
those Dragon Balls are nothing
more than worthless stones.
[ALL sigh]
[WOMAN humming]
[gibber]
Uh?
[screams]
[WOMAN]
Oh no, it's a giant egg!
[JEBEDIAH grunts]
[JEBEDIAH]
Come on, I don't have all day.
We interrupt our
regular programming,
to bring you a special
presentation of our
award winning docudrama called,
"How the Mysterious Boy
Defeated Piccolo."
Catchy title, huh? Enjoy!
[WOMAN]
Oh no, Jebediah! Help!
Help me. Ah!
--What's all the racket about?
--[WOMAN screams]
Come on, the whole
world is at peace now.
Is it too much to get a little
peace in my own home?
It was the biggest egg
I'd ever seen. Huge!
I thought it was
going to get me,
like a big fish floating
by with nowhere to go.
A big egg?
[WOMAN]
Is it a dinosaur egg?
Yeah, it might be.
Oh! Maybe it could be a child.
You know, like a gift from
the heavens or somethin'?
You're kidding?
I'd almost bet on it, my dear.
Then, crack it open.
Then go get my club. Hurry up!
[WOMAN]
Mm-hm.
[screams]
[BOTH scream]
[BOTH gasping]
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
[BOTH gasp, scream]
[GOKU laughs]
[GOKU]
Look at me!
I'm cured! Ha! Yeah, I feel
great! I'm good! I'm great!
[GOKU laughs]
And a- one, two, three...
[KORIN] Those Senzu Beans
really did the trick, huh?
I'm beginning to understand how
you were able to beat
Piccolo on your own.
The way you've recovered
from your injuries
is truly remarkable, Goku.
Master Korin, didn't you let
Piccolo go because you were
afraid you'd lose to him if
you fought him yourself?
Uh... I, uh...
Well, to be completely honest,
I thought the odds would be
better if Goku fought Piccolo
instead of me.
I'm glad things turned out
the way they did, though.
You fought an impressive battle.
You really should
be happy to be alive.
Wow.
What else could I do?
Goku was our only hope,
and if he lost the fight that
would mean it'd be up to me
to take care of things.
[GOKU]
Mm?
It was all part of my plan.
Someone had to be around to
collect all the Dragon Balls.
My boy, had you of lost,
I'da revived you,
as well as everyone else
destroyed by Piccolo.
So Master Korin, you knew about
the Dragon Balls the whole time?
[grunts] Of course I did.
You see, I know everything.
Then I guess it's no big secret
if I tell you the Eternal
Dragon was killed by Piccolo?
What did you say?
No, really? The Eternal
Dragon is no more?
Oh, no. I never thought
Piccolo was strong enough
to do something like that.
It's not fair!
If the Eternal Dragon
was alive today,
he could bring
everyone back to life.
There's nothing you can do
about it, Goku. Just let it go.
People are always getting
into trouble all the time.
It can't be stopped.
That's just the way it is.
[KORIN]
Mm-hm.
Yes, it's quite correct,
but don't forget,
those people who were
attacked by Piccolo
must spend eternity all alone,
and will never be able
to rest in peace.
[gasps]
It's true. There is no way for
them to go to the other world
because their lifeless
bodies float in limbo.
The poor souls'll
be lost forever,
unless they are revived
by the Dragon Balls.
That's good to know.
I'm glad Piccolo didn't get me.
That's terrible!
My friends are going
to be miserable forever,
and there is nothing we can do?
That's right.
There is nothing we can do
now that the dragon's gone.
No! Hold on, I think we
might have a chance left.
[BOTH gasp]
Are you sure?
I can't believe I could forget
such an important thing.
Yes, this might just work.
Great. What do we do?
It's simple,
you just have to meet the one
who created the Dragon Balls,
and ask him to bring the
Eternal Dragon back to life.
You mean a person actually
created the Dragon Balls?
Of course, silly.
It's not like they just appeared
out of thin air on their own.
[KORIN]
It's true.
So who is it?
You mean you don't
know who made them?
It was Kami, of course.
Who's he?
Hey, what's the deal?
Is this some kind of joke?
I thought you really
wanted to help us.
Instead, you make
up some crazy story.
So all I have to do
is meet this Kami guy,
and he'll revive my friends?
[YAJIROBE]
Hey, Goku.
[GOKU grunts]
Come on, you know this
Kami guy doesn't exist.
He's just make believe.
Korin's just pullin'
your leg, that's all.
Oh, he exists all right.
But if you want to meet him,
you must be strong
and pure of heart.
Only a chosen few have
proven worthy enough
to have a personal
meeting with Kami.
[KORIN]
Hello!
Yeah?
Goku, you have earned
this right to meet Kami,
whereas Yajirobe has not!
Who cares?
That's great! So when do
I get to go and meet him?
[KORIN] Kami is here,
on top of this temple.
[GOKU gasps]
No way! He's up here? Come on.
This is the top of the temple.
[KORIN] Well, Kami is floating
high above the tower.
And when I say floating
high up in the sky,
I mean really high,
smarty-pants!
Is this another one of your
practical jokes, Korin?
You're not fooling me.
There's nobody
floating up there.
[GOKU]
Yeah, I don't see anything.
[KORIN]
You'll just have to trust me.
Good! All I have
to do is fly up there.
[KORIN] That's impossible. You
can't go any higher than this.
Ah. I bet he could get up there
pretty fast on the
back of a rocket ship.
[laughs]
Oh, no, that won't work either.
Even if you took a
rocket up there,
I know Kami would send
it back right away.
He doesn't like to be disturbed.
Okay. So, I'm stuck here,
unless there's another
way up to the top?
[KORIN chuckles]
Oh Goku, you already
have a way to get there,
and you don't even
know it, do ya?
Remember you have that very
special Power Pole of yours?
Use it, and it'll
take you to Kami.
Use my Power Pole?
The Power Pole was
originally created
to get the owner from
Earth to this temple.
You see, a long time ago,
Master Roshi begged me
to lend it to him,
so I let him have it.
I thought he'd be the last.
I didn't think anyone else
would be qualified to carry it,
until you came along.
I see. I never realized
it was that important,
but it was a big help
when I fought Piccolo.
I'd better hold on to it.
[GOKU]
Uh, uh... Hey! It's gone.
[gasps]
Where'd it go?
I know what happened to it.
You dropped it when
you fought Piccolo.
You're right!
Flying Nimbus!
[KORIN]
Find that Power Pole, Goku!
It's the only way to get Kami.
I'm counting on you.
Mm. Don't worry. I'm gonna
find it, Master Korin.
No matter what it takes.
[GOKU thinking]
I never knew my Power Pole
had such a secret past.
So, King, what are
you going to do now?
The first thing will
be to rebuild the city,
and then next, the castle.
After that, you'll
have to wait and see.
Next question, please.
[REPORTER A]
Uh, King, do you know
the identity of the boy
who defeated Piccolo?
[REPORTER B]
Yeah, who is he?
Uh, the boy? Ah...
[REPORTER A]
What is that? Is that a cloud?
--[KING] Huh?
--[CROWD gasps, screams]
--[KING] It's him!
--[OFFICER gasps]
Hold your fire!
[OFFICERS grumble]
Oh, I'm so glad
you could come.
I've been looking
forward to meeting you.
Sir, have you seen
my Power Pole?
Power Pole?
Yeah it's about this long.
[KING]
Do you know anything about this?
We haven't found anything like
that. Everything was destroyed.
There's nothing left but ashes.
It must have disintegrated
in the blast.
So that boy is the one
who defeated Piccolo?
[KING] Yes! We all owe him
a great big thank you.
What do I do now?
[GOKU gasps]
Your name?
And your date of birth?
What's your favorite color?
Are you married yet?
[REPORTERS chatter]
I've got to get my
Power Pole back!
[GOKU]
Oh no! It can't be gone.
[GOKU gasps]
Wait a minute, I know
who can help me. Baba!
She'll know what to do! [laughs]
Wait, please! Where are
you going? Come back!
What a mysterious little boy.
[GOKU]
So that's what happened.
Can you help me find
my Power Pole, Baba?
Please, I'll do anything to get
it back. You just gotta help me.
So I see.
You want me to find this
Power Pole that helped
you defeat Piccolo,
is that right?
Yeah, can you do it?
[BABA] Let's take a look
in my crystal ball.
Oh, boy!
[GOKU laughs]
Don't get your hopes up,
I just got this out of the shop.
Right. I'm getting a vision.
It's getting clearer,
and clearer. A-ha!
Oh, it's his house. That's where
you'll find your Power Pole.
You mean it's there,
inside Master Roshi's house?!
Thank you.
I still can't believe it,
a kid like that saved the world.
And now he gets to meet
Kami face to face?
I guess it's true, some
people are just born lucky.
I know what you mean.
That explains how I
ended up working for you.
[BABA]
Hm...
[laughing]
Hello!
[ALL gasp]
Oh, Goku!
Where's my Power Pole?
--[BULMA] Goku!
--[LAUNCH giggles]
--[OOLONG] Goku?
--[GOKU grunts]
I knew you'd need it,
so I put it over there.
[gasps]
It was here? Well, where did
it go? Is it missing again?
Uh. Not back here. Not in here.
Nope. Ah!
[LAUNCH gasps]
[ALL gasp]
Uh? Uh...
[laughs]
Here you go!
[GOKU laughs]
You found it.
You dropped it while you
were fighting Piccolo,
so I grabbed it and
brought it back here.
That's great. Now I can
use this to meet Kami,
and if all goes well,
Master Roshi and Krillin
will come back.
[BOTH]
Uh...
Thanks everybody,
I'll see ya later!
And I'll be back with
Krillin and Master Roshi.
What did he say?
He's going to bring
them back to life?
He's going to meet Kami?
[GOKU laughs]
[GOKU] Now I know everything's
going to be fine!
Look up there, it's that
kid that beat Piccolo!
Whoa.
[GOKU laughing]
[GOKU thinking] I can't wait
to see my old friends again!
[CROWD cheers]
[NARRATOR] Now that
Goku has his Power Pole,
he'll be able to meet Kami,
and with any luck, bring
his friends back to life!
But all is not well in the world
because a new danger is growing.
An old enemy has been reborn,
and he's got his mind
set on only one thing,
getting even with Goku!
[BOTH scream]
This is just the start.
I'll get Goku. He's all mine.
I'll have my revenge.
[PICCOLO JR. chuckles]
[NARRATOR] Piccolo's back,
and Goku had better watch out.
See what this monster
has up his sleeve,
on the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball!