[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball,
the search for the
third Dragon Ball led Goku,
Bulma, and Krillin
into an old Pirate's cave!
The only thing more dangerous
than the booby traps
they encountered
was the deadly General Blue,
who was secretly
pursuing the trio!
But, as the general soon
learned, not even his own men
were immune to the ingenious
traps the pirates had set
to protect their lair and
the treasures hidden within!
[ALL gasp]
[KRILLIN]
Creepy!
These skulls have lights
coming from their eye sockets!
[GOKU]
I hope this isn't another trap!
[BULMA] You never know
what these pirates
could have rigged up.
[ALL screaming]
[NARRATOR]
While Goku and the others
fought for dear life, General
Blue met with perils of his own
as he found himself in the death
grip of a giant electric eel!
[NARRATOR] For every
danger that was survived,
a new threat was lurking
just around the corner!
Wow! It's like a city here!
[BULMA, KRILLIN]
Yeah
[NARRATOR] But just when
it seemed that the worst
was behind our heroes, and that
all of the pirates' resources
were at their disposal,
something was found
lurking in the shadows!
[BULMA whimpers]
[NARRATOR] It seems that those
who had long ago abandoned
this secret underwater port
had left behind a guardian --
a titanic, swashbuckling
robotic pirate!
And he wasn't
taking any prisoners!
[GOKU, KRILLIN, BULMA yelp]
[BULMA, GOKU, KRILLIN panting]
[NARRATOR]
Is there any hope of defeating
the menacing metal giant?
Or is it time to walk the plank?
[ROBOT]
Yo, Ho, Ho.
[BULMA whimpering]
[KRILLIN whimpering]
What a magnificent little toy...
[ROBOT]
Arr, matey!
[BULMA, GOKU KRILLIN yelp]
[BULMA yells]
[GOKU yelping]
[KRILLIN yelping]
Look out!
Oh, my.
[GOKU, KRILLIN grunt]
[GOKU grunting]
Both of these kids are experts!
[KRILLIN, GOKU yelp]
[KRILLIN, GOKU grunt]
[KRILLIN, GOKU yell]
[KRILLIN, GOKU yelling]
[KRILLIN, GOKU yelling, panting]
[KRILLIN yells]
[GOKU yells]
[KRILLIN grunting]
[GOKU groans]
All right!
[GOKU, KRILLIN yelling]
[KRILLIN, GOKU yelp]
[GOKU growls]
[KRILLIN grunts]
[KRILLIN yelping]
[GOKU grunts]
Banzai!
[KRILLIN grunts]
[KRILLIN gasps, groans]
Huh?
[GOKU]
Krillin! Get up!
[KRILLIN growls, yelps]
He's not giving up! Is he?
Doubt it!
[BULMA] He must have been
built to defend this port!
Unbelievable! What a robot!
[BULMA gasps]
[ROBOT]
Shiver me timbers!
[KRILLIN]
Goku! Look out!
[GOKU grunting]
[KRILLIN yelps]
Take cover!
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU yelps]
Hey, careful!
[BULMA screams]
[KRILLIN screams]
[BLUE] Huh?
[GOKU] Aaaah!
[GOKU growls]
Uh, oh!
[GOKU panting]
[GOKU gasps]
[KRILLIN]
Ooh...
[BULMA]
He did it!
[KRILLIN]
Yay! Way to go, Goku!
You did it! All right!
[BULMA]
That was awesome, kid!
Hey, Goku, what's wrong?
Uhh...
That!
[BULMA, KRILLIN scream]
[GOKU yelps]
[BULMA, KRILLIN whimpering]
[KRILLIN]
Hey!
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU panting]
[BULMA]
What are we doing?
[KRILLIN]
Come on!
[GOKU panting]
[BULMA grunting]
[BULMA]
A little more!
[KRILLIN grunting]
[BULMA]
That's it!
Yeah!
[GOKU panting]
[BULMA]
Yeah! We did it!
[BLUE gasping]
[BLUE] She's going to bring
this whole place down!
[BULMA] Yay!
[KRILLIN] You hit Goku!
[BULMA]
Oh, my gosh! I'm sorry, Goku!
[BULMA, KRILLIN gasp]
Go get him, Krillin!
No way!
[KRILLIN, BULMA screaming]
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU panting]
[BULMA grunting]
[KRILLIN, BULMA scream]
[GOKU panting]
[BULMA]
Turn! Turn! Turn! Turn!
[GOKU screams]
[KRILLIN, BULMA scream]
[BULMA, KRILLIN yelping]
Those are my friends
you're shooting at!
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKY screams]
[KRILLIN]
Goku!
[BULMA, KRILLIN whimper]
Yikes!
Oh, no you don't!
[BULMA yells]
[KRILLIN yells]
[KRILLIN]
Is he dead?
[ALL gasp]
[BULMA]
I-I guess so!
Well, well! They're good!
For kids, I'd say
they're darn good!
[BULMA]
Superb technology!
And to think he was built
centuries ago! By pirates!
[GOKU] Are you sure
the pirates are dead?
[KRILLIN, BULMA]
Huh?
[GOKU] It's strange,
but even with the robot gone,
I still feel like
we're being watched!
What? Really?
[GOKU]
Mhm!
Why'd you have to say that?
Let's get outta here!
Now that you've said that,
I've got the willies! Big time!
[KRILLIN]
Wait up!
Come on, Goku!
[GOKU]
I'm coming!
[GOKU yelps]
[BULMA, KRILLIN gasp]
[GOKU grunting]
[KRILLIN, BULMA gasp]
[GOKU gasping]
[KRILLIN]
Are you all right?
Me? All right? Me who?
Uh...
[BULMA]
Goku!
[GOKU groaning]
[GOKU screams]
That must have hurt!
Nah! It tickled! Silly rock!
[BULMA]
Goku! Above you! Look out!
Uh?
[KRILLIN] Ow!
[BULMA] Oh, no!
[KRILLIN, BULMA scream]
[KRILLIN, BULMA whimper]
[BULMA, KRILLIN panting]
Nasty! Ick!
Huh?
[KRILLIN grunting]
[KRILLIN] B-Bulma d-d-do
you see wh-wh-what I see?
[BULMA whimpering]
[BULMA, KRILLIN scream]
[BULMA, KRILLIN panting]
[BULMA]
Come on!
[BULMA] I don't believe it!
We're really gonna die!
[KRILLIN] Great pep talk,
Bulma! Thanks a lot!
[BULMA, KRILLIN panting]
[BULMA]
This way!
Hurry, before he sees us!
[BULMA, KRILLIN panting]
[BULMA]
Wow! Check it out!
[KRILLIN]
Hey! We were just there!
[BULMA] Yeah! Amazing!
This must be the command center
for the whole port!
[KRILLIN] Really! Were they
swashbucklers or scientists?
[BULMA whimpers]
Krillin!
[KRILLIN]
What?
[BULMA]
We're not alone!
Wh-Who are you?
Hey there, buddy!
[BULMA grunts]
[BULMA, KRILLIN gasp]
[KRILLIN]
Gross!
Gosh! I wish my dad were here
to see this! He'd flip!
These old computers are like
priceless antiques to him!
Hey! Maybe I can turn off
ol' Metal-breath from here!
How much time are we
talking about here, Bulma?
I don't know!
This system's so old!
Can you do it?
Well, my Dad always says:
Where there's a will,
there's a way!
[GOKU grunting]
My goodness, look at him go!
A very worthy opponent indeed!
[GOKU grunting]
Hmm?
Hurry, Bulma! We're next!
Darn this thing!
[BULMA] The file structure
makes no sense!
[KRILLIN yelps]
B-B-Bulma! Time's up!
[ROBOT]
Arr!
[BULMA screams]
Bulma!
Power Pole, extend!
Haaa!
[BULMA]
Let's get outta here!
[KRILLIN]
What do you want me to do? Jump?
[BULMA] Well, yeah!
[KRILLIN] No!
Oh, hi, guys!
[BULMA, KRILLIN gasp]
And where the heck
have you been?
Really!
[KRILLIN, BULMA]
Hmm?
[BULMA screams]
[BULMA yelping]
[GOKU laughs]
Silly pirate!
[KRILLIN]
Goku! Let's get outta here!
[GOKU]
You guys go ahead!
Hurry! He's about
to be down there!
[KRILLIN] Whoa!
[BULMA] Come on!
[GOKU]
Power Pole, retract!
[BULMA]
Hurry! Keep going!
Oh, yes! Dragon Ball time!
All right! Aerial Attack!
[GOKU]
Come on! Stay for a second!
Good!
'Kay!
A One!
And a two!
Three!
[GOKU yelling]
Haaaaa!
Haaaaaaa!
[GOKU growling]
[GOKU]
Hyaaa!
Ha! Gotcha!
[BULMA]
Let's see!
Hmm. Strange!
Bulma! I'm worried about Goku!
I'm sure he's fine, Krillin!
[BOTH gasp]
[KRILLIN]
This whole place could cave in!
We'd better hurry up!
According to the radar,
we're practically on top
of the Dragon Ball!
Let's go!
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU]
This place is falling apart!
It should be right up ahead
just a little bit further!
[KRILLIN]
Oh, great! Now what?
Which way do we go?
[BULMA] It's gotta be
this way, Krillin! Come on!
[KRILLIN]
Whoa!
This oughta do it!
There!
[BULMA]
Good thinking!
[BLUE cackling] This should
spice things up a bit!
[GOKU]
Uh, oh! Which way?
Hum!
Hey! Krillin must
have drawn that!
They went this way!
[BLUE laughing]
[BLUE]
Little naïve twerp!
[KRILLIN] If we don't get out
of here soon, we're history!
We can't turn back now!
We're too close!
[KRILLIN]
Oh, great!
[BULMA]
What are we going to do?
[KRILLIN]
Look! Is that a stairwell?
Nope! It's a well well!
I hate to say it,
but it's the only way!
[BLUE]
What? I have to get wet?
Ew! I swear!
I knew I should have packed my
bikini trunks in my field kit!
Mmm! What a bod!
Bulma! Krillin! Where are you!
[GOKU]
Where could they be?
Bulma's not that fast!
I should have caught up
with them by now!
[NARRATOR]
As the dangerous Blue closes in
on his unsuspecting prey, Goku
gets further and further away
with every determined step!
Is there any hope
for his friends?
Join us next time
on Dragon Ball!