[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball,
Goku had a brush with stardom
as he fought Pamput,
a famous athlete
and action star.
The fourth match of
the quarter-finals,
with its talented contenders,
appeared to have all the
ingredients of a classic fight.
[PAMPUT yells]
[NARRATOR] However,
with Goku's first attack,
Pamput was immobilized, falling
short of fans' expectations.
Goku's superior fighting skills
not only won him the match,
but hundreds of adoring fans.
Of course, not everyone found
the boy's achievement amusing--
namely Tien, who vowed to
destroy Goku in the ring.
While Goku and Krillin
rejoiced over the victory,
Jackie Chun tempered their
excitement by warning them
not to underestimate the
incredible power of Tien...
...his next challenger
in the fifth match.
The tournament continues, now!
[TIEN] Goku's attack on Pamput
was calm and efficient.
I would have made
similar choices.
I may have actually found an
opponent worthy of my time.
[SHEN]
First things first.
Fighting Goku is in the future.
You need to focus
on the present,
which is your match
against Jackie Chun.
[TIEN] You're right, Master.
And Chun is skillful.
[TIEN]
Like the perfect predator,
he studies his prey, learns
their weakness, then waits...
[TIEN] ...until he finds the
best opportunity to attack.
To him there are no obstacles.
Not even his age.
[SHEN] For being such
an accomplished warrior,
it's odd that I've never
heard of him before.
We know so little about him.
That's what makes
him so dangerous.
[TIEN]
Mm.
[CHIAOTZU]
Uh. Look!
[SHEN]
Hm?
[TURTLE grunts, gasps]
[exhales deeply]
[SHEN] Well, well...
If it isn't Jackie Chun.
[chuckles]
I have an idea.
--[TIEN] Master Shen.
--[SHEN] Hm?
Let's test his strength
against Chiaotzu's.
[SHEN]
Ah! You mean now?
[TIEN]
Mhmm!
[SHEN]
But my ice cream!
I could use something to eat.
Are you hungry again, already?
How is that possible?
We just ate an hour ago.
An hour? No wonder I'm hungry.
Do you mind telling me where
you keep your spare stomach?
Eh, excuse me, but has anyone
seen Master Roshi lately?
[CHUN] Hrm!
He lives to aggravate me.
Maybe he got lost again.
[CHUN]
What do you mean, "again"?
I've never been lost!
It's more likely
he was told to get lost
by the countless number of
ladies he's been talking to
since he got here!
[laughs]
[CHUN] I've been meaning
to do this for a long time.
If he's trying to meet people,
he may be around the shops.
You're right. If I were
him, that's where I'd go!
[CHUN]
The shops, huh?! Well!
[BULMA]
Yeah, the city is crowded
with all sorts of people!
[CHUN] Oh, boy! You don't
have to tell me twice!
[laughs]
I just remembered there's, uh,
something I need to do, okay?!
[chuckles nervously]
[CHUN]
Oh-ho, yeah!
Perfect. This is going
to be easier than I thought.
[CHUN humming]
Nice hairdo!
[chuckles]
Nice pair of shoes!
What exactly are you
planning to do, Tien?
It's a surprise, Master.
One I think you'll like.
Bang! Bang!
Bang!
Chiaotzu, wanna play?
[CHIAOTZU]
Mhmm!
[CHUN] Nice shop you got here.
You sell ball caps?
Or sing-along tapes?
I don't get many
requests for caps.
And I'm afraid I just
sold my last two tapes.
[CHUN]
Eeeh...
--[DAD] Look out!
--[KID] Bang!
--[DAD] There!
--[KID laughs] Bang!
[CHUN]
There's a lot of people out,
but not much excitement.
Where do folks go
around here to unwind?
At least she's having fun.
[chuckles quietly]
[laughs]
Bang!
[KID] Wow...
[CHUN]
Hey!
[LADY CLERK gasps]
He ducked!
[BOTH]
Aaah...!
It appears Jackie Chun has
gotten wind of your scheme.
[TIEN]
Impossible!
[whimpers]
[CHUN] I didn't know
you had freckles.
--[LADY CLERK grunts]
--[CHUN groans]
[whimpers]
You scared me. Sorry.
[ALL gasp]
One punch?! Good work, Goku!
The next match is Jackie Chun
versus Tien Shinhan.
Tien Shinhan!
[grumbles]
Oh, please don't get upset,
Yamcha. Jackie will win!
No!
Ha!
[bellows]
[ALL screaming]
Okay...How did he--
Aah!
--[TIEN grunts]
--[YAMCHA yells]
[YAMCHA] I've had my share
of tough opponents.
But none have been as cunning
or dangerous as Tien.
He ripped through me
like a rag doll.
No one can stop him.
Not even Jackie Chun.
Aah!
[YAMCHA]
I hope I'm wrong.
I hope Jackie Chun does win...
...for Goku's sake.
Huh...?
Oh! My aching face!
What happened to you? You've
been gone a while--where?
Well... I... uh...
I-I just went somewhere
to warm up for the fight.
That's right.
Your match is next.
I'll be rooting for you.
Me, too! Get in there and
clobber that guy for Yamcha!
[KRILLIN]
We're not asking for much.
Just rip out his spine!
No. I'm the one who has
to beat Tien Shinhan.
I promised I would,
for Yamcha!
[CHUN]
I understand the frustration
all of you are feeling.
Now then...
Tien is a tough cookie.
But he won't find it
easy to defeat me.
[TIEN grunting]
Relax your mind, Tien.
I told you to focus on your
fight, not worry about it.
Jackie Chun
presents a challenge,
but nothing
that should overwhelm
a student of the Crane.
[TIEN]
I will crush them all.
First Chun...
and then... and then...
Goku! From this point forward,
that is my goal. My purpose!
[drum roll]
[drum roll increases]
[CROWD cheering]
[ANNOUNCER] The fifth match
is about to get underway.
At this time we
ask that fighters
Tien Shinhan and Jackie Chun
prepare for entry into the ring.
It's time. This should
be interesting.
[CHUN]
Let's go.
♪
[CROWD cheering]
And now, with the fifth match,
we enter our
semi-finals round.
This is the final
leg of the tournament
before we reach
the Championship Round
and determine who will become
the next Master of Martial Arts!
[SHEN] Just get on with it,
Johnny McBlabbermouth!
Any minute now,
the participants will--wait!
I think I see them.
Yes! Here they come now!
Tien Shinhan representing
the Crane school...
and the one
and only Jackie Chun,
winner of the last tournament!
Good luck, Jackie!
We're rooting for you!
[ANNOUNCER] Audience,
please remember that
use of flash photography
is strictly prohibited
during the match,
unless you catch my good side!
Just kidding, folks!
In all seriousness,
we're in for a stellar
fight as Tien Shinhan,
winner of the first match,
tries to best Jackie Chun,
whose hair-raising
victory in Match Two
gave us all moment "two paws."
Champion, no matter what
it takes, I will defeat you.
Hey, take it easy.
You shouldn't stress out.
It makes you lose your hair.
[CHUN chuckles]
Ready... You may begin, now!
[gong rings]
Tien! Get ready for
some payback, Chun style!
You can tell he's scared.
Jackie destroyed the moon!
He can certainly
take out ol' tri-clops!
I don't think so.
Huh?! What are you saying?!
[TIEN grunting]
[GOKU] I bet Tien Shinhan is
a lot stronger than we think.
He uses techniques
I've never heard of.
Both of them have a chance
at winning the match.
What? Really?
[CHUN grunts lowly]
How should we start? Slowly?
Or will you try to end this
quickly with a fierce charge?
[TIEN] So, you've decided
to take a defensive position.
Then I shall be the one
who commences the attack!
[yells]
[TIEN groans]
[TIEN yells]
[CROWD gasps]
--[GROUP cheering]
--[OOLONG yelling]
[PUAR]
Go Jackie!
--[GROUP cheering]
--[OOLONG yelling]
[CROWD chattering]
[CROWD gasps, murmurs]
See what I mean?
You'd think he'd
do something original.
Cheater!
[OOLONG]
Uh!
Thanks for the spin, but I have
my own means of transportation.
Mm! It was supposed
to be a one-way trip.
Heh. Your jokes are almost
as bad as your strategy.
[grunts]
[TIEN yells]
Oh my!
--[GOKU] He's gone!
--[CHUN] Eh?
[bellows]
[TIEN yells]
[CHUN grunts]
[CROWD gasps]
[TIEN yells]
[TIEN] You don't fight like
any old man I've ever known!
[CHUN] Pretty strong
for such a young punk.
[TIEN grunting]
All right! No more nice guy!
[bellows]
How can there be
three Jackie Chuns?!
Tha-That's impossible!
The mirror-image
technique, huh?!
Wow! It's like there's a
whole army of Jackie Chuns!
--[CHIAOTZU] One... Two...
--[SHEN grunts]
--[CHIAOTZU screams]
--[SHEN] There are eight!
Smart move. Tien won't know
which Jackie to watch out for!
[grunting]
[yells]
Jackie's done it!
Tien doesn't have a hope in
the world of defeating him now!
[laughs]
He might.
[CHUN] What's the matter?
Am I too much for ya?!
Chun... I'm disappointed.
Are you so scared of me
you have to hide behind
that second-rate trick?
Three eyes are better
than eight Chuns any day!
I choose...
...you!
[CHUN groans]
No, Jackie!
[TIEN chuckles]
What good's a third eye
if it can't help you out
from time to time, right?
Good choice.
Seems I underestimated you.
I can tell this fight's
gonna take brawn and brain.
Boo!
[Bulma]
Huh?
Aah! Hey!
Oh! Get this off of me!
--[PUAR] Oh no, look out!
--[BULMA] I can't see!
Aah!
I'm gonna pound you
into dust, old-timer!
[yelling]
[TIEN grunting]
[yells, groans]
[TIEN]
Uuuah!
He did it!
It's over!
--[KRILLIN laughing]
--[GOKU] Not yet.
Uh?
[CHUN]
Mm?!
[TIEN yells, grunts]
--[CHUN] What?!
--[KRILLIN] Oh no!
[SHEN chuckles]
[TIEN yells]
[TIEN grunting]
--[CHUN gutteral breathing]
--[TIEN yelling]
--[CHUN labored breathing]
--[TIEN grunting]
[TIEN yells]
Yaaa!
[CHUN groaning]
[TIEN groans]
[BOTH groan]
[panting]
[CROWD murmurs]
[ANNOUNCER]
Uh... Uuh...
[CHUN panting]
[TIEN grunts]
See what I mean?
[TIEN] It makes no sense
that an old man
should be so agile and skillful.
But whoever he is,
he's more powerful than
anyone I've ever faced.
[CHUN]
He's just a kid,
but he's taken everything
I've thrown at him
and keeps coming back for more.
I understand Yamcha's dilemma.
[chuckles]
If this continues,
I might start feeling my age.
Oh, face it, Roshi,
there's a whole new crop
of fighters coming up,
and I'll do my best
to stand in their way!
[NARRATOR] The fight is intense,
and the fighters are weary.
Who will win the fifth match?
The answer can only be found
in the next action-packed
episode of Dragon Ball!