♪
Eugeo: Kirito.
( Kirito murmurs )
Eugeo: Kirito!
( Kirito moans )
Just five more minutes.
eugeo: Come on.
I know it’s our day of rest,
but you sleep too much!
( Kirito moaning )
Good morning, eugeo.
( Eugeo chuckles ) Good morning.
Want to go into town today?
the sun’s out,
and the sky’s gorgeous.
♪
♪ shiny sword, my diamond
( singing in Japanese )
♪ It’s time
♪
( Overlapping chatter )
Vendor: Enjoy the pastries!
Kirito: Mmm. Damn, that’s yummy!
Eugeo: Can’t you wait
’til we get home?
Kirito: No. They taste better
when they’re
fresh out of the oven.
Wanna have a bite?
Eugeo: No, thanks.
I’m good for now. Maybe later.
Kirito: Suit yourself.
Man, I can’t believe
how time flies.
We left rulid, what,
two years ago now?
eugeo: Yeah. So much
has happened to us since then.
Let’s see.
First, we went to zakkaria.
we got to hone
our swordsman skills quite a bit
while living
and working on that farm.
( Eugeo grunts )
♪
( Yells )
( Crowd gasps )
♪
( Kirito yells )
( Sword shatters )
Eugeo: We won the sword-fighting
tournament together...
( Crowd cheering )
and joined
the zakkaria Garrison.
It seems like yesterday
we came to the capital
and made it
into the swordcraft academy.
I can’t get over how amazing
it is that we’re even here.
Kirito: Oh, come on.
It’s been, like, a whole year
since we moved to the dorms.
You should be bored
out of your skull by now.
( Eugeo chuckles ) I guess so.
Woman: Kirito!
♪
Kirito: L-liena!
Liena: What a coincidence.
kirito:
Hey, good morning, ma’am.
- Eugeo: Good morning, ma’am!
- Liena: Good morning.
We haven’t met yet.
You are eugeo. Is that correct?
Eugeo: Um, yes, ma’am!
( Liena chuckles )
There’s no need to be nervous.
Kirito: I thought you were
going home for the day.
Liena: Yes, I was
just there, actually.
They sent me back
to get some things.
Eugeo: Um, may I
carry that for you?
Liena: That’s very kind.
however,
you’re supposed to be
golgorosso balto’s page.
Eugeo: You’re right! I’m sorry!
I was out of line!
- Liena: As for you...
- kirito: Eh?
Liena: You are my page, yes?
so tell me, why is it
you didn’t offer to help first?
Kirito: Busted. ( Laughs )
Liena: Oh, honestly.
I appreciate your offer
to assist me, really.
However, i’m almost finished
with my shopping.
Besides, this is
your day of rest.
you shouldn’t
have to think about work.
your duty as pages
will be over soon, anyway.
Once we graduate,
it’s onward and upward.
Kirito: If anything, I wish I
could’ve learned more from you.
Liena: Your words are too kind.
I am blessed to be your mentor.
Kirito: Thank you
for everything!
It was an honor knowing you!
Eugeo: And an honor for me, too!
( Liena sighs ) Same.
( Eugeo sighs )
Kirito: What the heck are you
getting all flustered for?
Eugeo: I guess it’s because
sortiliena’s so beautiful,
and she’s kind of
intimidating, too.
Kirito: Yeah, you got a point.
I’m a nervous wreck
when we spar,
’cause she’s so intense.
Eugeo: Golgorosso can be
pretty intense, too.
in fact, even after all
the training i’ve had with him,
I still can’t score
a single point.
Kirito: Same here.
liena’s always
two steps ahead of me,
and she’s second seat
in her class.
Eugeo: I wonder
how strong volo is.
He’s in the first seat.
Kirito: Pretty strong.
Eugeo: Can you even imagine
beating an upperclassman?
I certainly can’t.
Kirito: And that there’s
the problem, huh?
Eugeo: Well, good night, kirito.
Kirito: Huh? Oh. Night.
After being stuck here
for the past two years,
I learned that, in this world,
your true power wasn’t
just expressed in numbers.
Only three stats
show up in your window,
your life,
your object control authority,
and your
system control authority.
If your object control
authority’s a low number,
you can barely even hold
a higher-class weapon.
But if your stat’s way bigger
than the weapon’s,
it feels crazy light.
Your system control
authority stat
tells you what kind
of sacred arts you can use.
if you’re low-level,
you can only use simple spells.
But if you level up,
you get access
to more sophisticated ones.
That’s how it works
in games, too,
but there’s an extra feature
here that affects your stats.
It’s something "s.A.O."
And "a.L.O." Didn’t have.
Sometimes, the strength
of a mental image you create
can influence your stats.
If a person has the confidence
or will to win,
their power can be amplified
many times over.
That’s what makes liena
so powerful.
she’s confident,
’cause ever since she was a kid,
she had the best training
in swordsmanship.
So if you can imagine yourself
to be more powerful than anyone,
you’ll have the potential to
rewrite the laws of this world.
♪
( Both grunting )
- ( Liena yells )
- ( Kirito yelps )
( Gasps )
( Sighs )
You win again, as always.
Liena: But you came close
a few times, didn’t you?
Kirito: No. It was all you.
Liena: Don’t be so modest.
I know you still have
some latent power
- you’re hiding from me.
- ( Kirito gasps )
one year ago,
I chose you for my page,
because I sensed a similarity
in our sword styles,
but over the course of the year,
it’s become obvious
how unrefined
my skills actually are.
Kirito: No way. You’re amazing!
In the end, I couldn’t even beat
you once during our training.
Liena: For two years,
give or take,
there is someone I have
not managed to beat, either.
Kirito: Oh. You mean
first seat volo leavantein.
Liena: Yes. Between you and I,
whenever I face him, I falter,
just like a coward.
No matter how hard I train,
I can’t seem to convince myself
I have the skill or the power
to withstand his sword.
Kirito: Liena.
Liena: However...
It is not the same for you
when you face me.
There is more
to the aincrad style
that you haven’t shown me,
isn’t there?
( Kirito gasps )
Liena: So before I graduate
the day after tomorrow,
i want to know
everything you’re capable of.
Kirito: With this thing?
( Gasps )
I will, but I can’t right now.
I’m sorry. But if you
can wait ’til tomorrow,
I promise i’ll show you then...
The greatest sword skill
i can use.
Liena: But tomorrow’s
a day of rest.
You know training
is forbidden then.
kirito: Yeah,
but it won’t be training.
it’ll be your--
your graduation present!
Yeah, that’s it! You can
give presents on days of rest!
( Liena laughs )
i’ve never heard
of gifting sword skills before,
but if you insist.
all right.
I look forward to it.
Kirito: Awesome!
Tomorrow, then.
♪
( Sighs )
- ( Woman clears throat )
- ( Kirito gasps )
Kirito here, ma’am!
I’m sorry i’m late, ma’am!
Woman: Why are you
38 minutes late,
primary trainee kirito?
Kirito: Practicing, ma’am,
with elite disciple
sortiliena serlut.
Our session went longer
than usual today.
Woman: I applaud your commitment
to your education.
It is your duty as a page
to learn from your mentor.
However, it seems to me
that you think your training
gives you permission
to break your curfew.
Kirito: Oh, of course not,
Ms. Azurica!
Uh, all I want is to get better
as a swordsman. That’s all!
Me comin’ in after curfew’s
just an accident. I swear.
( Azurica sighs ) Mealtime is
starting in 17 minutes.
Make sure you’re
not late for that.
( Overlapping chatter )
- Eugeo: Where have you been?
- Kirito: Sorry!
My sparring session
with liena went long.
Yum!
- mmm!
- ( Eugeo chuckles )
Student: I cannot tell you
how jealous I am, lord raios.
After we toiled so hard
cleaning this cafeteria,
they get to just waltz in and
eat as if they own the place.
I so envy their good fortune.
Raios: Now, now, humbert.
don’t slander.
Pages have their struggles, too.
I’m sure their duties are
beyond what even we can imagine.
( Humbert chuckles )
I suppose you’re right.
these pages have to be
at their mentors’ Beck and call.
Why, I heard they have
to indulge their every whim.
Raios: Could you imagine
what it must be like for them
having a mentor
from a lower-class house?
they must issue
the most outlandish orders.
Eugeo: Ignore those two jerks.
Just eat.
Oh, i’ve been meaning to ask,
how’s your garden coming along?
Kirito: Mm. ( Laughs )
Doing pretty good so far,
actually.
It should be in full bloom
in time for graduation.
eugeo: Nice.
Can’t wait to see it.
( Raios scoffs )
♪
Eugeo: They look like
they’re doing great.
They’re even starting to bud.
Kirito: It took three tries,
but I finally
got the hang of it.
Man, I really hope
this batch blooms.
Eugeo: It’s on course to,
by the looks of it.
They’re going to make
a wonderful graduation gift
for liena.
You’re so thoughtful.
( Kirito chuckles )
Give me a break.
Eugeo: After knowing you
for the past two years,
I had no idea you liked
puttering around a garden.
kirito: Yeah.
I’m as surprised as you.
Eugeo: You know what?
This might be a sign
that your memories
are coming back.
Maybe before you came to rulid,
you used to be a gardener.
Yeah, maybe that
was your calling.
Kirito: Uh, yeah, maybe.
I’m, uh, gonna get some water.
- Eugeo: Wait.
- Kirito: What?
Eugeo: At some point, you may
end up getting your memory back.
- What then?
- Kirito: Huh?
Wh-what do you mean?
Eugeo: You’re training
to be an integrity knight,
but you’re only here
because you’re helping me.
i’m here
because I want to find Alice
and bring her back home.
What if you remember your home?
( Kirito sighs )
♪
( Eugeo gasps )
Kirito: If I do get my memory
back, I ain’t goin’ home.
There’s one thing I know.
I’m a swordsman all the way.
For a swordsman,
being an integrity knight’s
a dream job.
Eugeo: I’m weak.
I always have been.
If I hadn’t met you,
I don’t know.
I guess i’d still be
swinging that ax right now,
still stuck in my village,
blaming it all on my calling.
The only reason i’m even here
is because I had you with me
to lead the way.
It’s all because of you.
And just now, when you said you
wouldn’t return to your home,
even if you got
your memory back,
it filled me with such relief.
Kirito: Aw, come on.
Quit your mopin’.
You think I could’ve made it
all the way
to the capital by myself?
I didn’t know where it was.
Plus, my memory’s a blank,
and, worse, I didn’t have
two coins to rub together.
The only reason i’m here now
is ’cause of you.
We make a great team,
so why mess that up?
we’re better
if we stick together.
we can worry
about going our own ways
after we become
integrity knights. Deal?
( Eugeo chuckles ) Okay, deal.
First things first, though.
We have to ace this exam.
Only the top 12
will get to advance.
Kirito: Yeah, well,
i’m havin’ a hard time
with my sacred arts skills.
so, what do you say?
Wanna help your partner out?
( Eugeo laughs ) Of course.
in fact,
tomorrow’s our day of rest,
so we can study.
Kirito: I can’t.
Eugeo: Oh. Right, I forgot.
Kirito: Yup. Tomorrow’s
the day I pick it up.
Eugeo: I bet you’re excited.
kirito: Hell, yeah!
I’ve been waiting all year.
Can’t wait to try it out.
( Horse neighs )
- ( Overlapping chatter )
- ( Thump )
- ( Both gasp )
Sadore: These things
don’t grow on trees!
A black-brick grindstone’s
supposed to last me three years!
I went through
six of ’em this year
workin’ on that thing!
Kirito: Uh, yeah,
sorry about that.
Sadore: That branch
was so tough,
it took me a whole damn day
just to scrape a sliver off it.
You have any idea
how many hours I spent
shavin’ away at this thing?!
Garitta: The tip
of the gigas cedar
is the part that absorbed
all the blessings of solus.
Take it on your journey,
and when you reach the capital,
go and see sadore the craftsman,
and leave it in his care.
he’ll make
a wonderful sword from it.
Sadore: See that?
I’m a craftsman by calling,
but metalsmithing’s where my--
kirito: I’m sorry.
Did you finish the sword?
( Sadore grumbling )
Young man...
I don’t remember us
talking about money yet.
( Kirito gasps )
Eugeo: Don’t worry. It’s okay.
Pay the man.
If you don’t have enough,
I can loan you the rest.
sadore: Of course,
I might let you just have it.
- Kirito: Huh? Really?!
- Eugeo: Huh? Really?!
Sadore: Really,
but there’s a catch.
you gotta be able
to swing this monster. Heh.
Good luck. When I finished,
i tried picking it up,
and the damn thing felt heavier.
Kirito: No way. It did?
( Gasps )
♪
Eugeo: What’s wrong? Draw it.
Kirito: Okay. Here goes.
( Grunts )
( Clapping )
Eugeo: Nice form, kirito.
sadore: Huh!
So a trainee can handle it.
Well, now i’ve seen everything.
Kirito: It’s a good sword.
Sadore: Damn right, it is!
Anyway, the sword’s all yours.
I’m a man of my word,
after all.
( Kirito gasps )
Thanks a lot!
Hey, i’m gonna go
try this out for a bit.
eugeo: Okay.
Just don’t be late for dinner!
Kirito: I won’t!
- ( Grunts )
- ( Sword swings )
( Grunting )
This world’s no game,
but it’s got sword skills.
I can only do two-hit combos
with my practice sword.
Let’s see what this can do.
( Yells )
Volo: Huh.
Kirito: This is great!
I can keep my promise
to liena now!
no, wait.
How ’bout a five-parter?
The blue Rose sword
couldn’t do one,
but maybe this can.
( Yells )
( Groans )
Volo: Hmph.
( Kirito groans )
Guess it can’t.
- ( Footsteps )
- oh?
First seat levantein!
( Gasps )
i-i’m sorry,
elite disciple levantein.
I didn’t mean to get dirt
on your uniform!
Volo: I’ve seen you before.
You’re elite disciple
serlut’s page.
Kirito: Yes, sir,
- primary trainee kirito.
- volo: Right.
practicing the sword
is forbidden on a day of rest.
Kirito: I, um--i wasn’t.
This isn’t practice, sir.
Um, I was just trying out
my new sword.
I couldn’t wait ’til tomorrow.
Volo: Your test swings were--
how shall I say?
- Enthusiastic.
- ( Kirito stammers )
Volo: You and I
are similar that way.
We both search for a reason
to wield a sword,
even on a day of rest,
yearning to scratch that itch.
- Kirito: You, too?
- Volo: Yes,
so I shall overlook
that transgression.
kirito:
You’re very generous, sir.
Thank you for--
volo: Do not thank me yet,
trainee kirito.
Kirito: Uh, pardon?
volo: I did not say
I would forgive you for this.
( Overlapping chatter )
Kirito: News travels fast.
( Door closes )
Eugeo: Kirito!
What’d you do this time?
Kirito: Nothin’. ( Chuckles )
Eugeo: Oh, well.
It was a good run.
You survived a whole year here
without getting into trouble.
Kirito: New record, partner!
Liena: Lord levantein,
what is the meaning of this?
Volo: Just a minor infraction.
your page
was disrespectful to me,
nothing that demands
serious punishment, mind you,
so we shall settle it
by sparring with real swords.
Liena: What did you say?
Kirito: You don’t have to worry
about me, ma’am. Really.
I can handle myself.
In fact, I sorta feel honored
to get the chance to spar
with the first seat here.
Liena: Kirito...
Have you discussed
the rules with him yet?
Kirito: No, but since
we’re using real swords,
isn’t it stop-short?
volo: I forgot
to mention something earlier.
I do not engage
in short-stop duels.
For all my personal matches,
I prefer to fight first-strike.
Liena: He’s never fought
a match with real swords!
Besides, you need his consent!
Volo: Of course. Mine, too.
This cannot proceed
unless we both agree.
and if he does not,
the match will be stop-short.
Well, trainee kirito,
do you agree?
Liena: Don’t do it, kirito.
Volo’s strong. He will hurt you.
Kirito: I think i’ll let you
decide it, lord levantein.
i’m the one
being punished, after all.
( Volo sighs )
( Eugeo sighs )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
♪ The Iris to you