In other news, the heat is on
as the temperature soars and the mercury rises,
though fun-seekers at Oarai Beach will not be deterred.
You know, when I was kid, I couldn't say "Oarai."
So I used to think it was pronounced
"Old Wall-Eye" Beach.
It did seem like a weird name, though.
Huh. Your brain must be a fascinating place.
Guys, it just dawned on me.
I haven't been to the beach yet this summer.
Yeah.
I haven't been to the beach,
like, once in my entire life.
Okay, that shouldn't even be possible! Wow.
You-You're absolutely serious?
Mm-hmm...
I'm just going to come right out and say that's sad.
Well, it's not like there's a
shoreline where we're from, so.
But don't they take you on field trips?
Sure they do!
In grade school they took us to Kyoto and Nara.
Then when we were older,
in middle school they took us to Nara and Kyoto.
Sounds like the teachers were really trying
to broaden your minds.
All right.
It's sand and surf time!
The schedule's flexible.
I think we ought to be able to
squeeze in some fun in the sun.
Yeah! We got a break coming up. Let's get our feet wet!
Woo-hoo!
Nice...
Ringo in beachwear...
Something fun...
Something skimpy...
That's a fabulous idea. Where do I sign?
Hell yeah! We've worked hard!
And now we play hard!
Yeah!
But on the big day...
Unfortunately for those planning a day at the beach,
this category one typhoon lost none of its strength
before making landfall.
Mother Nature had other ideas.
Flash flood warning, wind advisory, lighting advisory,
rockslide advisory. Whoa-boy. Trifecta plus one.
In poker, this would be a straight flush.
Are we counting high-tide and storm-surge warnings?
'Cause, uh, if so,
we're going to need another metaphor here.
This really sucks, guys.
Wow. A category one?
On top of all the rain we've been having
the past couple of weeks?
The weather this summer has been out of control.
Beach! Beach! Beach! Beach! Beach!
Hah. And speaking of out of control.
The point is to get wet, right?!
So why are we letting a measly little typhoon
rain on our parade?! Damn it, I want to go to beach!
This isn't fair!
Minori! Please! Look, we all want to go to the beach,
but we can't get there if the buses aren't running.
There's nothing stopping us from
using our bicycles, is there?
I vote we tranquilize her!
Bikes won't do a whole lot of good under water.
No one's going anywhere in this, all right?
The beach will still be there
when our next break comes around. We can go then.
I'll even buy you an ice cream cone.
Is that a promise?!
If you calm down, yes. Cross my heart, 'kay?
Okay! But we'll have to be good and wait thirty minutes
before getting in the water!
Forces beyond all human understanding are at work!
Ugh. Fantastic. Just what we need.
What happened to you?
They cancelled practical lab on account of the weather.
I didn't get the notification till I was halfway here.
And with all the buses shut down,
let's just say I've had worse
days, but not all that many.
So, have they cancelled everything?
Yep. And it looks like I'm stuck here
till the weather decides to
stop being a pain in the ass.
Huh. Actually, I guess we all are.
Yeah, well. At least we're staying dry.
What kind of practical lab was it?
Oh, just cymbidium repositioning.
Cym... bi... what now?
Cym-bidium. It's an orchid.
One that prospers in the southeast part of Asia.
Specifically in the crisp air of the plateau.
We haul them up the mountain each summer
to prevent their being blasted by seasonal winds.
The wind's that rough on them, huh?
Indeed, and the plants don't develop well
when it's too hot.
If they're stunted, then they're worthless.
Wow. Didn't know orchids were your thing.
Didn't I mention what they go for?
Of course.
Oh, historically, orchids have been known to fetch
a king's ransom on the open market.
Collectors the world over go
nuts for the little buggers.
So... Anyway, before the storm hit
the plan was for us to haul a batch of new cymbidiums
to market in the microbus.
Whoa. The microbus, huh?
You got to be brave to ride in that thing.
Truth is, with this wind, I'm just as worried
about the greenhouse as I am
about the flowers themselves.
One good gust and it's all she wrote.
Hadn't thought of that.
Hey, uh... You think we should close the storm shutters?
I mean, better safe than sorry, right?
Yeah. Good idea.
Ah! Can you believe this?
Kind of Humbling, isn't it?
It's like...
I know.
An ocean.
Right?
Like an ocean.
Ocean?!
Crap.
Stop her! Don't be afraid to use force!
Beach boys!
Sweet liberty!
Minori! Get back in here right now!
The glorious ocean has come to us!
I feel like a mermaid!
It's not the ocean, it's a flood!
This is beyond awesome!
Look at me! I'm swimming!
Earth to Minori! You'll drown!
The current's gonna sweep you away!
This is so much fun!
Idiot.
So. Much. Fun!
Really?
I've never felt so alive!
This is ridiculous. Get out of there, damn it!
This isn't... !
Yah-hoo!
Splash!
Oh, it is totally on now!
I ain't afraid of you!
Whoo!
No having fun without me, guys!
Should I feel dirty or is this normal?
Hey, it's just mud. There's not a thing dirty about it.
We're just two guys enjoying the scenery.
Key word: enjoying.
Someone find a beach ball right now.
I want to do like they do in the movies!
Volleyball!
Service!
Good game, everybody!
Yay!
Okay, now we have to split a watermelon!
Who's got one?
Somebody say watermelon?!
Huh?
Yeah! Watermelon!
Woo!
Right! Time for some barbeque!
I'm all over it!
The lighter won't cooperate.
Bring on the kerosene!
Aye aye, captain!
Stand clear!
We've made fire!
Yeah, because we rock!
Still, either way!
Bonfire!
I could really go for some music.
Music, coming right up!
Sick summer beats, anyone?!
Party time!
Are you plebeians out of your minds?!
You'll spook the livestock!
Yoshida, hey! Heads up, Fun Bags at 6 o'clock!
Yay!
What on earth is wrong with you people?!
Aw, come on! Live at little! Get this farm-wear off!
Proper beach party attire only!
Take your filthy paws off me this instant, Vulgarians!
Well, well! Lookie here!
For all your whining you actually came prepared!
You always wear a bikini under there?
It's not a bikini, it's my underwear, you moron!
Busting out! Busting out! Busting out!
Yay!
Not so fast!
Huh...?
How dare you? This is hallowed ground!
Our beach is not the place for
you people to let it all hang out!
Who are they?
Ha! Feast your eyes on Tamo No-Rin's world class
beach volleyball team-ah!
We have a volleyball team?!
Given that we're nowhere near an actual beach,
isn't that sort of like a regional
hockey league in the tropics?
Whatever you guys want, just leave us alone!
Can't you see we're busy stripping
our friend here down to her undies?!
Maybe we were a little too quick to judge.
Hey!
Allow me to introduce myself.
I'm the team's preppy nice-guy captain, Hamaoka.
My comrade's name...
Butter. Ken Butter.
Wait. Hold up. THE Ken Butter?
Does this guy have a reputation?
I don't know. Never heard of him in my life.
If I say he's one of Biotech's
so-called Sweet Musketeers
whose name everyone associates
with prize-winning treats,
I'm just talking outta my ass.
Want to make your toast slick?
Try... Ken... Butter!
Shut up, please.
Care for a little friendly competition?
Huh?
See, we're in the middle of gearing
up for the regional tournament.
Got to get your practice on when
and where you can, know what I mean?
Where are they having this tournament?
Nagano!
There's no frigging beach in Nagano!
Um, yeah. Hello. It's called a day trip, dude!
Where was it last year?
Gunma.
Oh, come on!
The year before that,
they held it in Saitama.
Not to be that girl,
but, none of those places are near the ocean.
Where exactly do you play?
Oh. Riverbeds.
Wow. Must hurt.
Look, never mind about that, all right?!
Just play with us!
Pretty please?
Can I talk to you for a second?
Sure, no problem. What's up?
The fields are taking a real beating.
Uh-oh. This is bad.
We've got to hurry!
The rice will be completely submerged!
So I'm guessing that's not a good thing?
Rice is a finicky plant, you have to be careful.
You want the stalks under water, but not the ears.
If that happens, they'll start to sprout
in which case, the yield will be nothing.
Really?
Really!
We won't be able to eat it, we won't be able to sell it.
We won't even be able to use it
to fertilize next year's crop.
All our hard work for nothing!
Oh no!
Now what? What's the plan?
I mean, what are we supposed to do?
It's okay. We, uh...
We got this.
Oh crap!
Look at it!
Sorry. If only I'd have noticed this sooner.
Calm yourselves, Vulgarians!
What's been the purpose of your training if not... !
One moment, please!
Okay. Take two... in five, four, three, two...
You disgust me!
As I was saying.
Once more, from the top.
Your training has prepared you for this!
We are nothing if not agricultural students
and this is our moment to shine!
Oohhh...
Kousaku, take charge! Everyone else, follow!
From here on out, we take all orders from you,
this includes me! Are we agreed?
Fun Bags!
A yes or no would suffice!
Right. First, we open the rear drain. It's all you, Kei!
And what's a rear drain?
It's a kind of like a vent. Regulates the water level.
To keep the ears from getting submerged?
Provided the wind doesn't blow them over, exactly.
Come to papa!
Kamatori!
Kei! Are you going to be all right?!
I'm good! It's just... Just a little mud!
I'll be damned if the drain gets clogged!
I got this!
Cool!
Now that Kei's bought us some
time, let's rope off the field!
Right!
I need everyone to be careful!
Don't fall on the plants!
Understood.
Hamaoka, run back to the school
and bring us some more rope, STAT!
You got it!
Yoshida, your jugs are crushing the stalks!
I'm sorry!
Minori, stop letting your ass poke out!
Ringo, you're doing perfect. Nice job!
Butter dude! What the hell are you doing?
Where are you pants?
Aw, no worries. Butter totally repels water!
Gross, but okay.
All right, that ought to hold her for now.
Good on us, huh?
Class D's field shouldn't take too long.
Kousaku!
What is it?
The rice in Class D's field is growing way too quickly!
Huh?
The stalks are so tall the ears are drooping.
The ropes can't support them! The crop is done for!
Why would they grow it so fast?
Hey, what's the deal with Class D?
I'm sorry...
We planted Koshihikari.
What in the hell would you do a thing like that for?!
Is that bad?
Koshihikari has a reputation for falling over so easily,
it's nickname is "Collapsikari!" It sprouts up too tall!
With the stalks already that long...
...they don't stand a chance.
This wind will knock 'em over like bowling pins!
Oh no!
Why would you guys cultivate something so risky?!
What was I supposed to do?!
This particular variety sells like gang-busters!
You won't be selling much of anything
when the whole field goes tits up!
You two, quit your bickering!
Now is not the time for that argument!
You're right!
There are more important things to focus on!
Captain Aramis must save the day! Pronto!
Just... Just give me a minute to think.
There's too many stalks for us
to move them out of harm's way.
The only thing to do is block the wind.
Except... how, exactly?
Hey, our volleyball net is super durable.
Why don't we use that?
Last I checked, a net is made of holes!
We need something that'll make a wall.
Well, sandbagging would be the best option,
except it's a little late for that.
Thank you, Captain Obvious!
Ah! Ah-ha! Kanegami! The keys!
Huh?
To the microbus! Give me!
You had it gassed up to move the cymbidiums, didn't you?
Ugh. Of course.
What are you cooking up there, chief?
Sorry! No time to explain!
I'll be back, just start roping off the field!
Ha! This is gonna work...
Kousaku!
Ringo! The field!
The others have it covered, it's okay.
Fun Bags didn't like you wandering off on your own
in the storm, so she asked me to stay with you.
Yeah, thanks. I'm a child.
Thank you, Fun Bags...
So what's your big plan, exactly?
We're gonna improvise a wall.
O-kay...
It's simple: drive this upwind and we block the gusts.
Stay with me here: Class D's
field is the furthest up, right?
Of its four sides, three are flanked by roads.
If we drive the microbus to the road up top,
it'll shield their crop from the wind.
I had no idea you even knew how to drive.
I don't, but it's a standard diesel engine.
So, you know...
It can't be that different from a tractor.
Okey-doke. First gear.
Release the emergency brake.
Rev the engine just enough to get her nice and ready.
Ease up on the clutch about halfway.
Release the clutch once we get things a-moving.
And give her some juice.
Hell yeah! Didn't even stall once!
That's incredible!
Nothing any farm boy couldn't do, really.
Thing is...
Yeah?
Driving without adult supervision
is majorly against the rules.
Miss Becky's gonna be out-of-her-mind furious.
Watch me get suspension.
You're not alone.
If she gets upset, it'll be at both of us.
Let's pull this mother out!
Whoa! Aw, damn it! I can't see the road!
Use the windshield wipers!
The, uh, what?
Those little things that go back
and forth on the windshield!
It comes with those, right?
Hello?
Yeah, I don't know.
Well tractors and combines don't come with them,
how am I supposed to know about buses?
What are you doing?!
Don't freak.
I'm going to act as your lookout, okay?
I need you to follow my directions to the letter!
Uh... Okay.
Keep going straight!
You got it!
Start veering to the right! We're passing the gym!
Veering right!
All right, now straighten the wheel!
Easy does it, easy does it.
Kousaku!
Make a sharp right when I give the word. Got it?
Yeah!
In three... Two... One... Now!
Ringo!
Hold on, I've got you, okay?
And...
Yoink!
Diet for me, please!
OJ, thanks.
Oh, orange juice for me, too, please.
Yeah. Here.
How about it, guys?
Is the marketing teacher awesome-sauce or what?
Hell yeah you treat the people who saved your rice crop
to a day at the beach! That's what I'm talkin' 'bout!
Yep.
I'm finally going to see the ocean
for the first time in my life!
The school's not above bending
the rules every now and then.
You're a lucky man, dude.
Can't believe you got off with a slap on the wrist.
No kidding, right?
If your little stunt hadn't saved the field,
you'd both be suspended.
Whatever. Big whoop. It was so totally worth it.
Hey. Kousaku.
Ha?
You, uh, might wanna listen to this.
The typhoon prone to make landfall
any minute now is even bigger
than last week's category one.
Residents are advised to stay indoors,
as potential wind speeds at the storm's core
are projected to be up to 72 kilometers per hour.
I'm going to the beach!
Try to stop me, I dare you!
Minori, no! Wait!
Someone restrain her!
Minori, it's okay.
Focus on the sound of my voice.
Beach boys!
You're a girl!
Veggie Battle: Ultimate v. Supreme