Thank you!
Thank you so very much!
You really know how to make a girl feel special!
Best audience ever-and I mean
that from the bottom of my heart!
Yuka! Yuka! Yuka! Yuka!
I love you!
You're my queen!
Before the next set,
I want to introduce you to someone very special.
This is the man all my songs are secretly dedicated to.
I love--
I... love you...
Aw, man...
Really?
You're late 'cause you're not married to a pop star?
Take a second to say those words aloud to yourself.
She has a point.
It's kind of sad.
Since we're on the subject of wet dreams,
when are you going to get a grip on
reality and stop fantasizing about Tokyo?
Place will chew you up and spit you out.
Not if I'm a trendy farmer, it won't!
A trendy farmer?
Hah! Yeah, let me give you a clue there, slick.
Two weeks, you'll come crawling
back on your hands and knees.
Yokel like you'd be lucky winding up
married to the hometown harvest queen.
Oh, so now you have a crystal ball?
Yukatan and me will be together.
We'll grow rice in Harajukua,
then we're gonna-wait for it
take Ropongi by storm with cows!
You'll see!
Harvest queen will have to find someone else.
Besides, the only hometown girl my age is you.
Huh?!
Crazy coincidence, huh?
Funny how little details like that can skip your notice.
Kousaku, Minori. Please.
How 'bout you stop whatever this is and, you know, work?
Sorry. My bad.
Gee, thanks.
Way to get me on Kei's bad side today.
Hey! It takes two to tango!
Mad cow! Mad cow!
Actually, I think it's a bull!
Whatever! It's out and it's pissed!
We've got a teacher down!
Medic!
Matador!
They need better pens.
It was one of the peacocks last time, right?
Nah. It was the goat.
The peacock was the time before that.
Hey! Back to work! What's not our problem?
Runaway cattle.
Huh?
Um... Actually...
Crap!
Whatever happens, we can't let it ruin the crop!
And how're we supposed to do that?
I'm on it, guys!
Dude! Kakizaki's insane! He's got this.
He made it to nationals!
No! Kakizaki--!
That thing is a monster!
Why do they keep it around?!
Whoa.
Kei!
Wha-What do we do?!
Just... take this and run like hell.
Aw, c'mon, give me some slack!
I got no beef with you!
Poor choice of words! Sorry! Don't kill me! Sorry!
Well, so far so good.
Oh, Wakadanna! It was just awful!
No one even cared I was almost trampled!
Kousaku.
You brought the career survey, right?
Yeah.
You made up your mind about college?
Nah, still kind of on the fence about it.
Only thing I know for sure is I
want to specialize in agriculture.
Least that's a plan.
Look at me. Heh.
I'm just here 'cause my family's
been farmers since, like, forever.
You telling me you got nothing lined up?
Well, there's Tokyo.
Ah...
Wait! Seriously?!
Yeah, why?
Ugh. Bumpkin...
You really think the "trendy
farmer" thing's going to take off?
As a matter of fact,
I already know where I'm going to start.
Ha!
A magical place called Furikoshi High School!
O-kay.
Just so I'm absolutely clear:
In dead earnest, you actually listed
"high school" as a career choice?
That's dumb. Like, really dumb.
Uh...
I'd appreciate it if you'd stop
talking to me like I'm an idiot!
Oh brother.
So, I guess it's safe to say you've
got it bad for this pop star chick?
Yukatan Kusakabe is not a "pop star
chick", she's a goddess!
And what exactly makes her a "goddess"?
Her dancing dinner-plate eyeballs!
Her delicate, duck-face mouth!
Those rosy apple cheeks!
That angelic voice from heaven!
Her long, naturally straight hair!
The way her eyebrows arch as if to say, "Who, me?"
Right. Thanks.
We get the picture.
Oh-ho, no you don't, my friend!
Not 'til you've heard me talk about
that one-of-kind, ice-melting smile--
Wrap it up, lover boy! No one here gives a crap!
The survey's about life after school.
Okay, fine.
What'd you put on yours, then?
Hmm?
College or job?
Uh! Ah! Um... Well, I guess all things considered,
Let's say, "job." Something in an office?
Hang on! Do-Don't read it!
If any of those things happen in an office,
you're doing them wrong.
This is dumb. Really dumb.
Don't talk to me like I'm an idiot!
I'm thinking long term! Ugh!
Stop running your mouths.
Vulgarians!
It's Fun-bags McGee!
The name is Kochou!
Say it with me, now: Kochou Yoshida!
Got it?!
The plebes in Cultivation are a tragedy.
Small-minded guttersnipes, that's you.
Production Science is wasted on you.
Why they lump Cultivators and Animal
Husbandry students together, I'll never know.
I'm charged with the care of animate creatures.
You all just roll around in the dirt.
A-hem.
The students across the hall will thank
you to keep it down to a dull roar.
Your inane chatter is distracting.
Oh, Like your big, smelly cow
isn't putting us all off our game?
Silence, Vulgarian tramp!
You know nothing!
Sit down and be schooled!
This magnificent beast, Agehagou by name,
is a Hidaushi, the highest of the elite wagyu rank!
Which makes no real difference in her market value.
Actually, her fetching price is
expected to be stratospheric, plebe.
Give the magnificent beast room to breathe, people!
You can't just switch sides on a dime.
That's not how this works!
I pick the side that doesn't murder me!
Hmph. Violence in lieu of dialogue.
I must say, you sum up the Cultivators perfectly.
Yoshida.
How dare you address me as though we were equals?!
We are worlds apart!
Cows are sort of on the skittish side, right?
They don't do all that great around people?
Not to tell you your job,
but do you think it's a smart idea to bring one into
a classroom full of loud, obnoxious "vulgarians?"
Trying to hoist me by my own petard, eh?
Well, your attempt at a touché is as predictable as you!
Wow. Not cool.
Following this morning's debacle,
I realized Agehagou's reaction
could create a teachable moment.
Call this an exercise in moron endurance.
Moron endurance?!
That actually makes sense.
Nice. Well done, Yoshida.
That's some cutting edge animal psychology technique.
Don't let anyone tell you different.
Well, so long as we're on the same page, I suppose.
So you understand why it's inappropriate
to confer with me on even terms.
Good! Cultivator Plebe!
Good morning, class!
Get a load of this spectacular weather we're having!
Not too hot, not too cold!
Makes a gal feel like Goldilocks at the wedding altar!
Miss!
Yes, Ms. Nakazawa?
Points for calling me "Miss," by the way.
Teacher may not look forty,
but that doesn't mean she's not feeling her age.
Fun Bags-I mean- Yoshida brought a
big smelly cow into the classroom!
Huh. How about that.
I'm assuming you have a really
good explanation. Yoshida?
Yes, ma'am. You see,
Mr. Mutsu suffered an unfortunate accident.
I thought it best that I care for her while he recovers.
That's a complete one-eighty from what you said!
Hmm. And you think you're up to
the task of babysitting a cow?
Oh, absolutely.
Hmph. You'd know better than me!
Aw, Miss Becky! C'mon!
This is totally ridiculous!
If she gets to bring a cow into the classroom,
then the rest of us should be
able to bring our planters, too!
Fair is fair! Who's with me on this?
Speak up, guys!
I'm with her! It's not right!
Why do the Animal Husbandry snobs
always get special treatment?
Because we don't make the school spend money
on stupid things like fertilizer trials!
But why don't you share some of that
produce you're always taste-testing, huh?!
Everybody, stop arguing!
Now listen and listen good!
We're all in the same boat.
Focus on each other's positive traits!
But Ms. Becky!
It's really unfair that she gets to bring her cow!
What's unfair about observing the caste system?
Give me a tomato!
Sure! I'll throw one at you!
Ah-ha! All right.
Who wants to hear a tale of romance?
Your favorite teacher found herself in an upscale
five-star restaurant last night, sipping wine
across from the most intriguing man she'd ever met.
Rich, sophisticated, handsome.
Hanging on every teensy little word she had to say.
A man a woman would love not to have to
make-up out of soul-crushing loneliness.
That's right, boys and girls.
Yours truly was on a date with an empty seat.
Okay, then! What do you say we get started?
Down the hatch!
Ahhhh...! Seconds please!
Good, right?
Alrighty then, coming right up!
Thanks for the grub!
Man, that was good!
Tempers flared today in the House of Councilors
over the Prime Minister's proposed tax increase.
Members of the opposing party
accuse the Minister's cabinet--
Why are human beings hard-wired to
care about taste when it comes to food?
I mean, it's a blatant design
flaw when you think about it:
we want flavor.
Nutrition? Meh.
We eat what tastes good.
If we're lucky, it's also good for us.
Why would God make us that way? Is he even real?
Blasphemy! Of course he's real!
He just put all of his genius into creating Yukatan!
Kousaku. She is living proof that God
loves us all and wants us to be happy!
Kousaku.
Any guy who doesn't grovel at Yukatan's
feet isn't worthy to call himself a man!
Earth to Kousaku! Come in!
Damn it, what do you want?!
Can't you see I'm deep in meditation?
You seriously need to look at the television.
Yeah, it's a pretty big deal.
What?
Like anything's a bigger deal than my Yuka--
Excuse me! Is it true you're retiring?
God is dead!
It's not true! I refuse to accept it!
No, no, no, no, no!
It's all a vicious lie!
Will you come out of there already?
We're going to be late for class.
Life marches on, dude.
Fine. I shouldn't have to do this, but...
Time to come out and face reality!
Why do you have to be such a pain?
Everybody gets--
What's wrong with you?!
Can't believe people actually buy those...
You're kidding me.
And here I'd been thinking you
were a semi-normal human being.
You do realize this means we have no choice but
to take you out back and put you down, right?
At least tell me you're wearing a shirt under there.
No, I am not wearing a shirt!
Yukatan and I are of one flesh!
Textbook PTSD.
He's like that guy who can't wash the sheets after
his girlfriend puts the kibosh on their relationship.
It might be too late for him.
Hey!
Stop being a freak for two seconds
and come back to the real world!
If you don't come to class, you'll fail.
Nobody wants that.
How else you going to be a "trendy farmer?"
What'd be the point?
Excuse me?
I only ever grew stuff
so I could send fresh vegetables to Yukatan.
Kibo 209 to Osaka boarding
on Platform Sixteen.
Kibo 209 to Osaka...
Let me make sure I get this:
You send it all to her?
Everything you've grown in class since forever
goes to feed a well-off Japanese pop star?
Yup.
Eggplants in particular, though. Big, bulging eggplants.
Pretty sure that's harassment.
Congratulations, you're a stalker.
What are you talking about?!
If you were a girl, how would you feel about some
complete and total stranger shipping you a box
of produce shaped like that?
But... she lives in Tokyo!
It's a concrete jungle over there!
It's impossible to find good veggies.
C'mon, who cares what it's shaped like?
It's fresh!
Listen.
I know in your mind this is all completely innocent.
Thanks. Knew you'd get it.
That's why you and me are bros.
You ever send this girl anything else?
Loads of big, warty cucumbers.
Vice Squad! Book this pervert, now!
I just said we're bros!
Come on, Minori!
We've got to wash our hands of this creep-a-zoid.
Guilt by association!
Wait! I sent a bunch of other stuff, too!
Sweet corn, bitter gourds,
some mushrooms from the forestry department!
Next shipment's going to have some daikon in there!
I try to give a little
Shut up!
I don't want to be an accessory!
You're so pathetic...
You really see nothing wrong with this, huh?
There isn't!
I'm just trying to do something
nice for someone special!
Uhh... It's creepy.
All right, that does it!
School me. Now.
Explain to me exactly what it is I'm doing wrong here.
Go on. I'm all ears.
Give me a break.
You need to be told why it's creepy?
Apparently, yeah.
What about sending something made with love to someone
who means the world to you is such a huge crime?
Uh, you don't think eggplants
might've been a little too suggestive?
Fine. Never mind the eggplants.
The real issue is you mailing them
anonymously to someone you've never even met.
Yeah.
No. Nuh-uh.
Don't skip over the eggplant thing.
You're the one who made it the hot button.
Put yourself in my shoes: your best friends
rag on your produce-I mean, come on,
you wouldn't need an explanation?!
No one's ragging on your produce.
It's just, eggplants are... shaped funny...
Oh, I see. So eggplants are shaped funny.
Funny as in: dirty. Uh-huh.
Remind you of something, maybe?
Seems like a personal problem if you ask me.
Hey. It's not--
Look, I don't make the rules, okay?
And what rules are those?
You'll have to spell them out for me.
Describe for me what the eggplant looks
like so I'll know for future reference.
C'mon. It's clearly important--
What're they shaped like?
Huh?
Uh... They're-They're shaped like a...
...pen...
Stop trying to make me sound like a pervert!
Nice one.
You have to admit you had that coming.
Yeah. Guess it's kind of hard to argue with
the logic of that from this perspective.
Whatever.
She probably doesn't even open the box you mail them in.
You ever gotten a response from this girl?
Never have, never will...
Don't be so dramatic.
You're bound to get something from her.
Eventually.
I've stayed anonymous.
There is officially no hope for you.
Makes it that much creepier.
It doesn't matter.
Just 'cause her career is over
doesn't mean you get to skip class.
Here!
Get off your rump and make an effort!
We're all in this together!
Pass! Life as I know it is over!
From now on if you want me...
You'll have to talk to Yuka-tan!
Oh, she's so beautiful! She's so sweet! So perfect!
Ugh. Fine.
The real one's probably a total bitch anyway.
Blasphemer!
Just because no man in his right
mind would give you his eggplant
doesn't mean you get to foul-mouth my true love--
Goodbye, future offspring...
I am not going to say this again!
Stop being a titty baby and grow a pair!
Our grades are on the line and
if you don't get it in gear,
I'll give the holier-than-thou's in Animal Husbandry
free reign to mangle your shriveled ball sack!
Now do we have an understanding,
or do I need to drill you a little more?
Got it...
Why are we doing this?!
There's no point!
Stop bitching! Nobody cares what you think.
Kei, make him focus on his work!
Huh? Right.
So last night was a complete wash!
Literally!
I bought this fabulously expensive essential oil
I read about online everyone says
makes you look ten years younger.
Talk about incredible!
Oh, my skin was so soft,
you'd think I just popped out of the womb!
Then I thought, "why spend so much," right?
What's so 'essential' about essential
oils that any old oil won't do?
So, it's into the kitchen for
a bottle extra virgin olive oil
with a sprinkle of chili powder,
'cause, you know, in for a penny, in for a pound.
And let met tell you boys and girls, it made me slick.
As in, like a fish. A fish!
So out comes the smart phone,
'cause we all know I'm a bit of an over-sharer.
Selfie after selfie posted on the web.
Good times!
Kind of pathetic actually.
A grown woman dousing herself in olive oil to try
and grab a little attention from the opposite sex.
That, class, is what adults call "desperation."
You might think you understand the
meaning of the word, trust me, you don't.
Oh. Right.
You have a new classmate.
It's not a cow, is it?
No. In fact, she's anything but.
Hey. Miss Kinoshita. Come on in!
No way this girl's an ordinary high school student.
She's too pretty. I mean, look at her.
She makes that uniform look like
something out of a magazine.
She looks like a pop star.
She looks like...
My Yukatan.
My name's Ringo Kinoshita.
Eh?
"The King of Farmers."