Gah.
Man, what is up with this heat?
Come on, look at the bright side, okay?
It could be freezing and we'd
have a bunch of dead vegetables.
Like our tomatoes and cukes.
Tomatoes and cukes don't do well in the cold?
Nope. Low temps mess with their growth and development.
It can cause them to bruise super easily.
Didn't know that.
Wow. That's awful.
Do soybeans do well in the heat?
Yeah. They'll be fine.
When you were planting them earlier,
I think I mentioned how incredibly useful soybeans are.
But what I didn't tell you is
that they have a special power.
They do?
Oh yeah. Hey Kousaku, why don't you tell her
about the three major nutrients in farming?
Sure.
Well...
Nitrogen. Acid. And Potassium.
Of the three, nitrogen is the most special.
It's true. Without it, crops won't grow properly.
Nitrogen.
Yes. The mighty power of the super special soybean
lies in its ability to make large quantities
of the nitrogen nutrient.
Hmm...
There's a lot of the stuff just
floating around in the air.
Soybeans can convert it to usable compounds.
Or... To put it another way,
they make their own fertilizer.
Soy beans are... neato.
It's July. The hottest season is upon us.
Not to mention that our agricultural lives
are heating up, too!
Alrighty then!
Here's to another hard day of work out in the fields!
Whoa. What's the deal with all this food?
Cucumbers, tomatoes, eggplant, peppers, bitter melon,
okra, pumpkin, zucchini, and corn!
We got bushels of reject vegetables!
So we dine for free!
It's "all you can eat," time, you guys!
Awesome.
There are many valuable lessons for a farming student
to learn about life.
But the most important lesson of all
is this:
Is what?
Students must always clean their plate!
No matter what!
Heck yeah. Think we've got you covered there!
Dig in!
Bon appétit!
What's wrong, Hata?
Minori cooked again, huh? This looks like her handiwork.
Uh-oh. It's reject veggie season again, isn't it?
Last year's melon festival was a real mess, too.
Yeah! Those were the biggest melons I'd ever seen!
Surprise, surprise, Kousaku's blathering on
about useless nothings again!
So big!
The biggest I've ever seen!
Uh. You know, I actually sent you some nice,
juicy watermelons too, Ringo.
I made sure to pick out the sweetest ones!
Yeah. I know, thanks.
Sure. No prob!
Wait. You know?
Here we are again!
At the end of a hard day of work in the fields!
Well, I guess being stuck with too much food
is a first-world problem.
Things could be a lot worse, you know?
So true.
All the more reason we should savor every single bite!
Yeah! Thank you for the grub!
Wow! This cold bitter melon salad is delicious!
Oh, you like that? The secret ingredient
is a little chili oil in the sesame dressing!
What is this stuff?
Pear curry!
The crunchy texture and mild sweetness
give this dish the perfect one-two punch!
Wow, this ratatouille is richer
than a bunch of steamed veggies have any right to be!
I'll have seconds!
Eat up, everybody!
There's plenty more where that came from!
Huzzah!
Yum, yum.
Sweet!
Hey, what's the matter with you?
Kei. Do you think that we're getting fat?
I don't know.
Maybe we're just packing on muscle
from all that harvesting.
That's totally what it is!
I thought I was looking a little
more filled-out than usual.
But it's probably just my pythons!
Hey, you two! Great meal. Right?
I was wrong! We're all fat!
So long to being trim and fit! Say hello to obesity!
Yep. We're chunky.
You're awful!
You know that's the worst thing to say to a girl, right?
Sorry if I offended you, maybe you'd prefer
I use a more politically correct term
like "pleasingly plump" or "fluffy?"
Here's the truth!
You two are fatties!
Huh?
He's right. You do look a little bit rotund.
Oh yeah, well, so do you. Fatty fat.
It's 'cause of those delicious meals you make every day!
Wait just a sec!
If you don't want what I'm cooking, then don't eat it!
Make me.
Jack pot! A catfight, every young man's
"dream come true!"
Well, at the very least,
it's a good sumo-wrestling match.
You remember that time they mud-wrestled?
That was way cooler than this.
Seems they haven't learned how to properly use size
to their advantage in a hand-to-hand combat situation.
Agreed.
Lose weight! Right. Now!
We're skinny.
Exercise is the root of any good weight loss plan.
Lucky for us, we have plenty of
opportunities to exercise here!
It's a good thing Miss Kinoshita's back to normal, too.
Well, that's a former celeb for you.
Their freakish ability to suddenly drop weight
puts us to shame.
Honestly, I was worried about Minori the most.
That so? And what worried you?
Oh, don't play dumb with me.
You forget this?
Huh?
So, who was the last fatty standing, huh?
Tell me.
Tell me!
No one will marry me
'cause I look like a marshmallow!
What am I gonna do?!
You're wrong, guys won't want to marry you
'cause they'll assume you're already pregnant.
You're so mean!
Has your family seen it yet?
I wonder what they would think
if someone were to text them this?
No, please don't do that.
Oops. It already sent.
No! Jerk! You give that here! I'm not joking!
You monster! You demon! You nasty little ringworm!
Kousaku?
Oh?
Huh?
The soybeans.
There's something really wrong with them.
This fuzzy white stuff I've never
seen is growing near the root.
Huh. Mold, maybe?
If you give them too much water they can get moldy.
Especially when the weather's as hot as it's been.
But I've been watering them every day.
Ah. Oh. Yikes.
It's true. I even watered them when it rained.
Well. For future reference,
best to skip the stormy days.
But a little mold's not that big of a deal.
We'll take care of it.
Hey. Let's go take a look on our next break!
Let's see.
See it?
Whoa... No way!
Is it bad?
Ringo. Go get a teacher, please.
Hurry up.
Southern blight.
Wait, I don't get it.
What is "southern blight?" Will the plants be okay?
Southern blight is a terrible disease
that can sometimes develop in soil.
Crops hit by this disease don't survive.
They just fade away.
What's worse is that blight forms sclerotia
in the ground, allowing it to keep multiplying there.
What does that mean?
It means the disease contaminates the soil.
How can we fix it?
Can't be fixed.
If any of the spores remain...
...then they'll infect next year's crop as well.
To prevent that, we have to throw out the soil,
and the crops, too. We burn them all.
That's awful.
This whole mess is pretty hard to believe, huh?
It sure is.
Southern blight turned up at another school recently.
Apparently, we both use the same dealer.
If only we'd heard about it earlier,
we might've been able to do something.
Maybe... But Kei...
you know this isn't your fault. At all.
Minori. How's Ringo?
Don't know, she said she wanted to be alone.
No dinner?
She said she wasn't hungry, so I set some food aside.
Kousaku?
Huh?
I think she needs your help.
Talk to her. I'm worried she's taking this on herself.
If she'll listen to anybody, it's you. Please.
I don't know.
Well, guess what?! I do!
Because that girl is...
Just go talk to her, please. She needs you.
Ringo. It's me.
So look. Farming can be really fun.
It can be one of the greatest
gifts that life has to offer.
But... at the same time it can be really brutal.
That's why so many people quit,
'cause it's too difficult.
We work so hard for so little.
It's not like we're gonna get rich doing this.
Sometimes we don't even get paid.
Then why?
If the bad outweighs the good, then why do it at all?
Good question.
My answer is, "I don't know".
I guess I haven't figured that part out just yet.
How'd it go?
I'm not really sure.
Oh...
Well, it's like they say, "time is the best remedy."
Kousaku?
Hm? What's up?
I wanted her to plant those soy beans for a reason.
It wasn't a random choice.
In the same way they enrich the soil
and give life to new things,
I hoped those beans might help her.
That her soul might be enriched.
And that she might also be born anew.
That's really thoughtful.
Yes, it's just that...
if she were to regret coming here,
I don't think I could stand it.
Kei?
Yeah, what is it?
You're nice. And I'm lucky to have a friend like you.
Same here.
Oh yeah, this is good stuff!
A deep, forbidden friendship reveals its true nature
in a secluded greenhouse!
We can call it...
I'll even put out a fan book!
What?
If we sell one thousand of these bad boys
at five hundred a pop, we'll be filthy stinking rich.
Who wants to buy a yacht?
This isn't really in character for me, but I'm here.
I had a feeling my services might be needed
and looks like I was right.
Hello there, my darlings.
Did someone say forbidden love?
I heard that phrase and came as fast as I could!
Uh, what's going on?
Does somebody want to tell me
what you guys are doing here?
What are these for?
Duh. That's advance payment for the footage.
Miso and a mountain lily?
Wait, are these for Ringo?
Uh. Yeah right!
"Ringo?
Of course they're not for Ringo, why would they be?
It's not like we're too embarrassed to give it to her
directly or anything!"
Great! Now they know the truth, you idiotic woodsman!
That was, by far, the weirdest thing
that's ever happened to me in my whole life.
Kei?
I actually think Ringo will be just fine.
Don't you?
Yeah.
Kousaku. You're awake.
This is bad.
Yeah. Let's get Minori. Ringo too.
I called everybody I could think of.
This is everyone who showed.
What happened? What are we doing up?
We're here to pick some tomatoes.
But it's so late.
Let's just hope it's not too late.
Huh?
Come on.
Look.
They're splitting open.
It's been nothing but hot and dry outside.
All this time, these tomatoes have needed water.
Now that it's raining.
The tomatoes will take in as much water as they can.
They'll split right open.
Where am I needed?!
Start with that row over there!
Right away!
Focus on the ones that haven't split yet!
Yes, sir!
We can still eat the bad ones.
We'll just puree them, or make them into jam, can them.
Keep on hustling, people!
I don't get it.
Why does everyone seem okay with this?
You raised them so carefully and waited so long for them to grow.
And now they're completely ruined.
I don't understand why you aren't more upset.
Hey. You got a sec?
I like it out here.
Though you must really think
we're out in the sticks, huh?
You know....
I like it too, actually. So much nature...
I'm glad.
But... There's no natural nature.
Not in anything you see out here, anyway.
Hm?
The fields, the farms. The roads and the rivers.
People made them all, bit-by-bit
and generation-by-generation.
Our predecessors had it hard.
There was a time when nature was
cruel and unforgiving to them.
And it's not just here.
Everywhere we humans live is the remains of
the great struggle between us and nature.
A battleground.
Battleground?
Yep.
You know, there's a whole lot
that's hard about agriculture.
But at the end of the day,
it's more fun than anything else.
Just getting to watch your crops grow.
And the same goes for the people who made this.
It must have been joyful.
They pictured the kind of town this was going to become.
They dreamed about us, here in the distant future.
And with all that to look forward to, they worked hard.
And who knows?
Maybe our vegetables will inspire someone.
Maybe one day they'll do something great.
And maybe they'll make the world a better place
for us to live in.
But even if they don't...
Even if they decide to just keep on doing their best.
Well, I think that ties into the
future of the landscape, too.
You asked why I do this?
'Cause I think we can help people be better.
There's real power in what we do. That's why.
I'm sorry.
That story went off the rails pretty quick, didn't it?
It was you.
Huh?
The veggies. You were the one who sent them to me.
Back then, I was so exhausted with my life.
It was like I didn't even have the strength to eat.
Then someone on my staff made me a salad
out of vegetables a fan had sent me.
Even though I was too tired to eat,
I figured I had to at least try it.
But when I put it in my mouth,
what happened next took me by surprise.
It tasted strange. Not like what I expected.
It tasted bad?
No. Not bad. It was very earthy.
And tough in an odd way.
But somehow gentle and sweet.
Well, it wasn't that big of a deal,
I just wanted to send you some vegetables.
No. It was perfect.
It really was.
You'd given me the taste of life.
You shared something I never experienced before.
It brought me to tears.
In that moment, I knew I'd be okay.
It was like someone was saying,
"If you trust this feeling,
and follow your heart, everything will be fine."
Don't you see?
You helped me. You helped me make my choice.
After that.
I happily ate every single
scrap of food you sent my way.
I looked forward to the letters that came with them too.
From the moment we started writing each other,
I knew beyond a shadow of a doubt
that I wanted to come here.
It was like I could taste how fun it was going to be.
Wait a sec.
Huh?
I... I didn't send you any letters.
But... those vegetables were definitely you.
Yeah, but I didn't put my name on the box.
And no letters.
No, you... You signed them.
Those letters were definitely from you.
And there was a picture of everybody, too.
A picture?
This picture? With a letter from me?
The tomato tragedy is over!
I'd say it's time we had ourselves some dinner!
Hm?
Huh?
Uh... You guys...?
Dinner's a good thing, so why do you look so stern?
Is everything alright?
There's something I'd like you to see, Minori.
Does this look familiar? You wrote it.
How could you do something like this, huh?!
Writing a bunch of fake letters to Ringo?!
I mean, to Yuka Kusakabe, pretending to be me!
I thought you'd be thrilled!
Huh?
I was only trying to help you keep
your super "creepazoid" factor down to a minimum.
You should thank me!
But... Mm... Well. That's thoughtful.
I guess...
Anonymously sending a girl you don't even know
a bunch of vegetables for no good reason,
that's a one-way ticket to restraining order town!
I think you're missing the point here!
Just think how Ringo must feel knowing all those letters
she read are actually from you and not from me!
Hmm... You've got a point.
Huh?
I am very sorry, Kinoshita. I hate that I mislead you.
I only wanted to help.
To paint a picture of what things are really like here.
But I see now that I was wrong.
Okay. Stand up.
I wanted to meet you.
This whole time... It was you...
Uh... Kinoshita?
All I ever wanted was to look
you in the eyes and talk to you.
About school, agriculture, all of it.
The way you did in your letters.
I wanted it more than you could possibly know.
So, you're not upset?
Of course not.
I pretended to be somebody else.
I lied to you.
But what you wrote was true.
That counts for something, right?
And besides... If we're being real,
it's not like I was entirely truthful either.
We're even. Truce? What do you say?
Yeah, sure.
I guess we're all kind of similar in some ways.
Hey. Can I call you "Minnopio?"
Sure!
I don't mind that as long as I can call you "Ringotchi!"
I'd like that!
Awesome!
Minoppio.
I sure love you.
I like where this is headed. Kinoshita's happy again,
mysteries have been solved, and all's well.
Looks like a fairy tale ending to me.
Well, I think this is the worst!
Happily ever after, my ass!
Cooking Granny.