Hello again.
Our story today begins a little while after
Ringo transferred to "Tamo No-Rin High."
Seriously, slow down, you're stressing me out here!
Geez. Not like we have anywhere important to be.
Life likes to surprise us sometimes.
Just when we think we're comfortable.
Bam: Game Changer.
And all we can do is stand there and take the moment in.
We've been terrorized!
Ugh. What a nightmare.
Maybe someone should call the police?
Had a feeling this would happen one of these days.
There's not even a fence,
this field's completely vulnerable!
Did anybody here happen to see who did this?
If so, speak!
I saw it.
Yes. The perpetrator of this foul deed was a child.
Child?
He was wearing a grey coat or some such thing,
running off with his arms filled with our vegetables.
Wait. What time would you say this happened?
I believe it was yesterday evening on my way back home,
after I finished feeding the cows.
I would say it was a touch after eight o'clock.
The fiend dropped this.
It would seem you're telling the truth.
The question is: what are you planning to do?
If it was a child,
then you have to impartially investigate
the facts and figure out his motives.
Yes. We have to figure out what happened fast!
Do you think it's possible the boy did this
'cause he's starving?
Please, sir. Please, may I have some more?
Aah! Don't you people get it?!
If we don't get to the bottom of this,
these kids will keep coming around and eating all our
vegetables, willy-nilly, with no consequences at all!
Hey, you guys!
The adults are talking, Minori!
In case you haven't noticed,
I am attempting to prevent what
could become a major crisis!
You know. It could've been a monkey.
A what?
I'm picking up a monkey vibe, aren't you?
This has monkey written all over it.
You're wrong! He was walking on two legs!
Wild monkeys may not be able to walk for miles
upright like that, but they can do it!
That's true. I've seen them run off
with whole watermelons before.
Wait. You've seen this with your own two eyes?!
Minori and I are seriously from
the middle of nowhere,
so we saw crazy stuff all the time.
Dogs, monkeys, pheasants. You name it.
What is this? Japanese folk hour?
Oh, man. I'm just glad there wasn't a starving orphan.
Okay, everyone, we're done!
What's going on?
Oh. We're just thinking we're
in for a bit of a battle here.
Let's do this.
All right.
Welcome to the first ever "A Monkey Showed Up
and We're in a Jam, So Now We Have To Come Up
With Some Countermeasures" meeting.
Now. Why don't we all take turns making suggestions?
Oooh! Kei! Pick me first!
Back where I come from, if we want to keep varmints
from treating our crops like a buffet,
we build an electric fence.
Yeah, but... Couldn't the animals get hurt?
It'll shock them, but they won't die.
Yes! Commence fence building at once!
Hmm...
While the idea itself isn't all that bad,
I'm afraid it's impractical.
Yeah, why's that?
We're flat broke.
That sucks.
He's clearly hungry, so why don't we just feed him?
Huh?
It does seem like the humane thing to do.
I get it now.
You're saying if we stuff his belly till he can't eat
another bite, then he won't need
to mess up our fields anymore
and we can get back to business as usual!
That is the greatest idea of all time!
Not bad, but there's only one problem.
The food supply isn't his only target.
He's been ransacking our potted plants as well.
It seems pretty obvious to me
the beast is doing this for fun,
so I'm not so sure a full belly will stop him.
So much for that!
Listen up.
I've spent my whole life battling these monkeys.
I know where their weaknesses lie.
Sheer brute force is the only
way to stop these evil bastards.
Behold! I give you Super Hitoshi, with thirty times
the power of the old Hitoshi,
a weapon guaranteed to blow
his monkey butt back to the jungle!
Oh my. That's an awful big gun you have!
This bad boy can launch up to
thirty fireworks simultaneously!
What the heck? Well, that's weird.
Maybe the gunpowder's wet or something.
Here, let me take a look.
Kids, believe me when I tell you this.
It's never a good idea to stare
down the barrel of a loaded gun.
Who's idea was this?!
Poop.
Because you have all failed miserably,
I will now unveil to you my super secret plan!
All right then. Spill the beans.
Listen, Vulgarians.
As you know, humans and monkeys are both primates.
If we deal with this rationally,
I think you'll see that...
Hell no!
Uh. Whatever. It was ingenious.
You can't deny humans and monkeys are both primates.
Hunter?
Yes. He's just one monkey.
It's not like a whole army.
We should be able to dispose of it easily.
Dispose?
Uh. Kei. I know we've got to put a stop to this,
but won't you feel bad about having the monkey killed?
Farming is a brutal business.
Truth is...
I'm prepared to do whatever it
takes to solve this problem.
Ah. Yeah, okay...
As a matter of fact, I know a skilled hunter.
He's just the man for the job.
Hello. My name's Ohmori.
Wow. Guy's a total creeper.
Whoa! Keep those thoughts to yourself!
No, she's right, the man's a troll.
Hey! Did you not hear what I just said?!
Surely this isn't your man.
You claimed you knew a skilled hunter.
I'll wager the only skill this man possesses
is finding the nearest box of snack cakes.
People are only 90% looks.
Which means there's 10% of them
that'll take you by surprise.
Ohmori might be large. But he's large and in charge.
And he's a blowgun pro!
You got to be kidding me!
Oh no. It's no joke. It's real.
Yours truly is the founder
of the Ohmori School of Blowgun Arts.
That's not weird.
Okay then.
If you're a master, where are your blowguns?
Right here.
Huh?
Seriously? Those are your blowguns?
They're my super stealthy sniper blowguns.
"Sniper blowguns?"
Right. Of course they are.
Didn't mean to doubt you or anything, it's just,
when I first saw them,
I kind of thought they looked a bit
like anime wall scrolls.
Oh. Actually, that's precisely what they are.
Huh?
These puppies make decent blowguns
if you remove the thumb tacks, take them off your wall,
and roll them up.
Uh, yeah, I can see they do.
So, Mr. Ohmori, if you don't mind me asking,
with your homemade blow dart wall scroll guns,
what do you typically hunt?
Just the occasional real-lifer.
Neat. Swell. So, I got to ask this.
Your job?
I mean, when you're not out
there tracking down real-lifers.
Do you have a job that pays you money?
I'm unemployed!
This potent little narcotic will send even
the heartiest of knuckle-dragging primates
on a one-way trip to "Monkey
Heaven", if you catch my drift.
It's name? Well, if I told you, I'd have to kill you.
Look!
I mastered my dart gun technique
by sucking on pasta several hours a day.
I call this specific blowing method the "deep throat."
Cool name.
It's the throat. You have to keep it relaxed.
I don't want to know!
Come on!
All right! Time to show this
monkey whose turf this really is!
Yeah, spank that monkey!
Poor thing. He's hurt.
Kousaku?
No, Ringo, I'm sorry. But we can't show him mercy.
He's right.
Our responsibility is to protect these fields.
I know not how this vile beast was separated
from his tribe, nor do I know why he has invaded
our grasslands, but I do know this:
The time to consider the manner
of his disposal is upon us.
Maybe try not to sound so excited about it.
Oh, Kei, what a fool thou art!
I take no pleasure in killing
beasts, only in caging them!
I have a dear friend who works at the zoo.
I've requested that a comfortable dwelling
be prepared for him.
I'm a bit surprised. That's very kind.
You see...
Currently, they only house female monkeys at this zoo,
so when he joins them,
he'll be in "Monkey Heaven" in the best way.
He'll perform husbandly duties
and live life like a king.
Wow. What a relief!
This will give a whole new meaning to the
phrase, "monkey see, monkey do!"
Great plan. Thanks. I owe you for this one!
Charitable deeds done in the name of
self-gratification or seeking attention
are not genuinely charitable deeds!
I did what I did for the monkey and the monkey alone!
I do not require your "thank you", thank you.
I was right.
Coming!
Hey, Kousaku, what's up?
Mind if I come in for a second?
There's something we need to talk about.
Uh, come back in one hour, please!
Uh... Actually now would be better.
But this is very last minute and I have so many things
I need to get ready. Just, uh, wait right there.
One hour?
All set!
Can I come in now?
Yes. I want you to come inside.
Did you redecorate or something?
Yes. I did. But there's no need to be nervous.
Would you like to take a hot shower?
Uh. No, I'm okay.
You filthy boy.
So, you'd rather do it down and dirty then?!
Kei. You're here!
Wait. Kei?
Yeah, I invited him to join us. Come on in!
Thanks for having me...  Whoa!
She just redecorated her room.
This was our moment.
I really thought it was...
Uh... Yeah. I see that.
So, what's up?
You wanted to talk about something?
Oh. Right. It's about Ringo, actually.
Goodnight.
What?
Die!
Why are you freaking out?
I haven't even given you the details yet!
Die in a fire and rot in hell!
Rude. You don't even know what I'm going to say!
Man. She's gonna stab you one of these days.
How come?! Whatever, I'm done trying to figure it out,
just look at this.
All right! Here we go. Sing along with me, you guys!
Oh, cool. This is a Yuka Kusakabe DVD.
I thought I threw those things away,
but I guess someone had a secret stash.
I used my allowance and bought some replacements.
Anyway, take a good look at Yukatan.
Notice anything strange?
♪
Well. This may seem pretty obvious.
But she's acting so friendly.
The Kinoshita I know doesn't have
a happy bone in her entire body.
He's right. She's so smiley it's weird.
Bingo!
This is all about her smile.
Think about it for a minute,
the girl hasn't smiled once since she got here.
She didn't crack a smile in her first class.
She didn't so much as smirk
during the whole panties thing,
or during dinner. Or during the king game,
or when she survived the contest with Minori.
Not even when the damn monkey's life was saved.
That's true.
But her happiness here could
just be part of her act, right?
You may be onto something.
But still...
There's a person living with us who is so down
they never smile at all. Don't you think that's sad?
Yeah. Actually, it really is.
I know, right?
If you need smiles. Then have no fear.
The comedy cavalry has arrived!
Fancy running into you here. Kinoshita.
Anyway... How would you feel about
watching me perform a little trick?
Dark matter!
And?
Looks like we're going to have to step it up a notch!
Well, hello!
Tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle,
tickle, tickle, tickle...
Minori! Damn you for making me jealous right now!
But keep up the good work!
So, tell me. How do you like my technique?
Here, try this on for size.
Okay. How about a little communication?
Talk to me. How else will I know what you like?
I'm... sensitive.
The body doesn't lie. There's no reason to hold back.
Just give yourself over to absolute pleasure!
I give myself, I do!
Come on now. Show me that smile.
Now it's my turn to show you what I've got.
Stop! Don't do this! Please!
I'm drooling!
Seriously, I'm drooling all over the place!
I think I'm going to pee my pants!
You gonna tell me what's going on?
Look. I'm sorry. I really am.
It's just you always seem so glum all the time.
I guess I'm worried life here
isn't really doing it for you.
I see.
So this whole thing was about getting me to smile?
Dumb. I know.
We didn't mean any harm by it, I swear. But...
We did get a little carried away, didn't we?
I can't smile.
Huh?
I try. But it doesn't work.
At first, they said my expression seemed
a little stiff and that I needed to relax.
But I really didn't think much of it.
I figured I was just tired.
But. Over time,
I completely lost the ability to smile.
Eventually, I couldn't summon
up other expressions either.
The way things were, it didn't make
sense for me to stay where I was.
So I left, just like that monkey.
Yeah... But...
In the end, the monkey found a
safe place where he belonged.
So you can too...
That's nice. Thanks.
But there's no point.
How can someone not be able to smile?
It just doesn't make any sense.
I'm guessing it's psychological.
That's the only explanation I can come up with.
Maybe it was all too much for her.
Maybe she got burnt out living in the limelight
and always trying to meet other people's expectations.
She needs rest.
That'll make her go back to normal, won't it?
Well. One can always hope.
I want her to smile again.
Do you think it's selfish of me to want that for her?
If it is, maybe I don't care.
Kousaku. Kousaku!
Whoa! Who are you?
Do you not recognize me? Silly.
I am Gaia.
Gaia?
Yes. I have come to deliver a message.
Uh... What message?
You must remember, Kousaku.
Remember what mankind has done to me.
Remember your ties to the soil.
Please. Whatever the future holds. Stand firm.
Gaia is always with you, my friend.
Till the end of time. Listen and you will hear me.
Imploring you to honor the land!
No. Don't leave me here!
Please! Gaia!
Gaia!
What was all that? Wacky.
"Remember what mankind has done to me."
Guys. I think I'm going to take Ringo to you-know-where.
I really want to show her that soil.
Good idea. After all, she does have
something in common with it right now.
Yeah. That's true.
Maybe seeing that field and hearing a positive
message would help her realize there is always hope.
Schools like ours have things called
"Agricultural Clubs", or "Ag Clubs" for short!
Well, at any rate, we're headed to the site of a project
we inherited from some former students.
A project?
Yes.
And if you're willing, we'd like for you to join in!
This is it?
Yep!
Not the tomato field over there?
Nope. Here first.
Try touching the soil.
Right now?
Yeah.
It feels hard and dry.
Mm-hmm.
The reason it feels that way is 'cause the soil is dead.
It's dead?
It's a figure of speech.
Crops won't grow here in its current condition.
That's so sad...
It's replant failure.
Remember, Miss Becky talked about it?
If you continue to grow the same plant in the same soil
over and over, eventually, it won't grow anymore.
Yes. That's exactly right.
People try to get around this problem.
They use chemical fertilizers
to try to stimulate new growth.
But that only leads to disease and
winds up damaging the environment.
What you're seeing is the result of a vicious cycle.
Will the soil ever go back to
normal again or is it dead forever?
The process takes time.
This field started out with that very same soil.
It's been there since the very beginning.
Previous Ag Clubbers started this project
and we inherited it.
They worked for seven years. Day in and day out.
Now it's our turn.
Seven years?
It's not fixed.
There's still a lot to do to
get this soil back to normal.
But even though this soil has a long way to go,
this field is slowly improving,
doing her best to live on the land she's got.
So, eventually, this place will be reborn?
Hey, those tomatoes look good.
Can I eat one?
What? Now?
I'd like to.
Sure. Why not?
Here.
It's bitter.
Yeah, that's 'cause it's not ripe just yet.
Still, I'll eat it.
Huh?
Yep, definitely bitter.
Told you.
Yeah, but...
I like it.
Whoa. You... !
What?
Wait, this one's more ripe! Here.
It'll taste way better!
Mine is even riper than hers!
No, no, no, stick with mine.
It's definitely juicier than Kei's! Take it!
Mine is fresher!
Food made with love,
love of the earth, love of people, spreads happiness.
The secret?
Reminding yourself that it's Nature's gift.
Working the land is one the
greatest joys life has to offer.
One day, I hope...
I hope you'll experience that joy firsthand.
Farming's Five Top Four!