Let's make a
trade, okay...?
My name is Ruiko.
Now it's your turn...
Do you think you can
tell me your name?
I'm Febri.
[GROUP] Aww...
[SATEN] That's a
very pretty name...!
Okay, then, Febri...
What else can you tell us...?
Anything goes. You can
just pick something.
[FEBRI] Mikoto Misaka.
[GROUP] Huh?
What, me?
So, um...
is this little one somebody you
might've actually met before?
No, not that
I can remember.
A distant relative
or something?
[KUROKO] Any half-sisters
you've never told us about?
Half-sisters?
[MIKOTO] Yeah, around
ten thousand or so...
[KUROKO] Wait...!
No, no, no, no, no...!
Do not tell me she's
your daughter...!
No, you would never
have done that!
Surely not without
telling me fir--
Ow... www...
Hi, I'm Mikoto Misaka...
I'm just wondering
how you know my name.
[KUROKO giggles]
They say children have a sixth
sense about things like this...
Which people are safe and
which ones are more dangerous.
Uhh...
Heh. Maybe, but she
hasn't seen this yet!
[UIHARU] A finger puppet?
[KUROKO] A prize that
came with a soda...
I don't know how many cans she
drank before she finally got it.
[SATEN] Still into
that little guy, huh?
Ahh...
[MIKOTO high-pitched]
Yo...! My name is Gekota!
[laughs]
[MIKOTO high-pitched]
Your name's Febri, right?
Maybe you can tell
me something, Febri.
I would--
Ahh!
You only have a one
in twenty-four chance
of getting a pink Gekota!
Ugh...
Are you really going to
make a spectacle of yourself
over a lousy
finger puppet?
Hey, come on, now, Febri...
You can't just run off
with someone else's--
That is so cute.
[KUROKO] It's pretty obvious
who she trusts the most.
You know... that
Gekota isn't yours...
It belongs to Misaka...
Why don't we give it back?
No...! It's my Gekota!
[SATEN chuckles]
Well, I tried.
[KUROKO sighs]
[KONORI] Hm. I'm not finding
any information on her
under lost children
or missing persons.
[UIHARU] Nothing at all, huh?
[KONORI] It's too late for me
to get in touch with somebody
at Antiskill who could help us.
What are we
supposed to do?
[SATEN] Well...
how about I take
her for the night...?
I mean, just look at her...
I have a little brother,
so taking care of children
is nothing new for me.
[KONORI] Well,
I hate to impose...
but if you really
wouldn't mind...
I don't mind at all!
But, you know...
my place is a bit small...
and it probably wouldn't
hurt to have some help...
What do you say Uiharu?
Wanna give me a hand?
Yes!
[light laughter]
[UIHARU] Hmm.
[SATEN] How's it
going out there...?
Ready?
Yeah!
[FEBRI sighs]
Lolly...
What's a lolly?
Here... it's all yours!
Should we see if she
wants to eat something?
Hey... want some supper?
[stomach growls]
[UIHARU and SATEN laugh]
Boing, boing, boing,
boing, boing, boing, boing!
Boing, boing, boing!
Boing, boing, boing.
So, looks like it's
time to play house...
Are you up for it?
Totally!
It's time to dig in!
[FEBRI sniffs]
What's the matter?
Doesn't it look tasty?
Aaahhh...
Aaaaahhhh...
Good, huh?
Yeah! Heh!
[UIHARU and SATEN laugh]
[SATEN] Okay... here we go.
Close your eyes for me!
Whee!
[SATEN] Okay, now
it's your turn...
Will you spray some water on me?
[FEBRI] Yeah!
[SATEN] Whoa...!
Easy, now, or you'll fall!
Be careful, Feb--
[splash]
[FEBRI] Ooh...
Are you okay, Ruiko?
[SATEN] Ooh...! You did
that on purpose...!
I'm gonna get you!
[water splashes]
[SATEN and FEBRI laugh]
[SATEN] Hey...!
Aren't you coming in?
Uiharu!
Hey, Whee-hah!
Yeah! Heh.
[zipper unzips]
[MIKOTO sighs]
I hate to say it,
but you seem to be
a finger short of a froggy.
Hey, don't worry.
I'm okay...
One lousy
finger puppet...
A free prize with
a can of soda...
It's...
no big deal...
Well, it sure doesn't
sound like you're okay.
I just have a lot of
things on my mind...
You know, like...
How does a little girl
I've never met before
know my name...?
And, more importantly,
why is she so afraid of me?
What...?!
Please don't tell me
that little street urchin
hurt your feelings, Sissy!
Absolutely unforgiveable!
But you need not despair...!
I know exactly how to fill
the hole that wayward child
has left in your heart!
Huh? Ah!
[KUROKO yells]
[HEAD RESIDENT] Hey, Shirai...!
What's all the commotion?!
[MIKOTO] I really wonder...
How in the world does that
lost little girl know my name?
[UIHARU] So, um...
She's pretty unusual, huh?
[SATEN] Still a cutie, though.
Yeah.
Hmm...
My goodness...!
That's an intense flavor.
Yeah...! It's crazy, huh?
[MIKOTO groans]
And she just sucks on
them like they're nothing.
[UIHARU] Oh, you're terrible,
Saten, you know that?
She did the same thing
to me last night.
"Hey, this is delicious,
you should really try it!"
Oh, let it go.
I said I was sorry.
Having fun?
Yeah!
Good to hear.
Yeah, I'm glad you're
having fun, Febri!
Heh, heh.
Ugh...
[UIHARU] Still no luck.
There's no data on her anywhere.
I put her information into the
database that handles queries
from missing persons
and lost child cases...
but so far, there's
been no response.
We all know what
that means, right?
Little Febri here
might be a Child Error.
Oh, yeah.
[door opens]
[HARU'UE] Hi everyone!
[UIHARU] Hey, Haru'ue!
We're settled from the move...
So I thought I would stop by
here and say hello to you all.
[KOSAKO] Well, what d'you know.
So that's where she ran off to.
[typing]
Ah, excellent.
You managed
to find her.
[HARU'UE] A Child Error.
That's what you think she is?
It does seem likely...
I've tried everything,
but I haven't found
any other information on her.
Guess we'll have to
wait until someone
from an institution
can come to get her.
I hope she gets
into a good one.
There are good homes
and bad homes?
From what I've heard, things
can get pretty horrible,
depending on the
facility you're in.
Well, maybe... we can
choose where she goes...
Hey, Uiharu...
do you know of any sites
that rate and review
these types of institutions?
No, they don't
really do that.
Hey...! I know!
I've received
confirmation.
They're willing
to accept her.
Asunaro Park said okay!
It's a facility
in District 13.
Don't worry, we've
been there before.
We know first-hand that
it's a warm, welcoming place.
However, there's
one small problem...
They aren't ready to
take her in quite yet...
They'll need at least five days.
That shouldn't
be a big issue...
I am more than happy to
look after her 'til then.
I'll help take
care of her, too.
Yeah, so will I.
In that case, I shall assist
with childcare, as well.
[HEAD RESIDENT]
All right, then...
I'll inform them
of our decision.
So... little one...
would you mind sticking with us
for just a little bit longer?
With you, Ruiko?
Yeah...! And
everyone else, too!
[FEBRI] You mean, with Whee-hah?
Yep.
[FEBRI] And Kuroko?
Yes.
[MIKOTO chuckles]
[FEBRI] And Mii?
Of course. I'll be here, too!
[FEBRI giggles]
[MIKOTO groans]
[UIHARU] Five days, huh?
That means Febri's
going to be with us
until the day of
the Reach Assembly.
Oh yeah...!
Speaking of which...
it's just about time for
our on-site security meeting,
isn't it?
[KONORI] I really do hope that
you'll come and visit us again.
[HARU'UE] Of course I will...
Next time I'll bring
Banri with me, too...
Bye-bye now, Febri,
you be good, okay?
Okay bye, Erii!
[MIKOTO]
Huh...?!
Even Haru'ue?!
[FEBRI giggles]
[MIKOTO] So help me...!
I swear I will get that girl
to call me by my name!
[SATEN] Huh.
Is this really where they're
holding the Reach Assembly?
'Cause that's
kinda surprising...
[KUROKO] Yes...
Well, it's one of
the sites, anyway.
It's just that this
place is sort of--
how do I put it?--
sad and uninviting.
[KONORI] The focus of the Reach
Assembly is academic rigor,
prioritizing pure research
over esper abilities...
The result is an understandable
lack of glitz and glamour.
[UIHARU] It tends to
get pretty nerdy.
[SATEN] That makes sense.
You sound like you're really
disappointed about this...
What were you expecting
the assembly to be like?
Oh, well, you know...
something with street stalls
and lots of events...
Everyone working together
to get it all set up...
That sort of thing.
Okay, so that's
why you came along.
Yeah, that's
pretty much it...
I thought it would
keep Febri, you know...
amused... Right?
Right?
[UIHARU] Right.
[MIKOTO] So cute!
[KONGO] My...!
Look who we ran into...!
Isn't that Misaka?
[MIKOTO] Huh?
Yep, that's her,
all right.
What a strange
coincidence.
Oh, hey...
it's Kongo.
I can see that,
thank you...
What is she
doing here?
Well hello there...
It's nice to meet you...
My name is...
[MIKOTO] I see.
So Wannai, somebody you
know from the swim club
is presenting at
the Reach Assembly ?
Yes...
We're here to help her
set up her presentation.
Awatsuki and I volunteered
to lend her a hand
since we're friends with her...
Kongo doesn't know her but
selflessly came along, anyway.
It's nothing to fuss
about, I assure you...
We'll be set up in
a matter of moments...
I'm always happy to
help those in need.
[laughs]
[MIKOTO chuckles]
[KONGO] So, tell me, Misaka,
is this young lady
tagging along with you
somebody's little sister?
[MIKOTO] Oh, no...
It's kind of a long story.
Come here you two...
You need to meet this
darling little girl...
Her name's Febri.
Isn't that pretty...?
We've only just met...
but I can already tell that
we're going to be friends.
[gasps]
In that case,
I know that we are
going to be the best of
friends, as well, Febri...!
My name is Mitsuko Kongo...
It is such a pleasure
to meet you... Truly!
It's really nice to
meet you, too, Mitsuko.
[KONGO] Yet another friend...!
My list keeps growing!
[MIKOTO] Great...
Now Kongo, too?
[AWATSUKI] Nice to see everyone!
[WANNAI] Have a great day!
[FEBRI] Bye-bye!
[UIHARU] Okay, you guys...
We're headed off
to our meeting now.
All right,
sounds good.
We'll just have a
look around the area.
[MIKOTO] This should give
me the chance I need.
[KONORI] Let's see...
Just give me a minute...
I think it was...
This place is ridiculously
spread out, huh?
Hey, before you go...
tell me where the bathroom is.
Well, it's...
how about I just take you there?
Yeah, if you don't mind.
Ruiko...?
[SATEN] It's all right, sweetie.
I'll be back in a
minute. Until then...
Why don't you wait
with Big Sister Mikoto?
I'm giving you two
a little time...
Have fun, okay?
[SATEN giggles]
[MIKOTO laughs]
Wait right there...!
I'll be back!
Don't be gone long!
[YOMIKAWA] Of all the...
This campus is a big,
sprawling mess...
We're gonna need a few
more security personnel.
[DRIVER 19-A] No...
I'm totally sure.
This is where it's
supposed to be delivered.
[MALE JUDGMENT OFFICER 19-A]
On paper, that may be true.
However...
we simply don't have the
authority to receive it.
Is there some kind
of problem here?
Apparently, this is a
delivery for the assembly.
But the student who is
supposed to sign for it
hasn't arrived yet.
This school is one of the
regular assembly prize winners.
Yes, you're
right. It is...
Most of the
other regulars
haven't shown up
this year, either.
Not here or at the other sites.
It's really kinda' strange.
[YOMIKAWA] Hmm...
Hey...
What's the matter now?
It's just...
Maybe I'm wrong, but
I thought I saw somebody
from one of the schools
we were talking about.
Huh?
[ARITOMI] I have
arrived at the site.
The package appears to have
been safely delivered, as well.
[KOSAKO] Roger that.
That's all for now.
I'll contact you again once
I've located the target.
[MIKOTO] So, Febri...
you getting hungry at all?
[FEBRI] Uh-uh.
Okay, then. Thirsty, maybe?
Hey, look over
there, Febri...!
Those flowers are
beautiful, aren't they?
Why's Ruiko
taking so long?
[MIKOTO] She's one
tough customer...
and here I always thought
I had a way with kids.
[MIKOTO] Mm-mm...
I am not going to let
this discourage me...
I'm ready to make a
sacrifice if necessary...
It's time to call
in the super-rare,
one in every sixty cans...
rainbow Gekota!
All right,
check this out!
[MIKOTO] Oh, no!
Where is she?!
Ahh!
Aw, man.
Who knew having a job was
so freaking exhausting?
[gasps]
Wow...!
Well, aren't you just
the cutest little thing?
Or not...
[FEBRI] Gekota...
[MIKOTO] I'm sorry!
I just took my eyes
off her for a second!
[SATEN] It'll be all right.
She couldn't have
gotten very far...
I'll start looking for her, too.
[MIKOTO] Great, thanks!
Hey, Febriiii!
[KONGO] Is something wrong?
Where are you...? Whee-hah...
Kuroko...
Mii...
Ruiko!
[FEBRI sobs]
This is it.
Target located.
[KONGO] There she is!
[FEBRI] Erii...
Mitsuko...
[MIKOTO] Febri!
[sighs]
[alarm sounds]
Ah!
Ahhhhh... Ah!
That looked like...
[MIKOTO sighs]
Good, you're okay!
[FEBRI cries]
Uh?
Ruiko!
[MIKOTO] Heh.
Oh, well...
I'm just glad she's safe.
No doubt about it...
That's her.
[KUROKO] So, it has been
quite an eventful day.
[UIHARU] I'm so glad that
nothing bad happened to her.
[MIKOTO] It was my fault for not
watching her more carefully.
I'm really, really sorry, Saten.
[SATEN] I should apologize, too.
Please forgive me.
Uh... for what?
Come on, now, Febri...
You made Big Sister Mikoto very
worried, running off like that.
You should say sorry, too.
It's okay.
I'm really sorry.
[gasps]
[MIKOTO] Hmm?
Thank you, Mikoto...!
Bye-bye now!
Ah!
[chuckles]
Hey, you...! Get back here!
[FEBRI] Ha, ha! No-oo!
[MIKOTO] I'm gonna get you!
I knew they'd be
friends eventually.
They just needed a little
while, that's all.
I am glad to see them
enjoying themselves.
Seeing them together like
that really does make it
worth all the trouble
I had to go through.
[KUROKO] Honestly, Kongo...!
You're going to
take all the credit?
That isn't very graceful of you.
Downright petty, in fact.
But I really was helpful
this time, I swear!
You just didn't see, that's all.
[KUROKO] Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[KONGO] I'm telling you,
it's the complete truth!
[KUROKO] Of course it is.
I believe you.
[KONGO] Don't say it like that.
I'm being serious!
[ARITOMI] As you know,
there are only seven
Level 5s here in Academy City...
and now, in addition
to the fourth-ranked,
we'll be able to experiment
on the third-ranked, as well...
This is truly a
stroke of good luck.
Well, in that case, I move
we put it to a vote.
Let's see a show of hands...
Those in favor of conducting
the experiment on Railgun?
[ARITOMI] And, of course,
I am in favor, as well.
[ARITOMI laughs]
[FEBRI muffled] So, next time,
Ruiko and Whee-hah
and Kuroko and Mikoto and--
[MIKOTO] Who thought letting her
do the preview was a good idea?
She's still got a
lollipop in her mouth!