[radio static]
[FOREIGNER 7-A]
This time at night?
What's going on?
I'm sorry...
There's been a fire in the first
wing of the DNA map analysis lab
that's attached to Shiname Uni--
The cause and the
level of damage?
Still under investigation.
[MALE EMPLOYEE 7-B]
Sir! Bad news!
There's a fire at the lab!
At the DNA map
analysis lab,
yes I already heard about it.
No, another lab!
Huh?
[FOREIGNER 7-A] Hm...
[FEMALE EMPLOYEE 7-A]
The research data
at Rangaku Medical Labs is gone?
[MALE EMPLOYEE 7-C]
Bio-labs' system is down!
Can you hear me?
Is anyone there?
I can't get through to School
District Three's Thought Labs.
Excuse me,
I'm sorry...
There are fires in
Shiname's second, third,
and fifth wings, too.
What is this?
An organized
terrorist attack.
What method are
the terrorists using?
There are no signs of
attack from the outside...
And no witness
reports of intruders.
It appears...
the equipment just exploded.
[FOREIGNER 7-A] Hmm.
New information!
The attacks are coming via
the communications lines!
We can defend
against that.
Block all external
communications.
[MALE EMPLOYEE 7-A]
Uh... yes, sir!
[MIKOTO sighs]
They're onto me, huh?
Uiharu would have done a better
job at hacking these guys
if she had been here.
But still, that should
more or less take out
seventy percent of
the operation.
Now I just have to get out there
and take care of the rest of
the labs more... directly.
[KUROKO] Again, Sissy?
I've got to keep going.
At this moment,
while I sit here,
they could have another
experiment underway.
I can't afford
to collapse...
At least, not before
the project does.
[KUROKO] Oh... Head Resident!
[HEAD RESIDENT]
What are you up to Shirai?
You're acting
downright suspicious.
[KUROKO] Me?
I don't know what you mean.
I'm not doing anything...
[HEAD RESIDENT]
That's even more suspicious.
[KUROKO] Well, see you later!
[KUROKO sighs]
Huh? Ah!
Sissy!
You're actually home!
I can't believe it!
[MIKOTO] What's wrong?
I'm allowed to be in
my own room, aren't I?
Well...
I mean, yes,
of course you are...
but it's just that...
you never made it
home yesterday.
I had some things
to take care of.
Okay...
Well, you're here right in time.
[MIKOTO] Huh?
Ta-da!
It's Anshindo's special,
limited-time-only
sweet-treat summer buns!
Remember, you were talking
about how much you wanted some,
so I went--
That's okay, thanks.
I'm not hungry right now.
In a little bit, then?
[MIKOTO] Sorry...
I'm heading out again.
You are?
But what happens if
the head resident
does another one of her
surprise room checks?
Well, if that happens,
you can just trick her
again for me, can't you?
Wait, Sissy!
[KUROKO] Whatever
you're involved in,
it's obviously serious...
and something you
want to keep hidden...
even from me...
Don't you know I want
to be there for you?
[SATEN] Oooh, yummy!
Anshindo's sweet-treat
summer buns!
These are super rare,
limited-time-only products!
Oh, yeah?
Oh my gosh they
look so delicious!
Is one for me?
Well, um... it's just...
[SATEN] Hmm?
You're both welcome
to have some.
Really?
But... wait...
You had some of these
yesterday, too...
You said you were going to
bring them home to Misaka.
Are these the same ones?
[KUROKO] Yes, well...
Apparently she wasn't in the
mood for sweets yesterday.
But... that aside,
she seemed to be doing fine,
so there's nothing
to be worried about.
Oh, Wow!
I would recognize
those anywhere!
But those are hard to come by!
Did somebody hear me saying
how much I wanted one?
That's so considerate!
[SATEN laughs]
Why don't you have
some with us, Shirai?
No, thank you, I'm okay.
[UIHARU laughs]
[KUROKO] Huh?
Oh, don't be like that!
I'll make some of the special
tea I've been saving, too.
[SATEN] Mmm, these are so good!
[UIHARU] You can tell they were
made by a well-established shop.
Possible arson you said?
Yeah...
There's been a whole series
of unexplained fires...
They've occurred in research
facilities all over...
We haven't received any requests
for assistance from them,
and it doesn't seem
to be too serious.
I wonder
what's going on.
I would put my money on
a bunch of false alarms.
Ah!
I know
I had one left!
You ate it,
didn't you Saten?
How could I not when you
left it wide open like that?
That was a mean
thing to do!
[KUROKO] I'm heading out...
I think I'll patrol for a bit.
Maybe they haven't asked
for our assistance.
But that doesn't change the
fact that arson is involved.
I guess if something serious
did happen, we'd be too late.
My thoughts exactly.
So I think we should increase
patrols from now on.
Nothing out of the ordinary
so far in this district. Huh?
Oh, come on,
are you really sure?
I'm really,
really sure.
Yeah? That can't be true.
[GIRL STUDENT 7-B]
Well, it totally is!
I'm not being
vigilant enough.
At this rate I'm not going to be
any help to Sissy whatsoever.
[MINORI] Hey!
This is one, right?
Oh, wow! You really
found one, Minori!
Okay, so,
what's the number?
[MINORI] Gimme a sec...
[KUROKO] You there. Kids.
What are you doing
hanging out in a back alley?
[GREEN SHIRT GIRL 7-A]
Well, ya see...
[KUROKO] Looking
for lucky cards?
You mean like that Money
Card you've got there?
[GREEN SHIRT GIRL 7-A] Mm-hmm.
Except it looks like
this one's a miss.
[KUROKO] A miss?
[MINORI] Look...
It's got a code on the front.
You want one with a code that
has a repeating number...
Find one, and it
means you're lucky.
One with three sevens in a row
is the best you can get...
It will grant whatever
wish you make.
[SAILOR SHIRT GIRL 7-A] They
say one person who found one
became a billionaire!
[KUROKO] So that's it.
An urban legend that grew out
of the Money Card craziness
that went on a little while ago.
[GREEN SHIRT GIRL 7-A]
Huh? But how come?
[SAILOR SHIRT GIRL 7-A] Why...
we aren't hurting anyone.
You might get hurt.
This area can be dangerous.
Do you understand?
Get back to your
dormitories, all of you.
[GROUP] Aw, no fair!
Also, as a member
of Judgment,
it is my responsibility
to take custody
of this abandoned Money Card.
[GROUP] Huh?!
[GREEN SHIRT GIRL 7-A] Aw, man.
Can she really do that?
[SAILOR SHIRT GIRL 7-A]
I'm tired anyway.
Hey! Minori!
[MINORI] Sorry! I'm coming.
[SAILOR SHIRT GIRL 7-A]
What were you doing?
[MINORI] Oh... nothing.
[KUROKO sighs]
[UIHARU] Really?
And this happened earlier today?
[KUROKO] Yeah.
Money Cards with
lucky numbers on them.
What a funny thing for
an urban legend, huh?
Almost childishly adorable.
"Childishly adorable"?
That's rich coming from
somebody in that underwear!
[UIHARU sobs]
[KUROKO] It may start out as
a cute little urban legend.
But when people get caught
up in something like that,
bad things can happen
unexpectedly...
Accidents. Fights, maybe.
And let's not forget the
suspicious fires, either.
We should all be more watchful.
[SATEN] Fine. It's still
a cool rumor, though...
If I got my hands
on a lucky card...
what would I do?
There are so many
things to wish for!
I can't possibly
make up my mind!
And there you go again...
What about you, Shirai?
What would you do?
Huh? What're you talking about?
If you found a lucky card that
would grant you any wish at all,
what would you want?
What would I wish for?
Huh. What ridiculous,
unscientific nonsense...
This is Academy City
we're living in, you know!
[MALE EMPLOYEE 7-A]
Regarding the other facility
that was attacked last night...
We investigated.
And we found that somebody
physically broke in
and wrecked the place.
There were no human
casualties... however...
most of the data and equipment
there were completely destroyed.
At each facility, the locks were
deactivated from the outside.
None of the infrared security
sensors were triggered.
And the cameras...
none of them recorded
the attackers.
Also, and this is strange...
while the incidents
were occurring,
the nearby wind turbines rotated
in the opposite direction.
[FOREIGNER 7-A]
Hm. Interesting.
This business with
the wind turbines...
That could be caused by
electromagnetic interference.
Uh-huh...
If she is the culprit,
all of our standard security
measures are indeed useless...
What's more, we don't currently
have the force we'd need
to stop her once
she's gained access.
[MALE EMPLOYEE 7-A] But sir...
If this keeps up,
the experiment...
[FOREIGNER 7-A]
...will be shut down. Eh?
[KUROKO sighs]
[KUROKO] Sissy! Be still,
my beating heart!
You look so sweetly
vulnerable like that!
Almost as if you were asking
me to sleep there next to you.
How many days?
How long has it been...
Since I've gotten
to sit this close
and just look at
your lovely face...
[KUROKO gasps]
[SATEN] Well...
If you found a lucky card that
would grant you any wish at all,
what would you want?
There couldn't be an easier
question to answer...
I would want...
I would want to be able
to help you, Sissy.
Good morning, Sissy.
Did you sleep well last night?
[KUROKO] I'll just go out
there and do my best!
Nothing here...
[MINORI] Aww...
Nothing here, either.
[horn honks]
[tires screech]
Wha- I thought that...?
But I could've sworn I saw...
[KUROKO] Honestly!
Weren't you even look--
You're the kid I
talked to yesterday...
Are you still chasing that
rumor about lucky cards?
No wait, it's
not like that!
Uh... I mean, I guess
it kind of is...
but it isn't.
It's just... well,
uh... you know...
[KUROKO] I get it now.
You want to find one
of these lucky cards
so you can give it
to a friend of yours.
It's a generous
thought...
But ultimately, it doesn't
matter what your motive is...
What you're doing
is still reckless.
[MINORI] I know...
But pretty soon I won't
get to see her anymore.
She told me that
she's moving...
Her parents decided, and there's
nothing she can do about it.
No matter what, I have to
give her a going away present
before she leaves.
We've been friends
a long time...
She's really nice...
and we hang out together
almost every day.
So... I just want to...
[KUROKO] Here, use this.
Oh sorry,
thank you.
She's a really
good friend...
isn't she?
[MINORI] Mm!
[KUROKO chuckles]
[UIHARU] Hey, how far
are you gonna make us go?
[SATEN] Have some faith in
my instincts, will you?
It's nearby...
The lucky card's here
somewhere, I can tell.
Let's give up already!
Over there!
Oh, wait... Huh?
Oh, uh, hey, Shirai.
What are you doing there?
[SATEN sniffs]
That's how you're going
to find it? Really?
Just give it a little
time, and you'll see...
The nose knows, I'm telling you.
Now... Why don't you
come give me a hand?
O-Okay...
What are they doing?
They look ridiculous.
For the record, I was patrolling
like a good Judgment officer...
Despite how it
may have appeared.
[KUROKO sighs]
[UIHARU] I am surprised, though.
[KUROKO] Huh?
I just wouldn't expect
you to help someone
who's hunting for a Money Card.
I wouldn't say
I was helping...
I was just looking
out for her--
making sure she didn't
get into any trouble.
I wasn't doing any more than
my Judgment duties require.
[UIHARU] Uh-huh...
Wow, Shirai, you might be
the worst liar I ever met.
It's obvious that
you're doing this
because you want to help her--
So, you
were saying?
Oh, nothing
at all...
But... what are we going to do?
Do about what?
If we really do come
across a lucky card,
it's still classified
as a lost item...
so it can't just be given away.
[UIHARU] I don't see how
we can make it work.
[KONORI] Oh... hey, you guys.
So what in the world are
you two doing down there?
[KONORI] Hmm,
that is complicated.
Obviously, as
members of Judgment,
we can't turn a blind eye.
We have standards to maintain...
But, still...
Hmm. It's true. A lost
item is a lost item...
This could be
kinda hard to swing.
Impossible,
maybe.
[KONORI] Ah! That's it!
I just had a
fantastic idea!
Hey, you two... Listen up!
So, um, what exactly
is this good idea?
You just leave
everything to me.
[UIHARU] Uh...
[KONORI] Well, here we are.
When it comes to
things like this,
I think the lower
tech, the better.
Though... it's a bit cliché.
Ooh! I love clichés!
Konori's gonna
save the day!
What do you mean?
What's happening?
[SATEN] What's happening?
We're searching, that's what.
Huh?
We're looking for
something lucky!
[GROUP] A four-leaf clover!
[KONORI] Here we go!
[SATEN] Hey! Wait for me!
[MINORI] Huh? Wait...
Hold on a second, will ya?
You mean we're gonna
search this entire place?
[KUROKO] We're going to try.
Huh?!
You never know what you can
accomplish until you try...
Okay?
Give it all you've
got and in the end,
you won't have any regrets.
[UIHARU chuckles]
Nothing... nothing...
Nothing here, either.
Yep, it's like
they always say...
Happiness isn't an
easy thing to find.
Oh, please! Don't say that...
You just have to know where to
look, isn't that right, Shirai?
I'm not so sure about that.
[UIHARU] Huh?
[SATEN gasps]
Hey you guys,
look what I found!
What is it? Did you already
find a four leaf clover?
[SATEN] No, not that.
A butterfly!
[SATEN] Oh! There's another one!
How sweet! Those two
must be friends!
[KUROKO] Sounds nice,
doesn't it?
Being able to
connect like that...
Being so close to each other
without even needing to speak.
[UIHARU] Your efforts
don't go unnoticed, Shirai.
They definitely get
through to Misaka...
So don't worry.
Uh... What are you
talking about?
Why would I be worried?
[UIHARU] And it isn't
just Misaka, either.
We appreciate it, too.
Yep.
[KUROKO] Uh...
You know, you don't have to
do everything by yourself.
That's right.
We're here for you whenever
you need us, okay?
[UIHARU] Uh... what's wrong?
Was it something we said?
We're just trying
to cheer you up...
[KUROKO gasps]
I actually found one!
[UIHARU and SATEN]
Ah! It's a four-leaf clover!
Amazing! I thought it
was gonna be impossible!
I'm surprised I
saw it, though.
It's a bit on the small side.
Small or not,
it's still fantastic.
Hey... Minori!
Over here--
[MINORI] Found one!
Look! Look! Look!
There are a whole bunch of
them growing right here!
Oh, wow, you got one!
Good for you!
[MINORI] Here's another!
[KONORI] That's quite a haul.
[KUROKO] Oh, you're
getting dressed...
Are you heading out again?
[MIKOTO] Mm-hmm.
I have some things to do.
Sissy, wait!
[MIKOTO] Hmm?
Um...
It's just...
Come back safely, okay?
[MIKOTO] Well, I'm off.
[door opens]
[MIKOTO] Kuroko...
Thank you.
Sure.
[KUROKO] I'll be here.
Waiting for you to come home.
Good luck, Sissy.
[alarm sounds]
[MIKOTO grunts]
Sir, there's been
another attack!
That's the third
facility tonight!
[FOREIGNER 7-A] Hm.
One more down.
So, that means...
There's only...
...two to go!
[KUROKO] A clover that
makes wishes come true?
I only have one wish...
and when you walk
back through the door,
that wish will come true...
I believe in you, Sissy.