[MIKOTO] I can't believe this...
My path crossing
with hers again?!
[THERESTINA] No, you are all
my lab rats, don't you see?
Would you prefer
a different analogy...?
Very well, Academy City
is my breeding farm,
and all you children
are my livestock.
[MIKOTO] But right now...
This woman could hold
the key to saving Febri.
[THERESTINA] Hmm...
Long time no see, huh?
How I've missed you,
my little lab rat.
[MIKOTO] Therestina...
Kihara Lifeline.
Ahhh!
Hey, aren't you gonna swim?
[MUGINO] Yeah... maybe later.
[phone rings]
Jeez.
Are you okay?
[TAKITSUBO] Hmm?
[FRENDA] Ahhhh,
this feels fantastic!
[MUGINO] Huh...?!
What are you talking about?!
[FEMALE VOICE 8-A] It's a
question of saving face.
Given what happened,
we can't just sit back and
do nothing, you know...
If we don't act,
and soon, we're ruined.
[MUGINO] Getting taken in by...
Don't you wanna
swim around?
Floating is fun.
[MUGINO]
...clean up your mess?
[FEMALE VOICE 8-A] Oh,
get off your high horse...
I told you you were
going to get paid,
so stop your complaining...
Besides, weren't you the one
who said you were pissed
about being tricked?
Tch. We can get
rowdy if we want?
[FEMALE VOICE 8-A]
Go right ahead.
[FRENDA] What's
the call about...?
More work?
[MUGINO] Yeah.
Can't say I'm excited, though.
Hope you ladies are ready
to work up a sweat.
[THERESTINA] Hmm...
[MIKOTO] Yeah, what?
Your face is looking
more grown-up these days.
You seen your fill
of darkness yet...?
Has this city
made you jaded?
So, how did
it happen...?
Something hit too
close to home...
and you
investigated...
You went seeking
the source...
and you
found darkness.
[THERESTINA]
Then at long last...
you realized that what I
said was correct all along.
Academy City is
one big test site...
and all the students
inside it are lab rats.
Well? What did you
want to ask...?
Or did you come here
seeking the comfort of one
who knows the truth, as well?
I want to help a friend...
to save her.
Huh?
[MIKOTO] Her name is Febri...
She's a little girl who
was artificially created...
If I do nothing...
she is going to die
within seventy-two hours.
I'm here for her sake...
I know an underground
organization is responsible
for making her.
Given your connections,
I thought you might
know something about--
Oh, come on.
Don't you learn?
What is it going to take...?
You got a whole heap of
your own clones killed,
and you still get all mushy
about some girl you barely know?
This kid, whatever her name is,
she's just one more lab rat
spawned by this city.
You wanna survive
in this town...?
Give in to the darkness
and live like livestock...
or become one of the
people in charge...
Because those are the only two
options you have in this place.
[MIKOTO] That isn't true.
I've seen it.
I know the darkness that
you're talking about...
At first I felt
lost and hopeless...
desperate and destructive.
But you know...
It was the people I
met in Academy City
who wound up saving
me from myself.
I'm not alone.
I have a group of friends
who are dear to me...
and if it weren't
for this city...
I never would have
met any of them.
There are a lot of things that
disgust me about this place...
but even so...
I can't bring myself
to hate it like you do.
[THERESTINA] Heh.
I've heard enough...
You can go now.
[MIKOTO] No, I can't.
Not until you answer me.
Who was it that created Febri?
[THERESTINA] How should I know?
[MIKOTO] What is
their objective...
What is this?
You must know!
Please tell me!
[THERESTINA] And what if I lie?
What possible motivation
could I have
for answering you honestly?
You and I have a history...
Can you really
believe what I say?
[MIKOTO] Yes.
I'll believe you.
Why is that?
Because right now it's
the only choice I have.
Hold out your hand.
Well, aren't you
going to eat it...?
It's just ordinary chocolate...
Nothing sinister about it.
What's the matter...?
Eat up.
You believe me, right?
I said I'd believe
you, didn't I?
Go away.
I'm staying...!
Now tell me about Febri.
You're wasting
your time.
I don't have
anything to tell you.
I'm not going anywhere
until you answer!
[THERESTINA] No, thanks.
I'm done talking.
[MIKOTO] Tell me about Febri!
What do you have to lose...?
Please, tell me!
[THERESTINA] Ugh,
you are such a pain.
Chemicaloid.
If I'm remembering correctly,
that's what they called it.
[MIKOTO] Called what...?
You mean a chemicaloid
is what Febri is?
[THERESTINA] At the time,
of course,
it was all just theoretical...
But those boys must have found
some way of making it happen.
These "boys" are the ones
who made Febri, then...?
Well, what was their objective?
[THERESTINA] Hmph. Beats me.
It's probably their
elaborate way of getting
their existence noticed.
Getting noticed?
[THERESTINA] There's
some kind of fancy event
coming up, isn't there?
[MIKOTO] An event... Uh...
The Reach Assembly!
They had to artificially
create a person
in order to get attention?!
That doesn't make any--
[THERESTINA]
Doesn't make any sense?
[THERESTINA laughs]
Oh, yes, that's good.
Spoken like a true Level 5.
[MIKOTO] Huh?
[THERESTINA] Don't you
understand, little girl?
Here in Academy City, you are
one of the privileged elite...
Pin on your Level 5 tag, and
even a pathetic lab rat like you
will have plenty of dear friends
flocking eagerly to your side.
Don't think for a second
that you understand
the true darkness
of those who lack
even your status in this city...
At the end of the day,
you know nothing.
Stupid brat!
[UIHARU] What?
You actually met with
that witch Therestina?!
Yeah... sorry...
It happened so rapidly
there was no time to
tell you guys about it.
So, according to her,
"chemicaloid" is the official
term for what Febri is?
[KONORI] And the
people who created her
are planning to do something
at the Reach Assembly?
She didn't say that exactly.
I just put it together...
That strange guy Kongo saw...
the one who was
talking on the phone
about "retrieving" Febri...
he was at one of the Reach
Assembly campuses, right?
Therestina mentioned an
event that's coming up...
I'm guessing that's it.
I'm still confused...
It was the hospital doctor
who arranged it...?
It was his idea for you to
ask Therestina about this?
[SATEN] There's something
about that guy's face...
What's his role in
all this, anyway?
There is something else
he told me that I think
all of you should know.
What's that,
Sissy?
[MIKOTO] He made some
calculations based on
the number of lollipops
Febri had with her.
Without more, she only
has seventy-two hours.
To live...?! Oh, no!
That's all...?
Three days
isn't very long.
[SATEN]
Uiharu?
I'm going to screen everyone
who's involved in the Assembly.
Administrators...
participating students...
That's a good idea.
Hey there, sleepy head.
Hello...
[door opens]
[KONGO] Good afternoon!
How is everyone?
We brought something
I think you ladies
will be excited about.
Oh, really?!
Were you finally
able to get a lead?
Huh? Oh... no...
No, we weren't.
We're really sorry.
We searched everywhere
for that man. I swear!
All through the city!
But I'm afraid we didn't find
anything worth mentioning.
Never fear...!
Give us more time, and
I know we will find him...!
Anyhow... we're here
on other business today.
We came because we have
a little present for Febri.
A present for me?
[WANNAI] While we were
out scouring the city,
we found an adorable outfit.
[AWATSUKI] And we thought...
"Wow, that sure would
look cute on Febri!"
Yeah...? Isn't
that nice, Febri...?
A new outfit, just for you!
[SATEN] Okay, then...
why don't we open it?
[UIHARU] Wow!
That's really perfect!
[FEBRI] That...
that's for me?
[WANNAI] Yes.
Mitsuko, Wanna, Atsuki...
Thanks so much!
[KONGO] There's no
need to thank us...
Anyone else would
have done the same.
For Febri!
Yes! Very pretty!
[SATEN] Febri!
Your face is flushed...!
Do you feel like
you have a fever?
Don't know what
a fever's like...
My head just feels all foggy.
Um... A lollipop! Right...!
She's getting worse.
We have to hurry.
[typing]
Hey...
It's him! It's him! It's him!
That's the man we saw...
The one who was
talking on his phone
at the Reach Assembly Site.
Take a look, you two.
That is him isn't it?
[WANNAI]
Yes, definitely.
Oh, yeah.
I would recognize
him anywhere.
[MIKOTO] What's that photo from?
[UIHARU] The participant list
from last year's assembly.
Haruki Aritomi.
Oh! According to this he won
the Academic Reach Assembly's
first prize two years ago...
In fact, it seems he's a regular
participant and winner.
[WANNAI] Wow...!
If he consistently wins top
prizes at the assembly...
[AWATSUKI] ...it means
that he's one of the most
brilliant people
in all Academy City.
[KUROKO] This man?
Really? That's odd.
I've never even
heard of him before.
Of course not...
In a city that's full
of high-level espers,
an ordinary genius
doesn't really stand out.
[THERESTINA] Don't think for
a second that you understand
the true darkness
of those who lack
even your status in this city...
[UIHARU] Oh, hey...
Something else...
It doesn't look like he's
participating this year.
[KONORI] Hey, you know...
that reminds me of something
Captain Yomikawa said...
about how a lot of
regulars apparently
weren't showing up to
the assembly this year.
[UIHARU] Let me see...
Yeah... you're right, Konori...
It seems like a bunch of
the usual participants
aren't signed up.
[KUROKO] Let's take a good look.
Some of these people could
be his associates,right?
[typing]
[NUNOTABA] No relevant
data retrieved.
Okay, then...
That just leaves Lab One.
[SATEN] Gotcha!
Ahh! Hey!
I can't see!
[SATEN] So, little one...
Not still feverish...?
You really feel all right?
[FEBRI] Uh huh!
She had a good
appetite, too.
I think we can
rest easy for now.
[SATEN] Have you still been
searching this whole time?
Well, yeah...
I felt like I needed
to do something...
I'm checking out
this Aritomi guy...
Apparently he dropped out of
school just a little while ago.
Oh...
that's a shame, huh?
I mean, if he wins those prizes
every year, he must be smart...
wouldn't you agree...?
He could be doing something
that's more respectable.
Instead he works
for the underground
and tries to abduct
a little girl...
I just don't get it.
Yeah... why turn
to a life of crime?
Exactly...
I just learned about
the Reach Assembly.
But knowing there are non-espers
out there who are successful...
it really gives me hope.
Right, of course.
[KUROKO] Yes... If you
don't mind, Captain...
That would be great.
Okay.
She says there's not
enough evidence yet
to justify taking action...
Oh, well...
That's what we were expecting.
We knew they weren't
going to be much help...
not when you consider
how much pressure Antiskill's
under right now...
You're pretty quiet...
What's wrong?
Is something bothering you?
Yeah...
It was something that
she said to me earlier...
Therastina.
A lot of people in
Academy City have heard of
the Railgun of Tokiwadai
at some point, right?
I've met a bunch of people
because of that title...
It opens doors.
So, I was just wondering,
if I wasn't a Level 5...
if I wasn't, do you think...
Would it be the
same between us...?
I mean, you and
all the others...
would we still be good
friends like we are now?
Oh, don't be silly.
[KUROKO] The reason I'm so
attached to you is not because
you're the fabulously talented
Level 5 Railgun of Tokiwadai...
It's because you're
the reckless, stubborn,
and a little childish...
but still strong and
kind and thoughtful...
Big Sissy Mikoto Misaka.
That's good ...
Thanks, Kuroko...
However...
[KUROKO] Ahh!
[MIKOTO] Don't take advantage
of the situation...!
And don't call me
childish, either!
[KUROKO] Th-There's that, too...
I also love how
you show no mercy
when you decide that somebody...
deserves to be punished.
[MIKOTO] Heh.
[MIKOTO] STUDY Corporation?
[UIHARU] Yes...
Haruki Aritomi's name came up
as one of the company's
lead directors.
[KUROKO] Okay, so what
kind of company is it?
[UIHARU] They seem to
do a lot of things...
but mainly it's
pharmaceutical manufacturing
and chemical engineering.
[MIKOTO] So...
do they have any
suspicious facilities?
[UIHARU] According to
what I've found so far,
STUDY Corporation owns a
factory in School District 17.
It's an old factory and
nothing very special...
but the fact that they paid a
huge amount for it bothers me.
It's not much, but
it does seem fishy.
If it's a factory, do you
think it could be the place
where they created Febri?
[KUROKO] Maybe that's where
they made her candy...
If we could at least find out
what its components are, then...
I can think of one way
to find out for sure...
Go to the factory
and take a look.
We need to
move quickly.
[MIKOTO] The most important
thing for us to focus on now
is keeping Febri alive...
which means we either need
to get more of that candy
or figure out how
to manufacture it.
[MIKOTO] I have
to do this right.
Febri's life depends
on my success.
That bridge again...
[KAMIJO] I know you
have your own goals...
Mine is seeing everybody
get through this alive...
So... Let's work together...
Maybe we'll both win.
[MIKOTO] Thinking
back on it now...
It's such a naïve, and
unrealistic goal to have.
He can dream all he wants...
but is he prepared
for the consequences
if we should all lose?
[chuckles]
In the end, I guess...
You have to believe
in something.
[alarm sounds]
What is it?
[KOSAKO] There's an
intruder in Lab One.
That's unexpected...
Who could it be?
[KOSAKO] I don't know...
The security system just
went into Shift A alert.
The security at that laboratory
is intentionally low-priority.
After all, it is a decoy...
It's not surprising that
somebody is sniffing around.
It shouldn't interfere with our
plans at this point, should it?
Not if they're just
now finding Lab One.
There's nothing there that can
be used to hurt us, correct?
[MADARAME] All of Janie's
data has been relocated.
The info on the
neutralizing agent
is the only thing that's left.
[NUNOTABA] We should
make sure...
I'll go have a look around.
You're going
to Lab One?
Sounds like an
unnecessary risk to me.
I'm not going to do
anything heroic...
but we've come too far
with this to fail now...
I just want to make sure that
everything is still secure.
We don't want any surprises.
Very well. Go.
[gunfire]
[MUGINO] And once again,
there's nobody here.
What the hell?
Just like last time...
We were given ultra-bad intel.
We are still gonna get paid
for the job though, aren't we?
[MIKOTO] What...?
Those guys?
I didn't expect
to see them here!
Did they set up a trap because
they knew I was coming?
It doesn't look like
that's what they're doing...
Are they working against
STUDY Corporation?
Like some kind of
underground feud?
[FRENDA] Huh...?
What's the matter Takitsubo?
Mugino!
[FRENDA] Ha...!
It's no use!
Takitsubo's badass AIM
Stalker lets her track
any ability she has
sensed before...!
All told...
that makes sneaking
up on us impossible!
[MIKOTO] An ability?
Does that mean that
someone is moving those
unmanned powered suits
using psychokinesis?
But there's no sign of
anybody around here...
Then, how are they doing it...
Maybe... some kind
of remote control?
[YOMIKAWA] It was lying
inside the powered suit...
It seems to be made of
the exact same components
as those that comprise
the girl Febri's body.
[MIKOTO]
It's theoretically possible
that the hair Antiskill found
acted as a sort of receiver
for some ability...
If that's the case...
and if one person alone
was moving that
many powered suits...
They must have
Level 5-grade power.
That severely limits who
the hair could belong to.
[FRENDA] Takitsubo!
Are you okay?
Yeah. I must be
tired from swimming.
Sure that's all?
Ugh... I'm sick of this...
Let's just go.
We'll be right
behind you.
Come on...
We're leaving.
[MIKOTO] Crap!
[FRENDA] What is it...?
Is something the matter?
No, nothing... It's okay...
My mind's just
playing tricks on me.
[FRENDA] Oh?
Ahh, I'm all sweaty...!
Let's hurry back to the pool.
That sounds good.
[KINUHATA] You probably
shouldn't swim anymore, though.
[MIKOTO sighs]
[MIKOTO] Man,
look at this place.
They really made a mess
of things in here...
I don't know...
I'll be lucky if I
can find anything.
Hold on...
Over that way...
An area with
functioning electricity.
[typing]
[MIKOTO] Stay where you are.
And don't even think
about trying anything.
It's you!
What're you...
doing here?
[MIKOTO] I was right, then.
You are involved with this.
What is going on...?
Are you in league
with these creeps?
[typing]
That's how Febri
knew my name!
You're the one who told
it to her, aren't you?
[computer beeps]
[MIKOTO] Hello!
Say something, would you?!
[NUNOTABA] Take that with you...
It's the neutralizing
agent data.
The what data?
[NUNOTABA] The formula
for the candy.
If you act now there
should still be enough time.
[MIKOTO] But why...
why are you giving this to me?
[NUNOTABA] Hmph. Sorry...
I guess you deserve
an explanation.
Yes... As you already suspected,
I'm the one who gave
Febri your name.
It's all I could think of...
I didn't know who
else to turn to.
This wasn't how I
originally planned it.
But today...
there was an unexpected
disturbance here in the lab...
Fortunately, I was able to get
away in time to meet you...
and now you'll be able
to keep Febri alive.
You can give her a future.
[ARITOMI] I'm afraid not.
What you have there
is just a dummy formula...
It won't do anything to help
with Febri's condition.
I knew it would be a good idea
to have some insurance.
So you were the one who
orchestrated Febri's escape.
For a traitor, you sure
keep interesting company...
Enlisting the help
of a celebrity.
Very resourceful...
I am quite impressed.
It's nice to finally have
the chance to meet you
in person, Railgun...
Put a face to the
data I've collected.
And very useful
data it has been.
So you're Haruki
Aritomi, huh?
Huh? This is surprising.
You seem to have gone to a
considerable amount of trouble.
And all just to
save Febri's life?
She is a fine product,
but even so...
"A fine product"...?!
Then it's true.
You're the one who created her!
[ARITOMI] Easy, now...
You shouldn't use electricity.
Unless you want to destroy
the real copy of the formula.
Nunotaba...
Inject that into
Railgun, here.
It will only incapacitate her...
She won't die.
And what's more...
if you follow my
instructions exactly...
I'm willing to hand
this over to you...
After all, we have no real
use for it at this point.
No, I can't do it.
Inject me.
This is to save Febri's life.
[ARITOMI chuckles]
[MIKOTO groans]
[ARITOMI] Ha...!
Strong enough to render
even a Level 5 powerless.
[NUNOTABA] All right.
I did what you asked.
Now give me the data.
Well... about our deal...
[gasps]
[ARITOMI] It's like I said...
We have no use for Febri...
She is just a spare.
She's a spare?
[ARITOMI] Yes.
For an invention that's
truly revolutionary.
We call it Janie.
[MIKOTO] I knew you were
involved in this...!
Care to explain yourself?
[NUNOTABA] To tell the truth...
It's a long,
complicated story...
See, once upon a time--
[MIKOTO] Come on!
This is no fairy tale!