[FEBRI hums]
[MIKOTO] Scientifically
engineered...
Are you serious?!
[FROG DOCTOR] Hm.
You mean that...
she's artificial...
made by a bunch of
guys in lab coats?
[FROG DOCTOR] More or less.
No way... You're joking!
I can't blame you for not
believing. Most wouldn't...
Common sense seems to
negate the possibility
from the very start...
However...
We humans aren't always
good at knowing the limits
of common sense.
Of all people...
I have to imagine
you would understand.
I began my investigation
by analyzing the proteins
of which Febri's
body is composed...
It wasn't long before I
realized that they were not
proteins that occur in nature.
Lolly...
Would you like some, Gekota?
For her part, though,
she seems unaware that
she's not just an
ordinary person,
wandering through the city.
Of course, you can't tell
just by looking at her.
[SATEN laughs]
[FROG DOCTOR] Her body
functions very similarly
to the way yours or mine does.
Except there is one problem.
Every time her body produces
new cells to replace the old,
it involuntarily produces
a certain amount of toxin
at the same time, as well.
Toxin?
Yes...
If left alone, it will
accumulate in her body...
causing her internal
organs to shut down...
and killing her.
You must be wrong...!
She's doing
better now--
That's because
of her candy.
A component within it
neutralizes the toxin.
It is no exaggeration to
say that it's those suckers
that are keeping her
alive right now.
Without the lollipops,
she dies...
is that what you're
trying to tell me?
[FROG DOCTOR] I'm telling
you what I know.
Unfortunately, I can't fill
in the details for you...
This could be a mistake
made in the lab
or something
deliberately built in.
But, either way...
If you want to find out how
to keep her body functioning
as it should... The best idea...
is to track down the people who
created her in the first place.
Who is that...?
Who are the people
that created Febri?
And for what reason...?!
Are the people who run this city
starting up another
twisted experiment?!
[FROG DOCTOR] I don't know
whether this will help or not,
but a number of years ago,
I heard some rumors
about a group that
was looking into
scientifically recreating
human life...
but the rumors evaporated,
and I can't say for sure
what happened next.
So... she's a product
of that research.
At the time, those
sorts of experiments
were the province of
the city's underworld.
Meaning...?
There are some
organizations in the city
that aren't above board.
They exist in the shadows,
and are so powerful that not
even Antiskill can touch them.
[FRENDA] In case
you haven't noticed,
I work for the underworld.
[MUGINO] Do you think
this kind of child's play
will get you anywhere against
the underworld of Academy City?
[FROG DOCTOR] I assume you
want to save the girl.
But if you do...
You had better be prepared
to face the darkness
at the heart of this city.
Tell me. Is that something
you think you're ready for?
[FEBRI] ♪ Ge-ge-geko!
My name is Gekota! ♪
Oh, good. You're back...
What'd the doctor have to say?
[MIKOTO] Oh...
He says that there's
nothing more to worry about,
and we can all get out of here.
[SATEN] Did he really?
Aw, that's wonderful!
So, are you
ready to go home?
With you, Ruiko?
Yep...! And Uiharu.
Mm-Hmm!
Do we really think it's safe
to go back to my dorm...?
There could be another
attack couldn't there?
That's a good point...
I'll get in touch
with Antiskill.
I'm sure they can
step up some patrols.
[SATEN] Yeah... good idea.
[SATEN] That is a long time
to spend in a hospital!
[UIHARU] Are you hungry?
What would you
like for breakfast?
A hamburger!
[SATEN laughs]
[SATEN] You've got a new
favorite, don't you?
[UIHARU] Sounds like it.
[KUROKO] Out with it...
I know something's
bothering you.
[MIKOTO] Uh, what?
[KUROKO] You've looked pale
ever since you got back
from talking to the doctor...
Something got to you.
Something he said.
Uh, You... think I look pale?
[cat meows]
[KUROKO] A cat?
I wonder what it's doing here.
What's up?
Oh, uh... well...
I... um...
I forgot to ask the
doctor something,
so I'm going to
head back there.
You guys go on ahead.
I'll catch up, okay?
Now what are you
hiding, sissy?
[MIKOTO] It's been a while since
we've seen each other...
Is it okay for you
to be out and about?
"I got permission from the
doctor to go out alone,
so it shouldn't
be a problem,"
Misaka says,
providing explanation.
[MIKOTO] Oh, you did...?
Well, that's good, then.
[MISAKA 10032] I spoke to that
girl who came into the hospital
with you last night.
[MIKOTO] Huh...?
Are you talking about...
You mean Febri?
[MISAKA 10032] Yes.
I could not help but notice
that you stayed up all night,
waiting to see the outcome
of her treatment.
"She must be quite
important to you...
You haven't even visited
your younger sister lately...
Hey, hold on--
...and yet you waited
for hours out of concern
for this young girl... Right?"
Misaka asks with a pouty look
and a dejected slump
of her shoulders.
You stop that right now...
It's not like she's more
important to me or--
May I continue, please?
Late last night I had
a look inside her room.
[footsteps]
[MISAKA 10032] You have regained
consciousness, I see.
[FEBRI] Mikoto?
"Not her...
Her younger sister...
Or, more precisely,
a cellular clone
synthetically created
from her DNA map,"
says Misaka, politely
introducing herself.
[FEBRI] Oh, wow, really...?
Mikoto is your older sister?
Yes.
She is troublesome at
times, but still...
[FEBRI] Do you want
to know something?
I have an older sister, too...
I'd like to see her.
[MIKOTO] She... has a sister?
[MIKOTO] If Febri was
artificially created...
what does that mean...?
Could her sister have been
made in a laboratory, too?
"That is not all...
Something else stood out when
I was talking to the girl...
See..." Misaka
pauses for effect...
[MISAKA 10032] I sensed that
all the knowledge she possesses
seems to adhere to
a specific pattern,
one embedded at the
most basic level.
Uh-- What
does that mean?
"It is something that
Misaka has experienced.
Similar to the initial stage
of the Testament
learning process,"
Misaka reports,
observing a comparison.
"In Misaka's opinion...
it is not unlikely that
she received her knowledge
through the use of Testament...
In fact, considering
all the similarities
in the underlying pattern,
it is highly probable
that the Testament program
developed for the girl... was
created by the same individual
who developed
Misaka's program...
Says Misaka, expressing
her conjecture.
Which would mean...
...that she's involved...
I haven't seen her
since it started.
Could she really have
something to do with Febri?
Did she get involved with
another screwed-up project?
I thought...
[MISAKA 10032] She was nice.
That other girl...
She showed Misaka what
milk tea tasted like.
[MIKOTO] Huh?
"If it was possible, I would
like to see her again...
to express gratitude... but...
That may never happen,"
Misaka says, resigned.
[MIKOTO] She may or
may not be involved.
Right now I have to focus on
the information I do have...
According to what Kongo said...
the people behind the
robot attack were upset
because they had failed
to "retrieve" Febri.
"Retrieve" implies
getting her back.
Does that mean Febri could have
run away from them
at some point?
Whatever the case, the best
way to obtain more information
is to find out who these people
are and ask them some questions.
And if it turns out that the
underworld really is involved...
Then I can't drag Kuroko...
or any of the others into this.
I'll do it... alone.
[cell phone "ribbit" rings]
[MIKOTO] Hello...?
Yeah...
Hey, Kongo. What's going on?
[KONGO]
What's going on, you ask?
I've been on pins and
needles about Febri
ever since I left
you yesterday...
When I called the hospital they
said she'd been discharged.
Oh...
Right, sorry...
Mmm... She's fine now.
By the time we left, she'd
even gotten her appetite back,
so there should be
no cause for concern.
[KONGO] Well, that's
terrific news!
I'll pass that message along
to Awatsuki and Wannai.
[MIKOTO] Yeah... Please do.
Uh...
I actually feel pretty awful...
I'm afraid in all the confusion,
I might have hurt
their feelings.
[MIKOTO] Huh?
I told them everything that
happened yesterday and...
well both of them
felt really horrible
about not being there, too.
They said, "true friends
are there for you during
the bad times as
well as the good."
"That's what caring
about someone means."
So...
They're right.
I thought about how I would
feel if things were reversed...
and, you know...
I think I would
have been very sad
if I hadn't been
able to help out.
So I feel really bad now for
leaving them out of the loop
like I did.
Friendship is a very
precious gift, isn't it?
[MIKOTO] Yes... yes, it is.
Well... I have to go.
Tell Wannai and Awatsuki
hi for me, okay?
[footsteps]
[KUROKO] There you are.
Did you get the
information you were after?
[MIKOTO]
Huh...?
Oh... yeah...
All right then...
Are you ready to head back home?
[MIKOTO] If I'm gonna
act on my own...
I'll need to be
efficient about it.
First I'll search through
all the databases,
keeping an eye out for leads.
[KONGO] They said, "true
friends are there for you
during the bad times
as well as the good,"
"That's what caring
about someone means."
[footsteps]
[door opens]
[KUROKO] Hey, Sissy.
You're going out again?
Oh, um... Yep...
There's something I
need to take care of.
Okay, sure.
[MIKOTO] I'll be back
sometime this evening.
[KUROKO] Well...
come home safely.
You know...
if you need assistance
with anything,
no matter how big or small,
I'm happy to help in any way.
Just ask me...
Whatever happens,
I'm always here for you.
Is there
something wrong?
[MIKOTO sighs]
[MIKOTO] I'm just being stubborn
at this point, aren't I?
Sorry... What did you sa--
[MIKOTO] All right!
Well, here goes nothing.
I need to talk to you.
Huh?
Ah! Yes!
[MIKOTO] Hey, your towel,
your towel!
[SATEN] Huh?!
[UIHARU] Easy. Keep it down!
[SATEN] Oh... right,
I'm sorry...
but... you're saying...
..that Febri was
artificially created?
[grunts]
Imagine if your life
depended on eating a lollipop.
Whoever it was who made
her in the first place...
did they intentionally build
that dependence into her?
[MIKOTO] Probably.
They're beyond
Antiskill's control...?
Organizations like
that really exist?
Well, yes...
I think.
Do you have any idea
who it could be?
[MIKOTO] It's possible...
There was this one time...
I got into it with some people
who I think were a part
of the underground.
And they were
extremely dangerous.
If we're really going
to help Febri...
It'll mean taking serious risks
and exploring some shady places.
I want to make sure
you understand that.
I hate the idea of putting
you in harm's way.
And, honestly...
I don't know how well
I can protect you...
With that in mind...
I understand if
you don't want to--
[UIHARU] First up, we somehow
need to track down the people
who created Febri.
[SATEN] Kongo got
a look at that guy,
so we know what at least one
of them looks like, right?
That's a
good point...
Let's fill her in and
see if she'll help, too...
And we should check out
the place we were attacked
to see if we can
get any leads there.
[KUROKO] It's entirely possible
that the surveillance cameras
weren't working due
to the construction.
[UIHARU] I'll check to see
if there are any signs
of a system break-in.
[SATEN] Also, we can't
forget that Febri needs
those lollipops to stay healthy.
I wonder if we'd be able to
make them ourselves somehow.
[UIHARU] You're right,
good thinking...
Do you think you could
look into that Saten,
just to see what you can dig up?
And there is also the question
of that powered suit.
I'll check with Antiskill
to see if they've been able
to discover anything.
[UIHARU] Right,
that sounds good.
[SATEN] Now, what else...?
Everybody...
Hmm?
Misaka, you've
been awfully quiet.
We could really use
your help making plans.
It'll be best if
we can strike first,
before they have
another go at us.
[MIKOTO] Right.
[FEBRI hums]
That sure is pretty.
What are you drawing there?
Gekota!
Yeah...? You're doing so well!
[FEBRI giggles]
When I'm done with this
then I'll draw you!
You will, huh...?
That would be nice!
[UIHARU] We really
appreciate this, Konori.
It's great of you to keep
an eye on Febri for us.
It's no problem...
How's your work coming?
Have you found any
promising leads?
[UIHARU] From what
I can tell so far,
there aren't any signs of
intrusion into the system.
I think I'll widen the search
parameters a little more.
That's an idea.
Look! All done!
Let me see.
[FEBRI and KONORI laugh]
[SATEN] Hi... I'm back.
[UIHARU] Oh!
How did it go?
[KONORI] You look beat...!
Find anything out
about the lollipops?
It's about what
we were expecting:
[deep voice] "It would be an
extremely difficult task
to analyze all the
components of the candy,
and even if we succeeded there,
reproducing the exact formula
would be an even more
impossible undertaking,"...
[normal voice]
So he said.
Oh, that's
a shame.
He did say he
would get in touch
if he found out anything
helpful, though.
Honestly, I'm not sure how much
faith I have in that guy...
A doctor just shouldn't
look like Gekota.
Hey, now... be nice, Saten.
[YOMIKAWA] The powered
suit from the alley?
Yes... There's something we
wanted to check. If we could--
Sorry, too late...
The item in question
is no longer here.
Headquarters has taken over
investigation of that case...
They left with all
of the evidence
pertaining to
it this morning...
They took those security
robots along with them as well.
You mean the robots
from the other day?
The ones that went out of
control at the assembly site?
Yeah...
This isn't the first time HQ's
come barging in, guns blazing...
but they were pretty quick
about it on this case.
Anyhow, I did get
a preliminary look
at what little investigation
has been done so far.
But I can't say there's
much in the way of results.
The whole suit was a patchwork
of unregistered parts...
and there weren't any solid
leads on its footprints, either.
That's disappointing.
I guess there's nothing we
can do about it, though.
[MIKOTO] Well, thank you anyway.
[KUROKO] See you.
[YOMIKAWA] Hey!
Take this with you.
Why, what is it?
[YOMIKAWA] It was lying
inside the powered suit...
Who knows? It may
be some kind of lead.
Are you sure about this?
If it's gonna be taken
out of my hands anyway...
then it makes no difference
to me if it's you guys
or HQ who has it.
With that said...
Don't do anything
stupid, okay?
[UIHARU] Hmm...
What could it be?
Some kind of part that
got detached, maybe?
It seems like they carted off
every other shred of evidence.
What good is this?
The timing is
very strange.
I almost wonder if somebody is
putting pressure on Antiskill.
You mean like that
shadowy organization
Misaka was talking about?
Maybe. I wish we knew something
more about them, though.
Think hard, Febri...
Can you remember anything?
Even the smallest thing
could really help us out.
Hmm... Mm-mm.
That's okay.
How did the surveillance
cameras pan out?
[UIHARU] No luck there.
Right around the
time it happened,
the cameras all went dark...
Every last one in the area
showed an operational failure.
There's no way...!
Did you check all of them?
Of course...
The entire area must
have experienced
some kind of interference.
That makes sense,
if you think about it.
None of our phones were
working... remember?
[KUROKO] That definitely doesn't
seem like a coincidence to me.
[UIHARU] Oh!
[SATEN] What's wrong?
I was just thinking...
On that same day, not too
far from where we were,
there was some trouble
with the traffic signals.
Like the kind Konori asked us
to help out with that time?
Oh, yeah! Do you think
the two could be connected?
Not necessarily,
but it's possible.
This seems like a lot of
trouble to go through...
Just to track down
a little girl...?
Maybe there's more to their
agenda than we realize.
[phone "ribbit" rings]
[KONGO] We attempted to trace
the path of that creepy man
from the other day,
but I'm afraid we have
not made any progress.
[MIKOTO] I see.
Right... It was a
long shot. Thank you.
[KONGO] We will continue to
expand our search radius.
[MIKOTO] Be careful,
though, okay?
[KONGO] Oh... what about
the powered suit...?
Have you found anything
interesting there?
Well, Antiskill started
looking into it...
but they didn't learn anything.
[KONGO] I'll see if I can
find out something on my end.
Oh, yeah, didn't
you know...?
My father's company has
some research divisions
within Academy City that
deal in powered suits.
Great...
That helps...
Okay, talk
to you later.
Was that Kongo
on the phone?
Yeah...
It sounds like they've still
got some looking to do.
You know,
I wonder...
What was this strange man doing
at the Reach Assembly location?
[SATEN] Well, he was looking
for Febri, wasn't he?
[UIHARU] Hmm...
We cannot allow
Mitsuko Kongo to outdo us
in our search for the truth!
We must keep working!
Follow all avenues!
Consider every possibility!
We'll keep at it!
I'll look into any blackouts
that have occurred
anywhere in the city in
the past couple of days.
I've got an idea...!
I'll go back to where
we first found Feb--
[FEBRI] Mikoto Misaka.
[MIKOTO] We never did figure
out how Febri knew my name...
Somebody must have told her.
Somebody...
[MIKOTO] Was it her...?
But... if it was... Why?
[ARITOMI] We have taken
the necessary measures
with Antiskill.
I doubt they'll be able
to uncover anything,
the bumbling fools...
still... we can't
be too careful.
We don't want them snooping
right before the Reach Assembly.
It's too important to our plans.
We're sure about allowing Febri
to remain out of our control?
We took a vote yesterday.
I thought we had
settled the matter.
Just confirming...
We can all agree that we don't
want anything interfering
with our big moment.
No need to worry.
Febri will die before
the assembly...
She's a back up, after all,
and imminently expendable.
The Reach Assembly
is almost at hand...
We need to be sure that
everything is ready.
So, is it?
Well, people, have we
overlooked anything?
Oh, no...
Not a chance.
Right, Nunotaba?
All of the pieces
are in place.
I will do everything I can.
[MIKOTO] Looks like Little Miss
Condescension got herself
expelled from
Nagatenjoki Academy.
I can't find any trail
on her since then.
And that means...
I've got just one avenue left.
[FROG DOCTOR] Hmm...
I've performed an
analysis on the fiber
from the capsule
you brought me...
And, interestingly enough,
it seems to be made of
the exact same
components as those
that comprise the
girl Febri's body.
To put it more simply...
This is a hair.
[MIKOTO] Hair...?
One of Febri's, then?
[FROG DOCTOR] No, it isn't.
This belongs to a
different individual.
[MIKOTO] Somebody else?
Maybe... her sister?
Actually, I'm glad
you came by.
There's something I wanted
to discuss with you.
I took a closer
look at the candy
young Febri's been carrying.
Considering the number of
lollipops she has remaining,
I believe her situation
is more urgent
than I had originally
estimated it to be.
Urgent how?
Roughly seventy-two hours.
That is how long I believe
her current store will last.
When they're gone, she'll die.
[MIKOTO] Oh, no...
Isn't there something
you can do?!
It's like I told
you before,
if there is anyone
who can save the girl,
it's the one who created her.
That's your only
real hope, I'm afraid.
Where are you
planning to go?
[MIKOTO] Everywhere...!
Anywhere I have to...!
One way or another we're
going to find the monsters
who did this!
You don't even
know where to start.
I... have no choice.
I will ask you
once again...
Are you ready to
face the darkness
at the heart
of Academy City?
It will be
dangerous...
You could very easily end up
getting hurt, yourself.
If it'll save her...
I'll do whatever it takes.
[FROG DOCTOR sighs]
[FROG DOCTOR] The quickest way
to find out about the underworld
is to ask someone who has
connections within it.
If that is what you want...
I will arrange a meeting.
[door opens]
[FROG DOCTOR] There is something
you should be aware of
before you go.
[FROG DOCTOR] The person
you are meeting...
...is someone with whom you
are already well acquainted.
[THERESTINA] Hmm...
Long time no see, huh?
How I've missed you,
my little lab rat.
[THERESTINA] My favorite little
lab rat has come back to play.
[MIKOTO] Hey, aren't you--
[THERESTINA] Yes...?
[MIKOTO] That one lady...
[THERESTINA] Yes, that's me.
[MIKOTO] What's your name?
[THERESTINA] Therestina!