[HEAD RESIDENT] An after-hours
pass request? Really?
Um. Yes!
[HEAD RESIDENT] After making
such a pathetic excuse
for being out all those
nights without permission,
you ask for this?
You've got some
nerve, don't you?
All of the necessary paperwork
does seem to be accounted for.
[MIKOTO laughs]
[HEAD RESIDENT] As it happens,
I received a virtually
identical request from Shirai.
It was dated tomorrow, and had
the same reason for absence
"a study group with friends."
Oh, yes.
Kuroko and I are both--
What are you
two scheming?
Nothing, I swear!
We're just studying
with some friends.
[HEAD RESIDENT] Hm.
Can't you study in the dorm?
Why do you need to
leave the premises?
I guess you could say,
for a change of pace?
These friends are
from another school,
and we're all really loaded up
with summer vacation homework.
You know?
[HEAD RESIDENT]
Very well. You may go.
[MIKOTO] Huh?
I hope your study
group is productive.
However, if you are even one
minute past your return time,
you know what is
going to happen.
Don't you?
[MIKOTO] Uh... yeah!
[SATEN hums]
[phone rings]
A good day to
you Uiharu!
What's happening?
[UIHARU] I've got good news!
Misaka and Shirai both got
their after-hours passes!
[SATEN] Oh, really?
That's fantastic!
They said getting approved
might be kind of tricky.
But, I'm glad it worked out.
[UIHARU] So that means
we can proceed
with today's study
group as scheduled!
It's been so long since
we've all been together!
[SATEN] Mm-Hm. Heh!
And Misaka will be there, so
it's the perfect opportunity
to find out who she
made those cookies for!
Behave yourself, Saten.
We aren't entirely sure
she gave them to a boy.
Oh, I'm completely sure!
There was a look on Miska's face
that I've never seen before.
There we have it.
All ready!
And now we put
them in the oven.
And then we just have to wait
a little while for them to bake.
I hope I'm not
putting you out.
It's really great of you to
let me use your kitchen today.
No, it's not a
problem at all!
Though for something
like baking cookies.
I would think your dorm
would be better equipped
than my lame kitchen.
Oh, um, not really.
When it comes to prying eyes, my
dorm has more than its share.
You know?
[MIKOTO] Mainly Kuroko,
Kuroko, and Kuroko.
Ho-ho.
So this present you're
preparing is for someone
you don't want other people
asking you about, huh?
No, that's not it!
I'm in this person's debt,
and I don't like being
indebted to anybody.
I would have
thought store-bought
would be good enough,
personally, but the idiot said
something about how cookies
are best if homemade.
I'm not doing this
'cause I feel obligated.
I'm just tired of listening
to all the whining,
and I thought this
way it would stop.
Well, then. Good for you.
Uiharu and I have been concerned
about you for a while, Misaka.
And you know poor
Shirai's been distraught.
[MIKOTO] Ehh...
I understand if I'm not the
person you want to confide in,
but I hope you know I'm
always here if you need me.
[MIKOTO] I'm sorry. It's just...
I'm the one who caused the
problem in the first place.
I didn't want to drag
anybody else into it.
Looking back on it now.
It was almost more
than I could handle.
I'll try to be more careful.
I'm really sorry.
Great.
Anyway, you seem to be
feeling a lot better now.
Having a new boyfriend
can do that, huh?
Boy? Uh n-no.
I don't have a boyf--
Ah! Oh, no, the flour!
Whoa, and the eggs, too!
[SATEN] How adorable.
She sure made a mess,
though. Heh, heh.
[UIHARU] It wouldn't be
very nice to try to force
the information
out of her, Saten.
Yeah, yeah. I know that.
[UIHARU] Once we're finished up
with our Judgment work,
Shirai and I will do our
shopping and head over.
As for Haru'ue, she says
she has something to do,
so she'll be a little late.
All right. I'll get
things ready here.
That sounds good.
I'll see you later.
[UIHARU gasps]
[UIHARU] Hey Shirai!
How has your morning been?
[KUROKO] Good so far.
[MAIKA] Lots of free time on
your hands again, huh, Misaka?
[MIKOTO] Just a minute,
when you say it like that,
you make it sound
like I'm a loser.
I'm just taking it easy now
because I have plans
later in the day.
[MAIKA] You've been skipping
meals in the dorm a lot lately.
What have you been up to?
You know, a little of
this, a little of that.
[MAIKA] A lot of the time,
Shirai came here and
just ate by herself.
[MIKOTO] I know.
[crashing sound]
[ALLEY CATS growl and hiss]
[KUROKO] Hm.
It sure is peaceful now.
That whole Money Card situation
seems to have settled down
and the back streets and
alleys of Academy City
have finally returned
to their usual calm.
[GIRL 17-A] Cute!
Where did you buy that?
[GIRL 17-B] I can show
you the store now.
[GIRL 17-A] Really?
That would be great!
[SAILOR SHIRT GIRL 7-A]
I found one!
[GREEN SHIRT GIRL 7-A]
Whoa! Another?
[MINORI] See? Isn't
this place amazing?
Not for me.
I've only found
three-leaf ones.
[MINORI] Judgment lady!
How are you doing?
Long time no see.
Here, take a look!
When I told my friends
about the clovers,
they all wanted one,
so I brought them here.
That was nice of you.
I don't want you guys staying
out here too late, though.
[MINORI] Mm.
[SAILOR SHIRT GIRL 7-A]
Found another one!
I finally found one!
It's got five leaves!
[MINORI] Let me see! Let me see!
[SAILOR SHIRT GIRL 7-A] Look!
[MINORI] Oh!
Yep. Things are
nice and peaceful.
[UIHARU sighs]
[UIHARU groans]
Tough homework?
[UIHARU] Yeah.
There was this book
report I was assigned,
but I'm not sure what
I want to write it on.
There's not much time
until the vacation's over.
I know, don't remind me.
There are still so many
loose ends to wrap up, too.
[alarm sounds]
Ah, not again.
[KONORI] What's up?
[UIHARU] Someone is trying to
crack into the newspaper club's
server at Sakugawa
Middle School.
I was asked to look out for it.
We have a hacker.
This seems to be
happening a lot lately.
Why would they even
want to go after
a middle school
newspaper, anyway?
You know how
hackers are.
They're always
after a challenge,
and you are one of the best
goalies in the whole city.
[UIHARU] Huh? Did
you say something?
[KONORI chuckles]
[UIHARU] Ah, they broke
through the firewall again.
That's pretty impressive.
You're almost in now.
Keep trying!
Uh, "keep trying"?
You're rooting for them?
No, it's okay.
The server itself
is actually a trap.
I just have to log
the hacker's IP address
and send it on to Antiskill.
[UIHARU] Ugh.
Maybe I should try to find
a different book to read.
But I'll probably just have a
hard time with that one, too.
The legendary digital
goalie of Academy City.
Brought low by a book report.
What was that?
You say something
about a goalie?
[KONORI] Never mind. There
anything I can do to help?
It's so sweet of you to ask!
Oh, well, this isn't
about the book report.
But maybe you could help me out.
Do you happen to know of
a supermarket around here
with a good selection?
Supermarket?
What for?
[UIHARU] I'm going to
a study group after this.
We're each supposed to pick up
an ingredient at the store,
then we're meeting
at Saten's place.
[SATEN] There we go.
[KUROKO] Hm...
[KONGO] Oh, would
you look at that!
[KUROKO] Uhh...
[KONGO] Hello, Shirai.
Such a small world, isn't it?
Lovely. It's Kongo.
Doing some shopping?
Yes, I am.
So, what are you
in the market for?
Just getting some
food, that's all.
What a coincidence!
That's what
I'm doing, too.
I could accompany you.
I don't mind. It isn't
too much out of my way.
Oh, but I would hate
to inconvenience you
in the slightest.
I'm sure you have a
very busy day of snobbery
and condescension planned.
I felt it was my civic
duty to approach you.
You just looked so
lonely out here,
shopping without a single
friend by your side.
Interesting you
should say that,
considering that you
appear to be shopping
all by yourself,
as well.
[KONGO gasps]
I am doing no such
thing, thank you.
In fact, I'm going to meet up
with Wannai and Awatsuki
in a little while.
I mean, we don't
have plans, exactly.
But they'll be done with
swim practice shortly.
Until then, I'm just
passing the time
with some personal shopping.
Would it help if I clarified the
definition of "alone" for you?
Now, just come with me.
There is a fantastic
shop over here
that is one of my favorites.
[KUROKO] Huh? Hey!
[dog barks]
Why are we in
a pet store?
[KONGO] Yes!
The selection here is every bit
as good as I've come to expect!
Hey, um, Kongo.
Oh these are
nice and plump.
They should be
the perfect size.
I'm confused, here.
Would you mind holding
these for a sec?
[KUROKO] Uh-- Ahhh!
I thought you said you were
out shopping for food today!
Ecaterina will be happy.
She has a very sophisticated
palate, you know.
And this "Ecaterina,"
would be...
...that giant python?
[KUROKO screams]
Turtle?
[KITTY meows]
[MIKOTO] Heh.
[FROG DOCTOR] Ah.
I'm guessing you're
here about the girls?
[MIKOTO] Yes.
[FROG DOCTOR] I'm sure
you'll be happy to hear
that they're all
doing very well.
That also includes
the one who was injured.
She seems to be
making good progress.
On the surface, anyhow.
[MIKOTO] What does that mean?
Following my
initial examination,
I have learned a few things.
As we suspected,
they are clones,
created from the somatic
cells of the Original.
Which is you, of course.
During the creation process,
various drugs were administered
to the culture fluid.
These drugs promoted the
rapid growth of their bodies.
They developed incredibly
quickly from fertilized eggs
to their current form
in a mere fourteen days.
The girls already have shorter
lifespans than ordinary people,
but the accelerated
growth process
has shortened them even further.
[MIKOTO] Ah!
Shortened? How much?
Hm. I can't really give
you an exact timeline,
but I would guess that, at most,
they have another year or two.
Oh, no.
[FROG DOCTOR] Which is why
they need to be adjusted.
Adjusted?
[FROG DOCTOR] Here,
take a look at this.
What we'll do is balance
the hormones that promote
rapid growth and regulate
the rate of division
of the cell nuclei.
By doing so, we should
be able to recover
a certain degree of
their lifespans.
We can't cut so many
young lives short, can we?
We're currently in the process
of dividing this research
among organizations
outside of the city.
There will be
constant communication
between these facilities,
ensuring that everything that
can be done for them is.
Outside facilities?
That sounds perfect.
[FROG DOCTOR] The fight for
those girls will continue.
And it may be a long road yet.
Although, at least this time
it won't be a fight to die,
but rather a fight to live.
Hmm. I just don't know.
I wonder what everybody
else is going to bring.
[KUROKO hums]
I'm so excited!
I've found the ultimate
ingredient for tonight.
Sparkling clean.
[MIKOTO] Oh, man.
I'm running late!
Kuroko's probably
there by now.
[WAITRESS 17-A] Table for one?
[MIKOTO] No.
I'm meeting someone.
[FRENDA] Huh?
[MIKOTO] Uhh--
I'll be right back with
some water and a menu.
[MIKOTO] Oh, no! Please don't!
I'm not with them.
I knew there was something I
didn't like about this place.
Apparently they
cater to spoiled,
sheltered
little princesses.
[thud]
You know, that fight was far
from a clear victory for you.
Huh?
[FRENDA] To be fair, it's an
issue of prior information.
If I had known you
were the Railgun,
I would have taken more care
setting up my stuffed doll-
Frenda!
[FRENDA] Huh?
You haven't forgotten that
it was because you neglected
to clean up those
very same dolls
that she was able to
get away, have you?
Ah! Oh yeah, I guess
that's right, huh?
[FRENDA] Owwww!
Clean up your
messes, bimbo!
[FRENDA sobs]
[KUROKO] What's going on here?
If you are going to fight,
take it outside the restaurant.
As a Judgment officer,
I cannot allow you to
disturb the other cus--
Sissy! I'm disappointed in you!
You know better than
to start a dispute
in a public place like this!
Hey, hold on!
I didn't start this.
I was just waiting for--
We've discussed this sort of
thing so many times before!
You can't
get into fights
with members of the weaker
general population.
Excuse me, who are
you calling weak?!
What are you, a fourth-grader?
[KUROKO] Heh.
I'm certain you
aren't talking to me,
as I am quite clearly a
full-fledged middle schooler
who was only speaking
out of a serious concern
for your welfare.
Angering Sissy here
is very dangerous.
It could cost you
your life, in fact.
[FRENDA] Like I said.
You should really keep your
nose out of this, little girl.
Your friend would be
the one shredded to bits
if we got into it.
Just like I thought.
You don't know anything.
I'm sure you'll
revise your opinion
knowing she's the
Railgun of Tokiwadai.
Well, Mugino has more
combat experience than her.
She would blow your
friend to pieces.
[KUROKO] Sissy will
rip her apart.
Mugino will win!
The victory will go to Sissy!
[FRENDA] Mugino!
[KUROKO] Sissy!
[MIKOTO] Hold on, Kuroko.
Take is easy, Frenda.
Okay, fine.
Sissy may have cartoon
characters on her underwear,
and her taste in general does
tend to be more childish
than one might want.
However, as Tokiwadai's Ace,
she is still quite
a formidable opponent!
Yeah, well, Mugino may have her
flaws, like a shrewish temper
and a tendency to flaunt
her underwear to passersby,
but in a fight she's
completely unstoppable!
Honestly!
You think your flat-chested
friend can win against
this kind of power?
How ignorant to think
that size matters!
When it comes to
future potential,
Sissy is the clear winner here!
[MIKOTO and MUGINO]
Get your hands off of me!
Man. I'll never be able to
go to that restaurant again!
Wait for me, Mugino!
[MIKOTO] Hey, we're here!
[SATEN] Ah. Come in!
Shirai, you look
a little disheveled.
[KUROKO] Heh. Oh,
it's nothing, really.
[SATEN] Ta-da!
[MIKOTO] Ooh. Nice stewpot!
Yep, I borrowed it
from a friend of mine.
And I've got the stock
all ready to go.
Wow, that's exciting.
I bet we're the only ones
in town having a stew party
in the middle
of summer.
Now let's be clear.
This isn't a party.
It's a study group, as is
written on our permission slips.
Oh yeah, right.
Well, whether it's an
official party or not,
eating hot food when it's hot
outside is good for the body.
Okay, so what ingredients
did everybody else bring?
Well, actually I had a hard
time deciding what to get.
But the man at the meat
counter suggested these.
So I went ahead and got them.
Boxes?
[UIHARU] Hmm...
[gasps]
[SATEN] Wow!
They're full of
great-looking beef!
[UIHARU] The marbling
is incredible!
Um, is that good?
Not good, Misaka. Wonderful!
What about you?
Oh! Here,
take a look.
I decided to go
with vegetables.
I focused on summer veggies.
Stuff that's in season,
like okra and corn.
And also some
mushrooms and tofu.
Great idea!
Sounds delicious
and full of vitamins!
[KUROKO] I'm up next.
I've brought something
that can enhance
a young lady's
natural beauty!
You should prepare yourselves,
because I think you're going
to be very impressed with
my contribution to the pot.
Sounds interesting,
Shirai.
What did you bring?
I admit I was unsure at first.
There I was, standing in the pet
shop with plump mice in my hand,
not certain what to do.
Plump mice?
You went shopping
at a pet store?
[KUROKO] However!
It wasn't long before
I had an epiphany!
And I knew I'd found an
ingredient fit for Sissy.
Are you going to
tell us what you got?
[UIHARU] Yeah, Shirai we're on
the edge of our seats, here.
The ingredient that
I chose is turtle!
[MIKOTO, SATEN, and UIHARU]
Turtle?
[KUROKO] The soft collagen
will enhance Sissy's fresh,
youthful skin, making it even
more beautiful than before!
And that's not all!
That looks like...
[KUROKO] Fresh soft-shell
turtle blood!
Mixed with apple juice,
to make it easier to drink.
Go ahead, gulp it right down!
One glass and you'll
be full of energy.
No, you'll be positively
bursting with vitality!
It's possible
you'll be so fired up
that you won't be able
to get to sleep tonight.
When that happens, I'll come
and lie down beside you.
Yes!
Okay. let's eat,
shall we?
Mmm. Oh my gosh!
It's amazing!
[UIHARU] This is the first time
I've ever eaten turtle,
but it's delicious.
[SATEN] The turtle is good, but
I think the beef is my favorite.
[KUROKO] The fresh veggies
are pretty tasty, too.
[MIKOTO] So, basically,
everything turned out great!
[UIHARU] Yes it did.
I hope Haru'ue gets
here before much longer.
Oh, I think she should be
arriving any minute now.
I wasn't thinking.
Should we be waiting?
We'll still have plenty
of ingredients left
when she gets here.
[SATEN] Oh, yeah.
I say we keep eating!
You know, it's
a real mystery.
What's a mystery?
[UIHARU] Why is it that food
always seems to taste better
when it's eaten as a group?
[KUROKO chuckles]
Mm-Hmm. I think
cooking it while we eat
like this makes
a difference, too.
I guess there's nothing
that can beat homemade
when it comes to
cookies or stew.
Right, Misaka?
[MIKOTO coughs]
[KUROKO] Hey, Sissy,
what's the matter?
Are you okay?
[MIKOTO] Oh. Yeah,
I'm fine, really.
[KUROKO] Are you sure?
You're panting and sweating,
and your face is all red.
Yeah! I said I'm okay!
Oh! These mushrooms
look delicious.
That's just adorable.
Oh, you're pure
evil, Saten.
[doorbell rings]
Hi, you guys. I'm
sorry I'm so late.
[SATEN] Nah, don't worry!
Come in, come in!
Oh. Hey, Haru'ue.
Oh, wow! Everything
looks delicious!
So, you were able to get
your errand taken care of?
Mm-Hmm. I needed to have a
talk to my teacher, that's all.
This stew we put
together is really good.
Let me get a bowl
ready for you, okay?
What's in the bag?
Did you bring
something to add, too?
Yeah, I just picked
up some noodles.
Ooh! Exactly
what we needed.
[SATEN] Sounds great!
Throw 'em on in!
[laughter]
[KUROKO] Yeah, sure, Sissy,
whatever you say!
[MIKOTO] Oh, come on!
I'm telling the truth!
[MIKOTO] Ah, I am
officially full!
I think we may have
to diet after this.
That was a lot
of fun, huh?
We should really have another
study group sometime.
Yeah.
I just wish it didn't
require so much paperwork.
Ah! Paperwork?
We're not late, are we?
No, we're still okay.
I do think we might want to move
a little bit faster, though.
If we are so much as a
minute past our return time,
the punishment won't be pretty.
[MIKOTO] Ugh! Let's hurry!
Kuroko? What's wrong? Come on.
Nothing.
Let's go.
Right. I'm with you, Sissy.
[UIHARU] There.
That should do it.
That didn't take nearly as long
as we thought, huh, Haru'ue?
[HARU'UE] Yeah. Um, Uiharu?
[UIHARU] Yes?
[HARU'UE] You know.
I really am grateful.