[ARITOMI] The idealist
will say...
No man has inherent superiority.
That we are, all of us,
beings of equal worth.
While the spiritualist
will argue...
No effort goes unrewarded.
So, endeavor we must...
For, it is the process
itself that is important.
[scattered applause]
[ARITOMI] Of course...
all of that's a lie.
Every child learns one thing
quickly, living in this city...
It doesn't matter
how much you study...
or how great of a
thesis you produce...
In this city, you're either
an esper or you're neglected.
A person's ability
determines their worth...
their standing ...
It is the one and
only benchmark.
However, abilities are
such unpredictable things...
They're affected by
one's innate qualities,
and only in the rarest instance
is a high-level esper produced,
yet they are an important
part of our social structure.
So, you see...
I could not help
thinking to myself...
What if I could create
my own esper...?
I could use an approach
that differs completely
from the existing methods.
I could design an esper that was
both stable and consistent...
but because it was
artificially produced
would not be too valuable
to be quickly used up.
So I collaborated with a few
like-minded individuals,
and together we bent our minds
to developing a certain project.
One that would allow
us to create an esper
with absolute certainty.
"Project Chemicaloid" was born.
[MIKOTO] And that project...
It produced Febri
and her sister...
They exist because of
your petty ambitions.
Heh... Yes, you
would say that...
Like most people in this city,
you are entrenched
in ability Levelism.
I've dealt with your kind.
What do you mean?
You see... I have
presented this project
to people with skills
like yours before...
skills that would be
necessary for a chemicaloid.
[SAKURAI] How is it someone
from the underground
is so short-sighted...?
You would think they would see
the potential in our proposal.
[MALE RESEARCHER 23-A] I'm glad
you made it here safely.
Now we can finally implement
Project Level 6 Shift
on the scale that we had
originally planned for it.
[ARITOMI] Ah! Is that...
Dr. Gensei Kihara?
[MALE RESEARCHER 23-A] I have
to admit I began to sweat
when I heard there
was some competition.
Oh, was there...?
Ah...! You mean the one
where they wanted to
grow espers like sea-monkeys?
From that I learned
a valuable lesson...
Even famous intellectual minds
can be clouded by an outdated
obsession with esper Levelism.
Revolutionary ideas are always
initially suspect, after all.
To be recognized we would
have to prove ourselves
on intellect alone...
and so we produced what
we said we would all along.
Chemicaloids.
Products that would
prove our worth...
our true superiority...
to this city...
indeed, to the whole world!
So... what is it about
these chemicaloids
that proves how
superior you are...?
What ability do your
"products" have?
[ARITOMI] Trying to draw
information out of me...?
Now, now, I've already given
you a good number of clues.
[MIKOTO] Remote operation...
With a strand of hair
acting as a medium.
Well... that's part of it,
but certainly not all...
Nice effort, though, Railgun.
Want to know more...?
Well... You will...
After much waiting,
at day break tomorrow,
we will begin our large-scale
chemicaloid experiment.
Experiment?
[ARITOMI] No...
that word really isn't
big enough anymore...
Allow me to revise.
Revolution...!
STUDY Corporation will turn
Academy City on it's head!
We will teach this
wretched city...
No...! We will teach
the whole world a lesson!
Ultimately, progress is not
brought about by abilities...
but by intelligence!
[MIKOTO] I...
feel...
[MIKOTO] Is that the time...
really?
[NUNOTABA] Don't bother
trying to move.
Only your eyes and
your mouth will respond.
Your body is paralyzed.
It's because
of the drug...
the one I injected you with...
It blocks the transmission of
commands to your nervous system.
You won't be able to move
a finger for two more hours yet.
So... I'm curious...
How did you... get involved
with these people?
I remember what you said.
You talked to me before
about my sisters...
about how you stopped
seeing them as things
and were trying to shut down
the experiments...
After all that...
why get mixed up in
something like this?
During the Sisters case,
I made a mistake.
I was caught by an
underground organization.
And then... I was sold.
To STUDY.
That's when I was introduced to
the artificially created twins.
Their names were
Janie and Febri.
The involuntary neural activity
essential to keeping
them alive...
what you might call
their core programming...
was based on a thesis that
I had written a long time ago.
[NUNOTABA] That particular sin
is one for which I will
never be forgiven...
It will follow me
my entire life.
Even so...
I must keep trying...
I must atone by helping in
whatever way is possible...
That was all I could think...
when I saw those girls.
Janie...
That's Febri's sister...
She only has enough programming
language installed
to allow her Diffusion Ghost
core to function properly.
[MIKOTO] Diffusion Ghost?
[NUNOTABA] That is
Janie's ability...
I'd planned to give
her consciousness
comparable to that
of a normal girl...
I'd get my hands on
the neutralizing agent...
and then I would
run away with her.
But now...
Things have gone too far...
and that isn't possible.
I have to get the
formula from Aritomi.
That's the only choice,
since he's the one
who came up with it...
I'll do whatever I have
to go get it from him.
[MIKOTO] Yes. I see.
[NUNOTABA] I don't care
what happens to me...
I will save those girls...
no matter the cost.
[MIKOTO] I get it...
I understand her guilt.
Hey...
[NUNOTABA] I know what
I've done is unforgivable--
[MIKOTO] My sister never
got the chance, but...
she wanted to tell you thanks.
You think you have to
do this by yourself...
but if you take a look around,
I think you'll realize
you're wrong...
You're not alone...
There are people out
there who want to help you
if you'll let them.
[NUNOTABA] And you're one of
those people I suppose...?
But how do you think you
can help me right now...?
You're effectively paralyzed...
Thanks to me, the only thing
you can move is your mouth!
[MIKOTO] Oh, really?
Just my mouth... huh?
How can you...?
[NUNOTABA] Incredible!
She's using her ability
to directly control
the electrical signals
that run to her nerves!
[MIKOTO groans]
[MIKOTO] I've never
tried this before.
But, hey... it seems to
work pretty well, huh?
[NUNOTABA] Doing something
like that should be causing
intense pain throughout
her entire body.
[MIKOTO] Let me tell you what
I've come to realize recently...
Other people count on you...
but you can count
on them, too...
If you work with someone
instead of on your own,
your combined strength can
make all the difference.
You know...
when I first found out
about my sisters...
I reacted the
same way you are...
I just kept thinking...
"This is my fault.
I have to do something."
However...
It took a while, but
I've finally stopped
thinking like that...
Which is why--
[explosion]
[MIKOTO] Here they come.
[NUNOTABA] Huh?
[alarm sounds]
[ARITOMI] Hey!
What's going on?
More intruders...
The guard robots
are down.
[KUROKO] Uiharu...
I've got the entrance
under my control.
You're certain there are
no civilians in the area?
Yes, the coast is clear...
You can do whatever
you need to...
Come in, Saten.
What's the status outside?
[SATEN] It's all good...
No suspicious activity so far.
[NUNOTABA] How did they
know where to find you?
[MIKOTO] I borrowed one of those
implantable tracking devices
they use when you go
outside of Academy City.
And then...
I talked it over
with my friends.
I told them if I
was gone too long,
they should come and get me.
You actually dragged your
friends into this mess--
[MIKOTO] No.
I explained the
situation to them...
and then I asked.
I asked for help.
And without hesitation,
they agreed...
They care about Febri, too.
Although... it looks like
Febri may need more help
than my friends
and I can give.
So now I'm
asking you...
Do you think you can
help us save her?
But this is all my fault.
You can't trust me.
[MIKOTO] Yes I can.
I trust you completely.
Look--
[NUNOTABA]
No, this is all wrong...
you shouldn't be saying that.
I'm the one who should
be asking you...
So, now I am...
I'm asking...
Please help us!
[MIKOTO] Kuroko!
[KUROKO] Hi, Sissy!
[MIKOTO] Ah--Hold on.
You don't want to--
Ahh!
How cruel...!
I came to help and you
repay me like this?!
I'm... sorry...
It's kind of a long story,
but basically I'm going
to be a human stun gun
for a little while.
Huh?
[MIKOTO] Anyway... I think
we've worn out our welcome.
[KUROKO] What's going on?
I'll explain soon enough.
Let's get out of here.
[ARITOMI] She regained
all motor function
after a full dose of the drug...
Incredible.
It seems she's every bit
as strong as we'd heard.
So... what are you
still doing here...?
Why didn't you run away?
What choice did I have...?
Everybody knows my history--
that I was sold to
your corporation.
If I ran, then the entire
underworld would be after me.
In this town, that's as
good as a death sentence.
So, you stayed out of
fear rather than loyalty...
That's not surprising...
It's just as well, however.
If you weren't here to assist,
we'd have to resort to
the whip when using Janie.
The only place you have left is
here in the darkness with STUDY.
For your own good, I do hope
you'll keep that in mind.
[MIKOTO] Are you sure
you want to stay?
[NUNOTABA]
Aritomi is cautious...
He doesn't want
to be discovered...
He's relocated
Janie someplace else.
If I leave, we won't be able
to find out where she is now.
But you...
Don't worry about me.
I still have at least
a little value to them...
They won't dispose
of me right away...
I just have to bide my time...
I'll find out where
their base is
and I'll get the
formula we need.
Just be careful.
Anyway... about
what Aritomi said...
He mentioned something was
going to happen tomorrow.
What's that all about,
do you know?
They haven't given me
any of the details...
But like he said, they do
have something planned.
Tomorrow.
[KONORI] A terrorist attack
at the Reach Assembly sites?
Yes...
Actually, the word he used to
describe it was "revolution."
That sounds crazy!
These guys
mean business...
They have Febri's sister, Janie,
and they plan on using her.
Or, at any rate...
they'll use Janie's ability.
[UIHARU] Huh?!
No way!
Sorry, but did you
say "Diffusion Ghost"
was the name
of her ability?
[NUNOTABA] Her ability is
called "Diffusion Ghost,"
and it requires
hair for a medium...
With it, she is able to convert
the AIM diffusion fields
in an enclosed space
into virtual matter
and achieve control.
[MIKOTO] In other words,
those empty powered suits
and the berserk security
robots were controlled
in the same way... With Janie...
And her strange ability.
This use of AIM fields
sounds familiar to me.
Like what Dr. Kiyama
did that one time.
[SATEN] You understand this?
[UIHARU] Kind of...
I do think I've seen it--
[KUROKO] Let's think...
With operating
system abilities,
there is a limit
to how many things
can be controlled at once...
This isn't really suited
for a large-scale attack.
[MIKOTO] Okay, but...
they did say that a number
of simple commands
are placed ahead
of time into the fields
that Janie
virtually materializes...
For example...
"Eliminate any opponent
who attacks."
Something like that.
So, basically...
it's like having a bunch
of autonomous robots
on hand, right?
If all this is true...
a large-scale attack
wouldn't be impossible.
Febri's sister.
Do you know where STUDY
has been keeping Janie...?
If we stop her, they
can't launch an attack!
Well, yeah,
that's true...
but this Nunotaba woman I
mentioned to you before...
she wasn't told what the base
for the attack was going to be.
Oh, no...
[MIKOTO] Once Janie
uses her ability,
Nunotaba thinks Febri
will be able to give us
an idea of her
sister's location,
or at least the direction
of where to start looking.
That's all well
and good, but...
If she's used
her ability,
doesn't that mean that
we are already too late?
If we're going
to forestall this,
the best thing to do would be to
pursue the powered suit angle.
There must be quite a number
of them currently deployed
in the area around the
Reach Assembly site...
Uiharu... look that up?
I have more parameters to
apply to the search now...
I think I can do it!
Hey, you know...
with all this new information,
Antiskill might be able to act.
You're right!
[YOMIKAWA] I'm sorry,
I really am.
But I don't think Antiskill can
get involved in this case.
[KUROKO] But why not?
[YOMIKAWA] The STUDY
Corporation, huh?
Now that I hear that name,
things are starting
to make sense.
They're fairly new...
but they've quickly
risen to prominence,
forcing out the competition
to become our
equipment suppliers...
Their swift ascent has
been bothering me...
but, I guess this explains it.
Mm. Ya' know, for that matter,
it explains why I was
suddenly suspended, too.
[KUROKO] Suspended?!
[SATEN] Are you all right?
[YOMIKAWA] Yeah.
I'm weathering the storm
at a friend's place...
Don't worry about me. I'm fine.
I'm a lot more worried
about you guys.
Don't do anything crazy.
[KONORI] The situation is even
more dire than we first thought.
[UIHARU] I've got it!
The record of STUDY
Corporation's bulk containers
and the sites they have
been delivered to.
They made it into the
sites...? How could they--
[UIHARU] Well, look.
It says here that
there was a blackout
at each site during delivery,
and all of their records
appear to be incomplete.
Blackouts! Of course!
And now we know the
reason behind them.
How many are we
talking about?
Give me a second.
I'm tallying them now.
[KONGO] Bad news, ladies!
I finally got a hold of
some relevant information
using my father's channels...
When you add up...
Approximating by container
capacity and contents...
...you've got enough to
build a truly incredible
number of powered suits!
No way!
That's so many!
The number has to be--
[UIHARU] Over 20,000!
[KONGO] I beg your pardon?
Impossible...
[UIHARU] The thing is...
Since they went through official
channels to deliver the suits
to all of the various sites...
we can't take any action
without Antiskill's cooperation.
If we do, there's a good
chance we'd be arrested.
Essentially... it doesn't
sound like there's a whole lot
we can do until they
make their move.
Then we have to find this Janie
girl and stop her somehow.
Yes, except... we have
no way of knowing
where she is until she
activates her ability.
Which means we'll have to
allow the attack to begin.
[SATEN] That's crazy!
[MIKOTO]
We're totally unprepared...
These guys are light
years ahead of us.
All this time...
they've been getting
ready for a coup.
[UIHARU] If they get
out into the city,
who knows how much
damage they'll do?
What's on your mind?
Please tell us.
[MIKOTO] I just want
to save Febri...
and her sister, Janie as well...
I want to save Nunotaba,
who, right now, is still
embedded with the enemy ...
And, of course, I want to
protect Academy City.
I also...
I want to keep every single
one of you out of danger...
So, I wonder...
am I just being selfish?
[KONGO] Well, if you are--
If that's the case, then I have
to admit I'm selfish, too.
Mm-Hm. And actually...
I may be worse...
because I want all of that,
and on top of it,
I want you to stop
looking so miserable.
[KUROKO] Saten is right.
Even when things are going
as well as they can...
you still seem to find something
to worry about, Sissy...
It makes it hard for the rest
of us to really relax, you know?
That's true...
Cheer up. We can do this
if we all work together.
Exactly...!
Together, there's
nothing we can't do!
I-I believe so, as well...
We are unstoppable.
It won't be easy...
but when this is
finally over...
...we'll still be standing,
shoulder to shoulder.
We'll have a happy
ending, you'll see!
[KAMIJO] I know you
have your own goals...
Mine is seeing everybody
get through this alive.
Heh. I know what you mean.
Now it's my goal too.
[GROUP] Uh?
Oh, hi...
Everybody's here.
[MIKOTO] Yes, Febri...
...we are all here...
and we're about to go and
see if we can help Janie.
Would you like to come, too?
[FEBRI] Yeah!
[MIKOTO] Heh.
[phone rings]
[KONORI] Oh, Aomi?
Sorry to be calling you so late.
[AOMI] That's okay.
If you're the one calling, well,
I know there's a good reason,
no matter how late it might be.
So, spill.
All right. Tell me...
What do you think
about this city?
[AOMI] Huh?
[KONGO] Thank you, Father,
I really appreciate this.
Okay... I'll leave
you to it, then.
Heh. Well, you heard her.
Let's indulge my daughter.
You'll see to everything...
right, Pops?
[FEBRI] Oh, hot! Hot! Hot!
All done!
[UIHARU] Wow!
That's very pretty!
I'm gonna save it so
my sister can eat it.
That's so sweet ...
And how is it going over there?
Hmm. I'm not sure
how well it's going,
but I'm not giving up anytime
soon, I promise that much!
--[FEBRI] Hang in there!
--[SATEN] You bet!
[UIHARU] Okay! We'll keep
working hard, too, right, Febri?
[door opens]
[MIKOTO]
That's refreshing! Ahh...
[KUROKO] I've got everything all
ready to go over here, too.
This should make a good decoy
in case the head resident
comes barging in here.
[MIKOTO] Wait.
This only makes it look like one
of us is sleeping, doesn't it?
And this side is too big...
See... they are sleeping...
in each other's arms!
[thud] Oww!
Aww. But I had them
positioned just right.
[MIKOTO] Good grief.
We can at least try to
make it look realistic.
If we get found out,
we're both in for it.
Let's see...
[KUROKO] Hey, Sissy...
What's this?
It's a four-leaf clover.
Huh?
It's a good-luck charm that
I picked especially for you.
Thanks a lot.
[KUROKO] By the way...
Who was that you called earlier?
[MIKOTO] Oh... Just someone.
[MADARAME] Ten minutes
remaining to sunrise.
It has been a long
night, indeed.
But, at last...
we are about to see the
dawning of a new day.
All systems are prepped
and ready to go.
All that remains is
to activate them.
Janie has reached
critical phase, as well...
It's almost as if she's aware of
her own role in what's to come.
[NUNOTABA] Almost time...
What I have planned may
work, and it may not...
Either way, it won't
absolve my sin.
But... even so...
I resolve to do whatever I can.
[ARITOMI] Now then.
Time for final confirmation...
Those in favor or proceeding
as we have planned?
Okay, we're ready...
Let us begin our Silent Party.
[MIKOTO] You know, you look
very nice in that outfit.
Is that the present
Kongo bought for you?
[FEBRI] Mm-Hmm. It's pretty,
and it reminds me of
the one from before.
One from before?
From Shinobu...
She picked it out for me.
Oh?
Well...
It's time now.
All right!
You will not be taking...
[KONGO]
...one tiny little step...
[AWATSUKI and WANNAI]
...beyond this point.
You... you go right ahead...
... and give us the
best you've got to give!
[FEBRI gasps]
That way...!
My sister--
[MIKOTO] Here.
Don't forget this.
[MIKOTO] This is our last shot.
[MIKOTO] Up you go...
I need you to trust me, okay?
[FEBRI] Aaaahhhhh!
[MIKOTO] Right... Here we go!
[MIKOTO] To protect
Academy City...
[UIHARU] To save
Janie and Febri...
[KUROKO
...and Nunotaba, too.
[SATEN] For a happy
ending for all of us!
[MIKOTO] That's why
we're fighting...
[GROUP] To make
that dream come true!