[NUNOTABA] Excellent.
It looks adorable on you.
Very soon, you'll be
going outside on your own.
[FEBRI] Shinobu?
Remember...
every once in awhile,
suck on one of these.
And now there's...
one last thing.
Mikoto Misaka.
Don't forget that
name, all right?
Mikoto Mi...
[NUNOTABA]
That decision was it...
The beginning of everything.
What happens now?
Have I finally done
something to help...
instead of causing more harm?
[MISAKA 10032] Honestly.
She is nothing but trouble.
[ARITOMI] Hmph.
We have some uninvited
party guests, do we?
Poor things...
facing down twenty
thousand powered suits...
I think we can handle one
or two gawky teenagers.
Sorry to keep
you waiting... Hi.
Heh. You know,
you're late.
Hey, guys!
Wha--?! Who are these people?!
You've disrupted the
peace of Academy City.
You've hurt our friend.
An innocent little girl!
[BOTH] This shield is
a symbol of duty.
And that duty...
Is to stop you!
[gasp]
[AOMI] You may have Antiskill
under your control...
But they're not the
only law in this town.
I think today we'll
do this Shirai style.
Huh?
[GROUP]
Judgment is on the scene!
[KUROKO] That's right!
[MIKOTO laughs]
[FEBRI] Mikoto?
[MIKOTO]
Oh, uh... it's nothing.
Okay, guys...
I'm counting on you.
[RIOTERS yell]
[KUROKO] By all means,
come and get it...
I am Kuroko Shirai,
Sissy's right-hand gal...
And by my pledge...
None of you shall
set foot past me!
[RIOTER A] You're up!
[AOMI] Tank squads E and F,
come to the left flank...!
Squads J through M,
switch off...! Let's go!
[RIOTERS yell]
[KONORI] Careful now!
Don't forget our
main objective...!
To prevent these things
from leaving the premises!
[SATEN] We're buying time!
Misaka is sure to
come up with something!
I, for one, am glad... that
these machines are running with
simple, easily-controlled
programming.
First, you have to
select a target.
[AWATSUKI] ...then it's all just
a matter of maintaining aggro!
[RIOTER B] Whoa!
[RIOTER C] Awesome!
A water current and
buoyancy control combo!
[AWATSUKI and WANNAI] Hi, Kongo!
[KONGO] Those are my friends.
Don't you even think
about harming them.
I simply won't allow it!
[SATEN] You're not
gonna get by me!
[UIHARU] Me, either!
We're doing this for Febri...
and also... Because a
good friend asked us to!
[SATEN] This is for Misaka!
[KUROKO] Take that, robot!
I'm kicking it up a notch today!
[RIOTER D] Shirai!
[KUROKO] Because today...
I don't just fight for Judgment.
I fight for Sissy!
They're better
than I had expected.
[SEKIMURA] Yeah,
well... Our attrition rate
is still running at
less than two percent.
[ARITOMI] I want to
know where Railgun is.
Once you do find her...
let Kosako and Madarame loose.
[SEKIMURA] Nunotaba...!
I'm increasing Janie's
operating ratio.
Keep everything regulated!
[NUNOTABA] Why did I do that?
Of all names, why did I give
Febri that particular one?
Is it because I believed in her?
Yes...
Maybe that's it...
I just hope... I'm right.
[explosion]
[SEKIMURA] What's that?!
We have an intruder!
Is that...
...Railgun?!
[gasps]
[SEKIMURA] But...
how did she find this place?
[ARITOMI]
Damn that girl.
[ARITOMI over TV]
Hello, Railgun.
Excuse the mess.
I didn't expect company,
but I guess you negotiated
your own invitation.
Shinobu...? Shinobu!
And now that you're here,
I'm afraid you leave us
little choice. Please
enjoy our hospitality.
[MIKOTO] Just hold on
a little longer...
We'll see her soon enough.
[ARITOMI] All you espers
have one common weakness...
You're only human, which
means you will eventually tire.
And you are no
exception to this rule.
I don't care what
level esper you are...
When you're this outnumbered...
you don't stand a chance.
Yeah, you're right.
If I was all on my own,
this would be difficult.
However...
Things are different this time.
[MIKOTO] All of us...
...are fighting
against you together!
[FEBRI screams]
Incredible...
We have planned
for this situation...
Activate scenario B-7...
Send Kosako and Madrame, now!
[AOMI] Squads A and B,
hang in a little longer...
Espers, Attack...!
Go once again from
the left flank--
[KONGO] Hah!
[KONGO] Okay. Who's next?
What do we
do, you guys?
We can't get through
to the others!
There's no signal!
I expected this.
[UIHARU] I don't
know what to do!
The commands to my
security robots aren't--
Yeah, seriously...
What now?
[KOSAKO] It's time
you learned a lesson.
Intellectual prowess
cannot be neglected...
or we will all become helpless
sheep in thrall to the espers.
[MADARAME] It would have
been a lot more satisfying
to have gone up
against Railgun...
Well...
...what are you gonna do?!
[panting]
[ARITOMI] You seem to be
getting worn out, Railgun.
Unfortunately for you, this
party is just getting started.
These models are
equipped with weapons made
after analyzing the
city's fourth-ranked esper.
I guess you could call
it our version of Meltdowner.
Enjoy your first-hand look.
[UIHARU screams]
[SATEN] Uiharu?!
No, I'll be all right...
Please, don't worry a--
[SATEN] Behind you!
[YOMIKAWA] Sorry we're late.
Your friend suggested
that I bring this along.
What is it?
[HARU'UE] Let us
take care of contacting
the other sites, okay?
[UIHARU] It's Haru'ue!
That's right...
and Banri is
helping out, too...
We're making a
network of telepaths.
I thought something
like this might happen...
[AOMI] Thank you for this.
[EDASAKI] Please,
it's no problem!
Being able to help
Judgment out is like
a dream come true for me!
[KONGO] "Always be prepared and
you will never be surprised."
Philosophy in action.
Isn't there a
manual for this?
Yeah, don't worry.
It's in my head.
Well, mostly.
Okay then, here goes.
[scared yelling]
[KONGO] Allow me to introduce
the variable-form, large-scale,
all-purpose machine built
with the latest technology
from Kongo Airlines'
Metalworks Plant Number 2.
[grunts, gasps]
What is that thing?!
What do you think of her?
Ecaterina the Second...!
New and improved!
[HARU'UE] That's
what she calls it!
[SATEN] Whoa...!
Nice choice, Uiharu.
You're fired up today, huh?
[shocked yelp]
[SATEN] Okay! Let's see
if we can do them justice!
It's so fast!
[SATEN] Ready, and...
Knockout punch!!
[UIHARU] Saten, be carefuulll!
Fire!
[MIKOTO] Oh, please!
That's nothing like
the real Meltdowner.
[MADARAME] Damn!
Damn every last esper!
This is a day of revolution!
[UIHARU] I'm taking
over control now, Saten.
[SATEN] Okay!
[SATEN] You hate espers? Well,
I'm actually a Level Zeeerooo!
Are you serious...?
That was a poor,
pathetic imitation.
Oh, quit it.
I'm damn sick of
these pieces of junk.
[FRENDA] Whoa...!
Just like our intel said...!
It really is copying Mugino...
That's just plain asking for it.
[KINUHATA] This is an ultra
huge number of powered suits...
What do you think is going on?
Who knows?
[MUGINO] So this is what's
behind all those fool's errands
we've been sent on lately.
Damn it...
You bastards were using us this
whole time to collect data...?!
Screw you!
[FRENDA] Whoo-hoo!
[KINUHATA] Ultra-pretty fire.
[TAKITSUBO] Hey, Mugino...
Over there I sensed--
[MUGINO] Hmph!
We don't have time to waste
on a spoiled little brat
who doesn't want
to learn her lesson.
[FEBRI] Hey...
Those people earlier...
[MIKOTO] Oh, those guys...
It's best to forget
about them... okay?
[MIKOTO] We need to hurry!
[ARITOMI] Madarame!
Kosako...! Do you copy?
[SAKURAI] Not getting
anything from above, either.
[ARITOMI] It's not over!
It isn't over!
We have not been defeated!
[MIKOTO] See, that's
where you're wrong.
[ARITOMI] You!
[MIKOTO] I suggest you
put an end to this...
and let Janie go this instant.
[FEBRI gasps]
[FEBRI] Shinobu!
Hi, Febri...
[MIKOTO] Well, I came.
Like I promised.
This disgusts me...
Espers reveling
in their triumph!
Aritomi!
What are you...?
[FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE]
Code input confirmed.
Initiating final phase.
[alarm sounds]
[NUNOTABA]
...Janie!
[KONGO] Huh?
[BOTH] They stopped the attack?
[KUROKO] Sissy...
[SEKIMURA] N-N-N-N-N-No!
Don't, Aritomi!
You can't be
serious about this!
[NUNOTABA] You're setting the
system to a runaway state?
[ARITOMI] If I force
the connection to break,
she will die.
[ARITOMI] This is
the final phase...
also known as the
last possible resort.
I'm going to turn
Academy City into ashes.
[MIKOTO] Oh, yeah? And what
exactly are your plans?
Seriously now...
you really think
I would tell you?
[SAKURAI] What are you doing?
There's not much time
left... I hope you're ready.
It-... it's time to die...
[SEKIMURA stammers] Oh, no!
[NUNOTABA] I can't...
It's no use...
What am I going
to do? It's over!
[gunshot]
[MIKOTO] You want to
take the easy way out?
I'm not gonna
let that happen.
You know, there was
somebody I met once...
He had all the power
he could ever need,
but still he
reached out for more.
I also know someone
who was a lot like you...
ashamed of her lack of ability.
She was willing
to do cruel things...
to make up for her
perceived inadequacies.
And then there's this
group of girls I know...
They thought of
themselves as tools.
And quietly accepted
an inhumane fate.
And let's not forget
the biggest fool...
The reckless, stubborn girl...
who thought she could
make everything better
by throwing her life away.
Now here I am... I finally
figured it out...
Life isn't about being strong
on your own all the time...
See, I made a promise
to my friends...
That no matter what,
I'd help Febri.
And protect the city.
I'll keep that promise.
Even if it means saving you.
[NUNOTABA] So that's it.
[MIKOTO] Now... what
do we do to abort...
[NUNOTABA] This is why...
[MIKOTO] Answer me!
[NUNOTABA] I knew I could...
believe in you.
[ARITOMI] I... I don't think...
[SAKURAI gasps]
It's too late now...!
The final phase
can't be stopped!
The plan involves
scattering
five thousand filaments in
the skies over Academy City
and then running the Diffusion
Ghost ability out of control,
triggering a decay chain
in the AIM diffusion fields
that fill the area!
[SAKURAI] The launch
mechanism is in some
construction equipment
in stationary orbit
thirty-five thousand
kilometers up.
The missile has
already been launched.
Every second,
it travels seven kilometers
closer to us...
So... It cannot be stopped...
Not by anyone...
Certainly not by you!
[MIKOTO] You're right...
I doubt I can stop it.
Not all by myself.
[SATEN] A missile?!
[KUROKO] How can we help...?
[UIHARU] Give me
its specifications...
[FEBRI] It's Ruiko...!
Shinobu, this is Ruiko...
[MIKOTO] Just a sec, okay?
[KONORI] Judgment has its
share of science students.
I'll ask around.
[MIKOTO] Yeah, do that!
[KONGO] I will
help out, as well.
[SATEN] Hey...
Febri is looking flushed.
[MIKOTO] Huh?
Show me your lollipop!
I guess it's all gone.
[KUROKO] Tell me
she has some left!
[MIKOTO] That was the last one!
[SATEN] Oh, no!
[NUNOTABA] Let me handle this.
[NUNOTABA] It isn't a
matter of "can" or "can't."
I will find a way.
I'll do this somehow.
Anything is possible.
Because I know
I'm not in this alone.
[UIHARU] Aghhhh! Man!
[HARU'UE] What's the matter?
[SATEN] Is something wrong?
[UIHARU] Using
Judgment's system,
not only is there no
way to intercept it,
I can't even compute its orbit!
[KONORI] Given the
machine's specs...
[phone "ribbit" rings]
[MISAKA 10032] "I have heard
about what's happening...
It looks like it's
finally my turn,"
says Misaka, announcing her
intentions with superb timing.
[UIHARU] It's an
ingenious design...
When the missile's warhead
reaches thirty thousand meters,
it's set up to then
subdivide into five thousand
micro-warheads.
Once that happens,
it'll be too late.
So it's imperative that
the missile be shot down
before the split occurs.
[UIHARU] And the only way
that can possibly be done...
[footsteps, panting]
I made it! I'm here!
[FEBRI] Lollipop?
[NUNOTABA] Thank goodness.
This'll buy us a little time.
[SATEN] They were exactly
where that Aritomi man
said they would be. What now?
First, we need to free Janie
from the runaway system,
and to do that...
We're going to
need Febri's help.
Right now, she's in a state
where she will accept
no outside input...
but if we can get a strong
emotional response from Febri,
who is basically
identical to her...
[SATEN] That makes sense...
Because when all else fails,
love can still
get through, right?
Huh...? Uh...
okay... Yeah.
[UIHARU] It took some doing,
but I had Kongo rig the airframe
so that all eight thousand
and ninety-two jet points
will activate to a precision of
one one-thousandth of a second.
Theoretically,
This should work out... but...
How did you get such
a complex calculation
done in so short a time?
Oh, well... you know...
[buttons being pressed]
[MIKOTO] Sorry, Kuroko.
I never had
any intention
of dragging
you into this.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
I'm really glad... There's
nothing that could make me
prouder than having you
rely on me to assist you.
Your confidence
means the world to me.
[MIKOTO] Thank you.
[NUNOTABA] They're in synch.
Okay, Febri's up.
[SATEN] Got it...
[FEBRI gasps]
Big Sister, it's Febri...!
and this guy here
is Gekota...
He's a really good
friend of mine.
You know what...?
I've been outside...
[NUNOTABA] Please work...
I know I'm asking for more
than I deserve at this point.
If not for me... for them...
Let Febri's emotions
get through to her sister!
[NUNOTABA] This processing
speed can't keep up!
[beep]
[NUNOTABA] What's that...?
Access from outside?!
[MISAKA 10032] "I will
give you a hand, okay?"
Asks Misaka, retroactively
seeking approval after
having already acted.
Why would you do this?
[MISAKA 19090] To say thanks
for the fragments of our mind
we received from you.
Your mind...? I...
[MISAKA 19090] By the way...
This Misaka's serial number
is one nine zero nine zero.
[NUNOTABA] Wait, do you
mean... What I did before...
it reached you?
That's right...
and, moreover...
[MISAKA 10032] ...those
two young girls have
a thought base program that
is identical to the Misakas'.
Which means they are
basically like family
to the Misaka sisters...
"Does an older sister really
need a reason to help out
her younger sister?"
asks Misaka, adopting a tone of
wisdom and sisterly affection.
[MISAKA 19090] Like those
girls, we, too, want to know...
[MISAKA 19090] ...how bright and
beautiful the world can be...
...when you are not alone.
Good morning,
Big Sister!
[FEBRI] Shinobu!
Big Sister finally woke up!
She did...
[NUNOTABA] Good
morning... Janie.
[SATEN] Go on now,
Febri...
You have something to
give her, don't you?
Oh! Here!
[FEBRI] Take it! It's for Big
Sister and for you, Shinobu...!
Do you like it?
I made it myself!
You made something... for me?
What's the matter?
Oh, it's nothing...
There's just so much to do...
So many beautiful
things I want to show you.
[SATEN sobs] I can't take it...!
it's just, she's
growing up so quickly!
Come on,
Saten, stop...!
You promised that
you wouldn't cry,
and now you're
gonna make me...
[FEBRI] Ruiko, Whee-ha,
don't cry. It'll be okay.
Here, Janie. I brought
this for you...
It's a good luck charm...
Keep it with you.
I promise, it's
quite effective.
Guess that's it, then...
So they'll be going to
a facility overseas to be
examined and reconditioned?
That's too bad...
now that we've all
become such good friends.
It's difficult to
believe how well
everything turned out.
Almost like the bad parts
never happened at all...
as if the record of events had
been completely rewritten.
Oh... Really?
Electronic records
can be so...
Well... unreliable,
would you say...? Anyhow...
I get the feeling that some
of the human memories
have been doctored, as well.
[MIKOTO] Oh, um, yeah...
Well... if you're willing to
put differences behind you,
swallow your pride, and reach
out... the results can be...
...Impressive...
[NUNOTABA] I guess
it's my turn now, huh?
It'll be okay...
I know I can do this.
After all...
I'm not alone anymore.
You're ready?
Yes.
[MIKOTO stretches]
Okay... should we get going?
[UIHARU] If we leave
now we'll be in time
for the afternoon lectures.
[KUROKO] Yeah, you're right.
[SATEN] I think I'll
stop for lunch somewhere.
[MIKOTO] Man, this city...
There's never
a dull moment, huh?
[ALL] Not when
you're around, Misaka!
[MIKOTO] Hey, hold on...!
What's that supposed to mean?!
[UIHARU] So... is
everybody ready for
the regional field trip?
[KUROKO] Is it
that time already?
[SATEN] Liberal Arts City,
huh...? I can't wait!
[MIKOTO] Wait, come on...!
Seriously, guys...!
What did you mean by that?