[AMAMI] Oh, wow!
You know, it's hard
to believe how big
she's gotten after
only two weeks, isn't it?
[KUSAKABE] Not really.
She does have a ZID-02 cocktail
to stimulate her growth...
You've been through
training, right?
You should already be aware of
what to expect from the process.
Of course. I'm sorry...
I know all about it, I do!
I just got so excited,
seeing it in action.
Let's get started.
Oh, right!
I'll just go get ready.
[MIKOTO] Oooh! The sun is
almost blinding today, isn't it?
I know I should be
worried about sunburn,
but then again
that's what makes it
feel like summer,
don't you think?
[MIKOTO] Ooh!
Look it's a cicada shell!
[KUROKO] The Sissy
I know doesn't like
sunburns and cicada shells.
[MIKOTO] It's not
quite noon yet.
We've still got
some time.
[MIKOTO] Kuroko!
Oh! Yes, what is it?
[MIKOTO] What would you like?
It's my treat today!
[KUROKO] Wha-?
[KUROKO] She always uses
kicks on that vending machine...
not cash... and she's
paying for mine, too?
[MIKOTO] Well?
I-I guess I'll take
an iced coffee!
Oh! I am so sorry.
It was an accident!
I absolutely did not mean
to dive headlong
into your breasts.
[MIKOTO] Calm down. I know that.
You should be
more careful, though.
[MIKOTO] Okay, now
what should I get?
[KUROKO] Something is wrong!
What has come over
my dear, grouchy Sissy?
Could she be an imposter?
All right, I think I'll
go with the coconut cider.
You are wearing
orange underwear today...
They are polka-dotted with
a winking Gekota-- Aaah!
[MIKOTO]
Where did that come from?
[KUROKO] Just... checking...
It really is you.
[SATEN] Look! There they are!
Hey, sorry we're late!
[UIHARU] What are
you guys up to?
[HARU'UE]
Great looking tan, Shirai!
So, What do we have
on the docket for today?
[MIKOTO] Well, let's see...
I wouldn't mind
doing some shopping...
There are a few things
I need for our field trip.
[UIHARU] Yeah, that's right...
It's coming up soon, huh?
So, where are you
all going, Misaka?
I'm pretty sure it's
called "Liberal Arts City..."
[UIHARU] Oh, yeah?
The artificial island
in California?
Uh... Mhmm.
[HARU'UE] That's the
same place we're going!
[KUROKO] I didn't realize that.
[MIKOTO] How great!
We're all in the same group!
The five of us can hang
out the whole time...
We can eat together...
and go shopping...
Oh, and then there's
the beach, too.
[SATEN] Wow!
I'm starting to get excited!
Now I have an
excuse to get a new swimsuit!
Though maybe
I should wait on that...
There are a lot of other
things I need to buy first.
This would
be a great time
to have a big stack
of Money Cards.
You can't be serious!
Yeah, yeah,
I know, I know!
I was only kidding...
Anyway... what's been going
on with that case lately?
There have been no new
developments in a while,
but it hasn't been
open too long.
I see...
You're obsessing
about it, aren't you?
Well... I am kind of
hooked on it, yeah...
It's like I can sense
something bigger
lurking in the
shadows behind it!
So, are you basing
that on anything?
Just my sharp instincts
as an urban legend hunter.
Oh, you're starting
with that again?
Again?
What do you mean, again?
Please, give me an example!
[HARU'UE] Is something
bad going on?
[UIHARU] No, don't worry...
Saten just has an
overactive imagination.
[SATEN] Wha--Uiharu?
[MIKOTO] I think that's about
enough of that conversation.
[MIKOTO] Come on.
Let's go shopping...
The daylight isn't
going to last forever!
[KUROKO] Huh? Hey, wait for us!
[MIKOTO] There! I'm all set now.
[SATEN]
That's all you're getting?
[MIKOTO] Yeah.
There was only
one thing I needed
to get a little bit more of.
What about the rest of you guys?
Oh... well...
[KUROKO] A rice cooker?
[UIHARU] Yes. Ever since
we became roommates,
we've started cooking
at home a whole lot more.
But, uh... you already
have one, right?
Yeah, we do,
but we want another.
Oh... I remember.
Yesterday you said...
it was too small.
Uh-huh...
Sorry I eat so much.
[UIHARU] I'm not blaming
you at all, Haru'ue!
You've seen how much I eat!
[SATEN] Yeah, really!
Uiharu can be a serious glutton!
Excuse me?
[MIKOTO] Hey!
What do
you think of this one?
Now that's an
amazing machine.
It sure is, huh?
Although... It's not
really in our budget.
[MIKOTO] Surely you can come
down on the price just a bit...
You know how it is, don't you?
I suppose I do.
[KUROKO] Sissy haggling?
Really?
[HARU'UE] Wow...
We ended up with
a really nice one!
[UIHARU] I know!
I had no idea Misaka was
such an expert at bargaining!
Just think of all
the amazing things
we'll be able to
cook at home now!
We'll practically
be gourmet chefs!
Wow... There sure
are a lot of them.
Tons and tons!
This place has such
a wide variety of stuff!
Look at this!
These would be too cute!
How could I ever eat them?
[MIKOTO] Uh... I'm just kidding!
I can totally eat cute cookies !
Whatcha think?
Are any of these
swimsuits the kind of thing
you're looking for?
I don't know.
There are so many different
styles to choose from...
I've never picked out a
swimsuit myself before,
so it's difficult.
Why don't you let me
give you a hand, then!
[MIKOTO] Are you ready? Well?
It's just...
It looks like it was
made for a little girl.
[MIKOTO] You think ?
[MIKOTO] Huh...?
II think we're still having
the same problem here.
[MIKOTO] Okay... if you say so.
I brought another
one you can try.
[UIHARU] Misaka's bouncing
off the walls today.
What's gotten into her?
Yeah, I'd noticed
that, too...
Do you know what's
going on, Kuroko?
[MIKOTO] This one?
[UIHARU] We really lucked
out with the rice cooker,
didn't we, Haru'ue?
[HARU'UE] Mm-hmm.
Oh, hey, I just
realized where we are...
This is where
I saw "you," Misaka.
Oh... You mean Misaka's
look-alike, or whatever?
Are you still going
on about that?
I'm serious; she was
almost identical...
I wonder... That's it! I know!
What if she's actually
your long-lost twin!
Oh, yeah!
Speaking of look-alikes,
I heard the craziest rumor
from Konori earlier...
Something about using
cloning technology
to mass-produce a Level Fi--
I mean... um...
Cloning, huh?
As far as Academy City
rumors go,
that one is right up there...
Let's see, if I had a clone,
what would I do?
[MIKOTO] How about you, Saten?
If I had a clone?
Well, let me see...
First of all, I'd have her take
care of all my summer homework.
I would leave
mine in our room...
Then I could break curfew
without getting in trouble.
With my own clone,
I could eat enough
for two people.
That's an awesome idea!
If you couldn't choose
what to eat at a restaurant,
you could order two dishes.
[MIKOTO] What if
you have it backwards
and each of you could
only eat half a serving?
[UIHARU] She has a point.
[HARU'UE] Yeah...
What a shame...
It's your turn to
answer now, Sissy.
What would you do if there was
a clone of you
wandering around the city?
[MIKOTO] That's
a good question...
Incredible! She looks
like a real person.
Well, sure she does.
She's a clone...
That is sort of the point.
As you can see...
her mental age is approximately
still that of a newborn.
She can't understand
language or walk on her own.
She can't do much
of anything, really.
[KUSAKABE] What are you doing?
[AMAMI] Huh? Well...
I was worried she might
catch a cold if she's all wet.
You can do things
like that for now...
but soon you won't have time to.
Word is we're creating
the rest in one batch.
[KUSAKABE]
Language... motor skills...
and ethical data are input
like this using Testament...
This system transmits the data
electrically via all five
senses, forcibly writing the
information into her brain.
Well... Keeping up so far?
Yeah... I was thinking
about what you said.
Which part?
Isn't the process
a bit inefficient?
Without repeated conditioning,
the data input isn't
going to take very well...
Shouldn't they make them in
series, according to usage?
The higher-ups
have their own reasons
for doing things...
They give us orders.
We accept them and
do what we are told.
[SATEN] Aww, I can't believe
the day's over already...
At this rate, summer vacation
will be over before we know it.
It's getting close
to festival time, huh?
Oh, yeah... It is
that time of year.
[UIHARU] It doesn't
really feel like it here
in the city, though.
Barely anybody
goes back home for it.
[MIKOTO] That's okay...
It means we get more
time to spend together.
[SATEN] Yeah, you're right!
[MIKOTO] Let's enjoy ourselves,
instead of counting the days.
[MIKOTO] There's
plenty of summer left!
[MAIKA] Breakfast? At this hour?
Well, isn't someone
living the good life!
[MIKOTO] And why not?
It's not like I have
anything else to do today.
What are Shirai and
the others up to?
Everyone's
got something...
Uiharu and Kuroko both
have a Judgment function ...
Saten and Haru'ue
already had plans too.
With this much free
time on your hands,
life must be seeming pretty
empty and isolated, huh?
Who asked
for your opinion?
[MAIKA] It doesn't matter to me.
Just hurry up and eat, okay?
Otherwise, I'll never have time
to get everything
straightened up.
[MIKOTO] Jeez...
I can't even enjoy
a leisurely meal now?
[MAIKA] Do you seriously not
have anything better to do?
[MIKOTO] I'm sure
I can find something.
Hey... How come...?
It sucks when
you're all ready to read
your favorite magazine,
and then you realize
it's the same double issue
from the week before.
I'm so bored.
[GIRL A] Really?
Uh... what's up?
You're that
same girl. Right?
We helped you find your bag .
Since you don't
have anything else to do,
I think you should come and play
with us!
Uh, sorry, I'm actually
kind of busy, you see...
[PINK RIBBON GIRL]
You fibber!
I just heard you
say you're bored!
Yeah!
[MIKOTO] What can I say to that?
All right, Big Sister
will play with you.
[CHILDREN] Hooray!
Ha! Our "Big Sister," huh?
She's at that age.
They like to start thinking
that they're grown-ups.
[BANDAID BOY] Wait up!
[MIKOTO] No way!
[BANDAID BOY]
Rats! She did it to us again!
[MIKOTO] Go on...
hurry and get away!
It's not fair when
you kick it so far!
Do you always hafta' try
so hard against little kids?
Sorry... but you wouldn't
want me to go around
acting like I'm a
grown-up, would you?
You're a big jerk!
A stupid- dummy head!
I'm rubber,
you're glue...
You're ugly and
you smell funny!
[MIKOTO] What did you
call me, you little brat?
How does that bratty,
smart-talking mouth
of yours like this, huh?
Cut it out you big,
stupid freak!
Someday, I'll become a Level 5,
and then I'm gonna get
back at you for this!
I'll take you on any
time you want, short stuff.
Big Sis!
You've got an ability.
You're a big-shot
electrical user, aren't you?
I guess.
Oh, really?
That's Nao's ability, too.
[MIKOTO] Is that right?
But look.
No matter how hard I try,
that's all I can do.
That's the same for
everyone at the beginning...
Keep practicing, and you'll
be able to do lots of things.
What kinda things?
Like, will Nao be able
to "cell phone" with you?
"Cell phone"?
You know, use
electricity to talk.
Oh... No, sorry.
I can't even tell where someone
is using my ability,
much less talk to them.
Not even a little?
[MIKOTO] If there was
no interference at all...
like if we were out at sea...
it might be possible.
[MIKOTO] But here in the city,
where EM waves are
flying around all over,
there's just too
much noise for that.
Hmm? Oh... okay...
[MIKOTO] Although...
there was the case
of the Level Uppers...
As long as the brainwaves'
waveforms were close,
they might be able to
construct a network...
[MIKOTO]
Like that'll ever happen.
Good morning.
Do you know what that means?
"A routine beginning
of daily conversation.
Otherwise known as a greeting,"
affirms Misaka swiftly.
Your specimen number?
Specimen number
nine-nine-eight-two.
It appears that
you're plugged into
the Misaka Net, all right...
Here you go, start
by putting this on.
Uh, I'm sorry...
All this shameless nudity is
kind of making me uncomfortable.
Really?
[AMAMI] Couldn't we add
maybe a touch of modesty
when it comes to
displaying the body?
[KUSAKABE] If we add any
unnecessary emotions
and then they rebel,
that would be problematic.
The "safety devices"
aren't exactly perfect.
Oh... is that right?
It's true... Besides,
we couldn't do it...
You and I don't have
the necessary skills...
That machine over there.
It was overseen by
Nuno-something-or-other...
the girl genius...
and even she just
barely got it functioning.
[AMAMI] Oh...
[MIKOTO] Children sure
have a lot of energy.
Me too. And it's
really warm out here.
[MIKOTO] Young lady!
This is very important: from
whom did you get that button?
[BLUE RIBBON GIRL] Huh?
I got it from the
vending machines
in the shopping district.
[MIKOTO] It's the type
where you have to turn
the knob to drop the capsule.
With something this low-tech,
my ability's not going
to be of any use at all...
Well, here goes.
[WOMAN 4-A] Look at that!
There's a girl from
Tokiwadai at the toy machine.
[WOMAN 4-B] I see her...
I'm sure she's buying them for
those children, though.
[MIKOTO] This is ridiculous...
Not a single one.
You, kid,
go get me change!
Huh? Why should I get y--
Did you see her eyes?
Just do it, man.
Okay. Good call.
[GIRL A] Wow.
There weren't any in there, huh?
Well, um...
If you want to,
I can trade you for--
[GIRL A] I forgot!
There are more in front
of the train station.
You got it! Good job!
Isn't it pretty?
[CHILDREN thinking]
It's over... It's finally over.
[PINK RIBBON GIRL]
I'll go get some bags
or something to carry 'em in.
[BANDAID BOY]
Yeah, me too.
Well... now
that I've finally gotten it...
What am
I going to do with it?
[MIKOTO] Collector's fever:
That unfortunate condition
that drives sufferers
to obtain every product
even remotely related to the
subject of their obsession,
regardless of the consequences.
[MIKOTO] Even I know
that wearing it on my shirt
like this little girl would be
pathetic and embarrassing...
Really... I can just
imagine the pitiful look
Kuroko will give me
when she sees this.
[Another one, Sissy?
[MIKOTO] Yeah...
but if I put it on a bag...
that might be just
barely cool, right?
[GIRL A] Oh, wow.
I didn't know how late it was!
We have to go home
or we'll get in trouble.
[MIKOTO] Well, there
went my entire day.
[BLUE RIBBON GIRL] Hey!
If you're at the pool
and you go underwater,
how long can you
hold your breath?
[GIRL A] We played
for hours and hours!
[MIKOTO] Just because
you're on vacation
doesn't mean you can
do nothing but play games...
You have to do your
summer homework too.
[GIRL A] What's the matter?
Is something wrong?
Oh... no.
Everything's just fine.
Come on, let's go.
[GIRL A]
Goodbye, Big Sister!
Thanks for playing today!
[MIKOTO] Any time. And you'll
be careful going home, right?
[CHILDREN] Yep!
[MIKOTO] Okay...
now what was that before?
A power very
similar to mine... no...
It felt like my own power
was washing over me
from the outside in.
[MIKOTO] It's not possible.
[MIKOTO] There's no way...
Except... except...!
[AMAMI] Let's see...
There.
That looks about right...
One last thing...
[KUSAKABE]
Muscle strength, stamina,
and cardiovascular
endurance all check out...
You still need to pass your
interpersonal response test...
After that you can move
on to external training.
[MISAKA 9982]
Misaka has already mastered
every possible situation...
from ordering a hamburger...
to spotting a con-artist...
She is confident
that she can blend in
with people in
the outside world.
Therefore, she has some doubts
as to the necessity
of such a test.
You're not prepared
for everything...
There are times on the outside
when what you learned using
Testament will not work...
Maybe... if you were to run into
the Original, for example...
Though that's not likely.
Well... even if
that does happen,
it shouldn't interfere
with the experiment.
[MISAKA 9982] "What is
the Original?" Misaka asks.
Good question.
She's the model
for the Sisters...
I guess you could say she's...
sort of like your older sister.
[MISAKA 9982] Older sister...
[MIKOTO] Around here...
This is where it came from.
[MIKOTO] Who... are you?
[KUSAKABE] Hmm...
Now for your clothing...
You've been provided
with an outfit...
so go ahead and change.
[KUSAKABE]
Oh... uh... actually...
Would you mind
cleaning those up first?
You know... before
the next experiment.
[MISAKA 9982]
Misaka understands.
[MIKOTO] What is this?
The same face...
The same hair...
She looks just like
me in every way...
Who are you? Tell me!
[KUROKO] Uh, Sissy... Why are
you yelling at the mirror?