[MISAKA 10031]
Thank you for waiting.
[ACCELERATOR] Hm?
"I hope I have not
kept you long.
I am Misaka 10031, your next
opponent," Misaka reports.
[ACCELERATOR] Huh?
Tch, okay.
You guys get kinda
confusing after a while.
[MISAKA 10032]
Operation confirmed.
Misakas 10031 and 10032
will proceed with the
predetermined course of action.
[gun cocking]
The time has come.
We will now be commencing
trial number 10031.
[ACCELERATOR sighs]
[MIKOTO] Tree Diagram
has been destroyed.
But how?
Shot down by some hostile force?
An accident with space debris?
Although.
That's not really
the point, is it?
The point is, the last chance
I had of putting a stop
to the project is now
garbage in outer space,
and then there's the fact that
the experiments have been
proceeding according to plan,
even without Tree Diagram.
Oh, That's right.
One of the facilities on this
block was among the project's
transferee offices that
I was looking into yesterday.
Heh.
[KAMIJO] Thanks for waiting!
Uhh...
Or not.
[KITTY meows]
[KAMIJO] Oh, hi, On Hold.
You're still here.
So where did she go?
[alarm sounds]
[FEMALE SECURITY ROBOT 13-A]
Entry code not recognized.
Entry to outsiders
is not permitted.
Please exit the premises.
[KAMIJO sighs]
[KAMIJO] Hey!
Misaka's sister!
Well.
I don't know why she would
be back here, anyway.
Uh... That doesn't look good.
[distant gunfire]
[RESEARCHERS] Ahh!
Was that an explosion?
[FEMALE RESEARCHER 13-A]
No! Just look! Over there!
Ah!
[FEMALE RESEARCHER 13-A]
It's her!
[MALE RESEARCHER 13-A]
Go! Go!
[MALE RESEARCHER 13-B]
The electromaster!
[FEMALE RESEARCHER 13-A]
Hey, wait up!
[MALE RESEARCHER 13-B]
Let's get out of here!
[gunfire]
[yawns]
[ACCELERATOR] So. You done yet?
Can I go ahead and
kill you now? Huh?
[ACCELERATOR] That's some
pretty heavy firepower
considering we're in
the middle of the city.
You should be careful.
[MISAKA 10031 gasps]
Now, what are you
running away like that for?
Don't get me wrong,
I do appreciate the view.
After all, you've got
such a cute little ass.
[MIKOTO] No.
This isn't close
to over yet.
It's too soon to give up.
Yes.
I'll just bring it all down.
Everything they've done.
Everything they will do.
All of it!
[KAMIJO] There was
definitely a loud noise.
But what happened here?
Still no sign
of her, though.
[KITTY meows]
It's okay. We'll head back now.
[gasps]
Is that? Her shoe?
[distant gunfire]
[ACCELERATOR] I've got
a pop quiz for you.
Which technique
was it I just used?
Please answer.
Out of the many skills
I have to call upon,
which did I just employ
to put you on the ground?
[MISAKA 10031 groans]
[MISAKA 10031] Reflection?
Aw, that's too bad.
Yeah. You're close,
but I'm afraid that's not
this particular technique.
[clicks]
Would you like to
try guessing again,
or should I just go
ahead and tell you?
[ACCELERATOR]
The right answer is...
...Vector transformation.
Kinetic energy.
Body heat.
Or, of course...
...electricity.
Any vector, anything
that has direction,
once it touches my skin,
I can transform it.
[ACCELERATOR laughs]
See? Simple.
[alarm sounds]
[MIKOTO] I'll destroy it.
All of it.
Equipment, research,
their greed, their ambition.
I'll tear it all apart.
Until there's no trace left.
[explosion]
[MIKOTO laughs]
[MIKOTO] It will take time,
but someday.
[MIKOTO] Someday?
Someday it will
all be over, huh?
But what good does that do?
Before "someday" gets here.
How many more Sisters
are going to die?
[MIKOTO] Shut up!
What else do you want me to do?
End it all? Right now?
This minute?
Please, tell me!
How the hell am I
supposed to do that?!
[MISAKA 10031 groans]
[ACCELERATOR] Now then,
shall we return our focus
to this little match of ours?
[ACCELERATOR] Bear with me,
'cause I think I'm gonna get
a little creative, here.
What do you suppose would happen
if I reversed the flow of
blood through your veins?
Heh.
[MIKOTO] No.
Please, no.
What are you doing? Stop!
[MIKOTO sobs]
[ACCELERATOR] Tch.
[ACCELERATOR] Hey.
So I'm guessing you're the
one I'm up against for this
experiment of
theirs, that right?
"That's correct. It is
a pleasure to meet you,"
replies Misaka,
offering a kind greeting.
[ACCELERATOR] Back at you.
This is my first time going
head-to-head against a Level 5.
I'm looking forward to--Huh?
[ACCELERATOR] A gun?
[MISAKA] All checks
have been completed.
Now...
Shall we
get started?
Misaka is excited to
begin her first trial.
Incidentally, you've been given
permission to use a firearm,
have you not?
You are certain you
do not want one?
[ACCELERATOR] Hm...
[buzzer]
[SUNGLASSES MAN 11-A]
All right, if you're ready,
let's get the first
trial under way.
[MISAKA]
"Yes, please.
Misaka is ready.
So," Misaka trails off,
commencing her attack.
"Target appears to be deflecting
the bullets," observes Misaka,
analyzing the situation
with some surprise.
[MISAKA gasps]
[ACCELERATOR] Is the
point of this experiment
to screw with me?
Hey.
What the hell's
going on here? C'mon.
Is that really a
clone of a Level 5?
[SUNGLASSES MAN 11-A laughs]
[SUNGLASSES MAN 11-A] There are
some specification differences
from the Original.
However, all of the
clones you'll face
share a common memory
through their mental network.
Over the course of
twenty thousand test runs,
they'll continue to
learn and develop.
When you reach the end,
you may find yourself
fighting an uphill battle.
That's a long time away,
and until then
I'm stuck fighting these
losers over and over?
Tch. Man, talk
about a buzzkill.
That all for now?
I'm getting out of here.
[SUNGLASSES MAN 11-A] Well.
Actually, the first trial
hasn't been completed yet.
And it won't be until you have
dispatched the test subject.
Fulfillment of this
experiment requires
the elimination of twenty
thousand armed clones.
This subject's actions have
not yet been terminated.
Please continue with combat.
[MISAKA] "Continue with combat
until the experiment
is complete.
Yes," says Misaka,
following her orders.
Terminate? Dispatch? Eliminate?
That sounds like...
[gunfire]
[ACCELERATOR] Huh?
[thud]
[clattering]
[MISAKA] So dark and cold
like sinking slowly
down through water.
An ocean.
"So this is what death
is like," says Misaka.
[buzzer]
That's what you
were talking about?
[SUNGLASSES MAN 11-A] Uh, yeah,
that's we were looking for.
Good work today. This
concludes the first trial.
It may be dull now, but they'll
improve quickly enough,
so just keep hammering away.
There's no need
to hold back.
Keep in mind that your opponents
are nothing but wind-up dolls.
Just objects synthesized
from chemicals and protein.
[ACCELERATOR] Well, then.
Guess I'll go get some dinner.
[KAMIJO breathes heavily]
[KAMIJO] S-So much blood.
[KAMIJO screams]
[chattering]
[GIRL STUDENT 13-A] What's up?
[GIRL STUDENT 13-B]
There's been some kind of
incident, apparently.
[GIRL STUDENT 13-C]
I heard that somebody died!
[GIRL STUDENT 13-A]
Seriously? Like a murder?
[ANTISKILL 13-A] Hey,
how much further is it?
[KAMIJO] It's right up here.
[ANTISKILL 13-A] What's wrong?
[KAMIJO] Oh, the uh, the body.
It was right there just
a few minutes ago.
[ANTISKILL 13-B] Huh?
Listen, kid.
You sure about what you saw?
[KAMIJO] How the...?
No way, you're kidding.
[KAMIJO] Was I just dreaming?
[ANTISKILL 13-A]
Yes? Is that right? Roger that.
Hey!
Our people have checked all the
security cameras in the area.
They say there isn't a hint
of anything suspicious.
[KAMIJO] Impossible!
I mean, I just!
We're going to write
this up as a simple
eyewitness error this time,
but kid, you pull this again,
and we're contacting
your school.
[ANTISKILL 13-B] Man,
I'm sick of these brats
and their stupid pranks.
[KAMIJO] What's going on?
What the hell
is happening?
Damn it!
[KITTY meows]
[KAMIJO] M-Misaka?
I am sorry
about this.
"It was my intention
to meet back with you
after I completed
the op, so,"
Misaka apologizes with
complete sincerity.
[KAMIJO] Hey, hold on!
Are you... You're Misaka's
younger sister, right?
And you're alive.
Heh, heh...
I'll be damned.
I must be losing my mind.
Sorry, It's just,
until a second ago,
I thought I had found your body.
Heh, ha...
I guess I was wrong.
"No, you were correct
about Misaka's death."
Misaka confirms
your observation.
Huh?
That, that bag.
What are you carrying in there?
[MISAKA 10032]
"Before saying more.
I must verify your
password, please."
Misaka says, as she
was instructed.
"ZXC741 ASD852 QWE963, well?"
Asks Misaka, testing you.
Uh. Say what?
[MISAKA 10032] It does
not appear you are able
to decode the password.
Given that fact, you
have obviously not been
read in to the experiment,
so Misaka cannot
say anything more.
[KAMIJO] That's it!
What the hell are
you talking about?
What exactly do you
have in that bag?
[MISAKA 13-A]
"It contains Sisters,"
Misaka says calmly.
"I apologize for having to
leave the cat behind with you,"
Says Misaka.
"But I did not feel
right bringing him."
"It seems obvious that a
violent battle between humans
is no place for
an innocent animal,"
Misaka says,
justifying her actions.
[MISAKA 13-E] "I appear to
have caused undue concern.
That is an unfortunate
result of the experiment,"
Misaka says,
apologizing again.
"But there was no real
need to be worried."
"You see, we are many.
All Misakas
here are Misaka."
[KAMIJO] What the hell is this?
Up to now, you have had
contact with one Misaka.
Serial number
one-zero-zero-three two.
You see, I am that Misaka.
"However, the Misaka who
died today was serial number
one-zero-zero-three-one.
She is the same Misaka you ran
into yesterday with Big Sister."
Misaka explains,
to differentiate.
"All Misakas have the ability
to control electricity."
"And our brainwaves are
all linked to each other."
"Therefore, we all share
a common memory."
Misaka adds,
explaining further.
I don't get it,
who are you?
"We are simply cellular clones
that have been mass-produced
for military purposes.
The original donor
is Mikoto Misaka
one of only seven Level 5
espers in Academy City."
"We are her sisters," says
Misaka in conclusion.
Misaka's clones?
Really? But, what is this?
What are you all doing here?
[MISAKA 10032 "We are
performing an experiment."
Misaka reiterates.
"The details are
classified as top-secret,"
[MISAKA 13-J] "So I
cannot explain further."
[MISAKA 13-K] "But it is nothing
for you to be concerned about,"
Misaka says reassuringly.
[MISAKA 13-L] "Once again,
I hope you will accept
my sincere apologies"
[MISAKA 13-M] "For involving
you in this experiment."
[MISAKA 10032] Misaka
requests, bowing her head.
[KITTY meows]
[MISAKA 10032] Now then, if
you would look after the cat.
[MISAKA 10032] It is
just an experiment.
Cellular clones that
have been mass-produced
for military purposes from the
original donor, Mikoto Misaka.
[KAMIJO] Experiment? Military?
[KAMIJO] I wonder.
Misaka, does she
know about this?
[MIKOTO] Project Level 6 Shift.
Test Subject will kill Railgun
one hundred and
twenty-eight times.
Thus achieving Level 6.
[MIKOTO] That's it.
That's what I can do.
[KITTY meows]
[MALE ANNOUNCER 13-A] The next
stop is School District 7,
Tokiwadai Middle School Dorms.
School District 7, Tokiwadai.
[door opens then closes]
[KAMIJO] So, she's in room 208.
[KAMIJO] And when you see her,
what are you planning to say?
Are you just going to
ask her straight out?
"Hey, did you know
someone out there's
killing off clones of you?"
[MIKOTO] It was no use,
any of it.
The whole thing is my fault!
But I think,
I think there's one last
thing I can do to save them.