[SUIT MAN 8-A] Confirm.
It's three minutes past
the rendevous time.
[SUIT MAN 8-B] This is Point A.
Confirmed, there's
no one in sight yet.
[SUIT MAN 8-C] All right...
So they're no-shows.
Guess they realized they were
messing with the wrong people.
[MUGINO] Now you're
just being ridiculous.
[SUIT MAN 8-A]
Hey! Who was that?
[MUGINO] I'm here,
as we agreed...
Closer than you know, in fact.
[SUIT MAN 8-B]
The deal is off... It's off.
Get out of there right now!
Who are you?
[FRENDA] Heh.
[SUIT MAN 8-B] Ahh!
You! Stay back!
[KINUHATA sighs]
[SUIT MAN 8-A screams]
[MUGINO] What's that? Again?
Yeah... Yeah, all right...
Fine. So who is it?
Pharmaceuticals? Really?
Isn't that a little...
[FRENDA] Sure, that's true.
It's not like I don't
see what you're saying...
but, all told...
the whole point of a swimsuit
is to show off your
body to other people...
so going to a private pool
defeats the purpose of wearing
one, if you see what I mean.
[KINUHATA] Okay.
But all of the public
pools and beaches
are always ultra crowded...
There's no room, so it's
next to impossible to swim.
[FRENDA] Yeah...
I guess you're right.
I hadn't thought about that.
What do you think,
Takitsubo?
[TAKITSUBO] Hmm...
As long there's space to
just float like a corpse,
it doesn't
matter to me.
Oh... Okay...
[clapping]
Ladies, let's cut the chit chat
while we're working.
Kinuhata, that's enough...
We've got a new request,
so we're heading back.
What time?
[MUGINO] Good question.
The request is somewhat vague.
Huh?
That said...
our task sounds like
it'll be simple enough.
Hey... I don't know
how much I like
taking on a job
that's so vague...
But, all told, Mugino,
you're the boss, so whatever.
So, what is the job?
Protecting a facility from
a mysterious invader...
The pay isn't too bad, either...
I think this is perfect.
Just the kind of job we here
at ITEM like to take on.
[MUGINO] An esper with the power
to control electricity, huh?
[FEMALE VOICE 8-A] The attacks
have been conducted
via communications lines,
and no intruder has been
caught by electronic security,
so that's their guess.
Actually... the client
seems to have this
rather narrowly
profiled already.
So they've got a
suspect in mind?
In that case, why don't they
set up their own counterattack?
I think that it would be
ultra easy to stage an ambush.
[FEMALE VOICE 8-A]
You are only to act
once the target is
within the facility...
and you are not to pry
into the particulars...
those are the client's orders.
Uh? What's with these guys?
I don't like how this
job is going so far.
[FEMALE VOICE 8-A]
What do you want?
A job's a job.
We don't take them
because they're fun...
Anyway... they sought
you out for this gig...
I'm sure they had
their reasons...
Now quit your whining
and get to work!
[FRENDA] Okay.
So that's the job...
just lie in wait then
take out the opponent?
[MUGINO] Basically.
With one catch, though...
There are two facilities
that our mystery attacker
could potentially target.
Ooh! I can cover one
of them by myself!
[MUGINO] Huh?
What's with you?
I thought you didn't
like this job.
[FRENDA] Liking the job
has nothing to do with it...
I mean if I'm the one
to take 'em out,
then I earn the kill shot
bonus, don't I?
[MUGINO chuckles]
[MUGINO] All right, Frenda...
Just make sure you
stay in contact.
Don't get in over
your head, okay?
[horn honks]
[MIKOTO] Only two places left.
Including this one.
[MIKOTO] At this point,
I don't know how far they've
gone with the experiment.
And I don't think
I want to know.
But either way.
It ends tonight.
[FRENDA] I volunteered for this
'cause the pay
was so enticing...
but waiting around for somebody
who may not even show up
certainly is boring...
All told, this really sucks.
And if they go to
the other facility
while I'm stuck here
waiting at this one...
then all these tedious
minutes of utter boredom
will have been for nothing!
[creaking]
No way!
The target's actually here!
[FRENDA]
Well, I'm ready...
Time to earn that
kill shot bonus.
[MIKOTO] All right.
The research facility I'm
after is on the top floor.
If I get lucky...
maybe I can pull this
off without a hitch.
Of course not.
Like it would ever
actually be that easy.
[FRENDA] Not a single
one hit her?
Did she use magnetism to
divert the stone's path?
It looks like the intel about
an electrical esper was right.
There we go...
Ordinarily, this is a tool used
to burn through walls and doors,
but tonight...
[MIKOTO] A bomb?
What kind of
scientists are these?
Putting bombs inside
of stuffed animals?
[MIKOTO] They're igniting
the bombs using fuses
they set up in the room
ahead of time...
I don't get it.
Why would they want to make
this such a big production?
Wha--? A bomb in the rubble?
[MIKOTO] They're
predicting my moves.
Does that mean they know
they're being attacked
by an Electromaster?
[MIKOTO groans]
[MIKOTO] I was hoping not to
use my maximum magnetism...
It does a lot of damage.
Never mind that...
Where are they?
More of those fuses?
Maybe if I follow
where they lead...
She's the one, huh?
[MALE RESEARCHER 8-A]
Are you sure?
Yes... I heard it was
pathological analysis.
Word is they're
the ones who got hit.
What a relief.
That should buy us some time...
Still, we need to
hurry up with our move.
[MALE SUBORDINATE 8-A]
Excuse me...
[MALE RESEARCHER 8-A]
What is it?
[MALE SUBORDINATE 8-A]
Well, uh...
There's a visitor.
[foot steps]
[MALE RESEARCHER 8-A] Hello.
I'm sorry if I've
kept you waiting...
It's nice to meet you...
Uh... please forgive
me, but you are...?
I'm the one who was in
charge of your company's
Testament oversight.
My name's Nunotaba.
[FRENDA] Almost!
That stupid girder
is in my way.
[MIKOTO] I don't want any
more interference later on.
I'll deal with her now.
[FRENDA] She's put up
quite a fight so far...
Chances are if I'd used
my remote-control bombs,
she'd be dead by now.
But with an Electromaster
of her level, it's possible
she could've taken control
of them, instead.
All told... it was
the right decision.
And... boom!
[FRENDA] No way!
She can deflect ceramic bombs?
She's on an entirely
different level
than any other esper
I've gone up against.
[MIKOTO] You won't get away...
I don't know if you're directly
involved or just a hired goon.
But anyone who supports
this experiment...
...will pay!
Oh, dear!
I'm terrified!
Just look at her!
If she catches me, she'll tear
me into tiny little pieces!
Heh. Yeah, as if!
[FRENDA laughs]
I lured her up as
high as I could,
so that was quite
a fall she took.
It doesn't matter how high-level
an esper you are after...
...that?
No. That's impossible.
If you were wanting
to see me fall,
you should've fought me
in a different building.
One that wasn't built using
any steel, for example.
You should be gone! No fair!
Oh!
Looks like you've
hit a dead end.
[FRENDA] It does, huh?
I never expected to be backed
into a corner like this.
[MIKOTO] It happens.
It is a pretty easy
mistake to make...
Perhaps you were panicking and
took a wrong turn somewhere...
Or maybe...
[FRENDA] Heh.
What do you think?
[MALE RESEARCHER 8-A] Oh, I'm
sorry if it wasn't clear...
There isn't really anything
specific we need from you.
It's just, this is the
first time we've done
a large-scale move like this...
so I thought, you know, if
anything were to happen...
it would be good to
have you around...
given your previous
involvement with the project.
[NUNOTABA] Of course.
I understand.
Thank you, I thought
that you might...
Well, then, if you'll
excuse me for a moment.
[door closes]
[MIKOTO] There's something
I want to ask you,
while I still can.
It's a simple question...
Who hired you?
[FRENDA] Huh?
Now isn't the time to be
concerned about loyalty...
This facility is part
of a cruel experiment--
[FRENDA] Yeah, yeah,
never mind about all that.
My employer's background,
their objectives,
the morality of the person
I've been hired to eliminate...
the possibility that they're
fighting for a noble cause...
All told, those
sorts of things...
Just don't really
matter to me.
Do you understand
your situation now?
Let me explain something to you,
you've heard those
stories before, right?
The ones about the hunter
becoming the hunted.
Take a look at where
you're standing.
[FRENDA]
Your retreat is cut off.
There's nothing to
shield your self with...
Now what will you do?
Go ahead. I'd love to see
you get out of this one!
Heh.
[MIKOTO sighs]
Well, so much for that...
You try to end things
in a civilized way,
and look what happens.
[FRENDA gasps]
[MIKOTO] My work's not over.
I need to save as much
of my strength as I can.
[FRENDA] She actually
lifted up the floor!
Oh no... Does that mean...
Am I fighting a Level 5 esper?
I'm done with you!
[FRENDA] Then again,
people with too much power
do have a tendency
to be careless.
[MIKOTO] Uh-oh!
That's what you get for making
your next move so obvious.
[MIKOTO grunts]
[MIKOTO] A stun grenade!
Serves me right... I got sloppy.
[FRENDA laughs]
[FRENDA] I love seeing a
cocky, powerful esper like that
trapped by my own hands...
It makes me feel all
warm and fuzzy inside!
[FRENDA laughs]
All told, messing with me can
be hazardous to your health!
All right! That's
half the paycheck!
Half the money for
this gig goes to me!
Money for me! Money for me!
I'm so excited! I wonder
what I should buy...
She's gone?
That wasn't enough firepower
to incinerate her.
So... I guess...
if she's not there,
she must be...
[MIKOTO] I'll give you
this much, at least.
You've done your homework
on Electromasters.
But I'm at a slightly
higher level...
EM waves provide me
with a picture
of the surrounding space.
Whoa, there!
Best not to make
any sudden moves.
I'm starting to get my sight
and my hearing back...
And at such a close range,
nothing can outrun
my electric shocks.
Uh... Mijihi!
Huh?
Miji... cavi... capri...
[MIKOTO] Huh?
What is she saying?
I've never heard a
language like that...
Hold on... one of those
words could have been...
It's gibberish... Gotcha!
Hah!
[MIKOTO] Another bomb?
When will she give up?
[MIKOTO] What is that?
[FRENDA] Academy City's
specially-made
gaseous explosive.
They call it Ignus.
It won't do you any
harm to breathe it in...
but then, it's an explosive,
not a poison.
The way it's filling
the air now...
It's turning this room
into one big bomb.
So...
do you know what would happen
if you used electricity?
Well... I think I'll kill
you now nice... and slow!
[MIKOTO] Not good.
Electricity is out
of the question,
and using magnetism runs the
risk of creating friction.
Ah!
[MIKOTO] Is this girl a psycho?
It's not impossible that all the
stomping around she's doing
could kick up a spark.
[FRENDA] I can tell
you're wondering
if I have a death wish.
In case you haven't noticed,
I work for the underworld.
You think I can do that and
still be afraid of dying?
[FRENDA] Yeah, right!
I couldn't be more full of it!
There's no way I'm
dying in here with you.
The canister I tossed first was
the real thing, all right...
but what I dispersed afterward
was just ordinary nitrogen.
I didn't think she would fall
for it so completely, though.
[MALE RESEARCHER 8-A]
So, what's the deal
with the underworld cleaner
they've got standing by?
[MALE RESEARCHER 8-B]
Oh, nothing much...
I don't know what
she can do, really.
She's only a little girl.
Never mind her.
I wonder what's happening
at the other facility.
Who knows?
Any means of
external communication
have been disabled.
I just want to hurry and
get this move over with.
But if something
were to go wrong.
Well, that's why we
called in a patsy, right?
So somebody else can
take the responsibility.
Yeah,
there is that.
Sorry to keep you
waiting, Nunotaba--
Where is she?
[MALE RESEARCHER 8-A]
Restroom, maybe?
[NUNOTABA] Moving the Sisters
that are being adjusted
would normally come last.
With the abrupt
transfer of control
and the watch out for attackers,
they've ignored
internal security.
If I'm really going
to do this...
it's now or never.
[FRENDA] You're hanging
in there pretty well.
But if I don't finish
you off pretty soon,
Mugino and the others
will show up,
and I don't like to
share with others.
I told you before that
I don't care much
about my targets' lives...
I do care about their
deaths, however,
and I'm especially
interested in yours.
When I take a life...
it's an exquisite feeling.
Because in that moment,
I am in complete control of
someone else's destiny...
It feels great... that power...
As if the only reason
that person was born...
was to have their
life ended by me.
[MIKOTO gasps]
[FRENDA] Now, enough talk.
All told, I just want to hear
one good, final scream from you.
[MIKOTO] To be born for the sole
reason of being murdered...
To accept that...
to take life for granted...
never trying to escape...
or attempting to fight it...
never seeking to be saved ...
from such a
godforsaken destiny...
I say to hell with that!
[FRENDA] Oh no.
A choke hold...
Shocks aren't her
only line of defense.
Can't breathe!
[FRENDA yells]
[FRENDA coughs]
Not a bad idea.
You almost had me, but--
Huh?
[FRENDA] That was a
really close call...
I can't believe I almost
blew half my body off
with my own explosives!
Just imagine...
My beautiful legs
would have been--
[MIKOTO]
Okay, I see...
so that's how it is...
It was a trick...
You didn't fill the room
with explosive gas, did you?
All told, I fell
for a simple bluff.
[FRENDA] Well... uh... I...
[MIKOTO laughs]
Man... "I said "All told,"
You're rubbing off on me...
[MIKOTO laughs]
[FRENDA laughs]
Tee-hee!
[FRENDA yells]
[FRENDA groans]
[MIKOTO] You seem like a pretty
terrible person to me...
I'm not gonna lose any sleep
if I shock you to death...
Just thought you should know.
I want all the info you
have on the project...
I mean every last detail.
Who's the one in charge?
Who hired you to do this?
[FRENDA] Yeah, Too bad
I don't know that,
since we go through
an intermediary.
Oh, I forgot...
You said somebody else was
on the way here, didn't you?
Who?
[FRENDA] There's no way
I'm telling you that.
[MIKOTO] You've got three
seconds to answer me...
unless you want to be
burned to a cinder.
Three...
[FRENDA] No! No!
I'll talk! I'll talk!
[MIKOTO] Two...
[FRENDA] My tongue!
That last shock must have...
Wait! Hold on! My tongue is
too numb to talk! Honestly!
Please don't kill me!
[MIKOTO] One...
[MIKOTO] Zero.
[FRENDA] Huh?
[MIKOTO] I see.
So you're not going to
sell out your friends, huh?
[FRENDA] No... I would,
I just can't talk.
All right... I can't
hold that against you.
[MIKOTO gasps]
[MUGINO] It got quiet
in here all of a sudden.
I was sure the Electromaster
had finished you off.
Looks like I got
here just in time.
Hello, Frenda.
[NUNOTABA] Mikoto Misaka...
[MIKOTO] I'm putting
an end to this.
[NUNOTABA] I can't let her take
them on without any help at all.
[MIKOTO] I'll save
the rest of them!
[NUNOTABA] Yes...
I'll do what I can...
I'll help her.