So, like I was saying...
[MIKOTO] Good morning!
Eh?
Oh, hey. It's Misaka...
Um... You got here
pretty quickly, huh?
Huh? Quickly? No...
Same time as normal.
Really? But we just
saw you in town.
Yeah, it was definitely
you, and you were walking
in the opposite direction
from the school.
Oh... well, that's
impossible, isn't it?
You must've seen someone
who looks like me.
[GIRL STUDENT 3-C]
Clones? That's crazy!
[GIRL STUDENT 3-D] I mean it!
There's a story that's
been going around
about a project designed
to clone Level 5 espers.
You haven't heard of it?
No, I haven't.
Sounds pretty amazing though?
[MIKOTO] Really? The rumors
get dumber every day.
[BOY STUDENT 3-A] Seriously!
You mean they're mass-producing
them to use as weapons!
Oh, yeah, it'll be
common practice soon.
[BOY STUDENT 3-A] No way!
[BOY STUDENT 3-B] Absolutely!
[MIKOTO] That's ridiculous.
[GIRL STUDENT 3-E]
Think about it:
there are only seven
Level 5s in Academy City, right?
[GIRL STUDENT 3-F] So, which
of them are they cloning?
[MIKOTO] Oh, come on!
Well... That's just the thing.
I heard who they might be using.
The Level 5 is supposedly
that Railgun girl.
[NUNOTOBA] So, it's you...
The Original.
Original? Sorry?
[NUNOTOBA] You must at least
have heard the rumors, right?
What rumors?
[sighs]
[MIKOTO] Hmph... I have
to say, I'm surprised.
I guess the students at
Nagatenjoki like gossip
as much as anyone, huh?
So... that's all?
You've heard some rumors,
but do you actually
know anything-
You are still a
middle-schooler.
But I am a high-schooler...
And you will
observe my seniority...
Basically... Watch
your tone with me.
I... I was just
wondering if you had
any more substantial
information about it.
More than you do...
Although, from
what I can tell...
Their methods and objectives
have changed considerably
since I was there.
[NUNOTOBA] Knowing more
would only hurt you.
What's the point
when there's nothing you
can do about it, anyway?
I asked you
for information,
not for protection...
And what do you mean
I can't do anything?
Are you saying there's
something that you can--
[MIKOTO] Is there, maybe,
something that you can do?
I have taken some
action already.
Distributing those Money Cards
was part of the plan.
The plan to eliminate
this city's blind spots.
[NUNOTOBA] Placing the
Money Cards all over directs
people's attention to the
alleys and back streets
that the surveillance
cameras don't reach.
[NUNOTOBA] By doing so,
I hoped I could put an end
to the experiments
that have been taking
place in the shadows.
Of course...
I was careless enough
to let myself be spotted
by those thugs and they
followed me back here.
[NUNOTOBA]
If they had seen this,
it could have created some
serious problems for me...
As always...
Leaving physical
evidence isn't smart.
I'm not legitimately
renting this place, either.
It would be best if we got out
of here before they woke up.
[MIKOTO] Hold on a second!
I mean...
Please tell me...
What are you even talking about?
And who exactly are you--?
Now you're thinking...
"As long as I'm destroying
physical evidence,
shouldn't I get rid
of the witnesses, too?"
Whoa, I am not!
Come on, we need
to get these guys...
[NUNOTOBA] Not my problem.
[MIKOTO] Eh?!
[FEMALE ONLOOKER 3-A]
What's going on? Is it a fire?
[MALE ONLOOKER 3-A]
Yeah, a small one...
Doesn't look like
anyone was hurt, though.
[MIKOTO] Man!
Who was that psycho?
She actually got
two good hits on me...
and said nothing I understood.
Why am I taking
anything she said seriously?
That's it! I'm just
wasting my time...
I'm going to head home,
have a nice shower...
and hit the sack.
[MIKOTO] It's ridiculous...
I don't care how many people
said it, it isn't true...
There's just no way...
There are no clones of me.
[MIKOTO] Although...
[FEMALE TEACHER 3-A] As you can
see, the model DNA information
is absolutely indispensable
to cloning technology...
[MIKOTO] It's true...
I did give someone
my DNA map once...
but that was a long time ago...
and it was for a
different reason...
I'm sure he put it to good use.
Besides... not
long afterwards...
that hospital was closed
down for good... and now...
[MIKOTO] She goes
to Nagatenjoki Academy.
I can hack into the
student records...
Academy City's
public telephone
net terminal security is Rank D.
The data terminals used by
school faculty
members are Rank B.
[MIKOTO] However...
if I just use my ability...
Right there!
"Shinobu, Nunotaba...
Third year of high school...
Age seventeen."
Has distinguished
herself in the field
of biological psychiatry
from a young age...
Worked with Yamashita
University Hospital Network
and Higuchi Pharmaceuticals..."
Eh?! Hold on!
Yamashita?!
She was really there?
So she might actually
know something...
"...and Higuchi Pharmaceuticals,
collaborating
on a project at the
Seventh Research Center...
She later reenrolled
in school."
So is that the place where
they've got my DNA map?
[NUNOTOBA] Knowing
more would only hurt you.
What's the point
when there's nothing
you can do about it, anyway?
[MIKOTO] Asking her for more
answers won't do any good.
She'll just keep
evading the question.
All right!
I guess I'll have to
sneak into this place!
Going in my uniform
would be a bad idea.
[MIKOTO] I'll take this
along with it, please.
[FEMALE CLERK 3-A]
'Kay... Oh, yes.
I can tell these will
look adorable on you!
Cash or card?
[MIKOTO] Oh... I'll
pay with cash, thanks.
[MIKOTO] Got the clothes.
And now I need to find somewhere
I can go to change into them.
[MALE FRONT DESK 3-A]
Unfortunately,
all of our single rooms
are occupied.
We do have some doubles...
[MIKOTO] All right... I'll
take one of those, please.
[MIKOTO] This room's
kind of a waste
just for changing my clothes...
Well... Here goes.
[HARU'UE]
Wow, those are all yours?
[SATEN] Pretty impressive, huh?
[SATEN] Well, to be honest,
Misaka did help me find them...
Now... I know there are a lot
of people looking for them...
but finding this many in a
single day has to be a record!
When you add them all up,
it's quite a tidy sum.
Really? Then I wonder
if that means I'm rich, too.
[SATEN] You... you
found these? All of them?
Before term started,
I wanted to familiarize
myself with the area.
I collected these
while I was exploring.
[UIHARU] Hey, I'm home!
Sorry I'm so late.
Thanks for
doing this, Saten...
You know how things can be
when we've got a new case...
Uh... are you okay?
[SATEN] I've been beaten.
Uh... I'm sorry...
Anyway, I hope you're hungry
'cause I bought
all of us supper!
[HARU'UE] Ooh, I'm starving!
[UIHARU] Mmm...
it smells delicious!
[HARU'UE] Yeah.
[SATEN] It doesn't
sound so good to me.
I like this stuff as much
as the next person...
But maybe you could've gotten
something cold instead?
[UIHARU] Really?
I actually think it
was a perfect choice...
Hot meals taste even
better in hot weather!
It's so good!
You've converted her.
Wow, these are
delicious, Haru'ue!
You think so?
Mm-hmm.
[UIHARU]
Oh, that's right... I forgot.
You've taken up cooking
lately, haven't you?
[SATEN] Oh, yeah?
Uh... Well...
I'm still learning.
[SATEN] Really?
As far as I'm concerned,
this is just about perfect!
You know my secret?
I add a little bit of soy sauce
and oyster sauce to the mix.
It's absolutely fantastic!
[UIHARU] Mmm-hmm...
I think it's exactly
what this meal needed!
[HARU'UE] It complements the
strawberries' sweetness, huh?
[UIHARU] It sure does!
I just realized
I used up the rice.
We don't have
any for tomorrow.
That's okay...
I'm sure we can
make do without it...
Although...
It would be nice
if we had a larger rice
cooker, wouldn't it?
You two do eat a
lot of the stuff, huh?
[HARU'UE] Do... Do we, really?
[UIHARU] Oh...
by the way, Saten...
I was wondering,
what did you mean
by what you said on
the phone earlier?
[SATEN] Huh?
About what?
[UIHARU] The stuff you were
saying about Misaka...
Something about
a mistaken identity?
[SATEN] Oh, that.
It was no big deal, really...
I just thought I saw somebody
who looked like her
that's all... Although...
Oh... never mind...
They say everybody
in the world
has a look-alike out
there somewhere.
I probably just
thought it was her
because she was wearing
a Tokiwadai Uniform.
[HARU'UE] Now that
you mention it...
Misaka and Shirai always seem
to be wearing their uniforms.
Tokiwadai requires
students to wear uniforms
at all times, even
outside of school.
That's pretty strict.
I can see why
you might think that...
but those uniforms
are constant proof
that they are
young ladies.
I have a hard time
imagining Misaka
wearing anything
but her uniform.
[HARU'UE] Oh, yeah?
Okay, but still...
It would be nice to see them
in street clothes
sometimes, you know?
Okay... well...
Alright! Here I go!
That was a close one...
She seemed bound and determined
to find someone
to punish tonight.
Still not back.
It's long past curfew now.
What are you doing out there?
Oh, Sissy!!
Oh, how improper of me.
I should be ashamed of myself!
But then... It has
been a really long time!
[KUROKO] Siiissssy!!
What the...
What was that?
I just got a creepy
chill down my spine.
Oh, well... It's gone now.
[KANAMIN] Transform!
Magical Powered Kanam--
[WATCHMAN 3-A] Huh?
Hey, what's going
on with this thing?
I just bought it...
Stupid piece of junk.
[KANAMIN] Okay! Are you ready!
[WATCHMAN 3-A] Oh, that did it.
[GUARD 3-A] Ugh! I lost again?
Hah! You get to
make the rounds now.
Yeah, I know...
Don't rub it in.
I still don't see why
we have to do rounds...
This place has
airtight security.
[GUARD 3-B] Yeah, yeah.
Quit your griping
already and get to it.
[GUARD 3-A] I'm goin'!
[MIKOTO] Security cameras,
infrared sensors,
and electronic locks.
They've got it all...
But, since everything
depends on electricity,
I should be fine.
[MIKOTO] I just have to
make sure to keep an eye out
for guards and any
other late-night staff.
[MIKOTO] Hmm?
That doesn't make sense...
No departments match
what I'm looking for.
Wait... There is a
section that has power
but is disconnected
from the network.
[MIKOTO] I was
wondering why they
only put surveillance
cameras in the hallways.
But I guess it's
because they don't want
other departments to know
what they're researching.
[MIKOTO] All right...
I think I'll start by
checking that section.
[GUARD 3-A] Who's there?
I-I'm not imagining
things am I?
Is someone there? Show yourself!
[MIKOTO] Uh-oh...
[MIKOTO] What do I do?
Worst case, I guess
I could always
shock him unconscious
and get myself out ...
But I'd really rather not leave
any trace that I was here.
[MIKOTO] Let me think...
[GUARD 3-A] What's this?
A security robot!
Of course it is...
There's no way anyone
could get in here.
Anything to report?
[FEMALE ROBOT VOICE 3-A]
No abnormalities
have been detected.
[MIKOTO] All right, good.
Keep it up.
[GUARD 3-A] No, huh?
Good enough for me.
I'll just skip the
rest of the patrol.
[GUARD 3-A] Huh?
The alarm? What the hell?
[MIKOTO] How come?
The sensors shouldn't
be able to pick me up!
Did I miss something?
[GUARD 3-A] Keep calm...
What does the manual say?
[MIKOTO] Well,
for now, at least...
[GUARD 3-A] Whoa!
What's wrong with you?
Hey! Come back!
[MIKOTO] What now?
Give up for tonight
and get out of here? No.
It doesn't appear
to be me they found...
and all this confusion
could be my chance...
All right... Keep going!
[GUARD 3-A] Hey!
What the hell is going on?
[GUARD 3-B] Sorry, man!
I totally forgot to tell you...
We have a visitor
coming in tonight.
[GUARD 3-A] What? It's too loud!
I can't hear you!
Just turn it off!
[GUARD 3-A] It finally
stopped. Who's there?!
[MIKOTO] Alright, let's
see what they're hiding.
What are those?
[MIKOTO] Incubators? Each big
enough to hold a person.
[GUARD 3-A] Can I help
you with something?
What are you doing?
You aren't lost, are you?
How exactly did
you get in here?
[GUARD 3-B] Oh...
Never mind about her.
I got word that she
would be coming tonight...
She's here to clear her
data for that project.
You know, that one
they've got frozen.
The idiot
watchman forgot
to give her a staff
card to get around.
You can take care
of this, right?
Just escort the nice young
lady here to the secret base.
Oh, so that's what this
is about. I see now.
[GUARD 3-B] Here...
You need to put this on.
[MIKOTO] There are traces
of quite a few erased files.
I should be able
to restore them.
[MIKOTO] Impossible!
[MIKOTO] "Project Radio Noise...
The goal for this project is to
resolve the genetic sequence
that gives rise to a Level 5,
allowing a Level 5 that is born
by chance to then be reproduced
with one hundred
percent certainty...
Further...
...for this project,
it has been decided...
...that Railgun... Misaka...
will serve as the model."
I mean it!
There's a story going around
about a project designed
to clone Level 5 espers.
Don't act like you
don't remember...
It was just a little while ago.
You were walking in
front of Seventh Mist...
[MIKOTO] It really exists.
A project to... to... clone me!
[DOCTOR 2-A]
To create a new Railgun,
we take a fertilized egg and use
a cell that has been extracted
from the original
Railgun's hair follicle.
[DOCTOR 2-A] Prior to
this, of course we obtained
the necessary genetic
sequence pattern sample.
We were then able to
successfully register
her DNA map in
Academy City's databank.
[DOCTOR 2-A] In order
to shorten the time
required to create
a test subject...
we determined that
it was necessary
to curtail the
developmental process...
both physically and emotionally.
[DOCTOR 2-A] To assist with
the development of the body,
a cocktail of ZID-02, RIZ-13,
and HEL-03 was administered...
and in roughly fourteen
days we had successfully
created a subject that was
physically identical to Railgun.
[DOCTOR 2-A] The development of
the mind and persona was dealt
with under the direction
of external staff member
Nunotaba Shinobu,
who used Testament to install
necessary basic
information within the brain.
Once the results
were confirmed...
everything was in order...
Project Radio Noise was set
to move on to the next phase:
The mass-production
of Railgun clones...
also known as Sisters.
[MIKOTO] This is it?
This is what they were after?
[DOCTOR 2-A] It's the
simplest thing in the world.
All you have to do is
give us your DNA map, okay?
[MIKOTO] Stupid girl.
Why did you say
yes to him? If only...
[DOCTOR 2-A] However...
As the project reached
its final stage...
projections were calculated
using Tree Diagram...
The results were not
what we expected.
[MIKOTO] They used Tree Diagram?
But... that's Academy City's
greatest supercomputer...
It hovers in orbit
above the Earth.
[DOCTOR 2-A] Regrettably,
the projections revealed
that the Sisters'
specs were less
than one percent of
the model Railgun's...
On average...
their ratings reached
only as high as Level 2...
And even the most
powerful individuals
did not exceed Level 3.
[MIKOTO] Okay, so...
They were only able to
make less powerful copies...
But even if they mass-produced
a lot of Level 2s...
[DOCTOR 2-A] Regardless
of genetic manipulation
or acquired development...
it was impossible to produce
a Level 5 from among the clones.
Thus...
having received Tree
Diagram's computed results...
and to minimize the losses
incurred by this project...
the committee ordered
all of the research
in progress to be
terminated immediately.
The project intended
to mass-produce
Railgun "Sisters" was halted
and is frozen in perpetuity.
Okay... I knew it!
Of course there aren't any
clones of me out there...
I'm guessing... word of this
ridiculous project leaked out
some how and the Academy City
rumor mill did the rest.
[MIKOTO] Whew... Even so,
it's a bit freaky...
Imagine, scientists using
my DNA map like that.
Well... whatever did
happen, at least it's all over.
Now... I'm heading
home to bed...
I wonder if Kuroko
managed to trick
the Head Resident and
keep me out of trouble.
[GUARD 3-A] Hey...
how much longer
is this procedure gonna take?
[MISAKA 9982] Total
deletion will be complete...
in forty-two point two
eight seconds, says Misaka,
reporting the time
with careful precision.
[MIKOTO] Of course there aren't
any clones of me out there!
Whew, that's a
weight of my chest!
[KUROKO] Sissy,
you really can't afford
to lose any weight
from your chest, you kn--
[MIKOTO] I don't
mean it like that!