[phone buttons being pushed]
[MIKOTO] Come on.
They're really late.
[MIKOTO] I wonder
what they're up to.
[MIKOTO] Well...
[SATEN] Like I said,
this group of creeps
is about to start
some trouble. Huh? Hey!
I was just minding
my own business!
[PUNK 1-A] Hey!
[PUNK 1-A] Whatcha
keep running away for?
[SATEN] Uh, oh!
[PUNK 1-B] Oh?
Hey, now. Wait up!
[PUNK 1-A] You're
not goin' anywhere.
Look, I need some help.
Just hurry, okay?
Okay, okay.
Just a little longer!
[UIHARU] I've pinpointed
the location of Saten's cell!
Good. Nicely done,
Uiharu... Now...
[UIHARU] Hold on
for just a second.
I have to get my armband!
[PUNK 1-A] Huh?
[PUNK 1-B] Oh?
[PUNK 1-C] Slow down, will ya?
[PUNK 1-D] Yeah,
just give up already!
[PUNK 1-A] Come on!
[thud]
[PUNK 1-B] There, you see?
Start actin' all hasty, and
you'll wind up with a boo-boo!
Um... I, uh...
Don't worry,
Judgment's on the case now!
You made it!
It's about time!
[KUROKO] You five are under
arrest for attempted assault.
[PUNK 1-E] I've never
seen anyone teleport before!
If all of us surround
her at the same time,
her ability won't matter.
Yeah? Try it.
That'll teach you a lesso--
[MIKOTO] Ah,
that's where you are!
I got tired of waiting for you.
What are you guys
doing here, anyway?
[PUNK 1-E] Who are you?
Uh... wai--
[PUNK 1-D] Are you friends
with these other little girls?
[PUNK 1-A] Since you were
the last one to the party,
why don't we get
started with you, huh?
Crazy, right?
So then she says--
[GIRL STUDENT 1-B]
Uh... what was that?
[GIRL STUDENT 1-A]
Lightning, I think.
[MIKOTO] Okay.
Can we get going now?
All the stores
are gonna be closed.
[UIHARU] But, you uh...
[SATEN] Alright, yeah...
Oh, and... Who were
those guys, anyway?
Zap people senseless first
and ask questions later, huh?
As usual...
[MIKOTO] Eh?
[KUROKO] Home to
2.3 million people...
Eighty percent of whom
are dedicated students...
All intently
focused on nurturing
and developing
their esper abilities...
This is Academy City.
[KUROKO] There are seven people
who have achieved
the status of Level 5.
Among them,
you are ranked third...
The famous "Railgun,"
Mikoto Misaka.
Sometimes
I don't think you really
understand who you are!
[MIKOTO] Huh?
What's that mean?
Ughhh! I really have
to explain it, don't I?
Sissy, your ability
is one people
will both aspire to and
be viciously jealous of.
Like yesterday,
when your rash attitude
made you those
punks' prime target.
People will always
fear you to some degree,
and if you're not careful,
you'll get hurt.
Hey!
Don't text while
I'm talking to you!
It's from Uiharu, she says
she just left the dorm...
I guess you should hurry
and finish up your work
if you want to hang
out with us sometime.
Ah... No fair.
You're always so mean, Sissy.
[SATEN] Man! Whew!
I'm telling you,
it was so amazing!
What would you call it, Uiharu?
An instant takedown?
One shot,
and she blasted 'em all!
That sounds
incredible.
Saten, you're never
going to change, are you?
Wandering around
those back alleys
always gets
you into trouble.
[SATEN] Yeah...
Ah! Well, look at that!
We're almost there!
Let's see, where
is that invitation?
Yep, changing
the subject, right on cue.
So, I'm curious...
Is there any reason
we're meeting up
at Misaka and Shirai's school
today instead of somewhere else?
[KONGO] Look who it is! Misaka!
[MIKOTO] Oh, hi Kongo, Wannai,
Awatsuki, how's it going!
Hi there,
it's so good to see you.
How have you been?
[MIKOTO] What's that?
Oh, yeah.
All of this stuff...
Materials for our
summer assignments.
It doesn't really feel
like much of a vacation
when they give us
this much work to do...
Seriously, couldn't
they take it easier?
Tell me about it...
Finding all the material is
almost an assignment in itself.
So, is that
why you're here today, too?
[MIKOTO] Oh uh...
I'm actually just killing time
until I meet up with someone...
I've already finished my work.
Eh?
No surprise there, huh?
Well...
If I had wanted to, I could
have finished in a day...
I just prefer to divide
the work up a bit.
Oh, whoops.
[MIKOTO] That is an awful lot
of books to carry by your self.
[KONGO] Oh, dear.
How could I be this clumsy?
[MIKOTO] Don't worry...
let me help you with that.
[AWATSUKI] Here, I've got a few.
[WANNAI] These, too.
[KONGO] Oh thank you.
[WANNAI] Look!
[WANNAI] It's Shokuho...
She's always surrounded
by her friends like that.
[AWATSUKI] So she's the
fifth-ranked Level 5, huh?
How glamorous!
It's no wonder they call
her the queen of the school.
[KONGO] I don't know.
[KONGO] I can't say
there is a single thing
I have ever found to
be likeable about her.
Did I just say that?
I didn't mean to!
I... It just slipped out!
I hope it didn't sound
like I was sniping!
I would never want to--
[MIKOTO] It's okay, we get it.
[KONGO] Well then, I guess
we should be on our way.
[WANNAI] Yeah, probably.
[AWATSUKI]
See you around, Misaka.
[MIKOTO] Yeah. Bye!
[SHOKUHO] Well, hello, Misaka!
[SHOKUHO] I said: hello, Misaka!
Sorry, no talking
allowed in the library.
[SHOKUHO] Oh, come on now!
But you were chatting up
a storm just a second ago!
You know,
I have to wonder...
Is it just that you don't
feel like talking to me?
[SHOKUHO] Oh, my!
What have we here?
Hey, stop!
You can't just go grabbing
someone's stuff without asking!
[SHOKUHO] Oh, no!
Now I'm scared!
What's the deal?
Oh, I bet I know!
Is it a present
for your boyfriend?
[MIKOTO] What's with you?
You tryin' to start a fight?
But why would
I want that?
Going one-on-one would be
so difficult. After all...
[SHOKUHO] It
would hardly be fair.
My tampering powers
don't seem to work on you.
[SHOKUHO] I admit,
it's a real pain...
that EM barrier of yours.
[MIKOTO] Listen, you!
[RINGLETS] Qu... Queen?
[GIRL STUDENT 1-C]
Are those two facing off?
That could be interesting!
[GIRL STUDENT 1-D] I wonder
what they're talking about.
[SHOKUHO] Like I said,
hardly fair,
but while going
one-on-one against you
would be difficult for me...
[SHOKUHO]
Going up against this many
of our finely trained
Tokiwadai students...
[SHOKUHO]
Well, that would be intense
even for you, wouldn't it?
[SHOKUHO] I'm just kidding.
[GIRL STUDENT 1-E]
I'm confused...
Why am I standing
around like this?
I don't remember
leaving my chair...
Oh, hey! Look everybody!
Misaka and Shokuho are talking!
[MIKOTO] I see
nothing's changed.
The way you abuse your
ability is still depraved.
And to think that
you're the city's
greatest mental ability user?
Misaki Shokuho...
Known as "Mental Out."
Honestly, don't be
such a bad sport!
This is just a warning...
I thought it only fair
to tell you to be careful
about the friends you're
making these days.
If you attempt to make any
moves into my territory,
let's just say,
it's going to cost you. 'Kay?
Shokuho...
I've got a question.
Well, go right ahead.
I'm listening.
[MIKOTO]
Are you sure
that you're really a
middle-school student?
[SHOKUHO]
That's a good question.
For the time being, at least,
that seems to be the case...
But with my tampering abilities,
just about anything
could happen, you know?
Hello, Sissy!
Uiharu and the others are here!
Come on, come on!
Let's go, let's go!
[MIKOTO] Quit teleporting
out of the blue like that!
[punching sound]
[SATEN] Hey, you guys!
[MIKOTO] Thanks for waiting!
[SATEN] Uh... Did something
happen to your head, Shirai?
A little over-zealous
affection, that's all.
I'm sorry for
having to drag you
all the way out here, Haru'ue.
Nuh-uh. I'm having
a great time, really...
And I've got some
delicious looking snacks
I brought along, too!
There are a lot
of great shops
throughout Academy City,
but they're especially
famous for them around here.
That's true...
Although I think you
enjoyed showing them off
to Haru'ue even more
than going to them.
Well, it's nice to share
something so fantastic.
I mean, the sheer
elegance of the area
is almost palpable,
don't you think?
I feel like a princess!
It's like the air itself
is scented with roses!
Oh... Is that why?
[UIHARU] Huh?
[SATEN] I was just
wondering why you went with
that particular
design today, that's all.
I don't get it.
What design are
you talking about--?
[UIHARU] B-b-but
how did you know?
[SATEN] Oh, it was earlier.
While you were
picking out your cake,
I took a quick little peek.
They were so pretty,
especially that rose pattern.
You, too, Haru'ue?
You are being corrupted!
[SATEN] Just so you know,
that kind of reaction is
what makes it so much fun!
[UIHARU] How else am
I supposed to reac--?
[MIKOTO] Now, now, guys!
Let's not waste our time
squabbling with
each other. Well?
Are you coming?
[RECEPTIONIST 1-A]
Here to visit someone?
[HARU'UE] Yes.
[RECEPTIONIST 1-A] All right.
Then please fill out all of the
required areas on this form.
[HARU'UE] Of course.
Wow, Haru'ue.
It looks like you've
got this routine down.
[YOMIKAWA] Hey, you guys.
[SATEN] Ah!
It's Yomikawa and Tesso!
Hey, what are
you guys up to today?
Oh! Visiting?
[UIHARU] Yes.
[KUROKO] If I may ask,
ma'am, why are you here?
Has there been an incident?
[YOMIKAWA] Oh, no.
There were some pseudo-radicals
we had to take care of...
One of them is
being treated here.
[YOMIKAWA] He's finally
ready to be discharged,
so we're relocating him to an
Antiskill-affiliated hospital,
where we can put the
squeeze on him good and hard.
C'mon...
take it easy, boss.
You were dealing
with pseudo-radicals?
Yeah... you know...
All sorts of problems
crop up in this town.
You never know
what it'll be next.
[EDASAKI] Yes?
Hey, Banri!
You mind if I come in?
No, of course not!
Is there something--?
Just thought
we would stop by!
[EDASAKI] You guys!
So delicious!
This is really wonderful, Erii!
[HARU'UE] Isn't it...?
Uiharu took me to the shop
where they make them earlier.
[SATEN] You two must have
eaten about twenty of them.
[EDASAKI] Amazing!
[MIKOTO] It seems like you're
doing a lot better, huh?
Mhmm. Slowly but surely...
The rehab can be pretty hard...
But having all you come see me
will motivate me even more!
So thank you!
[HARU'UE] If you can finish
your rehabilitation soon enough,
then we can go
to school together,
starting from second term!
Ahh...
So, uh...
Is... anybody else thirsty?
[UIHARU] Eh?
Thirsty?
Yes, I could use a drink...
Want to go see if we can
find some sodas somewhere?
Great idea!
Well, if you'll excuse us,
we'll step out for a bit.
[UIHARU] Wait, you mean...?
Everybody...?
Right...
Come along, now.
[UIHARU]
I still don't understand...
[SATEN] Misaka,
what's going o--?
[MIKOTO] Come on,
come on, hurry!
Okay! We'll be back in a jiff...
You guys have fun together!
[KUROKO]
A soda sure sounds good!
[MIKOTO] Why it
certainly does, Kuroko!
[HARU'UE and EDSAKI]
What in the world?
[rolling clattering wheels]
[SATEN] Okay. You want to tell
us what's really going on?
[MIKOTO] Soon enough.
Let's get sodas first, though.
[SATEN] So that's it?
Their physical therapy?
[UIHARU] Poor Edasaki.
She's working really hard, huh?
[KUROKO] Sissy... Hello! Sissy?
You zoned out.
Is something wrong?
Oh... mm-mm.
It's nothing.
[UIHARU and SATEN] You want
to plan... a surprise?
[MIKOTO] Yeah!
I don't feel like simply
handing over our gift
will have enough impact,
you know what I mean?
It's just...
Well, setting the mood
makes a big difference.
What would be great ...
Is if we could have
it come out of a cake!
Or put it at the bottom
of a champagne glass!
But neither of those
things would work.
[UIHARU and SATEN] How serious
is she about this?
But we could try...
Those things!
[UIHARU] You mean the...
[SATEN] ...flowers?
[MIKOTO] Yes! I call it...
"Operation: Oh, a
Bouquet of Flowers?
But Wait, What's This Inside?"
Okay...?
Uh... sound good?
Yes, sounds
like a great surprise.
Doesn't it? Alright,
I'll go buy them!
Do something!
What can I do?
You know how Sissy is--
[MIKOTO] No... Oh, no...
Oh, hey...
What is that?
Oh. That's
Misaka's bag.
[MIKOTO] Awww..
How could I be so idiotic?
It'll be okay.
There's nothing we
can do about it now.
It won't matter...
It's the thought
that counts, after all!
[MIKOTO] No, we can
still do it! Kuroko!
I'll need to use your ability!
You take me with you,
and we'll teleport our way in!
[KUROKO] Sissy, take it easy.
You're getting a
little over-excited...
[YOMIKAWA] Come on!
We gave them plenty of notice!
How much time does it take
to process a simple
patient transfer?
[TESSO] It'll be okay.
You know... Captain...
Wasn't there a guard outside--?
[YOMIKAWA] Hey!
Stop right there, you three!
What was that?
[alarm ringing]
[RADICAL 1-A] Come on move it!
[YOMIKAWA] Tesso!
[YOMIKAWA] Call below and
have them scramble... Hurry!
[TESSO] Uh... Right!
[YOMIKAWA] Damn.
[SATEN] Oh... it stopped.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER 1-A]
Please note that
while the emergency bell
has just rung, we cannot confirm
any fires in the building...
[KUROKO] Uiharu!
[UIHARU] Right!
Huh?
[MIKOTO] Kuroko?
We're going
to look into the situation,
just in case.
You and Saten
head back to Edasaki's room
without us and wait there.
Oh and one more thing...
No matter what
happens, please refrain
from repeating yesterday's
little scene, okay?
Uh... Yeah,
whatever you say.
[EDASAKI] This is kind of scary.
I wonder what's
going on out there.
I'll take a look and
see if I can find out.
Just be careful, okay?
[HARU'UE] Yeah.
Don't worry about me.
[RADICAL 1-B] Almost!
[RADICAL 1-A]
Hurry up and get it open!
[YOMIKAWA] Freeze!
It's no use
trying to escape.
There's an all-points
bulletin out
on you through all Academy City.
There's nowhere for you to--
[RADICAL 1-C] Shut up!
I mean it! Stop talking!
Captain, their hostage--!
[RADICAL 1-A]
Don't try anything stupid.
If you do, I'm gonna blow
her pretty little head off.
[KUROKO] The criminal scheduled
for transfer has escaped?
[ANTISKILL 1-C] Captain
Yomikawa is in pursuit...
Reinforcements are on their way.
Where we could really use your
help is preventing any panic.
[MIKOTO] Honestly!
I can't stand it
when Kuroko treats me
like I'm a stubborn child.
She's concerned
about you, that's all.
You do tend to be a bit
reckless at times, you know.
[SATEN] But, of course,
that's what we like about yo--
[YOMIKAWA] That's right.
Maintain your positions.
You heard me. I don't
want to provoke them...
They have a hos--
[SATEN] Is something the matter?
What are you doing here?
Why, has
something happened...?
It's the pseudo-radicals.
They've blocked our
access to the roof.
[YOMIKAWA] You should go
and find someplace safe.
[MIKOTO] Edasaki!
[SATEN] Why are you out of bed?
Looking for Erii...
She went to see
what was happening,
but she didn't come back.
Huh?
What happened to her?
I'm sorry to have
to tell you that...
Your friend's been
taken hostage.
Oh, no!
[MIKOTO] Calm down!
Thanks for helping me...
But they've still got Erii!
What about her?
She'll be okay.
All right...
Where are you going?
[SATEN] Whoa!
[EDASAKI] What are you...?
Come back! Hey, Misaka!
[HARU'UE] Nooo! Let me go!
[RADICAL 1-C] Be quiet!
And stop squirming...!
C'mon, we're ready
to go! Take off!
[RADICAL 1-A] What?
[HARU'UE] Misaka!
[MIKOTO] You've just
made a big mistake!
That's my friend
you're messing with!
[RADICAL 1-A]
This one has an ability...
All right!
Let's give it more power!
[PILOT 1-A] I am!
My controls aren't working!
[RADICAL 1-C] She wants her
damn friend back, does she?
Well, okay!
[RADICAL 1-C] Here you go!
I've got to catch her!
[MIKOTO] Thanks, Saten!
Can't... Hold... on...
[SATEN] Ow-ow-ow-ow-ow!
[MIKOTO] I've... I've got you...
[MIKOTO] Hang in there!
[KUROKO] Oh, honestly!
[HARU'UE] Huh?
[MIKOTO] Eh?
I'm okay.
[MIKOTO] Hey, good timing!
[KUROKO] I asked you not to.
But you just had to
interfere, didn't you?
[MIKOTO] Yeah, well...
I couldn't help it,
could I? I mean, if I--
No excuses!
[UIHARU] Thank goodness!
Are you okay?
You didn't get hurt
at all, did you?
[HARU'UE] No...
I'm fine, really.
[UIHARU] I'm so glad!
[HARU'UE] It was
pretty scary...
Ah!! The bag!
Eh?
Misaka's bag.
I had it with me...
Huh?
Kuroko...
[KUROKO] I guess we
don't have any choice.
[KUROKO] Whoa, Sissy! Can we
please think this through?
[RADICAL 1-B] Well, I guess
it turned out well enough.
[RADICAL 1-A] Yeah,
you guys saved my skin.
[RADICAL 1-A] What's that thing?
[RADICAL 1-C] Oh. I think
it belonged to that kid.
That girl
with the ability
was seriously
impressive though, huh?
So, she must be what people
call an "electromaster," right?
Yeah... And I'm pretty
sure that uniform
she had on was from Tokiwadai.
[RADICAL 1-A] Huh?
The super fancy school?
Just a second...
An electromaster
from Tokiwadai...
[MIKOTO] Hey, Kuroko...
[KUROKO] Yeah?
Uhhhh...
[MIKOTO] Thanks for this!
[KUROKO] Sissy--
I'll see you a
little later, then.
And you're welcome.
[RADICAL 1-B] I remember!
I've heard about
the electromaster
from Tokiwadai before!
The best electric shock
user in the whole city!
[RADICAL 1-B]
She's the Level 5--
[RADICAL 1-B
"Railgun"...!
Welcome back,
pseudo-radicals...
I hope you all had a nice trip.
There you have it...
Looks like she's still
the same old Misaka.
Yep, she certainly is.
But you have to admit...
That's what's
so great about her!
That felt awesome!
[UIHARU and SATEN]
Here! This is for you!
Huh? This?
Are you sure?
But that's Misaka's bag.
[SATEN] Never mind!
Just open it!
[EDASAKI] Oh...
[HARU'UE] Wow,
that's a school uniform!
If you keep working as
hard as you have been,
I know you'll be
wearing it soon!
[UIHARU] We went out
together yesterday and got it.
[SATEN] Are you surprised?
Mm-hmm!
You guys...!
Thank you-- Uh, Misaka?
Sorry,
I screwed it all up...!
I was working on
a better surprise,
but then there was
all that commotion,
and the stores closed, so this
is what we ended up with, and--
[EDASAKI] Please, Misaka!
I am really surprised!
And really, really happy!
Thank you!
[KAMIJO] Good grief.
[KAMIJO] There's never is a
dull moment. Not in this town.
[UIHARU] Misaka is still
as amazing as usual, huh?
[SATEN] Yep. All in all,
I'd say it was a rosy start...
I wonder what color
it will be next time?
[UIHARU] Please just
leave my skirt alone!