[MIKOTO breathes heavily]
[MIKOTO] The attacks
have stopped...
Somehow I don't think that
means they're letting me go...
Are they just waiting
for my next move?
[MUGINO hums]
Heh...
[MIKOTO] They seem
to have an esper
who can pinpoint
someone's location...
which means trying to
hide isn't an option.
Unfortunately...
If I do run into them...
I don't have much of
a fight left in me.
[MIKOTO] I saw this tape before.
The blonde girl used it.
So... what?
Does she have this stuff laid
out all over the facility?
That's a problem.
But maybe...
[MIKOTO] I can
make it her problem.
[MALE SUBORDINATE 10-A]
Good work in there.
We're meeting up
with Kinuhata...
at S Processor, okay?
The two of you wait here
until Mugino comes out.
[MALE SUBORDINATE 10-A]
Certainly.
[FRENDA] Phew!
I'm wiped out!
[TAKITSUBO] Frenda...
Huh?
We're leaving
because of me...
If it was just you,
you could've stayed.
Don't worry
about it, okay?
Mugino's fine handling
it on her own from here.
[FRENDA] And besides...
you were the one who was
really helping her, not me.
Speaking of which...
shouldn't you have reined your
power in a little bit sooner?
I was kind of starting
to get scared for you.
I'm okay.
As long as I'm here...
where I belong.
[FRENDA] Hm. Yeah, sure.
Sometimes it's good to
have more than one place
where you belong,
though, y'know?
--So then...
--Ah!
Ahhhh!
What's wrong?
My bombs...
I forgot to retrieve
them all when we left.
[footsteps]
Ah... you're finally here...
So you like being
fashionably late, huh?
[MUGINO] Frenda!
You took off without
cleaning up after yourself?
[MIKOTO] Where are
your little buddies?
[MUGINO] I sent them away.
Because I wanted to take
you on personally...
Railgun.
[MIKOTO] She figured it out...
Well, that's okay...
She wants to do this one-on-one?
That's fine by me.
Let's play, then!
[MUGINO] Ah...
Is that the plan?
You're using Frenda's bombs
to make up for the fact
that your power has
been diminished?
Of course, by doing so...
You're admitting you're too
weak to defeat me on your own.
You realize that, don't you?
[MIKOTO] Impressive.
She can deflect blast waves...
Which means...
[MUGINO] Heh.
Doing this again?
Wait--She could use the blast as
a diversion to get behind me...
Or maybe...
she'll ignore me entirely
and just charge inside.
However...
If I can shoot it down first...
[MUGINO] Hold on!
Did you rig the doll somehow?
With some metal inside, I can
control them magnetically.
Tch... You keep
getting more annoying.
[MIKOTO] If there's
just one of them,
I'm sure you have no
problem shooting it down.
Huh?
[MIKOTO] Heh.
But if this many dollies
come out to play?
[gasps]
[MIKOTO] As far as I can tell,
she can't lay down a curtain
of fire with her power.
That means there's
one thing to do...
[MUGINO] So this is how you
plan to incapacitate me?
"Silicon Burn."
I'm not afraid to shore up
my weaknesses with props
if it's necessary.
You would do well to respect
ITEM, you little brat!
[MUGINO] That imbecile Frenda
has made my job
more complicated.
But I think I can still handle
a middle schooler, thank you...
Honestly...
Third-ranked, my ass.
Why did you earn that title?
Because the research
applications of your ability
were so profitable?
And here I am,
ranked fourth.
All I have to do is
slaughter you right here.
That ought to prove
that you don't deserve
the rank you've been given.
[MIKOTO] The fourth-ranked
Level 5?
That makes her...
the esper known as Meltdowner.
All right, then.
Aw, look at that.
Only three left.
[MUGINO] Huh?
Hey, what's wrong?
Don't tell me you've run
out of moves already...
That would be so disappointing.
How pathetic.
You've been reduced
to a suicide attack?
Please.
Don't tell me you couldn't
even get the timing right?
What? Another?
She had one in reserve!
A shield! No...
At this range, there's
not enough time...
Damn you!
Yeah... Nice try!
Did you forget that quickly?
I can deflect those
electric shocks
that you rely so heavily upon.
You didn't actually think you
had won just now, did you?
This fight was over almost
as soon as it began...
Railgu--
Did you forget
that quickly?
I told you, I rigged
these things with metal.
They're lethal enough,
even without exploding.
[MIKOTO] Is this it?
Surely that'll be enough
to wipe it all out.
I would have
liked to have seen
every last inch of this
place burned to ashes...
but with the shape I'm in,
I would've gotten caught
in the blaze, too.
The problem now is
that other facility...
If there are espers
as strong as the ones
I was up against here...
I couldn't...
[MIKOTO gasps]
What the--?
How can she be gone?
She should still be knocked
senseless at this point!
[gasps]
[MUGINO] Hey, now...
this is no time to lie down.
We've still got some
unfinished business.
I'm gonna pay you back for this.
A trillion times over!
[MIKOTO groans]
[MUGINO] Aw, what's the matter?
Your tummy hurt?
Just get up already.
Unless you want to be turned
to charcoal where you lie.
[MUGINO] Well, well...
aren't we a spry little thing?
[MIKOTO] Lucky for me,
I haven't had anything to
eat in the last few days.
[MUGINO yells]
[MUGINO] Stop running away!
You're not so brave now that
you've run out of bombs,
are you?
You are a disgrace to your rank!
[MIKOTO] You know, I really
think I can live with that.
I've done what I
came here for...
Now I just need to get out.
With the electrical
systems shot...
I've got three escape routes.
There are the
emergency stairs...
No... not with her ability...
She could punch
through the staircase...
There isn't much room
to dodge her, either.
There's also the route
to the freight entrance...
Except... There's only
one way through...
If it's blocked in even
one place, I'll be trapped.
Which leaves...
[MUGINO laughs]
[MUGINO] Oh-h, you really
want this to end in a draw?
Just look at you
scuttling away...
Watching you flee like that,
you look more like a
cockroach than a spider.
In which case, I'll
squash you underfoot,
like the vermin you are.
[phone rings]
Yeah?
[KINUHATA] It's Kinuhata.
[MUGINO] What's up?
I'm at the best part of
the fight, so keep it short.
[KINUHATA] They've finished all
the preparations for relocation.
Takitsubo and Frenda have
just gotten here, too.
[MUGINO] Huh?
So knocking the ground out from
underneath her doesn't work...
I'll have to take a
more direct approach.
[KINUHATA] Mugino?
Yes... Yes...
I understand.
Huh? You want me to
tell her word-for-word?
Right,
got it... Bye.
She's given us
the all-clear.
We can go
ahead as planned.
Uh...
just wondering...
Yes?
[FRENDA] Did Mugino...
you know...
sound like she was
mad or anything?
What with... the
bomb stuff... and all?
Not really...
I'd say she sounded
more wound-up than mad.
Okay. Whew!
Although, there was a message
she wanted me to give you.
Hm?
What message?
"You may expect your punishment
to be both long and painful."
That's it.
[MIKOTO] Can I make
it out this way?
[MUGINO] Heh.
[MIKOTO grunts]
You just block, and
block, and block... Huh?
You're never going to beat
me by playing defense!
Do you think this kind
of child's play will get you
anywhere against the
underworld of Academy City?
Come on... at least make
this entertaining for me.
You're going to die,
no doubt about it.
But wouldn't you rather
go out with a bang?
[MIKOTO groans]
[MUGINO sighs]
[MUGINO] I get that
you're desperate...
but still, choosing
this place to run to,
you're practically begging
to be slaughtered.
The third-ranked Level 5?
More like a wet behind
the ears little girl!
Come on now, I'm giving you
one last chance to fight back;
Why not try out that little
Railgun you're so famous for?
This is the perfect opportunity.
[MIKOTO laughs]
[MUGINO] Huh? Hey, now...
It's no fun if you go crazy
before I get the chance
to torture you.
My Railgun?
After all of this...
I don't have enough power
to avoid one of your blasts,
much less use my Railgun.
You see...
that's why I gambled
and came this way.
Huh?
[MIKOTO] You know that
blond pal of yours?
She really gave me a hard time.
Blowing me away with her bombs.
Duping me. Kicking me...
And, of course...
Nearly plunging me to my death
by knocking out the floor.
See?
That got me thinking...
She was very thorough, setting
up traps all over this place...
So, I figured, the
chances were pretty good
that she rigged up some
explosives in this area.
Even as weak as I am...
I can make enough of
a spark to set this off.
Not too shabby for a wet
behind the ears little girl...
Don't you think?
[MUGINO gasps]
[MUGINO] Frenda!
Here... Grab on!
No way...
Did she just...?
[MUGINO] Hey, get down here!
[MIKOTO] That didn't kill her?
Man, she's a tough one!
She scampered away, huh?
My Meltdowner rays may
have slowed me up enough
to keep me alive...
but that landing still
leaves a lot to be desired.
Guess I'll need to
fine tune that a bit.
I'll get Takitsubo to track her
down again, and this time...
No, think...
She's a student at Tokiwadai
Middle School, isn't she? Yes...
So what could she have
been after here, then?
[MIKOTO] I accomplished
what I came here to do...
One more down... but
there's that last facility.
And my power is drained.
Damn...
[MALE RESEARCHER 10-A]
Come on, hurry !
Almost the entire
upstairs is in flames!
[MALE RESEARCHER 10-B] Huh?
But there's still
more stuff to move!
[MALE RESEARCHER 10-A]
Just forget about that junk!
Damn! I thought they
hired protection!
We were supposed to be
safe from these attacks!
Those underworld scum! Usele--
Hey... what the hell...?
[MALE RESEARCHER 10-C screams]
I've developed an
interest in the project
that Railgun came to this
facility to put a stop to.
Show me.
Uh... There's no
way I can do that!
I can't leak that
kind of information!
They'd have me elimina--
I can turn you into a bloody
pile of dismembered flesh
right here and now.
Or you can take your chances
living life on the run
from your former employers.
Which do you prefer?
[MUGINO laughs]
You can't be serious!
This is what they've got the
first-ranked Level 5 doing?
Trying to level up
by exterminating
twenty thousand cockroaches?
What can the Academy City
governors' board
possibly be thinking...?
Huh?
Oh... so that's it, huh?
And then, as for
those of us in ITEM...
This should be
very interesting...
I think I'd like to wait and
see how this drama plays out.
Why kill someone when
you can watch them suffer?
Right?
[MIKOTO] It's morning already?
[MIKOTO sighs]
Aww.
I must look like a mess.
[horns honk]
[MIKOTO] S Processor...
the institute for
neuroscience analysis.
The last facility associated
with the experiment.
Or, at least,
I think it is.
[MIKOTO] This is weird...
There's no traffic
going in or out.
Never mind security,
there isn't a single electrical
device at work here.
A trap?
[MIKOTO] It's totally
deserted, all right...
And it's not only that...
all of the data has been erased.
[MIKOTO] Have they given up?
Could yesterday's battle have
been enough to dissuade them?
I don't know.
Maybe they can't
sustain the project
with just one location...
That could be it.
I fought them...
and eventually,
they backed down.
Does that mean...
It's over?
Can it be?
That seems too good
to be true, somehow...
I guess that's not surprising,
given all the crazy things
that have been happening.
[cat meows]
That's all there is...
Farewell, Big Sister.
[MIKOTO yells]
[ACCELERATOR] Ah,
I understand now!
I was wondering what this was
since it wasn't on the schedule.
You...
You're the Original.
Hello there,
I'm Accelerator.
It's a pleasure.
[MIKOTO] Why?
You're breathing, aren't you?
You have life, don't you?
Isn't that enough?
What, not who...
Misaka is a product created
for this project...
Artificial bodies...
with artificial minds...
Laboratory animals,
with a unit price
of one hundred and
eighty thousand.
[MIKOTO] It's not like
I'll be able to pretend
that none of this
ever happened...
There's still
a lot for me to do.
A lot of things to
set straight... but...
The experiments...
are over.
And as for them...
[MIKOTO] The sisters...
they... they can finally live.
[SATEN] No matter what,
we're all here for you...
If your burden is ever too
heavy, just say the word, okay?
[MIKOTO] Well, guys...
I'm coming home now.
[KAMIJO] Come on!
[KAMIJO] What is
with this thing?
I gave it plenty of money.
I don't understand!
Is it out of order?
[MIKOTO] Heh.
[KAMIJO] Seriously?
[KAMIJO] Oh, you again, Zapper?
Wait a minute; there are two
of you. Is that your sister?
Ah, well, together we shall
embark upon a grand adventure--
[MIKOTO] No, we won't!
And why are you even
doing the preview, anyway?