[MIKOTO] So you're not going
to sell out your friends, huh?
[FRENDA] No... I would,
I just can't talk.
All right... I can't
hold that against you.
[MIKOTO gasps]
[NUNOTABA] Moving the Sisters
that are being adjusted
would normally come last.
With the abrupt
transfer of control
and the watch out for attackers,
they've ignored
internal security.
If I'm really
going to do this...
it's now or never.
[NUNOTABA] S Processor--
the institute for
practical neuroscience?
[MALE RESEARCHER 8-B] Yes...
I do apologize for
the short notice...
but I wonder if you could
come over here right away.
I'll fill you in on
the details later.
It's better if
we talk in person.
[typing sounds]
[NUNOTABA] It isn't
just one facility...
There are more than twenty.
Are you planning
to do this alone?
[MIKOTO] Yes, I am...
No one else needs
to get involved.
I'm the one who
made this mess.
I will be the one...
...to clean it up.
She was right about that... huh.
[thud]
[MUGINO] It got quiet
in here all of a sudden.
I was sure the Electromaster
had finished you off.
It looks like I got here
just in time, though...
Hello Frenda.
[FRENDA] Muginooooo!
It's so good to see you!
What were you thinking?
My orders were to
keep her confined...
You weren't supposed to begin
a real attack 'til we arrived.
Instead, you provoked her
and got yourself caught.
What a rookie move...
If you'd listened to me,
this wouldn't have happened...
but you were too damn eager.
[TAKITSUBO] It's all right.
I understand...
You just get like
that sometimes.
I know you can't help it.
[FRENDA] What do you
mean I get like that?
Nice try...
You're the one who's been
causing all this trouble, huh?
[MIKOTO] She blocked it...
No... she blew it apart.
Well, well...
[MIKOTO yells]
[MUGINO] That's a nifty
little trick you've got...
running around, sticking
to the walls like that.
Almost like you're
a spider, huh?
Who is she?
[MUGINO] Takitsubo...
[MUGINO] You know what to do.
Have you seen her yet?
No, nothing so far...
Where on earth could
she have disappeared to?
And why now?
We're way too busy for this.
I guess we should contact
those so-called cleaners,
just in case...
I hope this doesn't turn
into some kinda' big deal.
[MALE RESEARCHER 8-A]
Yeah, same here.
Here we are...
Time to get started.
[MIKOTO] She didn't dodge...
No... she's actually
turning away my shocks.
[MUGINO laughs]
[FRENDA] Woo... what a show!
[MIKOTO] That's weird.
I don't know why...
but I get the feeling
she's dangerous.
[MUGINO] What now?
Trying to blind us?
That's not gonna buy
you enough time to--
Tch...
She got away... Takitsubo?
Not a problem...
I've memorized the target's
AIM diffusion field.
[MIKOTO] The odds
aren't in my favor,
going up against three
of them like that.
Shutting this place
down comes first.
[MIKOTO grunts]
[MIKOTO] Oh, crap!
I've overused my ability...
It's failing.
What?
But I'm moving in a
completely random pattern...
How could she--?
A lucky guess?
[MIKOTO] No...
not a guess.
[TAKITSUBO] She's dodging us.
The target remains
whole and active.
[MUGINO] Did she jump
up onto the ceiling?
That arachnid move of
hers is annoying...
Takitsubo...
[TAKITSUBO] Mm.
Huh?
[FRENDA] Those two are
as impressive as ever.
First we have...
Academy City's
fourth-ranked Level 5...
"Meltdowner."
And then...
Takitsubo, with the
ability to track a target,
even to the other
side of the world...
"AIM Stalker."
ITEM 's got it made with this
awesome Level 5-Level 4 combo.
Is there anybody who
could escape from them?
Aww towd, not
vewy wikewy! Huh?
'ey! I can tawk!
Aaaaahhh...
Aaaah... Aaaah....
I don't know who our
mystery saboteur is...
but I do know she won't be
at large for much longer.
All we have to do
now is box her in
and make certain
she can't escape.
[typing sounds]
[NUNOTABA] She's in the process
of raiding that facility...
However, even if
she is successful...
it probably won't
stall the project.
The people behind it are
swimming in deep water...
deep and dark.
[NUNOTABA] This is all the
emotional data on the Sisters
that has been
gathered up to now...
I'm going to install it
directly into their brains.
I doubt they will develop
any genuine feelings
from a program this minor.
But it should create
a simulated response.
I don't know if this will
be enough to make them
suspend the project or not...
However... it should at least
show the girls another path
besides the hopeless one
they currently walk.
A better path.
Right now the Sisters accept
dying prematurely as inevitable.
Maybe this will inspire some
of them to lament their fate.
And when they do...
maybe there will be some
researchers who see them
as more than just
mindless guinea pigs...
Maybe...
As unlikely as it seems now...
the girls will cry and say they
don't want to fight anymore...
And maybe...
Just maybe, that will
touch someone's heart.
It's probably
a stupid plan.
More likely than not...
attempting this is pointless...
but...
What I felt in that
moment up on the roof...
I thought you might actually
be an authorized staff member,
so I checked with
the people upstairs...
but they said that this
place was ultra-off-limits...
at least until the data
relocation was complete.
[NUNOTABA groans]
[KINUHATA] Up to now,
they suspected the attacks
were the work of one person...
but it's best not to
dismiss the possibility
that the attacks are
really a diversion.
Therefore, it is
advisable to make sure
all vulnerabilities
are accounted for...
Security should be
ultra tight and on alert
for both external
and internal threats.
So here we are...
and as usual, Mugino's reasoning
was right on the money.
[MIKOTO] There!
Now!
Okay!
Here we go!
Arming the entire facility
was a totally brilliant plan!
[MIKOTO] Sure enough...
no matter where I go,
they know my every move.
There's no question...
They've got a psychometrist
or a clairvoyant...
One or the other...
Somebody on that team
can pinpoint my location.
An esper.
All right!
[MIKOTO] This sucks!
I'm at a serious
disadvantage here...
Although...
[KINUHATA] Please stop your
pointless struggling.
I've got you and now I'll
turn you over to my client.
Resistance is ultra futile.
[NUNOTABA groans]
[NUNOTABA]
Resistance is futile...
Maybe...
You might be right about that.
This project isn't
the only issue.
[NUNOTABA] Even supposing
I'm able to put a halt
to the project for good...
How can the cloned Sisters
possibly live normal lives?
Their empty, soulless eyes...
Their short lifespans...
Would that not be a crueler fate
than the experiment
has in store?
If so, better
to leave them be.
And yet...
She's borne the
weight of this...
All of it, on her own.
A fool... A noble fool.
Yes.
We are the ones who should
bear the burden of this sin.
For good or ill...
let them carve out
their own destinies.
[NUNOTABA grunts]
[MALE SUBORDINATE 9-B]
What the--?
Damn it!
It's no use.
The installation is complete.
They are all connected
by a brainwave link,
referred to as the
"Misaka Network."
The emotion program I
installed will be shared
by all the Sisters,
no matter where they are.
Now... nobody can stop it.
[alarm sounds]
What is that? What's happening?
[KINUHATA] I'm not entirely
sure what's going on.
But if I had to guess,
I'd say that whatever
your plan was, it failed.
[NUNOTABA] N-No way!
When did they install
that security ?
[MALE SUBORDINATE 9-A] 'Kay,
so, what do we do with her?
What else? We haul her upstairs.
Roger that.
Come on. Up!
Start walking, you.
[MALE SUBORDINATE 9-A yells]
[MALE SUBORDINATE 9-A groans]
Little brat.
[NUNOTABA] Don't move!
If possible, I'd rather
not have to fire this.
Now just back up...
Nice and slow.
I'm not going
to do that.
It's ultra-commendable of you
to shoot something
that's not vital...
Especially at this
stage of the game.
But unfortunately for you,
a simple pistol can't
penetrate my "Offense Armor."
[NUNOTABA yells]
Let's try this again.
Please carry her upstairs.
[MALE SUBORDINATE 9-B]
Uh... Right.
[MALE SUBORDINATE 9-A]
Ugh... Damn...
That capsule in there...
It looks like it's
got somebody inside.
You should stop
looking at things
that aren't related to the job.
You wouldn't want to be
deemed a security risk.
Right. Sorry.
Come on, now. Let's
make it snappy, okay?
[MALE SUBORDINATE 9-B]
So what do you think.
they'll do with her?
Dunno.
And I ultra don't care.
We're just doing
our jobs, here...
If she is of any use,
her life will most likely
be spared, at least.
Of course...
I'm guessing that life
will be ultra-crappy...
Sad, lonely, pathetic,
and stripped of everything
she cares about.
Target changed
location.
Twenty meters
to the northwest.
Ah! I just can't
seem to hit her, huh?
[MUGINO] I don't think it's
only the way she's moving...
What if she's able to detect my
attacks before they reach her?
The only espers who
could do that are...
[FRENDA] Are you okay?
Mm-Hmm.
Still standing.
[MUGINO] Takitsubo's
"AIM Stalker" is handy...
but it's a difficult
ability to use
as it has to be
intentionally overdriven...
It can't be sustained for long.
The target's not covering as
much ground as she was before.
She must be near her
breaking point by now.
It's not worth it to use
Takitsubo any longer.
If we've pushed her this far,
and she still hasn't left...
that more than likely means
she has some compelling reason
to make sure this
place is destroyed.
If we just wait for her
at her destination...
She's sure to show
up sooner or later.
She's a wounded beast:
exhausted, but more
unpredictable and
dangerous than ever...
It's risky, but if I keep
my cool dealing with her,
I shouldn't have too
much to worry about.
Still...
[MUGINO laughs]
It's so unlike me to
set up an ambush.
I'm rather excited!
Hey, Frenda!
Eh?
Come on, keep moving...
Mikoto Misaka...
You don't have time to
slack off right now...
Get back on your feet.
Geez, not again!
Fire, fire, fiiirrre!
[MUGINO] Bye-bye...
Spider girl.
[MIKOTO] Crap!
I can't dodge!
[MUGINO gasps]
[MIKOTO] I knew it...
I suspected as much when I saw
her repel one of my shocks.
In the most basic sense...
her ability is actually
the same variety as my own.
My Meltdowner should've
taken her out.
Is something the
matter, Mugino?
[MUGINO gasps]
[MUGINO chuckles]
So that's it...
I understand now.
[FRENDA] Whoa!
We've got a woman down!
Are... you... sure...
you're... okay,
Ta... kit... su... bo?
[MUGINO] Frenda...
take Takitsubo and
meet up with Kinuhata.
[FRENDA] Huh?
I'll be all right.
I can still help.
[MUGINO] This isn't just
for your sake, though.
Frenda, you took
some serious damage
from the spider girl, huh?
You're playing through
the pain, but it's bad.
[FRENDA] Uh...
[MUGINO] And when Takitsubo
reaches her limit...
she can't detect enemy
attacks anymore...
It's too difficult for me to
protect both of you on my own...
Especially against this girl.
Oh, of course...
I'm sorry we've been
holding you back.
[MUGINO] It's not like
I'm blaming you for it.
In fact, I think you've
done quite well...
Thanks to the two of you,
our opponent is on the ropes.
Let Kinuhata bring
up the rear...
You get some rest.
[TAKITSUBO] Mugino...
She was...
...kind of nice to us!
[MUGINO] Yes...
I'd hate for anyone to
say that I defeated her
because the numbers
were in my favor.
Academy City's
third-ranked Level 5...
Heh, heh...
The Tokiwadai...
...Railgun!
[MUGINO] Railgun of Tokiwadai...
why won't you face me head on?
[MIKOTO] While I'm here doing
this, they're out there dying!
Stay the hell out of my way!