[gunfire and explosions]
[clattering]
[FRENDA] So, all told.
What was our assignment
this time, anyway?
[KINUHATA] Yeah.
That's an ultra-good question.
Well, we were supposed
to come down here
and put a stop to an arms deal.
Of course, we get here, and
there's no arms deal in sight
and instead, one of these
toys starts attacking us.
You look funny.
What's the deal?
I dunno.
I have this feeling.
[clattering]
[FRENDA] Mugino!
Thank you for that.
Ultra happy to
be of service.
[FRENDA] Geez, don't startle
me like that, okay?
Thank you, Mugin--
[MUGINO] Tch.
[ARITOMI] I'd say those are
adequate enough results
for a field test.
We are steadily gathering
data for the real thing-
[KOSAKO] Aritomi.
Huh?
[sirens in distance]
[UIHARU] Oh, man.
I've got a tummy ache!
That was an exotic stew.
I've never eaten turtle before.
[UIHARU] The beef Misaka
brought was amazing, too.
And because of that,
I am now way too full!
Maybe we should find
some medicine for you.
[UIHARU groans]
Oh, by the way.
Did that talk you had with
your teacher go all right?
[HARU'UE] Yeah. It did.
I think we found
the perfect spot.
[UIHARU] You did, huh?
Then it's almost time.
[HARU'UE] Mm.
[both chuckle]
[SATEN] So?
Who's that you
were talking to?
[MIKOTO] Hm?
[SATEN] That fine
young man back there.
Oh, just
somebody I know.
So evasive!
Ooh! It was cookie
boy, wasn't it?
No, it wasn't!
I swear, that's the last
time I bake anything!
[SATEN] Okay, fine,
if that wasn't him,
who is the cookie guy?
[MIKOTO] I-I'm telling you he-
[KUROKO] Hello, Sissy.
You're getting here late.
What have you been up to?
Ooh, I'll
tell you-
[MIKOTO] Ah! Hey,
look, the elevator's here!
Come on, come on, let's go!
Quickly now, everybody! Heh.
[SATEN] There she
goes! So adorable!
[MIKOTO] Congratulations,
Edasaki.
[EDASAKI] Huh?
We hear you're being
discharged. Right?
Heh, yeah I am!
I owe it all to you guys.
Having that uniform waiting
for me really inspired me
to work hard and finish
my rehabilitation
before summer was over!
[MIKOTO] So, is everything set
for when you get out of here?
[EDASAKI] Mm-Hmm.
[UIHARU] Actually, Edasaki is
going to be living with Haru'ue.
Oh. Really?
Yep.
[EDASAKI] Well, you know.
I've been in a home for so long.
[UIHARU] Suddenly living on
her own would be really hard.
I talked to my teachers
about the situation,
and they agreed that Banri
and I could share a place.
Oh, that's nice.
So then, you'll be
moving again, huh?
We'd be happy to come by
and help you guys out.
[HARU'UE] That's okay,
thanks though.
Uiharu and I already
took care of it.
[SATEN] Seriously?
[UIHARU] Yep.
We made a few calls and got the
movers lined up for tomorrow.
[MIKOTO] Well, that was quick.
[KUROKO] You could
have at least asked us.
[UIHARU] Haru'ue said
there's still some stuff
she and Edasaki needed
to talk about.
[MIKOTO] Oh, okay.
Really, Uiharu, if you'd
just said something,
we totally would have
helped out on moving day.
Don't worry about it.
It's honestly not
that big a deal.
Though the whole
place is overflowing
with cardboard
boxes right now.
Yeah, I can imagine.
I remember what it was like when
Haru'ue first moved in with you.
There's even more now
than there was then.
Which is strange since she
didn't actually live there
for that long.
[UIHARU] Oh, I forgot!
[GROUP] Huh?
We have to go.
It's about time,
isn't it, Shirai?
Oh. Yeah,
you're right. It is.
What? You guys have some
kinda' Judgment work to do?
Yeah. We've been
asked to do security
for the upcoming
Academic Reach Assembly.
Today's the
preliminary inspection.
Oh.
[SATEN] Sorry.
[GROUP] Hm?
I don't really understand
what a school assembly
would need security for.
[MIKOTO] Uh?
Oh! I can see why
you were confused.
Shirai wasn't using
its full name,
the Academy City
Research Forum Assembly.
It's called "Academic
Reach" for short.
[KUROKO] Academy City's
students are dedicated
to research and study.
Those with outstanding
grades are given a setting
in which they can share
their work with others.
That's what the Academy City
Research Forum Assembly is.
Qualification for the forum
is based on the strength
of students' academic work,
rather than the strength
of their abilities.
Oh, I see.
Well, that sounds kinda fun.
It's like a festival
for smart people.
Maybe not quite as
fun as a festival.
There are professional
quality presentations,
great lectures, and all
sorts of other stuff.
Yeah?
I don't really get it,
but I guess it sounds cool.
I wonder why they picked this
year to start doing this thing.
[GROUP] Eh--
Uh, Saten.
They actually do it every year.
[SATEN] Seriously?
[AWATSUKI] Wow!
You mean you're really
going to help us?
[WANNAI] It's a request from
a member of the swim club.
Since you're not in the club,
you certainly don't have to-
Oh, nonsense. Don't be silly.
Club member or not,
you two are my friends,
so I would be happy
to assist you.
Besides, I'm still relatively
new to the area, you know.
So I've never seen an Academic
Reach Assembly before.
[WOMAN 18-A yells]
[KONGO] This would be
a perfect opportu--
[WANNAI] Kongo!
Are you all right?
You ruffian!
You dare to assault
Mitsuko Kongo?
[WOMAN 18-A] Somebody,
please help!
That man took my bag!
[KONGO gasps]
[THIEF 18-A yells]
[crashing sound]
It is the height of stupidity
to perpetrate such
a brazen theft
in broad daylight
on a busy street!
You're a moron
and a criminal.
And I will not allow you to
roam the streets any longer.
You're done.
Mitsuko Kongo has spoken!
[WANNAI] Kongo always
comes through.
She is
so amazing!
[KONGO] Now to dispose of him.
Wannai, there is an Antiskill
station just around the corner.
Would you please alert them?
Yes, right away!
[AWATSUKI chuckles]
A good day's work.
[ARITOMI] Excuse me.
Do you have a moment?
I saw this little
scene play out.
Don't you think you
went a bit too far?
[KONGO] What?
It doesn't matter
whether this man
is a purse-snatching
miscreant or not.
I don't think you should
be using your ability
so recklessly.
Oh? And who are you to say--
There were a number of ways
that you could
have handled this.
And any one of them
would have been better.
Like you told
those other girls.
There's an Antiskill booth
not far away from here,
and don't forget
the security cameras.
What exactly
are you--
If I may continue.
Did you not even stop
for a moment to think
how much danger you were
exposing everybody here to?
Huh?
[ARITOMI] You didn't
notice this, did you?
Fortunately for us, you were
able to incapacitate him
with one shot this time.
Can you begin to
imagine the results
if you had failed to do so?
The thief would
have been furious.
He may even have taken
a woman or child hostage.
[MALE ONLOOKER 18-A] Ya' know,
he's right about that!
[MALE ONLOOKER 18-B] That
would've been awful.
[MALE ONLOOKER 18-C] Those
abilities aren't foolproof.
[ARITOMI] You seem to be
quite confident of yourself
and your power.
But an ability isn't
always the answer.
I didn't mean to.
[WANNAI] Hold on a minute!
I don't know who you
are or why you're here.
But there's no reason
to be so hard on her.
Whether you
approve or not,
the fact remains that she did
safely secure the criminal.
[KONGO] Ladies, you're back.
[WANNAI] I'm really
sorry we took so long.
The Antiskill officers are
on their way down here now.
Oh. That's good,
thank you.
He's gone.
I wonder where he
could've run off to.
What a strange man.
[door opens]
[KUROKO] Hey Sissy, I'm home.
[MIKOTO] Hey.
You were gone for a while.
[KUROKO] Ugh...
What's up?
You seem exhausted.
[KUROKO] The preliminary
Reach inspection.
I knew the forum was
being held across
several different
universities, but still.
I didn't expect to
have to walk that much.
I think my feet
might fall off.
Judgment's a pretty
tough gig, huh?
[KUROKO weakly] Mm-hmm.
[MIKOTO] Uiharu was
with you, right?
How is she doing?
[KUROKO] The same
as she always is.
She carried out her
duties admirably.
[MIKOTO] That's good.
With the move and everything.
Moving can be hard, you know.
I mean, remember how
big of a mess it was
when you first moved in here?
Are you really bringing up
that whole thing again?
The statute of limitations.
[MIKOTO chuckles]
What's up, Sissy?
Thinking about
old times.
Pretty crazy, huh?
Ah!
Well... yeah.
Hmm... I know!
Since you're so exhausted,
I could give you a massage.
[MIKOTO echoing] I could
give you a massage.
I could give you a massage.
Kuroko?
[KUROKO yells]
Whoa!
What the...
Well, I just.
I thought I would
take a shower first.
Right.
[SATEN] Ui-ha-ru!
[UIHARU yells]
C'mon, Saten, is that
absolutely necessary?
'Kay, I'm sorry.
[UIHARU] Were you waiting
for me or something?
[SATEN] What? Oh, no.
I was just in the area, so.
I really am fine.
I promise.
Haru'ue and I have been
discussing the situation
for a while now.
And we both agreed that when
Edasaki got out of the hospital,
it would be best if the two
of them lived together.
Aw, really?
Really. Of course,
I'd be lying if I said
I wasn't going
to miss Haru'ue.
Still. I think this is good.
They're close.
And they've been through
so much together.
Besides, it's not like she's
moving far away or anything.
And once the
new term starts,
we'll still see each other
at school every day.
Oh, yeah. You will, huh?
Good, then I guess I can stop
worrying about you so much.
[UIHARU] Yeah. Now please
let go of my hair!
[SATEN] You're gonna
be all right.
[UIHARU chuckles]
[UIHARU] Yes.
[EDASAKI] Well, here I am!
So, how is it?
Perfect! It's totally cute!
It looks
fantastic on you!
Aw, thank you!
Oh! So before, when
you guys stayed behind
at the hospital to talk, this
is what you were talking about.
[HARU'UE] Mm-Hmm.
I couldn't wait to...
[KUROKO whispering]
Go on, Sissy, you're up.
[MIKOTO] Oh, right.
Here goes!
For you, Edasaki.
To say "congratulations."
--Thank you!
--[GROUP] Congratulations!
Thanks so much!
So, are we ready
to get going?
[EDASAKI] Huh?
Where to?
A little
celebration for you!
The place we reserved a
table at has amazing cakes!
[phone rings]
We get cake! That
would be wonderful!
Hello, yes,
this is Shirai.
Oh, hi Konori.
Eh? Traffic
signal trouble?
Huh? Hey don't
give me that look!
I didn't do it!
[car horns honking]
[KONORI] The signals in this
area are down across the board.
I'm sorry to ask,
but I need you now.
[KUROKO] Yes. Right.
On my way as we speak.
Um. Uiharu's
needed, too?
Of course I--
No. You can't go.
Edasaki is just getting
released from the hospital.
I can cover this.
You stay here-
[UIHARU] What are
you talking about?
I am a member of Judgment.
Please, start without us.
We'll be there as soon
as we're done with this.
We'll see you later, then.
Good luck with
those stoplights.
[UIHARU] Thanks.
C'mon, let's go, Shirai.
Huh? Oh, right.
Well, then.
[EDASAKI gasps] They're gone!
[MIKOTO chuckles]
Okay. We should get going, too.
[MIKOTO] It's not exactly how
we planned it, but once again.
[GROUP]
Congratulations, Edasaki!
Thank you so much!
That's delicious!
Isn't it?
Uiharu said if we
were celebrating,
it absolutely
had to be here,
and she handled everything from
the reservations to the cake!
Uiharu really is
something else, isn't she?
[SATEN] Huh?
[EDASAKI]
Before I was discharged,
she came to help me get moved
and take care of
my school admission.
Didn't she?
[HARU'UE] Hm.
[SATEN] Yeah?
That was nice of her.
Very nice!
I wonder if all Judgment
officers are kind like her.
[MIKOTO] I'm glad we let
Uiharu pick this place.
It's like she knew how
much you would enjoy it.
[SATEN] I know, right?
[EDASAKI] This might be
the best cake I've ever had!
[SATEN] Is that the key
to your new place?
[HARU'UE] Mm-Hm.
Uiharu has been pretty
helpful with all this, huh?
[HARU'UE] She was like this
when it was my turn, too.
You mean, when the two of
you were moving in together?
Yeah, that sounds like her.
Always the enthusiastic helper.
[HARU'UE] I was so nervous then,
but Uiharu was there for me.
So now, it's my turn to help
somebody else who needs it.
I'll be there to help
Banri however I can,
just like Uiharu
was there for me.
Of course.
[both giggle]
[SATEN] Well, I just hope
she gets here soon.
[HARU'UE] I'm sure she's
giving it her all at work,
even as we speak.
[SATEN] Yeah, wearing
an ugly helmet
and directing traffic or
something, probably.
She could stand to ease up
at a time like this, though.
[HARU'UE] But not being able
to is what makes her, her.
[SATEN] You're right.
[EDASAKI] Maybe I should
become a member of Judgment.
[MIKOTO] Huh?
Where'd that idea come from?
It's just a thought.
If I did join, maybe I
would be more like Uiharu.
[MIKOTO] Heh.
You know, Edasaki.
I don't actually think that
she was being nice to you
just because she's
a member of Judgment.
Really? Then why?
Because she's your
friend. Silly.
[EDASAKI chuckles]
Yeah, you're right.
[MIKOTO] Ah, free
from the hospital!
[EDASAKI] Huh?
Oh, nothing.
I know somebody else who
was in there recently.
I was just wondering
what it would've been like
for us to celebrate together
like this when they got out.
You know?
[EDASAKI] Uhh...
[MIKOTO] Oh, sorry!
Now I'm being silly.
Please forget I said
anything! Really!
Well, whoever your friend is,
I hope they're feeling
a lot better.
Yeah. So do I.
[KONORI] Good work today.
Sorry I had to call you
out of the blue like that.
[KUROKO] Stoplight trouble,
of all things.
I was kinda' surprised.
There was some irregularity
in the electrical system.
But in Academy City?
It's unusual for things like
that to happen here, you know.
[UIHARU] There you are!
Oh, Uiharu,
that's right.
Well, if we're all done
here, we'll have to be--
Geez, what's
gotten into you?
Hurry, there's someplace
I need you to take me!
Yes. Calm down, I
know. Let's head ba--
No, not there!
I want you to take us
somewhere else before that.
Huh?
[MIKOTO] Umm...
What do you think?
Should we call them?
[SATEN] That might
be a good idea.
Uh... Yeah. I'm calling
them right now.
[UIHARU] Hey, sorry to...
keep you waiting.
Uh, me too.
[MIKOTO] Well,
at least you made it!
[SATEN] Geez, it took
you long enough.
Edasaki had to stop by the
hospital, so she already left.
Oh! Really? She did?
Shoot! I'm so sorry!
Don't worry about it.
She wanted me to
tell you thanks.
She had fun.
[UIHARU] Um, here.
These are for you
and Edasaki to share.
[HARU'UE] Huh?
Are those
little cakes?
[SATEN] Oh, the
thing is, Uiharu.
We actually already had
cake while you were gone.
[UIHARU] Well. yes,
I know that, but--
[SATEN] Having cake
after cake is sorta...
[UIHARU] No, you don't understa-
[KUROKO] See, it's like
I was trying to tell you-
[MIKOTO] Hey, now. It's really
the thought that coun--
Listen, you guys-
[HARU'UE] They look just
like they did before!
[GROUP] Huh?
[HARU'UE] You see, these
are the same little cakes
Uiharu bought me once
when I was nervous to
make me feel better.
They were
so delicious.
[UIHARU] What's the
matter, Haru'ue?
[HARU'UE] I'm hopeless!
I promised myself
I wouldn't cry today!
Um, well.
[HARU'UE] Uiharu.
I want to be like you.
So kind and considerate.
I want to help Banri
like you helped me.
[HARU'UE sobs]
[UIHARU] It'll be all right.
You'll do fine, Haru'ue.
I know it. You can do this.
Thank you so much!
[HARU'UE sobs]
Now, now, calm down.
It's okay.
There's no reason to cry.
I mean...
[UIHARU sobs]
And now there bawling
like little babies.
Whatcha gonna
do, huh?
It's so
sweet.
[MIKOTO chuckles]
[UIHARU] Hey, you know.
I wonder how much of a help
I actually was to Haru'ue.
Oh, don't be silly.
I think it's obvious that
you were a big help.
[UIHARU] Ow!
And not just to
Haru'ue, either.
Edasaki, too.
I think you made a real
difference in both their lives.
Thanks, Misaka.
Yeah, and you know, Sissy,
you make a real
difference in my li--Ahh!
[MIKOTO] Well, let's head home!
[SATEN] Oh, I forgot.
I know of a shortcut up ahead.
[MIKOTO] Um, are you sure
this is the right way?
Don't worry, okay?
We just cut through here,
and we'll be on the
main road in no time.
[MIKOTO] How many of these
shortcuts do you know about?
[KUROKO] What is it?
Is something wrong, Sissy?
What is that
down there?
[GROUP] Huh?
[KUROKO] Hey, that looks like...
...a little girl?
[MIKOTO] Huh?
[SATEN] Wow!
She's adorable!
Don't just stand
there staring at her!
[MIKOTO] Hey, hold up, Kuroko!
[UIHARU] She's opening her eyes.
Hi, sleepy head.
Why were you taking
a nap in the park?
If you tell us your name,
maybe we can help you.
Okay. Well,
how old are you?
Can you tell us
where you live?
Your school?
Your homeroom teacher's
name, maybe?
This doesn't seem
to be working.
Maybe she speaks a
different language?
You guys are doing
it wrong. Let me try.
When you're trying to
talk to a little girl,
you need to get down to
her eye level, like this.
Oh! That looks like
some tasty candy!
Let's make a trade, okay?
My name is Ruiko.
Now it's your turn.
Do you think you can
tell me your name?
I'm Febri.
[GROUP] Aww...
[SATEN] That's a
very pretty name!
Okay, then, Febri.
What else can you tell us?
Anything goes. You can
just pick something.
[FEBRI] Mikoto Misaka.
[GROUP] Huh?
[MIKOTO] Huh? What?
[ARITOMI] The experiment
was successful.
It was conducted to obtain data
regarding the
fourth-ranked Level 5,
and the numbers came out
more or less as predicted.
We ran into some unexpected
complications on site,
but those ought to be
resolved before much longer.
Everything is ready now.
The time has come to
demonstrate our power.
We'll show this town of esper
supremacists what we can do.
Those in favor of moving to
the next phase of the project,
please raise your hands.
[MIKOTO] I want to know what the
story is with this Febri girl.
Why does she know my name?
[UIHARU] Maybe she's lost.
[SATEN] What should we do?
[KUROKO] We will decide at
the Academic Reach Assembly.
[MIKOTO, UIHARU, and SATEN]
The Reach Assembly?