Who do you think you are?
Trying to assault me...?
You should know that
I am Mitsuko Kongo
of Tokiwadai Middle School.
"Assault" you?
One of Tokiwadai's darlings
would bust out the fancy words
instead of talking normal...
Huh?
How sad that you have such a
feeble grasp of the language...
Well, I'll be happy to
teach you a thing or two.
Aw, what's wrong...?
Does the little girl
have a headache?
What's happening?
-Hurts, doesn't it?
-Who are you?
Hey, now...
picking on young
girls, are we?
Well, we can't have that.
Who's... there...?
Maybe this marks the end
of the recent outbreak
of esper hunts
conducted by Skill Out.
Though that could be
too much to hope for.
Going after somebody like
Kongo was a gutsy move...
No matter how many
of them ganged up,
Level Zeroes wouldn't be a
match for a Level Four esper...
I guess they learned that
lesson the hard way...
Unless they're stupider
than they look, of course.
That isn't how
it happened.
It's all in
Kongo's report...
For some reason, she wasn't able
to use her esper ability...
Fortunately, some stranger
appeared and helped her.
Tamezo?
What? Is something wrong?
Huh...? Sorry...
Let's see...
Maybe Uiharu's questioning
will produce something.
Yes.
And after that, I don't
know what happened.
I just passed out.
And when you
came to again,
your attackers were
all on the ground?
Yeah.
Can you remember anything
else about what happened?
Well, maybe...
I don't know what
they're called, exactly...
It's a particular
kind of garment...
Something you would
generally see on men
who ride motorcycles
and the like.
A leather jacket?
Yes...! That's what it was!
A black leather jacket...!
And the gentleman
who was carrying it
had what looked like a
large black spider tattooed
on his back.
Are you sure
you're okay...?
You seem sort of
distracted...
If there's something
wrong, just tell me.
Oh, no...
it's nothing.
So, we have a man
with a leather jacket
and a black spider tattoo...
Could he be the one who
beat all these punks up?
[Music]
Big Spider?
That's the name
of the group
that's been carrying out
all these esper hunts?
Who are they, exactly?
Big Spider has always been a
fairly well--known organization,
even within the
members of Skill Out.
At one time, they had
their own sense of pride...
They knew where
the line was.
But they've degenerated
into little more than
a band of outlaws.
I know you claim
that these people
had some sense of pride...
But they sound
like a bitter mob,
sulking at the
rest of the world.
Maybe... but still...
Despite all the
indignation they felt...
and the anger...
They maintained a sort
of admiration for espers.
It sounds like you really
know a lot about them.
Yeah... I guess so.
You've done your research!
Somebody attacked Kongo?
Calm down now...
you should just
take it easy, Sissy.
Those guys are disgusting!
Ganging up and attacking
a girl like that! Come on!
You, uh... seem pretty worked
up about this, Misaka.
I just don't have any
patience for people
who would rather
hurt others
instead of facing
their own reality.
If you want my opinion,
it's both futile and cruel.
It's beginning to sound like
you're talking about me now.
What...? You're nothing
like that, Saten.
Yes, she's right...
You're not like them...
Skill Out only act when
they can do so as a gang.
It takes a lot more guts
to act on your own,
like you did when you were
so desperate to level up.
Shirai... I know
you mean well,
but I don't think
you're helping here.
I thought that Skill Out
was made up of a bunch
of Level Zero runaways...
Why would they be going
after espers like this?
It's a numbers game...
No matter how
brilliant an esper is,
it'll still be difficult for him
or her to face a large group.
What's worse...
We've received information
that this Big Spider
organization
has gotten its hands
on illegal weapons
using black
market channels.
I think maybe these guys
would feel differently
after tangling with me.
Now, now, Sissy.
You know if you want
somebody to tangle with,
you don't have to look
any further than right here.
That's not what I meant!
You are a seriously disturbed
person, do you know that?
So... How'd it all go down?
Those Skill Out people
who attacked Kongo
were caught, right?
But who was responsible?
Apparently some
mystery man showed up
and took them all out.
Wow...! A mysterious
champion of justice!
Champion? Please!
Members of Judgment
and Antiskill
are the only people who should
be involved in fighting crime.
This person is nothing
more than a vigilante!
It's not you.
It can't be you, right?
-Kurozuma...
-Yeah?
Here's the thing...
The guy who took
out Tamezo...
You think you
can lie to me?
I know what I heard.
No way... we all
know he's dead...
He didn't suddenly
come back to life.
Hey, listen up!
Tell me what my name is!
Wataru Kurozuma!
That's right...
I am Kurozuma...
The rightful head
of Big Spider.
You haven't forgotten,
have you?
You know that look
as well as I do...
The taunting look
of the espers.
We're all here to take
'em down a notch or two.
We're gonna show
'em who we are.
They'll know Skill
Out means business!
Yeah!
It's Big Spider again?
Yes... this is the
third time this week.
They seem to be kicking their
campaign into high gear.
We'll have to take the wind
out of their sails, then.
Not "we," Sissy...
You know full well that
I don't approve of you
getting involved in
our cases like this.
From what I can tell, it
was about two years ago
that Big Spider began
expanding their organization.
Around that time, they
started carrying weapons
and got involved in a lot
of criminal activities.
That makes sense...
They were armed,
so they must've thought
they could do anything...
but the question remains:
how were they able to
smuggle those weapons
into Academy City?
The distribution of goods
is strictly monitored...
So, in theory,
illegal items should
be easy enough to spot,
shouldn't they?
People who deal in such
things must have their ways.
They probably aren't
working alone.
It's likely they have
others setting up routes.
You think they
have backing?
Interesting...
At any rate, it's an
idea worth looking into.
Um...
I've found something else...
It's the name of the
person who leads Big Spider.
Wataru Kurozuma...
By all accounts,
he's a very vicious man.
He doesn't seem
to have any qualms
about betraying
his followers...
Reports say that if
somebody leaves the group,
he won't hesitate to shoot
the so--called
traitor in the back.
So, basically this is
one of the biggest jerks
we've dealt with.
Oh... speaking of backs...
apparently this guy has a
tattoo of a spider on his.
A spider?
Really...? Didn't the
man who rescued Kongo
have a spider tattoo?
So he's the infamous
Wataru Kurozuma...?
But that doesn't
make any sense.
Maybe he wasn't
trying to rescue her,
but fighting a
faction of the gang...
According to Uiharu,
loyalty's not his strong suit.
You might be right.
It's at least something
we should consider.
According to my
information,
Kurozuma's base of operations
is in an area of School District
Ten known as "Strange."
Are we going?
Technically, it's outside
of our jurisdiction...
but since the incident
we're investigating
happened in District Seven,
I think we can make it stick.
Are you coming, Konori?
Sorry... I wish I could go.
But I absolutely have to
get these reports done today.
Huh?
Well... let's get going.
You know you shouldn't
get involved!
I'm pinch--hitting for Konori.
Now, come on.
Hold on, Sissy.
Did you hear what I said...?
Oh, all right...
I can never say no to you!
And off they go.
Always eager.
Here we are.
The headquarters
for Big Spider...
otherwise known as Strange.
Wow.
"Strange," huh...?
not a bad word to
describe this place.
It's not like
I expected them
to have their headquarters
in a mansion or anything.
But this is pretty bad.
Well, I guess I can see
how this would be a
fitting place for a gang
who commits the kind of
crimes that Skill Out does.
Although... as vile
as Skill Out is...
Maybe Academy City should
share some of the blame
for neglecting this area
and letting it become
so dilapidated.
I don't know about you,
but this definitely isn't
one of the warmer welcomes
I've ever received.
It would help if you didn't
have that armband on.
Wha-...?! You were
rushing so much,
I forgot to take it off...!
I'd planned on wearing
a disguise, b...
Hey, ladies. What brings
you to our part of town?
Take a look at this.
These two are
with Judgment.
-Are you here to arrest us?!
-So, like I was saying...
I get it, Sissy.
It looks like they're
having a little squabble.
It's too late to
run back home.
Hey now.
Picking on young
girls, are we?
I'm afraid we
can't have that.
What the heck?
Is that milk?
Yeah? Who do you
think you are?
Hold on a second, okay?
Huh? What the...?
I get it. He's trying to show
off in front of these girls
by playing hero.
Am I, now?
How 'bout you walk away
and mind your own business.
Uh... here you go, sir...
Um... Will this carton be
an acceptable replacement?
Yeah... thanks for
taking the trouble.
Oh, of course...
Well, we have to be going!
Sounds good...
You take care.
Good stuff. When it comes to
milk, it's gotta be Musasino.
You know, it's funny...
I don't remember
asking for your help.
Sorry about that.
It's just you reminded
me of a girl I once knew
whose chest was no bigger
than either of yours.
I couldn't walk away.
A man we've never met just made
a comment about our breasts.
And surprisingly, it
didn't sound offensive.
Hey hold on a sec.
We're not done!
Wait up, Sissy!
Mii...?,
You're home already?
It's not like you to be
home so early in the day....
What about your
work for Judgment?
Don't worry.
I'm gonna take care of it...
What about you?
You could stop by the
branch once in a while.
Being on campus
is enough for me.
I have matters of love
and youth to attend to.
Honestly... You're always
like this, aren't you?
Hey... Is something wrong?
Not really.
'Kay.
Well... since you're
home early for once,...
maybe you can take a
turn cooking dinner.
Huh...?
That's not fair, Aomi!
Wow...
Nice, isn't it?
It's kind of a
secret spot...
The streets below can
start to feel suffocating.
But the breeze up here takes
you away from all that.
The view of Strange
from this rooftop
isn't any different than
it was two years ago.
Two years ago?
Well... a lot can happen.
I have to wonder...
Why do the members
of Skill Out
choose to be in this
area of all places?
It's not something you
two would understand.
It's not like I
don't understand.
Understand what?
The way the members
of Skill Out feel.
You keep trying and trying,
but your level never
goes any higher.
And eventually, you
start to lose hope.
I don't know...
It's like, after a while,
you feel like giving
up on everything.
We really have given
up on everything...
The system's broken.
So we left Academy City behind,
where everybody's
judged by their ability.
What about you?
Huh...? Me...?
No, no...
I decided that giving up
on everything doesn't help.
Yeah... from now on,
I'm gonna keep on trying.
For us trying to use
our esper abilities
is like trying to
touch the sky.
And the sky is
especially far away
from the alleys of
this city... So...
Whatever the reason, Skill Out
is still Skill Out, isn't it...?
Individuals may
be different,
but the group
is up to no good.
That's pretty harsh.
So what did the two of
you come down here for?
Oh, I almost forgot.
We're looking for an
organization called Big Spider.
If I were you...
I'd be careful
dropping that name
around here too much.
By any chance do you recognize
the name Wataru Kurozuma?
Nope. I'm afraid I don't.
Well... have a safe trip home.
What is it, Sissy...?
Is something the matter?
I don't know...
something about him
just bothers me.
Oh...! No...!
I don't know if
I can handle you
getting all hot and
bothered by this guy.
It's too much...!
Too much!
Ow...
Did you hear him?
He said he'd come back here
after being away
for two years.
Yeah, I guess so.
But what does that matter?
It was also
two years ago
that Big Spider began
expanding its operation.
Doesn't that raise
any flags for you?
Now that you mention it,
that is kinda weird.
Let's go and check out
some other places...
Maybe we'll
learn something.
Uh... Sure, Sissy,
but at least wait for me!
What are you idiots doing?
Over a dozen guys
from our esper hunting
parties have been taken down.
How is it we still
have no leads?
W... we are
looking, I swear!
Oh, you're looking,
are you?
Well looking isn't
gonna be enough...
You need to
find something!
Do you know why you
can't find anything...?
It's because they think
they're better than we are.
Listen up everybody ...
We need to show
'em they're wrong!
We need to hunt
down those espers
until they realize how
much power Big Spider has.
They'll see that they're
too weak to fight us.
Once we do that there
won't be anybody
standing in the way of us
and what we want!
Yeah!
After all this time,
he's still alive?
No... no way can
that be true.
But if...
If it is...
if he is alive...
Something needs
to be done.
W... What is this?!
I see... you guys
are Skill Out.
You're messin' with
the wrong guy...
I happen to be...
See that...?
Now, unless the rest of you
guys wanna end up like him...
Think we're scared of
someone like you?
What happened to all that
brave talk of yours...? Huh?
Go ahead and use
your ability on us...
Assuming you can concentrate
enough to calculate
while you're gettin' the
pulp beaten out of you.
Survival of the fittest is the
rule here in Academy City...
Right now we're the predators
and you're the prey.
You know...
It's pretty amazing
how quickly the hunters
can become the hunted.
Time for you to
face Judgment!
Why don't you keep moving?
Yeah, little girls,
run along and play now.
Why'd you have to go
and make it difficult?
I left the victim
at the nearby branch
to make his report.
These guys are finished.
Man... we searched
all over Strange
and didn't find anything.
Then we come
upon these guys
while just walking down
the street like normal.
So...? All's well
that ends well, right?
Yeah... I guess that's true...
Where to now?
What's goin' on here?
We represent Judgment!
What do they want?
You kids shouldn't be
messing around here.
Oh...? Judgment's
paying a visit?
What the hell do
you want with us?
Wataru Kurozuma, right?
You are under arrest
for your involvement
in leading
the recent acts of
violence against espers.
You're here to arrest me...?
Sorry, but I don't have
time to play house with you
and your little sidekick.
Now get lost.
You aren't very
polite, are you?
I'm trying to explain
things to you nicely...
but if you don't get it,
we can make you
understand the hard way.
Stand back, Sissy...
I can handle the likes
of these wretched pests
all on my own
without any problems.
Don't get ahead
of yourself.
'Cause ya see...
we have a secret weapon.
What is that
horrible sound?
It feels like it's reverberating
directly inside my head.
Is something wrong?
I can't do it!
Well, why aren't
you fighting...?
I thought you were gonna
take us all out by yourself!
Kuroko!
What happened...? I can't
aim or use my full power.
Heh... technical difficulties?
Let me tell you about
our handy new weapon...
That device over there is
called a Capacity Down system.
I don't know
much about it,
but I'll explain
what I can.
essentially, it jumbles up
the arithmetic
capacity of the brain.
But... it doesn't work on
members of Skill Out...
All we hear is a
high--pitched sound.
Annoying, but
harmless to us.
Capacity Down...?
Where on earth did
they get that thing?
Now... I would like
to hear you say,
"Please forgive us,
Mr. Kurozuma."
If you do that, I might
consider letting you go.
Oh...?
Did you say your
name is Kurozuma?
Ah! It's him!
Yeah! That's the guy,
all right.
Kurozuma! It's
the man from before!
He's the one who's been
interfering with us.
Kurozuma... it's you.
I'm confused.
What's going on?
-Kurozuma, what's the matter...?
-Let's see...
Kurozuma!
There we go!
The noise!
It's gone now!
Are you okay?
And you?
Uh... yeah.
-Hey, y...
-Hold this for me, will you?
Hey, Hebitani...
long time no see, huh?
No... impossible...
You've been dead
for two years...
There's no way you
could've survived.
Not after what happened.
Fine then,
have it your way.
I'm a ghost.
A ghost...?
That's right...
a ghost...
Time for you to go
back to your grave!
Go on...
let him have it!
He's just one guy,
isn't he...?
And besides,
we're all armed.
It's such a shame...
You've changed, Hebitani.
Die!
Put that away...
With your aim,
you'll probably
just end up shooting
yourself in the foot.
Hey, wait for us!
All done.
Starting to feel a
little better now?
More or less. Still not back
up to full power yet...
I'll be fine...
So, that guy...
He wasn't Kurozuma?
A long time ago,
back when I knew
him he was Hebitani.
Apparently he prefers
to go by Kurozuma now.
But... the real Kurozuma
is actually you, right?
Yeah, I suppose I've
been called that before.
When it comes to milk...
It's gotta be Musasino.
Konori?!
It's been a long time...
Mii.
[Music]
Hey, Konori,
what's going on...?
I don't understand what
you're so upset about.
Sissy...! Sometimes you
can be really naïve...
The next episode might
be too mature for you.