Who's back there?
I am Mitsuko Kongo of
Tokiwadai Middle School.
Knowing that, will you
still dare to attack me?
[Music]
I'm so excited!
We're going to the
Garden of Learning!
I don't know why they
gave it such a fancy name.
It's just the
area of town
where there's a cluster of
girls' schools, you know?
But they aren't just
any ordinary schools.
The ones in the Garden
of Learning are special.
They're all well--known
girls' schools.
Tokiwadai Middle School
is only one of them.
Yeah, sure, whatever.
We're only allowed
in here today
because Shirai was kind
enough to invite us.
If she hadn't, a student
as lowly and common as I am
would have no
business visiting
such an exalted place as this.
Could you please
stop groveling?
You're starting to sound
like a brown--noser.
Oh, hey. What is this?
Oh, I see now.
You've got a page
highlighted in here.
Is this a bakery
you want to try out
while we're visiting, Saten?
Well, of course! It's
the Pasticceria Manicagni!
Just read what it says.
"The cheesecake
is a work of art,
made from an authentic
Italian recipe
and using only the
finest ingredients."
I've always wanted
to try a piece,
but the Garden of Learning
is the only place
in the whole country
where they have it!
You're more of a
sucker for advertising
than I thought, Saten.
Next stop, the entrance
to the Garden of Learning.
Repeat. Entrance to
the Garden of Learning.
Uh--oh.
The bus got us here
ahead of schedule, huh?
It shouldn't be a problem.
Three, two and one.
Wow! I've never seen weather
forecasts as accurate
as the ones they
have in this city.
The word "forecast"
is so vague.
It's more accurate to say
that they are readings
of future events established
by precise calculations.
It kinda gets
boring, though.
It would be more exciting
if they would slip up
every once in a while.
Enough of that.
Let's get moving!
We have invitations
from Kuroko Shirai,
first--year at
Tokiwadai Middle School.
I'm Kazari Uiharu.
And I'm Ruiko Saten.
Very good. Go on ahead.
This is such a charming
area, isn't it?
Everything looks different
from the rest of the world,
down to the crosswalks
and traffic signals.
Pretty impressive, huh?
It really does feel like
we're tourists visiting a
foreign country!
Yeah, it does.
You know, it kinda seems
like we're attracting
a lot of attention.
Huh?
Yeah, you're right.
I bet it's our outfits.
I'm sure it's unusual
for them to see students
who aren't from this area.
Yeah. That makes sense.
Whoops! Look at the time!
Huh? Oh yeah, you're right.
Come on. We should hurry.
It looks like they're
running late, huh?
This is where we're
supposed to meet them, right?
Yeah, it is.
They said that they wanted
to see our school,
so it made sense for them to
meet us by the entrance.
How inconsiderate of them,
keeping my Sissy
waiting like this.
Oh, here they come now.
What happened to you?
Well, you see ...
I sort of slipped
in a puddle.
Ah ...
You asked for a quick
change of clothes.
I'm afraid this school
uniform's the only thing
I have to offer.
No, this'll be fine.
Does the size
work for you?
Oh, yeah, it
fits perfectly.
Though the skirt's
a bit short,
so it's a little breezy.
It's not fair you
get to wear that.
-Huh?
-I know!
We should trade outfits!
What do you say?
I think it's a great idea!
Yours is too small
for me to wear.
Then, I'll go find
a puddle to slip in.
Let it go already.
It will only be
for a little while!
Give it up, Uiharu!
Aw, pleeease?
I sent your dirty uniform
off to the cleaners.
Stop by there on
your way home.
And if that doesn't work,
we can always have it sent
to your dorm for you.
-It's no trouble.
-Wow.
That's what I
call service.
Do you have maids at your
school, too? I bet you do!
I bet they come every day!
Oh, calm down.
Hmm ... Maybe I want that
strawberry crostata.
It looks good.
No, wait ... That Monte
Bianco over there
looks awfully delicious, too.
Ah! But how could I pass
up that cioccolata?
Is it really that difficult
of a decision to make?
Oh, not for me.
I've already decided on
the cheesecake for sure.
Uiharu the sun'll be
going down soon.
I'm sorry.
Just one more
minute, okay?
Hold on.
Yes?
Huh?
Uh,
okay. Yes, I understand.
-Is Judgment calling us in?
-They sure are.
Go figure.
Their timing couldn't be
any worse if they tried, huh?
We'll get yours wrapped
up for take--out, Uiharu.
Thanks. I appreciate it.
-We should probably hurry.
-Yeah!
Always on the move, huh?
Well, I guess
it's just us.
Uh, just a sec.
I need to use the
ladies' room real quick.
Honestly! Why are they
calling us in on our day off?
It's a Saturday!
-Hey!
-Ow!
No complaining. You can do
that on your own time.
Yes, of course.
Sorry, Konori.
So, are you going to tell
us why you've called us in?
It began yesterday and
continued overnight.
Six students, all
from Tokiwadai.
They've been assaulted in a
string of related attacks.
What's more, it's
all been happening
in the Garden of Learning.
There's no one lower
than a Level 3 Esper
enrolled in Tokiwadai
Middle School.
But these students
are being targeted
and easily bested, which
leads me to believe ... ...
that the perpetrator must
be a formidable Esper.
That is likely the case.
However, we don't
know their ability.
Every victim ... ...
was knocked unconscious
using a stun gun.
And then?
What happened to the victims
once they were knocked out?
I can show you
the photographs.
It's not pretty.
I suggest you prepare yourselves
before looking at them.
The tea is starting
to get cold.
I've prepared for
this sort of thing
since I first applied to
be a Judgment officer.
The same goes for me.
Right.
In that case ...
Hey, what's
taking so long?
What happened?
Saten, wake up!
Targeting our school?
Oh yeah.
She was wearing
our uniform.
How's she doing?
Is she all right?
Well, physically, it's
nothing too serious.
She should be fine after
she lies down for a bit.
It's just ...
Have you zeroed in
on any suspects yet?
No, not yet.
See, their particular ability
is making it tricky for us.
Tricky in what way?
The attacker
was invisible.
I'm telling
you, it's true!
I didn't see anything
when it happened!
Yes, but here. Take a look.
This is the image from
the surveillance camera.
I don't care!
For the last time, I
didn't see a single thing!
So the victims didn't see
their attacker at all.
Naturally, our first idea
was that it was an Esper
who could perform
optical manipulation.
We made a list of
forty--seven Espers.
They all have the ability
to make themselves
disappear completely.
However, every last person
on the list has an alibi.
Well, whoever it was
showed up on the surveillance
cameras, didn't they?
Maybe it's something different
than optical manipulation.
That could be the case.
-Oh, a dove.
-Eh?
Shirai, didn't you
see it just now?
No, sorry. I didn't
notice anything.
You didn't
Uiharu, there's something
I'd like you to try.
Here it is.
The ability's name
is "Dummy Check."
It's the power to
impair the awareness
that a person is looking
at a particular subject.
Apparently, only
one person has it.
Miho Jufuku, a
second--year
at Sekichu Middle School.
That's our attacker!
I don't think that's
possible, though.
She's only a Level 2.
She's not strong enough.
According to her test
results, she doesn't have
the power to completely
conceal herself.
Man, I really thought we
were on the right track, too.
-What happened?
-She's awake!
You should take it easy.
W--w--w--w--wha--?
Come on now. Just get
a hold of yourself.
I understand. This
has to be a shock.
If your bangs were
a little longer,
like this girl's are,
you would at least
be able to hide it.
Who has long bangs?
Hey! It was her!
You mean you saw the
person who did this to you?
That's right.
When it happened ...
I saw this girl
in the mirror.
First surveillance
cameras, now mirrors.
So that's how it is, then.
I think I get it.
She can make people
unaware of her presence,
but only if they're
looking right at her
with the naked eye.
That girl made me
look like a freak,
and now she's gonna
pay for it, big time!
Let's do it, Uiharu!
Do what?
You've got some skills
with that thing.
Yeah, well, I have
to do it like this,
or else the terminals here
won't be able to keep up
with the processing.
Anyway, the Garden of
Learning doesn't fall
under the hundred and
seventy--seventh
Branch's jurisdiction, Kuroko.
Are you sure this is okay?
Our superiors have just
given us the go ahead.
Now you're talking!
Uiharu, let's get
this show on the road.
I'm on it. And, "Go."
There you have it, girls.
We are now connected to all
two--thousand fifty--eight
surveillance cameras in
the Garden of Learning.
I'll find you now, creepy
chick with the long bangs.
Just you wait.
You're gonna get what's
coming to you soon.
I still haven't forgotten that
cake you promised me earlier.
Do this and I'll get you
a dozen of them if you want.
Yeah!
That's going
to be too many.
-Oh, you think so?
-Huh?
Really? Cause I don't
see any harm in it.
We're not talking about
cake anymore, you two.
Huh?
Uiharu, go ahead and
exclude areas E through H,
as well as J and N.
Okay.
Those are the areas
the furthest distance
away from Tokiwadai.
Since they're so far,
students from our school
rarely have reason
to go there.
I think we can go ahead and
exclude high-traffic areas, too.
Why do you say that?
The suspect's uniform.
Don't you think it
would stand out a bit
in the Garden of Learning?
Yeah, it would.
Think she uses her ability
whenever people are around,
even when she's
not attacking?
Probably. Even so,
she can't possibly maintain
it 24 hours a day.
Then she'll have to find
someplace out of the way
so she'll be able
to catch her breath.
Exactly!
And if that is
the case, then ...
You should put that away.
You were the one who gave me
these ridiculous eyebrows.
I fully intend to pay
you back with interest.
She really disappeared.
This is no time
to be impressed.
Go after her, Saten!
All right, I'm on my way.
-Ow!
-What just happened?
Something bumped into me,
but I don't know what it was.
Coming through!
Be careful!
Here we go.
As you can see,
I'm with Judgment.
I'm taking you
into custody.
Come quietly, or ...
Yep. She was never
going to come quietly.
Uiharu, could I get
some directions, please?
Working on it.
Go out to the
street, turn left,
then go up to Third Avenue.
Copy that. Thanks a lot.
Sure.
How?
This game has been fun.
But it's all over now.
Impossible. Why isn't my Dummy
Check working anymore?
Who can say?
This is why I hate all
you brats from Tokiwadai!
Nice try.
But, you see, stun guns don't
really have any effect on me.
Uh, um ...
And that was actually
holding back.
Uiharu! Please contact
Antiskill and inform them
that we have successfully
apprehended the suspect.
Right.
Good work today!
One last thing to do.
So, what'll it be?
What kind of eyebrows
should I give her?
No!
Oh, dear.
Funny looking, right?
Oh, well, uh ...
Go ahead and laugh!
Laugh as loud as you can.
Just like he did!
Just like who?
It was spring.
I was dozing off in the
glorious midday sunshine.
In my naiveté, I believed
that this time of peace
and comfort would
last forever.
But then ...
Spring came to an end.
It was so sudden.
Tell me why!
Are girls from Tokiwadai
really so special?
That's not exactly
the reason.
Then what is it?
Well, your eyebrows
are just so ...
Weird!
I hated the boy
who cast me aside,
and I hated the dumb
girl from Tokiwadai
who took him away from me!
But more than
anything else
I hated the funny eyebrows
that ruined my life!
And that's why I decided
I would give everybody
funny eyebrows like mine!
-Uh, what?
-Yeah, sorry.
You lost me about
halfway through, there.
What's the matter?
Just go ahead. Laugh at me!
You know you want to!
Um ...
I, uh ...
I don't think
they're weird.
Not weird they're just ...
um ...
Yeah! They give your
face character,
that's what it is.
Personally, I
really like them!
Now that's taking
it too far.
I, uh ...
Is it okay if I sent
you a letter sometime?
That's fine.
Impressive.
She really could make
herself disappear completely.
Now that you mention it,
wasn't she listed
as a Level 2 Esper?
That is odd.
I wonder, could the
info in the database
be incorrect?
No, of course not!
What is going on here?
Oh? The other
victims too, huh?
Yes, I see.
Here's the thing.
It's a special ink
developed by a university
in the tenth
school district.
They say there's no way it's
coming off sooner than a week.
What now, Saten?
Do you want me to get that
cute hat ready for you again?
That jerk.
Stupid eyebrow girl!
I knew I should've
drawn something on her!
Calm down, Saten!
Get a hold of yourself!
What am I gonna do?
Hey, Uiharu. Have you
heard of the sandal hag?
"#4 Urban Legends"
The sandal hag?
They say she's this ugly
old woman in sandals
-who chases after you!
-Yikes!
-And she's butt naked!
-That's just gross!