The attacks began
a week ago
and they have been
escalating ever since.
It is a series of
Graviton attacks,
with each
successive incident
the force and scale
have both increased.
We cannot find any pattern
in the times and locations
of the attacks,
and after examining the
psychometry of articles
left behind,
we still do not
have any leads.
We are working
with anti-skill
to prevent anymore
casualties.
We have increased security
that we must do
everything we can
to get this case solved.
[Music]
Are you sure you're
feeling okay?
You were up late
again last night
investigating those
serial attacks.
It's the only thing
I can think to do.
The search is still
turning up nothing.
For now, I'm just
checking to make sure
we haven't overlooked
anything.
Well, it's great you're so
committed to your work and all,
but you shouldn't
push yourself so hard.
Aw! Thank you, Sissy!
It warms my heart to know
you're so concerned about me.
I think what would
really help is
if we could sleep in the
same bed together tonight.
My fatigue would
evaporate immediately!
Aw, man!
Well, the least you can
do is wait for me, Sissy.
Really, must you
always be so coy?
AIM diffusion fields
are localized phenomena
that occur only
around Espers.
Of course,
AIM is an acronym.
It stands for
"An Involuntary Movement."
An AIM diffusion
field is a weak force
that Espers involuntarily
emit around themselves.
It can't be felt
with the five senses.
Without specialized
equipment,
it can't be
detected at all.
However, researchers into
applications in this field
have been making remarkable
progress recently.
Hey! What're you
poking me for?
You want to do some shopping at
Seventh Mist on the way home?
Yeah! Oh, I can't.
I still have work
to do for Judgment.
You can blow that off for
a bit, though, can't you?
Just say we were out
patrolling or something.
That won't work.
I really would love
to go with you,
but solving this case just
matters more right now.
Oh. Okay.
Hey.
We need cash.
You gonna lend us some more?
What? I can't.
I mean, I would,
but you haven't paid back
what you already
borrowed from me.
Huh?
We told you we'd pay
you back, didn't we?
Once we've got the dough.
Don't you remember?
You're giving us loans,
indefinitely and
interest, free.
That was the deal we had.
Is this seriously
all you've got?
Come on.
Let's get going before
Judgment shows up.
Nothin' to worry
about there.
They're too busy
with those bombings
to have time for
anything else.
Damnit.
He's right.
They're useless.
Judgment?
Don't make me laugh.
This wouldn't be
happening to me
if they'd do their job.
But just wait.
Aw, geez!
I wish we had just a
little more to go on.
Yeah, tell me about it.
So far all we know
is the suspect is a
Level 4 Esper or higher.
We really need
more information.
Hm.
And the databank
isn't coming up
with a match to the ability.
Maybe it's somebody
who's had a very sudden,
dramatic increase in power.
No. No way.
Over such a short
period of time?
That would be impossible.
Just wishful thinking.
You're right. Something like
that could never happen.
Let's keep at it.
We'll go over the fragments
left behind again.
Yeah, good idea!
Saten!
Kuroko's so stressed.
It must be just
as hard on Uiharu.
She's working so much!
I asked if she wanted to
go shopping with me today.
Of course she said, "No."
Yeah. They don't
really have a choice
until this mad
bomber is captured.
It all makes me feel ...
I don't know.
I feel so insignificant
right now.
Oh, how should I put it?
Uiharu and Kuroko are doing
so much work for
this Judgment case
and obviously, you're
in a league of your own.
And then there's me,
and I'm just ...
Oh, sorry! Really!
I'm not trying to
throw a pity party!
I just mean if I had
an ability, too,
it would really change
my life, you know?
Aw. If only I had a
Level Upper or something,
then maybe I could be
a Level 5 someday, too.
What's a Level Upper?
It's one of those urban
legends I mentioned before.
Apparently, it's a device
that will automatically upgrade
your ability level for you.
When we found out the
"Undresstress" was real,
I started thinking maybe
it could be real, too.
But that's ridiculous,
isn't it?
Say... Let's all go together!
You want me to go shopping
with you, Sissy? Really?
You and Uiharu
are both off.
I told Saten I thought it
would be fun for all of us
to make a day of it.
Oh. You said that, did you?
Well, I appreciate
the offer,
but I don't think
I'll be able to go.
I still need to do a little
bit more investigating.
Oh. Okay, then.
Well, good luck.
I'm going to sleep.
A new world order
is on its way.
And this time,
I'll be on top.
It's a shame Shirai
couldn't make it today.
Oh, she's not
coming at all?
Apparently, she
still has to work.
Judgment has never done
anything to help me.
Who needs them?
Over here! Come on!
So, are you looking
for anything specific?
No, but I haven't really
thought about it that much.
U--i--ha--ru!
Come look over here!
Uh, at what exactly?
See?
These are great,
aren't they?
No! Never, never, never!
On me?
I couldn't get away
with those, could I?
Think of how stylish
and mature they'd look.
You could show
them off proudly
whenever I flip
up your skirt.
I don't want to show off.
I don't want my
skirt flipped up!
Aw, that's too bad.
Oh, hey!
What are you in the
market for today?
Huh? Well, let's see.
Maybe some new pajamas?
In that case,
let's head this way.
They sure do have a
lot of stuff here.
But I haven't seen
anything I like so far.
Over here!
These are adorable!
Whoa. Hey, Uiharu.
You've gotta check
these pj's out.
When was the last
time you saw anybody
wearing something like that?
I had something that
looked very similar back
when I was in
elementary school.
But that was a while ago.
Well, yeah, of course.
Now that we're
in middle school,
we can't wear this
type of thing.
Obviously.
Well, I think I'm gonna
look at swimsuits.
Yeah, all right.
I'm pretty sure they
were back this way.
Cool.
Who cares, anyway?
They're just
pajamas, right?
It's not like anyone
else will see them.
How about this one?
Isn't it pretty?
All right,
now's my chance.
Nobody will notice if
I take a quick look.
Yoink!
Uh, what are you
doing, Zapper?
I'm shopping with friends.
What are you doing here?
What, am I not
allowed to be here?
Big Brother!
You're with the nice
lady from Tokiwadai!
Oh! The girl with the bag.
I didn't realize you
had a younger sister.
Yeah, well, I don't.
This little girl
just asked me
to help her find
a clothing store.
Seems she's nicknamed
me, Big Brother.
Now we're here!
Big Brother picked
out a perfect store!
I'm gonna dress up
real pretty and fancy!
And I'll look just like
the grown--ups on TV!
You will, will you?
Well, I think you already
look pretty snazzy this way.
Unlike a certain somebody
I happen to know.
You want a piece of me?
I'm perfectly happy to settle
what we started the other day.
Huh? You're still worked up?
Is that the only thing
you ever think about?
Here? Really?
You actually want
to start a fight
in front of all
these people?
Hey, hey!
I wanna look there!
Oh? Well, let's go.
Bye--bye, nice lady!
See you!
What's up?
Is something wrong, Misaka?
No. It's nothing.
That guy always makes
me lose my temper.
Why does he do that to me?
Gekota!
Never mind.
It's not.
It doesn't look much
like him at all.
I'm starting to wonder.
Could we have two
different suspects?
Both with the same M.O.?
Don't be silly.
I'm grasping at straws.
I just can't see any connection
between all of the attacks.
If we don't figure
this out soon,
we'll have another victim on
our hands-maybe more than one.
If only we had at
least one solid lead.
Nine of our colleagues
have been hurt already.
Nine?
What are you thinking?
That seems like an awful lot,
don't you think?
Maybe we're the targets!
Accelerated gravitons
have been detected!
Uiharu. That's your
phone, isn't it?
Oh. Yeah, it is.
-Yes, this is Ui...
-Uiharu!
Update on the
graviton attacks.
The surveillance
satellite has picked up
an explosive acceleration
of gravitons.
Where is it happening?
Antiskill officers in the area
are responding immediately,
but we need you to get
back here at once!
Wait, Kuroko.
Where is the attack?
A clothing store
called Seventh Mist
in the Seventh School District.
Seventh Mist clothing store?
That's perfect, then.
That's where
I am right now.
I'll start the
emergency evacuation!
Uiharu!
Hello? Are you there?
What does she
think she's doing?
What's going on?
What did she say?
Please listen
and don't panic.
We know where the
attacker's next target is.
We're standing in it.
Wha... What did you say?
Here's the plan.
I want you to start helping
with the evacuation, Misaka.
Yeah. Sure thing.
And Saten-you get
to safety, okay?
You'll be careful,
too, won't you?
He's got his next
target, all right.
Attention all customers.
We are experiencing
an electrical malfunction
inside the store.
We sincerely apologize for any
inconvenience this might cause,
but we must immediately
suspend business for the day.
Please follow the
clerks' instructions
to the nearest exit.
Again, we sincerely apologize
for any inconvenience,
but we must immediately
suspend business.
Zapper!
Have you seen
that little girl?
Huh? I thought
she was with you!
I can't find her anywhere.
She could still be
inside the store.
What is she doing?
Hey!
Uiharu!
Everyone has been evacuated.
Listen to me. You need to
get out of there right now!
The only human casualties
in the past attacks
were Judgment members.
The suspect's actual target
is any Judgment officer
who's in the area!
And that means
that this time
the target is
going to be you!
Hey there, lady!
Is that...?
A strange man wearing
glasses asked me to come over
and give this to
you as a present.
Here!
Get down right now!
That thing is a bomb!
I'll railgun
it out of here!
Uh--oh!
-What was that?
-An explosion!
It must be one of
those serial bombings!
It looked like there
were still people inside!
I think I saw a
girl from Judgment.
Everybody! Stand back!
Get back now, people!
Clear the area!
Awesome!
That was perfect! Perfect!
I'm controlling stronger
and stronger power every time!
I'm getting close.
A few more attacks
and I should be ready.
I'll take on Judgment
and those punks at school
along with 'em.
I'll blow every last one.
What the...
What happened?
Hi!
I assume you know
what this is about.
I'm right, aren't I?
-Mister Mad Bomber?
-No.
I have no idea what you're
talking about, really.
Well, there is a lot
of property damage.
I'll give you that.
But too bad for you.
There wasn't a
single causality.
Nobody suffered even
so much as a scratch.
No! That's impossible!
I was using the
maximum power.
Well, I mean, it looked like
a huge explosion from outside.
So, I seriously doubt
anybody still in the store
could have survived it.
It's Railgun.
The great Ace
of Tokiwadai.
Just my luck.
It's always like this.
No matter what I do.
People are always
beating me down,
but I'm gonna stop it.
I'll kill you all.
It's people like you
who are the problem.
And Judgment
is the same way!
And anyone who has power!
All you ever do is abuse it!
Power? Power, you say?
I'll show ya power.
Ahh!
You fool.
That punch was the
least that you deserved.
You use other people's
power as an excuse
for your own weakness.
There's almost nothing
more pathetic than that.
Don't you realize
even the great Railgun,
Ace of Tokiwadai,
started out at Level 1.
She didn't become a
Level 5 because of some fluke.
She worked hard for it
every step of the way.
You know, even if she was a
Level 1 instead of a Level 5,
I have a feeling
she still would have been
able to get the best of you.
There you are!
Oh! I was so
worried about you!
I know. I'm sorry.
But thanks to Misaka,
here we are.
All in one piece! See?
The lady from Tokiwadai
saved us just in time!
Yeah!
-She was pretty amazing, huh?
-Yeah!
There's something
strange about it, though.
The place where
they were standing
is the only spot
left unharmed.
I don't know how Sissy's
ability could have this effect.
Hey! There she is!
I have to admit,
you really outdid yourself
this time, Sissy!
Thank you so much
for everything!
Huh?
Oh. Yeah.
I know! Let me be your
personal slave for a day.
I'll do anything
you want me to!
I could wash your
back for you
or give you a nice massage.
What is your
bidding, Sissy?
I'll pass.
That sounds more
like what you want.
Thanks anyway.
Aw, come on!
Just a short massage, then!
Please!
[Music]
I don't deserve the credit.
My railgun wouldn't have
made it in time back there.
It wasn't me who saved
Uiharu and that little girl.
It was him.
An ambush?
-You angry?
-Huh?
Everybody seems to think
I'm the one who saved those guys
from the graviton explosion.
If you come forward,
you'll be a hero.
Huh? What are you
talking about?
Everybody got out
of it all right.
I don't really
see a problem.
Do you?
So what difference does
it make who saved them?
Stop acting so cool!
Why does he always
have to play the hero?
And why does he only
do it in front of me?
It's driving me crazy!
It's always the same thing.
That guy really
ticks me off!
You should calm down, Sissy.
You're turning red.
--Next time...
--I'm not turning red!
Ooh, bright red!
Your face is
burning my eyes!