- Teacher: DON'T FORGET TO
STEER CLEAR OF THE OLD BUILDING
WHEN WALKING TO CLASS TODAY.
THEY'RE KNOCKING IT DOWN SOON,
AND YOU DON'T WANNA BE NEARBY
WHEN IT HAPPENS.
- Nezu: MISS RANMARU!
- SUP?
- DOING ANYTHING AFTER CLASS?
- WE WERE THINKING
OF GOING TO KARAOKE.
YOU SHOULD COME! IT'LL BE
LIKE A WELCOME-BACK PARTY!
OUR TREAT!
- YEAH, I'LL GO
ON ONE CONDITION.
- YOU GOTTA STOP CALLING ME
'MISS RANMARU.'
- Both: OH!
BUT WE THOUGHT
THAT'S WHAT YOU WANTED!
- YEAH, IT'S REALLY NOT.
LADY PANTS! WHY DON'T YOU
COME WITH US?
- I DON'T THINK SO,
MISS RANMARU.
WHY'S EVERYONE
CALLING ME 'MISS?'
IT SOUNDS LIKE YOU'RE
TALKING TO MY MOTHER!
CUT IT OUT AND COME WITH US!
IT'S GONNA BE FUN!
- AT LEAST TELL ME
WHO ELSE IS GONNA BE THERE?
- ME! I'M GONNA
BE THERE! LET'S GO!
ARE YOU READY TO HEAR
THE MOST FEROCIOUS BALLAD EVER?
- YEAH, MY SOUL SISTA!
LET'S ROCK THIS!
...LIKE A CELINE MACHINE!
THANKS FOR INVITING ME.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- IT'S OKAY IF THESE GUYS
COME WITH US, ISN'T IT?
- I THINK IT'S OKAY
IF MOMIJI COMES.
- YEAH, BUT, I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT ICHIKO.
- WHATEVER. YOU AREN'T
'THOSE GIRLS,' ARE YOU?
- NO, IT'S OKAY.
I DON'T MIND.
THEY WANTED TO THROW YOU
A WELCOME BACK PARTY,
SO GO HAVE A GOOD TIME!
BESIDES, I'M NOT
THAT INTO KARAOKE
AND I'VE GOT LOADS OF OTHER
INVITES TONIGHT!
- AWESOME. YOU HEARD HER. LET'S
GO BEFORE THE ROOMS FILL UP.
- 'KAY. LATER.
- YOUR BAG IS BEGGING FOR
ME TO CARRY IT!
DID I JUST HEAR YOU SAY
YOU DON'T DO KARAOKE?
HOW DOES THAT WORK?
- WHICH SONG WERE YOU
TALKING ABOUT EARLIER?
- AN AWESOME ONE.
- ( Nezu grunting )
- HEY, LET'S GO TO
THE NEW COFFEE SHOP
BY THE TRAIN STATION.
- WE'LL BUY YOU SOME CHOCOLATE!
- DO YOU SEE WHAT SHE'S DOING?
WORKIN' HER TIT-CHIKOS.
- ♪ I SAID NO, I SAID NO, ♪
♪ I SAID NO MATTER HOW MUCH
I THINK OF YOU, OH... ♪
- IT'S LIKE YOU'RE SINGING
INTO MY SOUL.
- CAN I BE YOU WHEN I GROW UP?
- YOU'RE NEXT! DO YOU KNOW
WHAT SONG YOU'RE GONNA SING?
- UH... NO?
- HEY, IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
- YEAH, TOTALLY.
EXCEPT... I DUNNO.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT MISS THANG.
I GOT THE FEELING SHE KINDA
WANTED TO COME WITH US TODAY.
- THEN YOU DON'T
KNOW HER VERY WELL.
- WHEN WE LEFT, SHE WAS
RIGHT WHERE SHE WANTED TO BE.
SURROUNDED BY BOYS
BEGGING TO LICK HER SOCKS!
- I'VE TRIED TO HANG
OUT WITH HER,
BUT SHE ALWAYS SAYS
THE SAME THING.
"I DON'T REALLY CLICK
WITH OTHER GIRLS, SO..."
LIKE I SHOULD'VE KNOWN
AND WAS STUPID FOR ASKING!
- I DON'T KNOW.
EVEN WHEN SHE'S SURROUNDED
BY GUYS SHE SEEMS REALLY LONELY.
- Atsushi: ICHIKO?
ARE WE TALKING
ABOUT THE SAME GIRL?
- THAT WASN'T A
LOOK OF LONELINESS.
THAT WAS A LOOK OF 'OVER IT!'
- ARE YOU REALLY
THAT WORRIED ABOUT ICHIKO?
- I THOUGHT I HAD A GOOD REASON.
- BUT, MAYBE I'M JUST AN IDIOT.
- ( Nakamura singing )
THAT'S WHAT MY MIND SAYS.
BUT MY INSTINCTS DISAGREE.
- THEN WHY DON'T WE GO
OVER THERE AND ASK HER DIRECTLY?
- SHE'S NOT GONNA BE THERE.
SHE SAID SHE HAD
TONS OF OTHER INVITATIONS.
- OH PLEASE.
SHE'S PROBABLY COUNTING
THE FIBERS IN HER THROW RUG.
- LIKE INDIVIDUALLY?
- TWELVE THOUSAND, 206,
12 THOUSAND, 207.
- TOTALLY CALLED IT.
- THIS IS WHAT YOU
DITCHED US TO DO?
- YOU CAN'T BARGE IN WITHOUT
A WARRANT! I COULD ARREST YOU!
- YOU CAN'T ARREST ANYONE!
IF YOU HAVE A PROBLEM
WITH ME, SAY SO!
DON'T BE A WUSS AND AVOID ME!
- I SHOULD TAKE THIS
TIME TO POINT OUT
HOW FIERCE MY CANS
LOOK IN THAT TOP!
- I COULDN'T GIVE A CRAP
ABOUT YOUR TOP!
- THAT WAS THE FREAK
WITH THE CHAINSAW, NOT ME!
- STOP! DON'T!
- Ranmaru: CLASSIC DIVA.
- WASN'T THAT FUN? GOOD JOB.
- STOP THAT!
UGH! WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- Both: WE WANT FUN!
- SO WHY DID YOU COME HERE?
- 'CAUSE I WANTED TO HANG
WITH MY FRIEND.
I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
SPECIFIC IN MIND.
- WHO'S YOUR FRIEND?
- WE CAN WATCH THIS
IF YOU GUYS WANT.
IT'S 'SEVEN SAMURAI.'
I RENTED IT YESTERDAY!
- NO! LET'S WATCH
SOMETHING FUNNY!
- REALLY? DO YOU HAVE
SOMETHING AGAINST NINJAS?
- I JUST THINK NOW WOULD BE
A GOOD TIME TO LAUGH!
- TAKE THAT OUTSIDE!
- YOU HATE MOVIES.
- NO, I DO NOT.
- 'KAY, THEN HOW 'BOUT THIS.
WE, UH, SHOULD, UH...
- LET'S TRASH-TALK OUR EXES!
- I'M NOT TALKING TO
YOU ABOUT THAT!
- YAY, LOVE STORIES...
OR AS THEY SAY... LO-STO!
OUR FIRST STORYTELLER
WILL BE RANMARU.
- NO WAY! RIGHT NOW? OKAY.
SO THERE WAS...
UM, THIS GUY AND...
I CAN'T DO IT!
I FEEL LIKE SUCH A GOOBER!
I'M SO EMBARRASSED! I CAN'T
STOP LAUGHING! I'M SORRY!
- YOU'RE SO FREAKING LOUD!
THAT WHOLE SCENE
WAS UNCALLED FOR.
I DON'T REMEMBER EVER
BECOMING FRIENDS WITH YOU.
WHY ARE YOU LYING RIGHT NOW?
- WELL THEN YOUR MEMORY SUCKS.
DUDE, YOU TOTALLY GOT
ALL GHETTO ON MY DAD FOR ME!
- BECAUSE THE GUY WAS ASKING
FOR IT AND I HAD NO CHOICE.
TRUST ME, IT WASN'T
ABOUT YOU, OKAY?
IT COULD'VE BEEN
ABOUT ANIMAL RIGHTS
AND I'D STILL WANNA
PAY YOU BACK.
WHICH IS WHY, IF YOU NEED
MY HELP WITH ANYTHING,
JUST SAY THE WORD!
I'M NOT MESSING AROUND.
EVEN IF IT'S SOMETHING I
DON'T AGREE WITH, YOU GOT IT!
- UH, OKAY.
THAT'S FINE. YOU WANNA
DO SOMETHING FOR ME. GREAT.
IF YOU INSIST ON BEING
DRAMATIC ABOUT IT.
YOU LEAVE ME NO CHOICE BUT TO
BE PERFECTLY HONEST WITH YOU.
SEE, YOU'RE ANNOYING
THE CRAP OUT OF ME!
I CAN FEEL MY POPULARITY
MELTING OFF MY BONES
WHEN YOU'RE AROUND.
FACE IT, WE'RE FROM
TWO DIFFERENT WORLDS
AND I DON'T WANT TO MIGRATE.
SO, STARTING TOMORROW...
I THINK I GOT IT... WHAT THE
HELL... WHY ISN'T IT COMING OFF?
- ARE YOU INSANE?
OR LIKE SOME RABID ZOMBIE FREAK?
- NOT AT ALL.
I WAS TRYING TO HELP YOU GET
THAT MASK OFF YOUR FACE.
- THIS IS MY FACE!
- LITERALLY. BUT EVERYONE
KNOWS YOU'VE GOT TWO,
AND THE ONE YOU HAVE ON SUCKS.
I'D PREFER TO SEE
YOUR REAL FACE,
BUT THE MASK SEEMS
TO BE INFUSED.
WHICH IS REALLY KINDA SAD
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT.
- ( exhales angrily )
GO.
DON'T EVER COME NEAR ME AGAIN!
SOMEONE NEEDS TO LOCK YOU UP!
- DO YOU THINK
I TOOK IT TOO FAR?
- I THINK YOU GOT TOO CLOSE.
- WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- YOU HIT A NERVE.
- FOR REAL?
- I'M NOT SURE
YOU'RE EVEN HUMAN.
- SO THEN, YOU KNOW
WHAT HER ISSUE IS?
- NAH. THAT PART
DOESN'T INTEREST ME.
- OKAY.
- I CAN TELL IT'S BOTHERING YOU.
- YEAH, IT'S ALL
MAKING MY BRAIN HURT.
- YOU MUST GET THAT A LOT.
IN THAT CASE, I'M GONNA
LEAVE THESE WITH YOU.
I THINK THEY'LL BE HELPFUL.
POVERTY GOD ITEM,
TRAUMA STETHOSCOPE!
YOU CAN USE IT TO LISTEN TO
DEEP DARK SECRETS OF THE PAST
AND HEAR SUPPRESSED
FEELINGS WITHIN THE SOUL
THAT ARE REFUSING
TO BE DISCOVERED.
HUMANS ARE SO DARN COMPLICATED!
- THAT'S AWESOME. WAIT, DID YOU
SAY 'POVERTY GOD?' WHAT'S THAT?
- IT IS THE MAGICAL, RARE,
CELESTIAL CREATURE
STANDING BEFORE YOU.
- OH.
THIS IS GREAT.
AND THERE PROBABLY ISN'T
ANOTHER WAY TO EVER KNOW
WHO THE REAL ICHIKO IS.
- NO, NOT YET. I HAVEN'T
EVEN TRIED THAT HARD.
USING IT NOW WOULD
BE LIKE GIVING UP.
- Akane: I'M SO OVER TIT-CHIKO!
I CAN'T STAND THE THOUGHT
OF TRYING TO GET THROUGH
ANOTHER YEAR WITH HER!
- DON'T MAKE ME PUKE.
- THAT'S IT! I'M READY TO SEE
HER SQUIRM. HOW 'BOUT YOU?
- ( chattering )
- LOOKS LIKE SOMEONE
MUST'VE SLEPT IN.
- OH, MY GOD!
GO TO FREAKING CLASS!
WE'RE NOT GONNA BE BUDS
JUST 'CAUSE YOU WANNA BE
MY SECOND SKIN, STALKER!
DOES SHE REALLY NEED TO BE
AROUND ME ALL DAY?
I CAN'T EVEN BREATHE!
- HEY! THERE YOU ARE!
I BROUGHT YOU LUNCH...
- CAN YOU SHOW ME
HOW TO DO THIS AGAIN?
- SO YOU'RE GONNA MAKE HER WAIT?
I FEEL BAD
YOU HAVE TO AVOID RANMARU.
- AND WHO ARE YOU?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
I'M AKANE. YOU SHOULD KNOW
YOUR CLASSMATES' NAMES.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- I WANNA HELP YOU DITCH HER.
GIRLS ON OUR TIER
NEED TO STICK TOGETHER, RIGHT?
- Momiji: OH FOR CORN'S SAKE.
IS SHE SO DESPERATE
FOR POPULARITY
THAT SHE CAN'T SEE THAT TRASH
FOR WHAT IT IS?
- OH. OH, NO.
OH, NO-NO-NO.
CAPTAIN KUMAGAI, DO YOU
READ ME? COME IN.
REQUEST IMMEDIATE MOBILIZATION
OF THE CHAMPION OF JUSTICE.
- ALL SET, AKANE.
- YOU'RE SURE ABOUT THIS?
- I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER
BEEN MORE SURE.
THAT GIRL IS TRASH.
TAKE HER OUT.
- SO YOU DON'T THINK
THIS MAY BE TAKING IT TOO FAR?
- ARE YOU KIDDING RIGHT NOW?
IF THAT HAG FINDS HER
WAY BACK FROM WHEREVE
SHE'LL BE SO AFRAID OF US,
SHE'LL FEEL OBLIGATED TO
SUCK UP AND I CAN'T WAIT!
- ALL RIGHT. I THINK I'LL
GIVE HER A GOOD SCARE
BEFORE WE LEAVE HER.
- ( groaning )
- HOLY CRAP! WHAT HAPPENED?
- HE GOT CLOCKED FROM OUTSIDE!
- NO WAY!
THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING!
- FOLLOWING THE SHADOWY TRAILS
OF THE ONE WHO
EMBRACES LONELINESS.
HER FIGHT FOR FRIENDSHIP
GUIDES HER WAY.
HER HEART BECOMES
A WARRIOR FOR NOBILITY.
AND MOMENTARILY, SHE CONCEALS
THAT CHERRY BLOSSOM SMILE.
RANMARU HAS ARRIVED!
SO TAKE A SEAT, PUNKS!
- HOW DID YOU FIND US?
- YOU TAKE A SEAT!
IF YOU THINK YOU CAN
TAKE ME ON, THEN LET'S GO!
- WHO THE HELL IS THAT?
- YOU SCREW WITH MY FRIENDS,
YOU SCREW WITH ME!
SHE GOT MY KNIFE!
- SMILE! I WAS TRYING
TO BE POLITE!
- ( groaning )
- YOU TWO WITH HIM?
GET OUTTA HERE AND TAKE
THAT PATHETIC WUSS WITH YOU!
- Both: SIR, YES, SIR!
- ( crying )
- ( footsteps retreating )
- LADY BUG, ARE YOU OKAY?
WHOA, SHE DISAPPEARED.
WHEN DID THAT HAPPEN?
- ( door closing )
- ( whimpering )
- OH, I SHOULD'VE KNOWN.
SENDING GOONS IN
TO DO YOUR DIRTY WORK
- IS KIND OF A PANSY-ASS MOVE.
- SHUT UP! THIS HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH YOU!
- OF COURSE IT DOES.
WE'RE ALL IN THE SAME CLASS.
AND AS A WISE WOMAN ONCE SAID,
GIRLS ON OUR TIER SHOULD
STICK TOGETHER, RIGHT?
- ( crackling )
- HUH?
THE HECK IS THAT?
- THAT WAS STUPID.
WHAT IS HER DEAL?
I'M GLAD I CAME TO
BEFORE SHE FINISHED HER SPEECH.
WELL, AT LEAST SHE GOT
TO PLAY HERO.
NOW MAYBE SHE'LL GIVE ME
WHAT I REALLY WANT
AND QUIT BEING A STALKER.
YEAH. I CAN'T WAIT.
- ( glass shattering )
- ( explosion )
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- DON'T FORGET TO STEER CLEAR
OF THE OLD BUILDING
WHEN WALKING TO CLASS TODAY.
- RANMARU!
- ( rumbling )
- ( gasping )
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
WHY ARE YOU TRYING TO SAVE
US NOW? YOU'LL GET HURT!
- I HONESTLY HAVE NO CLUE.
I'M GUESSING THIS THING
FELL ON ME AND I CAUGHT IT.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
THAT PATH LEADS TO THE HALLWAY.
HURRY, BEFORE IT COLLAPSES!
- BUT HOW ARE YOU GONNA
GET OUT OF HERE?
- LOOK. JUST GO. HURRY!
- ( panting )
- HEY, HOLD ON!
WHAT HAPPENED
TO MISS KARATE CHOP?
- LIKE I KNOW!
- YOU HAVE TO!
IS SHE STILL TRAPPED IN THERE?
- GET OFF ME!
- WE DON'T KNOW ANYTHING!
- JUST WAIT!
- I'M NOT MESSING AROUND.
EVEN IF IT'S SOMETHING I DON'T
AGREE WITH, YOU GOT IT!
- YOU'RE SO STUPID.
HA! SEE WHAT HAPPENS WHEN
YOU DO THINGS FOR "FRIENDS".
YOU END UP STUCK IN
SITUATIONS LIKE THESE!
I GUESS YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN!
I WAS NEVER DUMB ENOUGH
TO SAY WE'RE FRIENDS SO I'M OUT!
I DON'T CARE IF YOU OWE ME!
I TOLD YOU I DIDN'T WANT
ANYTHING FROM YOU
AND I MEANT IT!
IF YOU'D TAKEN THE HINT
AND LEFT ME ALONE
YOU WOULDN'T BE STUCK
IN THERE RIGHT NOW!
IDIOT!
- IT'S OBVS YOU WANNA
HELP HER. SO DO IT.
- OH COME ON.
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK I'M
GONNA GO IN THERE?
- GEEZ, CAN YOU HEAR YOURSELF?
YOU'RE STANDING THERE
OBSESSING OVER IT
AND YELLING AT THE WALL
TO NO ONE.
IF YOU WEREN'T
WORRIED ABOUT HER,
YOU'D HAVE BEEN GONE ALREADY.
- YOU THINK YOU HAVE
ALL THE ANSWERS DON'T YOU?
- NOT ALL, BUT RANMARU WILL DIE
IF SOMEONE DOESN'T HELP HER.
- MAYBE SO, BUT...
IF I HELP HER THEN,
SHE'LL PROBABLY WANT TO BE MY...
I JUST CAN'T.
- WOW. THIS IS A LOT HEAVIER
THAN I THOUGHT IT WAS.
LET ME GUESS.
IT'S NOT JUST A FRIEND THING.
YOU DON'T WANNA BE
CLOSE TO ANYONE.
- SHUT UP! SHUT UP!
SHUT UP! SHUT UP!
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT!
- YOU'RE RIGHT. I DON'T.
- YOU DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT ME!
- NOBODY DOES!
- NOPE. YOU WON'T LET 'EM.
- ( crying ) PLEASE, I CAN'T
HANDLE GOING THROUGH THAT AGAIN.
I WON'T SURVIVE IT AGAIN!
- Kurumi: IT'S ALMOST
VALENTINE'S DAY.
HAVE YOU DECIDED WHO YOU'RE
GOING TO GIVE CHOCOLATE TO YET?
- YEAH, I WAS THINKING
ABOUT YUSUKE.
'CAUSE OUT OF ALL THE BOYS IN
SCHOOL, HE'S THE NICEST TO ME.
- HE IS REALLY NICE.
THAT'S WHY I WAS THINKING
ABOUT GIVING HIM CHOCOLATES
FOR VALENTINE'S DAY, TOO!
- YOU WERE?
- BUT THERE'S NO WAY HE'D
EVER LIKE ME MORE THAN YOU!
- YOU DON'T KNOW THAT!
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
SHOULD WE BOTH GIVE HIM
DIFFERENT CHOCOLATE BOXES?
- I DON'T THINK IT WOULD
BE RIGHT FOR EITHER OF US
TO BE WITH HIM.
FRIENDS SHOULD NEVER DO THAT
TO EACH OTHER!
- YEAH, LET'S DO IT
AT THE SAME TIME THEN.
- UH, ICHIKO.
HAPPY VALENTINE'S DAY!
- ( growling )
WHAT A PRETTY BROOCH!
- OH. THANKS!
- IT'S THE MOST BEAUTIFUL ONE
I'VE EVER SEEN!
IS THERE ANY WAY
I COULD HAVE IT?
- PRETTY PLEASE?
- ( gasping )
NO, YOU CAN HAVE SOMETHING ELSE.
( thinking ) THIS WAS
FROM YUSUKE.
- OKAY.
I GUESS THAT MEANS IT'S
MORE IMPORTANT TO YOU
THAN YOUR FRIENDS.
FINE THEN, STARTING TOMORROW
YOU AND I AREN'T
FRIENDS ANYMORE.
- HAVE FUN WITH YOUR STUPID PIN!
- NO! KURUMI. PLEASE WAIT!
OKAY, YOU CAN HAVE IT!
- ( giggling )
ADORABLE.
OH, AND GUESS WHAT?
I THINK I'M GONNA TELL
YUSUKE THAT I LIKE HIM,
- SO HE CAN BE MY BOYFRIEND!
- BUT...
- BUT YOU ALREADY SAID
THAT WE SHOULDN'T...
- I MADE UP MY MIND!
BUT ONE THING ISN'T RIGHT.
I WOULD LOVE YOUR BLESSING.
WILL YOU PLEASE PRAY
FOR EVERYTHING TO GO WELL
WITH ME AND HIM?
I'M SO GLAD WE'RE FRIENDS
AND THAT YOU'LL DO THIS FOR ME!
- AND EVEN IF IT MEANS LOSING
MY FRIEND AND BEING ALL ALONE.
PLEASE, GOD.
LET EVERYTHING GO WELL
FOR KURUMI AND YUSUKE TOMORROW.
- SORRY. BUT,
I THINK I LIKE ICHIKO.
- ( grunting )
- OH, YUSUKE,
I FEEL SORRY FOR YOU!
AND YOU GAVE HER
SUCH A NICE GIFT!
YEAH. SHE SAID IT WAS
SOME CHEAP, LAME TOY
AND GAVE IT TO ME.
BUT I REALLY LOVE IT!
- OH. HI, YUSUKE!
- I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT'S BEEN
BRINGING YOU DOWN LATELY,
BUT SOMETHING'S GOING ON.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT OR WHO IT'S ABOUT.
I DON'T REALLY CARE. I JUST
KNOW IT'S OLD AND I'M OVER IT.
IT'S NOT ANYTHING
I HAD EVER WANTED TO ADMIT,
BUT WHEN YOU'RE ALL MOPEY-FACE,
I CAN'T FUNCTION.
I'M ALLERGIC TO YOUR GLOOM.
- SO WHAT HAPPENS, THEN?
- I'M GLAD YOU ASKED.
YOU'RE GONNA STOP ACTING
LIKE A SELFISH WEINIE!
SNAP OUT OF IT AND CHEER UP!
YOU CARE ABOUT OTHERS
AND THAT IS OKAY.
YOU ONLY MAKE IT
HARDER ON YOURSELF
WHEN YOU PRETEND YOU DON'T.
IF YOU WON'T ACCEPT IT
AND LET GO OF YOUR PAST, THEN...
( groaning )
- QUIT TRYING TO TEACH ME
HOW TO LIVE!
I DON'T NEED LECTURES
FROM A POVERTY GOD!
- DON'T MISS! WHOOPSIE-DAISY!
GET BACK.... OW, THAT HURTS!
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU!
- ALL DONE.
- THAT WAS THE WORST PAIN I'VE
EVER FELT IN MY ENTIRE LIFE!
- I'M FLATTERED, BUT IT'LL START
TO FEEL BETTER SOON.
- HUSH! NO IT WON'T!
- HEADS UP!
- REALLY?
- AND HERE'S YOUR MISSION.
JUST THIS ONCE, TRY TO BE HONEST
ABOUT WHAT IT IS YOU WANT AND
WHAT YOU THINK YOU SHOULD DO.
I WANT THE ANSWERS TO COME
FROM YOUR TRUE SELF.
NOT FROM THAT OBNOXIOUS WEIRDO
YOU LIKE TO PRETEND TO BE.
- STARTING TO GET HEAVY,
EVEN FOR ME.
THIS IS NOT THE WAY
MY LIFE IS GONNA END, THOUGH.
- ( crackling )
- HUH?
- WHAT'S THAT LITTLE GUY DOING
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS?
- OH, MY GOD! IT'S A SNAKE!
- NOT QUITE. WASSUP?
- LADY PANTS?
WHAT THE CRAP ARE YOU DOING
IN THE MOUTH OF A SNAKE?
I THOUGHT YOU ESCAPED.
WHY ARE YOU BACK?
IF WE DON'T GET YOU OUTTA HERE,
YOU'RE GONNA DIE!
THIS IS GOOD.
WHAT IS IT?
- HAPPINESS ENERGY.
ALL NATURAL FLAVORS.
WHAT DO YOU THINK? YOU HAPPY?
- NO, IT DOESN'T HAPPEN
THAT FAST, GOOBER.
HEY, NEVER MIND.
MAYBE IT DOES HAPPEN THAT FAST!
- THEN LET'S START MAKING
OUR WAY OUT!
- THAT IS ONE CUTE MONKEY.
BUT HOW IS IT SUPPOSED
TO HELP US DOWN HERE?
- ( screaming )
- ( rumbling )
- HE'LL BLOW THE DEBRIS AWAY!
- WOW! THAT'S AMAZING!
- ( both yelling )
- ( explosion )
- THE GREAT
RANMARU RINDO RETURNS!
I GUESS I OWE YOU
TWO FAVORS NOW, HUH?
- LISTEN, IF YOU WANT
TO HELP ME.
THEN I NEED YOU TO STOP
FOLLOWING ME AROUND
ALL THE TIME.
- UM...
YEAH, SURE. IF THAT'S WHAT
YOU REALLY WANT, YOU GOT IT.
I'M GONE.
BUT FIRST... I HAVE TO KNOW,
WHY YOU ALWAYS PUSH THE PEOPLE
WHO CARE FOR YOU AWAY.
SOMEONE YOU LOVED IN THE PAST
SCREWED YOU OVER HARD CORE?
- YEAH. HOW'D...
- MOMIJI...
I WAS WORRIED AND SHE TOLD ME
SHE'D ALWAYS HAD A HUNCH
ABOUT THAT BEING THE CASE.
- IT'S NOT A HUNCH.
SHE'S GOT A BIG MOUTH.
- THEN THERE'S THIS.
- WHAT IS IT?
- MOMIJI GAVE IT TO ME.
SHE SAID BY WEARING IT,
I'D BE ABLE TO LISTEN TO
WHAT'S IN YOUR HEART.
IF YOU DON'T WANT ME
TO USE IT, I WON'T.
I KNOW YOUR PAST IS DIFFICULT
FOR YOU TO FACE,
BUT I'M DIFFERENT.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE
AND I WANT TO HELP.
EVEN IF IT MEANS
GIVING YOU SOME TIME.
BUT I HOPE...
I HOPE SOMEDAY
I'LL BE ABLE TO EARN YOUR TRUST
AND YOU'LL OPEN UP TO ME.
OR, LET ME USE THAT.
REALLY? ARE YOU SURE?
- YEAH, BUT IF YOU
DON'T WANT TO...
- OH, NO WAY, I WANNA LISTEN!
I WANNA GET TO KNOW
THE REAL YOU EVEN BETTER.
- Girl: NO WAY, SO THAT WAS
YOUR PLAN THE WHOLE TIME?
- YEAH, IT'S SO MUCH MORE FUN
IF YOU KEEP HER CLOSE TO YOU.
BEING MEAN WILL
ONLY SCARE HER OFF
AND YOU WON'T EVER GET ANYTHING.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS
PRETEND YOU'RE HER FRIEND
AND SHE'LL GIVE YOU WHATEVER.
MORNING, ICHIKO.
YOU CAN HAVE THIS BACK.
I DON'T NEED IT.
YUSUKE SAID HE WAS GOING TO
BUY ME SOMETHING BETTER.
- BUT THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR GIVING IT TO ME.
- I DON'T WANT IT.
- WHAT?
- I DON'T WANT ANY OF IT.
- WHY? WHAT'S WRONG?
THAT UGLY BROOCH
IS WHAT'S WRONG!
GET THIS PIECE OF JUNK
OFF MY DESK!
DON'T GO FEELING SORRY FOR ME.
IT'S TOTALLY NORMAL FOR GIRLS
TO GET JEALOUS OF SOMEONE
WHO'S PRETTY AND POPULAR.
LUCKILY I'VE LEARNED
NOT TO LET IT AFFECT ME
AND I'M A LOT STRONGER
BECAUSE OF IT.
- TRYING TO AVOID MAKING FRIENDS
DOESN'T MAKE YOU STRONG.
- SCREW 'FRIENDS!'
THAT'S JUST A SUPERFICIAL TITLE.
IT'S A JOKE!
IT'S SOMETHING PEOPLE SAY SO
THEY CAN USE EACH OTHER!
NO ONE GIVES A CRAP WHO YOU ARE!
THEY JUST DON'T WANT
TO FEEL GUILTY!
IF SOMEONE WANTS TO BE FRIENDS,
THEY'RE ASKING PERMISSION TO
USE ME AND I AM SO OVER THAT!
I'M MY ONLY FRIEND NOW,
AND I'M FINE WITH IT!
EVERYONE'S EXACTLY THE SAME.
EVEN YOU. SOMEDAY YOU'LL FIND
A WAY TO USE ME, THEN LEAVE.
- NO, I WOULDN'T!
THAT'S NOT WHO I AM!
- I KNOW YOU DON'T THINK
YOU WOULD RIGHT NOW, BUT...
- WHY TELL ME ABOUT YOUR PAST
IF YOU CAN'T LET IT GO?
I GET IT. YOU DON'T WANT TO BE
HURT LIKE THAT AGAIN. WHO DOES?
BUT YOU HAVE TO GIVE PEOPLE
A CHANCE TO PROVE YOU WRONG!
I AM NOT KURUMI
AND I NEVER WILL BE.
- I KNOW.
- I PROMISE YOU.
NO. I SWEAR ON EVERYTHING HOLY,
I AM NEVER GOING TO BETRAY YOU.
- YEAH, RIGHT. YOU SO WILL.
- NO. I WON'T.
- YOU WILL.
- WON'T.
- YOU WILL!
- NO, I WON'T!
- I KNOW HOW THIS ENDS!
- THE HELL YOU DO!
- YOU WILL LEAVE!
- I WON'T!
- WHERE AM I GONNA GO? TRUST ME!
- WILL WILL WILL WILL WILL!
- ( breathing heavily )
- I'M SORRY. BUT I'VE SEEN IT
TOO MANY TIMES.
- NOT FROM ME.
AND I SWEAR YOU NEVER WILL.
I AM NOT THEM.
- YOU...
YOU PROMISE?
YOU WON'T GO?
- TOTALLY! CROSS MY HEART!
- ( sobbing )
- READY FOR SOME KARAOKE,
LADY PANTS?
- FAR FROM READY, I'M UNWILLING.
- YAY! IT'S GONNA BE FUN!
IT'S ONLY BEEN ONE DAY,
MISS RANMARU.
I'M NOT READY FOR KARAOKE.
- AGAIN WITH THE 'MISS RANMARU!'
HOW DO YOU EXPECT OUR FRIENDSHIP
TO GROW WHEN YOU TREAT ME
LIKE A MATH TEACHER?
CALL ME BY MY NAME!
- LET'S GO! UNLESS YOU'D RATHER
COUNT THE FIBERS IN YOUR RUG?
- Ichiko: SHUT UP!
UM, RANMARU?
SEE, I'M TRYING.
CAN I ASK A FAVOR?
YOU ALWAYS CALL ME LADY PANTS.
WILL YOU PLEASE USE MY NAME?
- ( laughing )
I THINK I CAN DO THAT, ICHIKO!
- Momiji: WELL, I THINK YOU BOTH
SUCK. I WAS PROMISED KARAOKE.
- Ichiko: UGH! SHUT YOUR
FAT TRAP, POVERTY PUTZ!
- Students: THIS WEEK'S.
- Nadeshiko: OH, NADESHIKO.
- ( talking very fast )