- ( train horn blowing )
- ( yawning )
- Girls: ONE, TWO. ONE, TWO.
ONE, TWO. ONE, TWO.
- HUH?
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
DOWN THERE?
- MMM?
- WHAT ARE YOU
DOING UP THERE?
APPARENTLY YOU HAVEN'T
LEFT TOWN YET.
WHY'D YOU HAVE TO SHOW UP
AND HELP HER OUT?
YOU HAVE MADE MY JOB HERE
VERY DIFFICULT.
- WELL, WE ALL GOT
JOBS TO DO, DON'T WE?
ON TOP OF MAKING LIFE
HARDER FOR YOU,
I CAN'T LEAVE THIS PLACE UNTIL
YOU'VE BEEN VANQUISHED.
- YOU WANNA VANQUISH ME?
DIDN'T YOUR MOTHER EVER
TEACH YOU TO BE MORE GENTLEMANLY
AND KIND TO LADIES?
- YEAH, WELL. WHEN YOU
DON'T HAVE BREASTS,
I DON'T REALLY CONSIDER
YOU AN ACTUAL WOMAN.
- HEY, MASSIVE JERK ALERT.
BRING ME A SPEAR.
IF WE DON'T HAVE ONE, BRING
ME SOMETHING SHARP AND POINTY.
GOTCHA.
- I DIDN'T THINK YOU COULD EAT
RAW FISH OUT OF THIS RIVER.
- DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
I'M NOT FISHING FOR A FISH.
I'M USING POVERTY GOD
ITEM TO SUMMON A HELPER
FROM THE PLAIN OF HIGH HEAVEN.
- THAT'S COOL.
- BRING IT, DESTITUTE ONE.
( grunting )
IS THAT YOU? MOMO'O?
- LONG TIME NO SEE, MOMIJI.
- MOMO'O? IS IT REALLY YOU?
- IT IS ME, MOMIJI. IT IS,
IT IS. I'VE MISSED YOU SO HARD.
I WAITED AND WAITED,
BUT YOU NEVER CAME HOME,
SO I WAS WORRIED YOU HAD
BEEN TOSSED AROUND
BY THE ANGRY SEAS OF THE
HUMAN REALM, AND BROKENHEARTED.
YOU HAD FALLEN INTO A
LIFE OF DRUGS AND PROSTITUTION.
- GEEZ, WHAT AM I, A WANNABE
POP STAR ALL OF THE SUDDEN?
UGH. I HAVE TO ADMIT THOUGH,
IT HAS BEEN A LONG TIME,
HASN'T IT?
- SHAKE.
- ( mimics barking )
- OTHER HAND.
- ( barking )
- NOW BONDAGE.
- THAT'S A GOOD BOY.
HERE'S YOUR REWARD.
THIS IS WHAT YOU WANTED,
ISN'T IT?
- SPEAK.
- OH. HELL. YES.
- ( sighs )
- SO WHAT'S THE DEAL
WITH THE LITTLE DUDE?
- HE'S A DOG DEITY.
MOMO'O INUGAMI.
- HEY, WAIT JUST A MINUTE.
YOU'RE A HUMAN, RIGHT?
TELL ME, WHERE DOES A
PATHETIC EARTH DWELLER LIKE YOU
GET OFF TALKING TO MOMIJI
ALL CASUAL LIKE THAT, HUH?
- THIS ONE LIKES IT ROUGH.
- YEAH, I KINDA PICKED UP ON
THAT EARLIER.
- ( exclaiming )
- ( gasps )
- I'M A GENIUS. I JUST
THOUGHT OF THE BEST WAY
TO STEAL ICHIKO'S HAPPINESS
ENERGY.
AND SHE'LL NEVER SEE
IT COMING. THAT IS, OF COURSE,
IF YOU WOULDN'T MIND HELPING
ME OUT WITH HER, MOMO'O.
- HECK NO, I DON'T. FOR YOU,
I'D GO THROUGH FIRE, WATER, OR A
MOUNTAIN OF NEEDLES.
YOU NAME IT,
AND I'LL BE ON IT, LADY.
- GOOD GRIEF, THIS GUY'S
A NEEDY LITTLE BITCH.
- OKAY, FIRST THINGS FIRST.
WE NEED SOME BOILING
WATER, PRONTO.
- ( gasps ) IT'S WHISTLING.
I WONDER WHAT
SHE'S GONNA DO WITH IT NOW.
- DRINK UP.
- ( exclaiming )
- UM, IS THAT SAFE,
'CAUSE THAT DON'T LOOK SAFE.
- ( grunting ) HERE IT COMES.
( screaming )
- WHOA. NICE.
WHAT'S THAT ALL ABOUT?
- WHEN MOMO'O REACHES
A CERTAIN LEVEL OF PLEASURE,
HE CAN'T HELP BUT TRANSFORM
INTO HIS TRUE FORM
AS A DOGGIE DEITY.
- MAN, THAT IS MESSED UP.
- ( snarling )
- Momiji: WHILE DOG
DEITIES ARE REVERED
FOR FULFILLING THEIR
MASTERS' DESIRES,
THEY'RE ALSO WELL LOVED AS
BEARERS OF GOOD LUCK.
AND AS A RESULT OF
THEIR INTENSE LOYALTY,
THEY ARE FEARED
AS VENGEFUL GODS,
WHO MERCILESSLY BRING
ABOUT CALAMITY
TO THOSE WHO WOULD DO HARM
TO THEIR MASTERS.
- A VENGEFUL DEITY.
THAT'S GREAT.
WAIT, ARE WE SAFE? WHAT THE...
- ( yelping )
- I DID NOT SEE THAT COMING.
SO HE SHRANK.
WELL PLAYED. TRICKY.
- NOW, ARE YOU READY, MOMO'O?
- ( yelps )
- YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE WHO CAN
CARRY OUT THIS MISSION. OKAY?
- ( humming )
THINGS ARE GREAT, LATELY.
THE POVERTY GOD HASN'T BEEN
SHOWING UP, WHICH IS SO NICE.
MAYBE SHE'S FINALLY GIVEN
UP AND GONE HOME.
THAT WOULD BE AWESOME.
- THAT HAS TO BE HER.
COME TO ME, ICHIKO.
- WHILE YOU PRETEND
TO BE A REAL DOG,
I WANT YOU TO GET AS CLOSE
TO ICHIKO AS YOU CAN.
ONCE SHE STARTS TRUSTING YOU,
YOU SHOULD BE ABLE TO
TAKE AWAY HER HAPPINESS ENERGY
WITH NO PROBLEM.
HEY. DON'T YOU BE JUDGING ME.
THIS JOB IS A PAIN AND
THAT GIRL IS CRAY CRAY.
AND, MOMO'O,
IF YOU'RE SUCCESSFUL,
I PROMISE TO GIVE YOU
THE ABSOLUTE GREATEST,
MOST AMAZING REWARD
YOU'VE EVER HAD.
- ( gasps ) THE ABSOLUTE
GREATEST,
MOST AMAZING REWARD
I'VE EVER HAD?
THAT SEEMS MORE LIKE AN
EXECUTION, NOT JUST S AND M.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT A THING,
MOMIJI.
IT'S MY JOB AS A DOG DEITY TO
FULFILL MY MASTERS' WISHES.
TAKE THIS SECRET TECHNIQUE.
TEMPTATION!
- SHE'S WALKING AWAY.
WHAT KIND OF COLD
HEARTED CREATURE
CAN WITHSTAND THIS TEMPTATION?
- THERE'S SOMETHING ABOUT THAT
DOG I DON'T TRUST.
- Man: EXCUSE ME, MISS SAKURA?
- SORRY, I DIDN'T SEE YOU THERE.
- I DON'T REALLY HAVE
A PROBLEM WITH YOU
KEEPING A LITTLE PET HERE,
BUT I'M GONNA HAVE TO INSIST
YOU KEEP HIM ON A LEASH
WHEN YOU TAKE HIM
FOR A WALK.
- WAIT, WHAT PET?
( gasps )
OH, BUT SIR, THIS IS NOT MY DOG.
- I DUNNO, IT LOOKS TO ME
LIKE HE THINKS HE'S YOUR DOG.
- WHAT IS GOING ON HERE?
- I JUST WANT TO MAKE
SURE I DON'T GET SUED
IF HE BITES A KID OR SOMETHING.
LIKE I SAID, IT'S NO BIG DEAL,
JUST KEEP HIM ON A LEASH.
- ( whimpering )
- WHY SHOULD I HAVE
TO TAKE THE DOG?
OH, WHATEVER. I'LL JUST
FIND SOMEONE AT SCHOOL
WHO WANTS TO
RESCUE HIM, I GUESS.
DON'T GET ATTACHED, MUTT.
I'M ONLY TAKING CARE OF YOU
BECAUSE I DON'T HAVE
ANY OTHER CHOICE.
- YOU FOOL.
ONCE I'VE GOTTEN INSIDE,
IT'S ALL OVER.
I'LL STEAL YOUR GOOD LUCK,
AND YOU WON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT HIT YOU.
- ( exclaims in disgust )
IT'S DISGUSTING.
- GAH, THIS PLACE GETS
MESSY SO FAST.
- I HAD IT CLEANED
THREE DAYS AGO,
AND IT'S ALREADY A
COMPLETE DISASTER.
- THREE DAYS AGO?
UGH, THIS CHICK IS NASTY.
- I GUESS I'LL JUST HAVE 'EM
COME BACK, THEN.
- OF COURSE. HER BUTLER, SUWANO,
MUST'VE DONE EVERYTHING FOR
HER UP UNTIL NOW.
SHE COULD AT LEAST
CLEAN UP AFTER HERSELF.
IT'S GONNA TAKE MORE THAN
A FILTHY HOME TO STOP ME.
IT'S TIME FOR MOMIJI'S
POVERTY GOD ITEM.
THE GABRIEL TWO
THOUSAND AND TWELVE!
- A FALSE TEETH TYPE ABSORBER,
WHICH CONSUMES A
PERSON'S HAPPINESS ENERGY
WHILE ALSO INFLICTING
INCREDIBLE PAIN!
- PUTTING IN PLACE.
- UGH. I WISH I COULD
FIGURE OUT A WAY TO KEEP
THESE DIRTY DISHES
FROM PILING UP.
OH, WELL. OKAY, LET'S SEE, WHERE
DID I PUT THOSE GOODIES AGAIN?
- LOCKING ON TARGET.
YOUR HAPPINESS ENERGY IS MINE.
- NO. DAMN IT.
- ( gasps )
- SO CLOSE. ALMOST HAD HER.
MY EYES. MY EYES.
( screams )
WHAT THE HELL KIND OF
HAPPINESS ENERGY DOES SHE HAVE?
- OH GREAT. WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU MUST BE PRETTY
TIRED TO LIE DOWN RIGHT
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE FLOOR.
- IT'S OFFICIAL. I'M IN HELL.
- MOMO'O?
THAT'S A WEIRD NAME.
- ( laughing )
YOU'RE COMPLETELY
VULNERABLE, NOW.
HAPPINESS ENERGY WON'T
PROTECT YOU FROM ME
WHEN YOU'RE SLEEPING.
YOU'RE THROUGH.
( screams )
IS THIS HER FREAKING GOOD
LUCK AT WORK, AGAIN?
OR IS SHE JUST A
REALLY DEEP SLEEPER.
OH, YES. THAT FEELS SO GOOD.
AH. THAT WAS AMAZING.
NO, IF I EXPERIENCE MUCH MORE
PLEASURE THAN THIS,
I'LL TURN BACK INTO
MY HUMAN FORM.
DAMN IT, I WILL NOT
LET YOU BEAT ME.
EMERGENCY, MOMIJI.
I NEED YOUR HELP!
- AND DO YOU KNOW WHAT
SHE DID AFTER THAT?
SHE HELD UP HER
GIANT RACK AND SAID,
"AND YOU HAVEN'T
CONFUSED BEING A GOD
OF FLAT BROKENESS WITH
FLAT CHESTEDNESS?"
THAT IS BOTH CRUEL AND RUDE.
- WELL, HAVE YOU TRIED
DRINKING MORE MILK?
- YES, I HAVE.
I'VE BEEN DRINKING MILK FOR
A HUNDRED YEARS.
( grunts ) I CAN'T STAND
THAT EVIL TITCHIKO.
I SWEAR, MOMO'O BETTER
TAKE HER OUT FOR ME!
- ( exclaiming )
( howling )
- Teacher: OKAY. HERE ARE
YOUR QUIZZES FROM YESTERDAY.
- SEEMS ABOUT RIGHT.
- WAY TO GO!
- THEY SHOULD CREATE A SPECIAL
ADVANCED CLASS JUST FOR YOU.
- OH. THAT'S NOT TRUE.
YOU'RE SWEET, BUT YOU BOYS
ARE EVERY BIT AS SMART AS ME.
- YOU'RE THE BEST.
- Boys: YOU ARE
SO AWESOME, ICHIKO!
- Momo'o: COLD SHOULDER
FROM GIRLS, POPULAR WITH BOYS.
EVERYTHING IS JUST LIKE
MOMIJI SAID IT WOULD BE.
AND NOW I KNOW FOR SURE
HER HAPPINESS ENERGY
IS GOING TO COMPLETELY
PROTECT HER.
IT'S HIGH TIME TO
REGROUP A LITTLE
AND LEARN MORE ABOUT MINE ENEMY.
ESPECIALLY AFTER WHAT'S
HAPPENED TO HOT MESS.
- WATER. MY HEAD IS
ABOUT TO EXPLODE.
- ICHIKO SAKURA
OBSERVATION RECORD.
EXCELLENT GRADES,
A NATURAL ATHLETE.
HER BRAINS AND BEAUTY
ARE WELL ABOVE AVERAGE.
MEN CONSTANTLY
FLIRT WITH HER.
AND HER PERSONALITY IS,
SHOCKINGLY VIOLENT AT TIMES.
EVERYTHING IS EXACTLY AS IT
HAS BEEN REPORTED.
SHE'S HOME.
( yelping )
- ( chuckles ) HEY, PUPPY DOG.
- WHAT'S THIS?
SHE'S IN A GOOD MOOD.
- ( chuckling )
- THIS TYPE OF BEHAVIOR
WASN'T IN MOMIJI'S REPORT.
- ( laughing )
- I'VE NEVER SEEN HER SMILE,
LIKE, ANYWHERE BEFORE.
WHAT IS THAT?
WHAT IS SHE READING?
WHAT IS THIS?
OH, YEAH.
THEY MUST BE LETTERS
FROM THAT BUTLER.
I WISH IT WAS SOMETHING I COULD
ACTUALLY USE AGAINST HER.
- Suwano: I WAS GOING
THROUGH MY PHOTOS,
AND AN OLD ONE OF YOU CAME
UP, MISS ICHIKO.
AT THE TIME, IT
WAS IMPOSSIBLE FOR ME
TO HAVE KNOWN HOW VOLUPTUOUS...
THAT IS TO SAY, HOW BEAUTIFUL,
YOU WOULD GROW UP TO BE.
- IS HE SEXUALLY HARASSING
HER THROUGH MAIL?
- AT MISS SUMIRE'S SUGGESTION,
I HAVE TAKEN UP TAI CHI.
I AM NOW IN THE PROCESS
OF TOUGHENING UP MY BODY,
SO THAT SOMEDAY I'LL BE ABLE TO
PROPERLY FIGHT ANY MAN
WHO ASKS YOU TO MARRY HIM.
AND THIS IS THE GUY WHO WAS
ABOUT TO DIE IN THE HOSPITAL?
HER SUBSTITUTE FATHER.
- THIS MAN IS SUWANO.
HE IS THE ONLY PERSON SHE'S
ALLOWED HERSELF TO CARE FOR.
THEIR BOND MAY BE
CONSIDERABLY DEEPER
THAN WHAT SHE HAS WITH
HER REAL PARENTS.
- IF ONLY YOU COULD DIRECT
EVEN A TENTH OF THE KINDNESS
YOU'VE GIVEN TO YOUR BUTLER
TOWARD OTHER PEOPLE.
LUCKILY, MOMIJI GAVE ME
ANOTHER POVERTY GOD ITEM.
THE CURSING STRAW EFFIGY MAN,
TYPE MINI.
- IT'S A UNIQUE ITEM, WHICH,
LIKE IT OR NOT,
BRINGS UNHAPPINESS TO EVERYONE
WITHIN A ONE METER RADIUS
WHEN YOU PULL THE NAIL
OUT OF ITS HEART.
- THERE'S SIMPLY NO ESCAPING
THE CURSE OF THIS GUY.
- ( moaning )
NO. SUWANO...
- AW. I WONDER WHAT
SHE'S CRYING FOR?
NO. OH, WAIT. I'M PRETTY SURE
SHE'S JUST DREAMING.
( screaming )
I PULLED HIS HEART NAIL OUT.
THIS IS BAD! I HAVE
TO GET AWAY NOW,
OR THE CURSE WILL GET ME, TOO!
AIR. AIR.
( gasping ) LET GO OF ME.
WHY ISN'T ANYTHING
HAPPENING TO HER?
IS THIS BECAUSE OF HER
STUPID GOOD LUCK AGAIN?
HER HAPPINESS ENERGY
PISSES ME OFF.
- Ichiko: CRAP. I OVERSLEPT.
WAIT, WHY IS MOMO'O
SLEEPING LIKE THAT?
WEIRDO. I GOTTA GO.
- ( door closes )
- ( knocking on door )
- Woman 1: HELLO? HOUSEKEEPING.
- Woman 2: WE CAN JUST WALK IN?
- YEAH, OF COURSE
WE CAN JUST WALK IN.
HOW ELSE ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO GET THE JOB DONE?
- OH. IT STINKS IN HERE.
- WE CAN START CLEANING UP
THIS ROOM FIRST.
APPARENTLY, WE CAN
THROW EVERYTHING AWAY,
EXCEPT FOR THE GIRL'S CLOTHES
AND THE DISHES.
OH, BUT WE'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO TOUCH ANYTHING
ON THE DESK IN HER ROOM.
- 'KAY. SO, UM...
THIS WAS IN HER BED.
WHAT SHOULD I DO WITH IT?
- WE PROBABLY DON'T WANT TO
THROW THAT AWAY.
- NO. IT'S GONE. BUT HOW?
WHERE IS IT?
I THOUGHT I MADE IT CLEAR
NO ONE WAS TO TOUCH
ANYTHING ON THE DESK.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY
SHE HAS TO BE SO LOUD.
IF YOU DIDN'T TOUCH IT,
THEN WHY IS IT GONE?
YES, A BOX WITH A
FLORAL PATTERN.
- IS SHE TALKING ABOUT THAT BOX
WITH THE BUTLER'S LETTERS?
- WHAT? YOU MEAN YOU
THREW IT AWAY?
THEN, WHERE DID YOU DROP
OFF THE TRASH?
- I REALIZE YOU'RE UPSET,
BUT I REALLY CAN'T HELP YOU.
I MEAN, THE BEST I CAN DO IS
TELL YOU IF IT CAME IN TODAY,
IT'LL PROBABLY
BE OVER THERE.
- THAT'S FINE. I DON'T MIND
LOOKING FOR IT.
- NO, WAIT. HOLD ON.
- EVERYTHING'S FINE. I'M
SURE TO FIND IT. I HAVE TO.
AFTER ALL, I HAVE HAPPINESS
ENERGY ON MY SIDE, DON'T I?
LOSING IT... LOSING IT IS
ABSOLUTELY NOT AN OPTION.
- SO THIS IS WHAT
UNHAPPINESS IS TO HER?
I GUESS THE CURSE ENDED UP
WORKING AFTER ALL.
STILL, SHE'S LUCKY SHE DIDN'T
GET SOMETHING MORE PAINFUL.
FOR NOW.
I'LL WAIT. ONCE SHE
EXHAUSTS HERSELF,
IT'LL BE EASIER TO TAKE
HER ENERGY AWAY.
IS SHE STILL AT IT?
IF SHE'S LOOKED THIS HARD
AND HASN'T FOUND THE BOX,
COMMON SENSE SHOULD TELL HER
IT MAY NOT BE HERE
NO MATTER HOW MUCH HAPPINESS
ENERGY SHE'S BLESSED WITH.
OH. IS IT MORNING ALREADY?
I WONDER IF SHE FINALLY
WENT HOME.
- ( clattering )
- HEY, MISS.
HAVE YOU BEEN LOOKIN' OUT
HERE THE WHOLE NIGHT?
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
GIVE IT A REST?
- NO, I'M FINE.
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE.
- WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL? THEY'RE
JUST OLD LETTERS.
BESIDES, IT'S NOT LIKE
YOU'RE SENTIMENTAL
OR CARE ABOUT ANYTHING.
- ICHIKO SAKURA IS
A SELFISH BRAT
WHO DOESN'T GIVE
A SECOND THOUGHT
TO HOW HER ACTIONS AFFECT
ANYONE AROUND HER.
SHE DOESN'T CARE.
SHE'S AN OUTRAGEOUS GIRL,
WHO, CONTRARY TO HER
OUTWARD APPEARANCE,
HAS A TWISTED PERSONALITY,
AND IS NOT ONLY HAUGHTY
AND OVERBEARING.
SHE THINKS I'M FLAT CHESTED.
- COME ON.
I JUST HAVE TO FIND THAT BOX.
ANYTHING OTHER THAN FINDING
THOSE LETTERS IS NOT AN OPTION.
SUWANO GAVE THEM TO ME.
I CAN'T LOSE THE ONLY THING IN
THE WORLD I REALLY CARE ABOUT.
- ( crying )
- DAMN IT. ALLEY OOPA.
- HEY. WHAT'S THAT?
MOMO'O? HOW LONG HAVE YOU
BEEN OUT HERE, PUPPY?
THIS PLACE IS
TOO DANGEROUS FOR...
WAIT, IS THAT IT? GOOD BOY.
- GIVE A DOG DEITY'S NOSE
ITS DUE.
- ( gasps ) IT'S HERE.
YOU FOUND IT FOR ME.
THANK YOU.
- AN OUTRAGEOUS, HAUGHTY,
OVERBEARING BRAT?
NOT HER. SHE'S JUST
A LONELY KID. RIGHT?
- MOMO'O.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, MOMO'O.
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE THE BEST DOG EVER.
- WHICH ONE IS IT?
WHO ARE YOU? I MEAN, REALLY?
- GROSS. I'M DIRTY
AND I SMELL BAD.
BOY, DO I NEED A BATH, HUH?
- ( door closes )
- ( sighs )
I CAN'T BELIEVE I MISSED A
PERFECT OPPORTUNITY.
I'M SORRY, MOMIJI,
BUT, I COULDN'T HELP MYSELF.
- SERIOUSLY? YOU LET YOUR
EMOTIONS GET IN THE WAY?
- I DIDN'T REALLY MEAN
FOR IT TO HAPPEN.
I WASN'T TRYING TO
IMPRESS HER.
I JUST FELT BAD.
SHE'S A LONELY GIRL.
I HONESTLY DON'T THINK ICHIKO
SAKURA IS THE AWFUL PERSON
YOU BELIEVE HER TO BE.
THERE'S MUCH MORE TO
HER THAN THAT.
- YES, I THINK I UNDERSTAND.
- HEY, MOMO'O.
- STILL. I HAVEN'T ACCEPTED
EVERYTHING ABOUT YOU.
NO MATTER WHAT KIND OF
PERSON YOU MAY BE,
IT DOESN'T CHANGE
THE FACT
THAT I WILL TAKE YOUR
HAPPINESS ENERGY AWAY.
( screaming )
WHAT'S SHE DOING? WHAT'S
HAPPENING? SHE'S A SADIST.
- I HAVE TO ADMIT, YOU SEEM TO
BE MY VERY OWN GOOD LUCK CHARM.
I BET MY HAPPINESS ENERGY
ATTRACTED YOU TO ME.
- THIS SUCKS SO HARD.
- ( exclaiming )
- DO YOU LIKE THAT? DOES IT
FEEL EXTRA GOOD RIGHT THERE?
- YOU HAVE TO STOP
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
( exclaiming )
- UH, MOMO'O?
- OH NO.
- WHEN MOMO'O RECEIVES PLEASURE,
EVEN IF IT'S NOT S AND M,
HE REVERTS BACK TO NORMAL.
- WHAT IS THIS?
DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE WITH THAT
DAMN POVERTY GOD.
- OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
YOU NEED TO CALM DOWN.
TAKE IT EASY AND
HEAR ME OUT, PLEASE.
- SO IF I TAKE IT EASY,
THE FACT THAT YOU'VE SEEN ME
NAKED WILL JUST DISAPPEAR,
IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE
TRYING TO SAY?
- HOLD ON. I DON'T THINK
BATHTUBS ARE SUPPOSED
TO RIP OUT OF THE
CONCRETE LIKE THAT.
BWAM WHAM SLAM SMACK
YOU WERE PRETENDING TO BE
A DOG THAT WHOLE TIME...
- NO, I WASN'T PRETENDING
TO BE A DOG!
- I AM A DOG. BUT IT'S TRUE!
- YOU'RE NOT MAKING ANY SENSE.
- OKAY, SO MOMIJI WAS RIGHT
ABOUT ONE THING.
SHE'S CRAZY VIOLENT.
WAIT, VIOLENT?
YES, THIS VIOLENCE IS
STILL VIOLENCE.
MORE! HIT ME HARDER,
I BEG YOU.
- YOU'RE A SICKO PERVERT,
AREN'T YOU?
- I'M HERE TO SAVE YOU,
NAKED FOR SOME REASON.
- YOU JERK, YOU'RE NO
BETTER THAN HIM.
- WORSE.
- Momiji: WHAT'S GOING ON?
SOUNDS LIKE YOU GUYS
ARE HAVING FUN IN THERE.
I WANNA TASTE OF THIS PARTY.
WHAT? MOMO'O'S BEEN BEATEN UP,
BUT I GUESS HE SEEMS HAPPY.
- YOU LUNATICS ARE JUST
A BUNCH OF JINXES.
- NO, DON'T DO IT. MOMO'O'S
LIFE FORCE IS ALMOST AT ZERO.
- SHUT UP AND GET OUT
OF MY HOUSE.
- MUST REALLY COME IN HANDY
TO LOVE PAIN.
- PLEASE LET ME IN.
IT'S NOT WHAT YOU THINK.
JUST LET ME EXPLAIN.
- NO MEANS NO. GO AWAY!
- MOMO'O, WHAT'S SO SPECIAL
ABOUT HER?
- BEAR CLAW,
BEAR CLAW OF PLEASURE.
- Students: THIS WEEKS...
- Nadeshiko: OH, NADESHIKO!
AS FOR THIS EPISODE,
YOU COULD ONLY SEE ME HERE.
IF YOU WERE THINKING
YOU'D BE ABLE TO SEE
MORE OF ME EVERY EPISODE,
WELL, TOO BAD FOR YOU.
( laughing )
( crying )