- GOODBYE...
SWEET ICHIKO...
- PLEASE TRY TO BE NICE TO
THE OTHER MOMIJI FOR ME, OKAY?
- NO. I DON'T THINK SO.
TAKE THAT.
- ICHIKO. BUT WHY?
- DON'T GET THIS TWISTED.
IT'S JUST THAT THE
WAY YOU ARE NOW.
WELL, IT'S NOT QUITE AS BAD AS
THE OTHER VERSION OF YOU.
AND IT WOULD BE A REAL SHAME TO
LET THE HALF WAY DECENT SIDE
OF YOU GO TO WASTE.
BUT DON'T THINK THAT IN
ANY WAY MEANS THIS GIRL
WANTS TO BE FRIENDS WITH
A POVERTY GOD.
'CAUSE I DON'T. BUT EITHER WAY,
I WON'T LET YOU CHANGE BACK.
- NO, ICHIKO, WAIT.
- SO, I HAVE A QUESTION.
- WHAT IS IT?
- YOU STILL CAN'T GET TO YOUR
SOMIN SHORAI, RIGHT?
- ( screams ) OH CRAP!
- WHAT'S UP?
- RANMARU?
- YOU'RE LUCKY I WAS RIGHT HERE.
YOU ALMOST DIED.
- YEAH, BUT WHY
ARE YOU RIGHT HERE?
- I WAS BORED, SO
I DECIDED TO COME OVER
TO SEE WHAT YOU GUYS WERE UP TO.
THEN OUT OF NOWHERE, YOU GUYS
JUMPED OUT OF THE WINDOW.
I DIDN'T EXPECT THAT.
- WE DIDN'T EXPECT YOU, EITHER.
- OUT OF CURIOSITY, HOW FAR DID
YOU JUST JUMP?
- ( glass shattering )
- Momo'o: YOU WON'T
GET AWAY FROM US, MOMIJI. I...
- WHOA, GARBAGE BOMBS?
WHAT IN THE HELL IS GOING ON?
- LATER. FIRST, CAN WE FOCUS ON
GETTING AWAY FROM THOSE TWO?
- YOU WANT ME TO
TURN MY BACK TO THE ENEMY?
- YES, PLEASE.
- JUST GO ALREADY.
- OH, FINE. WHAT'S THE POINT.
I'M NOT EVEN SURE
WHAT'S GOIN' ON.
HOLD TIGHT, GIRLS.
WE'RE OUTTA HERE.
- NORMALLY, THAT WOULD BE
AN ACCURATE STATEMENT, YES...
UGH, BUT RIGHT NOW,
ALL THIS SMELLY GARBAGE HAS MADE
MY NOSE GO NUMB.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO WAIT A BIT.
WITH ANY LUCK IT WILL
START WORKING
SOONER RATHER THAN LATER.
- SO, IF YOU GET DIRTY, YOU'LL
GO BACK TO THE OLD MOMIJI?
THAT'S KINDA RANDOM.
- IT SEEMS TOO SIMPLE, I KNOW
BUT THAT'S HOW KUMAGAI CHANGED.
I'M STILL NOT
ENTIRELY CONVINCED.
BUT SHE DID ONLY
START ACTING THIS WAY
AFTER WE GAVE HER THAT BATH.
- SO IF WE DO THE OPPOSITE,
SHE'LL TURN BACK?
STILL, THEIR BEHAVIOR
IS INEXCUSABLE.
THE REASON DOESN'T MATTER.
THROWING GARBAGE AT A WOMAN IS
NOT SOMETHING A MAN SHOULD DO.
- CAN WE PLEASE CONCENTRATE
ON WHAT WE SHOULD DO?
I MEAN, IT'S NOT LIKE WE CAN
JUST KEEP RUNNING AWAY FROM THEM
LIKE THIS FOREVER, RIGHT?
- WE WON'T HAVE TO.
I THINK WE'LL BE FINE.
AS LONG AS THEY DON'T CATCH US
BEFORE THE SUN GOES DOWN.
I'M SURE THEY'LL GIVE UP
AFTER IT GETS DARK.
- WHY IS THAT?
- YEAH, IS THE DOG'S NOSE GONNA
STOP WORKING OR SOMETHING?
- WELL...
- ( honking )
- JIVE ASS TURKEYS. YOU GOT
A DEATH WISH OR SOMETHING?
I AM DRIVING HERE.
OF COURSE THE GIRLS THAT JUMP IN
FRONT OF ME'D BE YOU THREE.
- WHAT IS A MONK DOING
DRIVING A TRUCK?
- I GOT A JOB LAST WEEK MAKING
DELIVERIES FOR A LIQUOR STORE,
SO THAT'S WHAT I'M DOIN'.
- BOBBY, THIS IS PERFECT,
WE NEED YOU TO GIVE US
A RIDE AWAY FROM HERE,
LIKE OUT OF TOWN AWAY.
IT DOESN'T MATTER WHY.
THE IMPORTANT THING IS
ALL WE HAVE TO DO IS KEEP HIDDEN
UNTIL NIGHT FALL, AND WE WIN.
- THEN LEAVING TOWN
IS A BRILLIANT PLAN.
- HOLD ON. DID I NOT JUST TELL
YOU I WAS WORKING HERE?
- WHATEVER, IT'S JUST GONNA BE
LIKE AN HOUR.
NO MEANS NO. I DON'T HAVE TIME
TO DEAL WITH LITTLE GIRLS
GETTING ALL SELFISH ON ME.
- FINE. IF YOU AGREE
TO HELP US OUT,
I'LL LET YOU TOUCH MY BOOBS.
YOU CAN FONDLE THE HELL OUT OF
'EM FOR AS LONG AS YOU WANT TO.
- NOW JUST WHO
DO YOU THINK I AM?
THAT YOU DIDN'T SAY THAT
IN THE FIRST PLACE. GIRL?
- COME ON, MONK, GIVE IT ALL YOU
GOT. PEDAL TO THE METAL.
- ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
- ABOUT WHAT?
- I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU WOULD DO THAT FOR ME.
YOU'D LET SOMEONE
WHO EMBODIES LUST
DEPRIVE YOU OF YOUR CHASTITY?
- NO ONE SAID
ANYTHING ABOUT THAT.
- NIPPLES IN THE CENTER,
AND TWEAK!
- BESIDES, LIKE I SAID EARLIER,
LETTING YOU GET AWAY IS
FOR MY SAKE, NOT YOURS.
REMEMBER, I'M THE GIRL
WHO CAN ONLY EVER THINK
ABOUT HER OWN HAPPINESS.
- ( gasps )
- WELL, I GUESS
THAT'S OKAY, THEN.
I ALWAYS TALK ABOUT WANTING
YOU TO USE YOUR
HAPPINESS ENERGY FOR THE SAKE OF
OTHER PEOPLE, BUT, IN THE END,
YOU'RE ACTUALLY RIGHT.
PEOPLE WHO THINK
ONLY OF OTHERS
WILL EVENTUALLY RUIN
THEMSELVES IN THE PROCESS.
LIKE THAT KURUMI GIRL.
ALL YOU EVER WANTED BACK THEN
WAS FOR HER TO BE HAPPY, RIGHT?
AND LOOK WHAT
HAPPENED TO YOU.
- HOLD ON, HOW DID YOU
KNOW ABOUT THAT?
- LISTEN TO ME, OKAY?
IF YOU GENUINELY NEED ME HERE,
THEN I'LL ALWAYS BE WITH YOU.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE CONCERNED
ABOUT YOUR HAPPINESS
ALL BY YOURSELF ANYMORE.
- YOU'VE GOT IT WRONG.
WHATEVER IT IS YOU THINK I WANT,
YOU'RE WRONG.
- AFTER ALL THE CONSTANT
FIGHTING AND DEATH THREATS,
I NEVER GAVE UP HOPE
THAT THIS DAY WOULD COME.
- HEY, SORRY TO
INTERRUPT YOUR OVARY FEST
OR WHATEVER IT IS YOU DOING,
BUT WE GOT COMPANY.
- ( yelling )
- OH, CRAP. LOOKS LIKE THE
GARBAGE BOMBER FOUND US!
- BOBBY, DODGE THEM.
- ( tires screeching )
THIS IS PROBABLY VERY ANNOYING
TO OTHER DRIVERS.
- KUMAGAI. LAUNCH ME AT THEM.
INCOMING.
- INCOMING YOUR FACE.
- ( Momo'o screaming )
- SOMEONE'S ON THE CAR.
OKAY, LET'S TRY
THAT ONE MORE TIME!
- I KNOW!
- WHAT IS IT? WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
- IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
MOMIJI IS THE ONE WHO HAS TO
GET AWAY FROM THEM, NOT US.
SO THERE'S NO REASON FOR ME TO
TRY TO ESCAPE WITH HER, RIGHT?
- NO, I GUESS THERE'S NOT.
- AWESOME. I'LL BE ABLE TO
TAKE CARE OF THIS NOW.
- BE CAREFUL.
- 'TIS THE VICIOUS
ACT OF A VILLAIN
TO ATTEMPT TO COME BETWEEN
AND PULL APART
THE WEAVE OF FEMALE BONDS.
FOR THE LOVE THAT BINDS
TRUE FRIENDS TOGETHER,
I ACCEPT AND SHOULDER THE
DESTINY OF FOILING THE ENEMY.
SO BRING IT, PUPPY POWER.
FROM THIS MOMENT ON, YOU'LL
HAVE TO GO UP AGAINST ME.
- PATHETIC HUMAN.
IF YOU THINK I'LL HOLD BACK
SIMPLY BECAUSE YOU'RE A GIRL,
YOU ARE GREATLY MISTAKEN.
- ACTUALLY, THAT'S A RELIEF.
MOPPING THE FLOOR WITH
YOU WHILE YOU'RE TRYING
WILL BE SO MUCH MORE REWARDING.
- WRONG.
- HE'S STRONG.
- ( both grunting )
- ( yelling )
- GO ON WITHOUT ME, KUMAGAI.
I'LL CATCH UP AS SOON AS I
TAKE CARE OF THIS.
- GUESS AGAIN.
YOU'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
- RANMARU, NO.
- ( screaming )
- DO YA LIKE THAT?
- ( laughs ) NOT BAD.
HOW WAS IT FOR YOU?
HOLY DOG. THAT MUST'VE HURT
MORE THAN I THOUGHT.
- WHAT? WAIT. HEY.
THAT IS SO NOT FAIR!
THERE'S NO WAY IN HELL
I COULD BEAT A FREAKIN'
PUPPY TO NEAR DEATH!
TURN BACK INTO YOUR
ORIGINAL FORM AND DO IT NOW!
- HIT ME FIRST.
- WHAT?
- IF YOU HIT ME, I'LL TURN BACK.
JUST HIT ME.
- WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU,
YOU REPULSIVE SON OF A BITCH?
- YOU CAN PUNCH ME OR
SLAP ME OR KICK ME.
COME ON, KICK ME.
IT'LL BE AWESOME.
- I DON'T WANT RABIES,
GET AWAY FROM ME.
- WAIT, YOU CAN'T
USE YOUR SOMIN SHORAI,
IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE TELLING ME?
- MM-HM. DO YOU HAVE ANY OTHER
AWESOME GEAR ON YOU?
KUMAGAI SEEMS LIKE HE'S PRETTY
DETERMINED BACK THERE.
- WELL, WHAT CHOICE DO I HAVE?
HERE, SPECIAL DEAL,
JUST FOR YOU.
- WHAT ARE THOSE THINGS?
- THEY'RE A GIFT INFUSED WITH
MY VERY OWN SUPERNATURAL POWERS,
WHICH I LIKE TO CALL,
"PRAYER BEADS, THE HYPER".
PUT 'EM ON YOUR FEET
TO INCREASE LEG STRENGTH.
PUT 'EM OVER YOUR EYES,
AND THEY BOOST YOUR VISION.
- WOW, THAT'S NOT CREEPY AT ALL.
- WE'RE NOT TOUCHING THOSE
UNTIL YOU CAN PROMISE US
THEY HAVE NEVER BEEN USED
ON ANY OTHER BODY PARTS.
- WHATEVER, I'LL TAKE THEM.
WELL, LOOK WHO IT IS. KUMAGAI.
OH, HEY, TAMA. ARE YOU GONNA
HELP US OUT NOW?
- ( squealing )
- BOBBY. KEEP HER
SAFE FOR ME, OKAY?
- LONG AS THEM TITTIES
ARE STILL ON THE TABLE.
- ICHIKO. PLEASE DON'T DO
ANYTHING CRAZY.
- I TOLD YOU. I'M NOT DOING THIS
FOR YOU. I'M DOING THIS FOR ME.
THAT'S AWESOME.
I'M LIKE RANMARU.
- ( meowing angrily )
- ( lightning crashing )
- ( waves crashing )
- NO, TAMA, NO. BAD KITTY.
STOP. I'M NOT GONNA LET
YOU GET PAST ME.
- WHAT? "DON'T GET IN OUR WAY,
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING."
WHAT IS THAT SUPPOSED MEAN?
HUH? IF A POVERTY GOD IS WASHED
AND REMAINS WITHOUT THEIR POWERS
FOR SEVEN DAYS AND SEVEN NIGHTS,
THE UNTHINKABLE HAPPENS.
THEY WILL THEN
TURN INTO A HUMAN.
AND WHAT'S SO BAD ABOUT THAT?
A DOLL?
IN ORDER FOR DEITIES TO
COMMUNICATE WITH HUMANS,
THEY MUST FIRST TAKE POSSESSION
OF DOLLS KNOWN AS "HUMA FORMS".
IF THEY DON'T, HUMANS WON'T
BE ABLE TO SEE THEM,
MUCH LESS HAVE A
CONVERSATION WITH THEM.
FURTHERMORE, IF THEY GO LONGER
THAN THE TIME I MENTIONED
WITHOUT THEIR GODLY
POWERS RETURNING,
THEY WILL BE UNABLE TO
LEAVE THEIR HUMAN FORMS?
IF THAT HAPPENS, THEIR
PERSONALITIES WILL NEVER RETURN.
IN OTHER WORDS, FOR MOMIJI,
IT CAN ONLY MEAN ONE THING.
SHE'S GONNA DIE?
DEATH.
YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
WAIT. KUMAGAI, WHERE...
( groans )
NO. PLEASE WAIT. KUMAGAI.
BUT WHY? WHY DIDN'T
SHE SAY ANYTHING?
I MEAN, THAT'S KIND OF AN
IMPORTANT DETAIL TO MENTION.
SHE WON'T BE AROUND ANYMORE.
IN HALF AN HOUR, SHE WON'T BE
ANYWHERE ANYMORE.
IF SHE KNEW WHAT WOULD HAPPEN
THIS WHOLE TIME, THEN...
HUH?
IF SHE KNEW...
SHE HAD TO KNOW, SO WHY?
- OH. YOU'RE STILL ALIVE.
- HUH?
( screams ) TSUWABUKI.
- HOLY JEEZ THAT HURT. YOU
SCARED THE CRAP OUT OF ME.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT I WAS
ABOUT TO SAY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING OUT HERE?
- I WAS, UM, JUST, UH,
TAKING A NAP.
- NAP? THAT'S PRETTY BOLD.
MIDDLE OF THE STREET AND ALL.
- OKAY, YOUR TURN.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING OUT HERE?
- I AM IN THE MIDDLE OF WORK.
- I HELPED GET BOBBY,
THAT MONK FRIEND OF YOURS,
A JOB DOING DELIVERIES FOR THE
LIQUOR STORE WHERE I HELP OUT.
BUT HE HASN'T COME
BACK SINCE HE LEFT,
SO NOW I'M CLEANING
UP THAT MESS.
- UH...
- OKAY. WHAT'S THAT FACE FOR?
- NOTHING. FACE?
WHAT? NOTHING AT ALL.
NEVER MIND THAT ANYWAY, I HAVE
SOMEWHERE TO GO. BYE.
- 'KAY.
- SEE YA LATER.
SOMEWHERE TO GO. AND AFTER I
CATCH UP, WHAT DO I DO THEN?
DO I TRY TO STOP KUMAGAI?
WHAT IF HE CAN SAVE HER?
HEY. TSUWABUKI, HOLD ON A SEC.
I NEED TO ASK YOU A QUESTION,
IF THAT'S OKAY.
IT'S JUST LIKE A WHAT IF THING.
BUT, WELL, HERE GOES.
LET'S SAY THERE'S THIS PERSON
WHO REALLY GETS ON MY NERVES.
LIKE I HATE THEM,
A LOT, LIKE, YEAH.
BUT THEN, I FIND OUT
THEY COULD BE GONE FOREVER
AND, UM, AND ALL OF A SUDDEN,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT WOULD BE BEST.
AND NOW, ON TOP OF THAT,
THERE'S THIS...
THERE'S THIS WEIRD TIGHTNESS
IN MY CHEST, I GUESS.
SO, KNOWING ALL THAT,
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU WOULD
DO IF YOU WERE IN MY SHOES?
- AND THIS PERSON IS
GONNA BE GONE FOREVER.
ARE THEY MOVING AWAY?
- YEAH, SORT OF.
- AND YOU'LL NEVER
SEE THEM AGAIN?
- PROBABLY NOT. NO.
- AND THE WHOLE
SITUATION DEPENDS
ON WHAT YOU DECIDE TO DO.
- IN THIS
HYPOTHETICAL STORY, YES.
- WELL, YOU ALREADY HAVE
THE ANSWER TO THAT.
- ( gasps )
- IF YOU SERIOUSLY
WANTED THEM GONE,
I WOULDN'T THINK YOU'D
BE SO UPSET ABOUT IT.
- I DIDN'T THINK ABOUT THAT.
DO I SEEM UPSET?
- A LITTLE, YEAH.
- WELL, COLOR ME BAD.
I DIDN'T REALIZE SOCIOPATHS
COULD BE UPSET.
- ( grunting angrily )
NO WAY. THERE'S NO FRICKIN'
WAY. I DON'T KNOW HOW,
BUT SHE'S ANNOYING ME WHEN SHE'S
NOT EVEN HERE. YOU'RE RIGHT.
I AM UPSET. BUT WHY THE HELL
AM I GETTING SO WORKED UP
OVER SOMEONE I CAN'T STAND?
- ( laughing )
AND SUDDENLY
SHE'S BACK TO NORMAL.
YOU'VE SEEMED KIND OF DOWN
LATELY. WELL, AT LEAST TO ME.
MAYBE NOT DOWN, EXACTLY,
BUT DEFINITELY MORE CALM.
- YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I GUESS THAT'S TRUE.
AND NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT,
YOU TOTALLY SAW ME NAKED
THE OTHER DAY, DIDN'T YOU?
- WHY ARE YOU SO LOUD?
- DUDE...
STOP YELLING FOR REAL.
- STILL. YOU DID
ANSWER MY QUESTION,
SO I GUESS WE CAN JUST
CALL IT EVEN.
YOU DID AN
AWESOME JOB, TSUWABUKI.
- SHE'S SO WEIRD.
- BYE, THEN. I'M OFF NOW.
- YEAH. GREAT.
OKAY. THAT WAS COOL.
- WHAT DO YOU KNOW? HE'S RIGHT.
CAN YOU BELIEVE ME?
I'M JUST NOW REALIZING IT.
- ( screaming )
- GRACIOUS. WHAT IN
HEAVEN'S NAME WAS THAT?
- ( whimpers )
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO GET DOWN?
ICHIKO.
- I'M SORRY. BUT ICHIKO.
SHE'S CHANGING DRAMATICALLY.
SHE'S SO MUCH NICER TO
THE PEOPLE AROUND HER
THAN SHE WAS WHEN WE FIRST MET.
AND I REALIZE IF I TAKE HER
HAPPINESS ENERGY AWAY BY FORCE,
IT WILL RESOLVE THE PROBLEM.
BUT IN THE PROCESS, IT WILL
BRING UNHAPPINESS TO ICHIKO.
WHAT IF SHE WINDS UP
CHOOSING A PATH
THAT BRINGS HAPPINESS TO
OTHERS ON HER OWN?
WOULDN'T THAT BE BETTER?
WOULDN'T EVERYONE BE HAPPIER?
I THOUGHT I CAN STAY BY HER SIDE
AND HELP HER USE HER HAPPINESS
ENERGY FOR OTHER PEOPLE.
DEEP DOWN I KNOW
THAT'S WHAT SHE WANTS.
- COME ON... THERE ARE MORE
THAN ENOUGH POVERTY GODS.
BUT GUIDING THAT GIRL...
IT'S NOT SOMETHING
JUST ANYONE CAN DO.
OH, KUMAGAI.
NO.
( sniffles )
I GUESS THIS IS THE END.
FORGIVE ME, KUMAGAI
AND ICHIKO. I'M SORRY.
- ( yelling )
OH, HELL NO.
- YOU SAVED ME.
- WHAT WAS IT YOU SAID?
PEOPLE WHO ONLY
THINK ABOUT OTHERS
WILL EVENTUALLY RUIN THEMSELVES?
ISN'T THAT WHAT YOU'RE
DOING NOW?
UNLESS YOU THINK THAT
ELIMINATING YOURSELF,
AS A POVERTY GOD IS ACTUALLY
WHAT YOU NEED TO DO TO BE HAPPY.
- BUT...
- YEAH, BUT WHAT?
- IT'S JUST...
IT'S JUST THAT'S HONESTLY WHAT I
THOUGHT WOULD BE BEST FOR YOU.
- SURE ENOUGH,
ORIGINAL OR MIRROR,
YOU DO WHATEVER THE
HELL YOU WANT.
WHAT'S BEST FOR ME IS SOMETHING
I CAN DECIDE FOR MYSELF.
BESIDES, I FINALLY
REALIZED SOMETHING.
THE THING IS, WHEN YOU'RE
ALL MOPEY FACE,
I DON'T KNOW WHY, BUT
I CAN'T FUNCTION.
GOODBYE, MOMIJI.
- ( all screaming )
- ICHIKO, YOU FINALLY DID IT.
YOU FINALLY CALLED ME
BY MY NAME.
- AWESOME. A BOAT.
SHE'S GONNA BE OKAY.
- YOU DON'T KNOW THAT FOR SURE.
IF YOU DIDN'T NOTICE
THAT BRIDGE IS REALLY HIGH.
- YEAH, I DO KNOW FOR SURE.
CHECK OUT WHAT THE BOAT IS.
- WHAT?
YOU HEARD WHAT I SAID.
THE ONLY THING SHE'S DONE
SINCE SHE GOT HERE IS TURN MY
LIFE UPSIDE DOWN.
IF SHE WEREN'T HERE,
THE GAME WOULD BE OFF
AND I DON'T THINK THAT WOULD
MAKE ME VERY HAPPY.
I'M GONNA KICK HER OUT OF THE
HUMAN REALM ALL ON MY OWN.
I'M NOT ABOUT TO
LET HER HELP ME DO IT.
- LONG TIME NO SEE.
HOW YA FEELIN', PUN'KIN?
- I FEEL LIKE HAMMERED FECES.
THANKS FOR ASKING.
NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT IT,
YOU'RE LUCKY I DON'T CURSE
YOU FOR WHAT YOU DID TO ME.
- LIKEWISE, I'M SURE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I ACTUALLY
WORRIED ABOUT YOU
FOR THE FULL MINUTE THAT I DID.
BUT NOW I CAN GO BACK TO
LOATHING YOUR ENTIRE EXISTENCE.
- HA. YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT YOU ARE?
YOU'RE SO WEAK.
YOU PASSED UP TWO PERFECT
CHANCES TO DRIVE ME AWAY.
FIRST, WHEN YOU
HELPED TSUWABUKI,
AND NOW WITH THIS
LITTLE DISPLAY.
OMG, DIDN'T YOU JUST SAY THAT
YOU WORRIED ABOUT ME?
PLEASE, LIKE YOUR SOUL
IS CAPABLE OF THAT.
I'M GONNA PEE MYSELF.
- I'LL KILL YOU.
I'M GONNA WASH YOU AGAIN
IF YOU DON'T WATCH YOUR DIRTY
MOUTH. YA FEEL ME?
- OOH. THAT'S PRETTY
SCARY COMING FROM A GIRL
I'M ON A FIRST NAME BASIS WITH.
I WAS TALKING TO THE MIRROR YOU,
NOT THE AWFUL YOU. HER, I LIKED.
- ACTUALLY, THIS WHOLE SHE BANG
WAS A CLEVER PLAN TO GET YOU TO
REMOVE THE WALL AROUND
YOUR HEART, AND I WON.
- YOU WIN NOTHING.
- WELL, LOOK AT THAT.
I GUESS ICHIKO COULDN'T
KEEP HER SAFE AFTER ALL.
ALTHOUGH...
( laughs )
IF THAT'S SUCH A BAD THING,
WHY DOES SHE LOOK SO
HAPPY? WELL, FOR HER.
- I MEAN, WHO CAN TRUST
A CHICK WITH SUCH A FLAT CHEST,
AM I RIGHT?
- YOU SHUT UP.
- OH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I SHOULD HAVE CALLED THEM
PITTY TITTIES, SORRY.
I KILL YOU. TAKE THAT,
MISS POTATO SACKS.
- WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
NOTHING YOU SAY IS LOGICAL.
YOU'RE JUST JEALOUS.
- JEALOUS OF WHAT?
EVENTUAL KNEE BOOBS?
BECAUSE EVERYONE KNOWS DROOPY
TITTERS IS A SEXY LOOK.
- ( both groaning )
- DAMN, YOU. STUPID POVERTY GOD.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ ONE WAY, TWO WAY,
THREE WAY, FOUR WAY ♪
♪ GO WAY, GO WAY ♪
♪ YOU MAKE MY DAY ♪
♪ ONE WAY, TWO WAY,
THREE WAY, FOUR WAY ♪
♪ NO WAY, NO WAY ♪
♪ GOODBYE, BAD DAY ♪
- HUH. IT FEELS LIKE I'M
FORGETTING SOMETHING.
- ARRESTED YESTERDAY FOR
VIOLATION OF TRAFFIC LAWS,
LICENSE FORGERY,
AND DESTRUCTION OF PROPERTY,
WAS A MAN IDENTIFYING
HIMSELF AS BOBBY.
- I HEARD THE VOICE
OF A BREAST GOD...
SHE OFFERED ME THE CHANCE
TO FONDLE, SO I HAD NO CHOICE!
- HE'S CURRENTLY IN
CUSTODY BEING HELD
FOR PSYCHIATRIC EVALUATION.
- Nadeshiko: ENEMY AFTER ENEMY
APPEAR IN BUTSUMETSU CITY.
THERE TO TAKE THEM ON IS ME.
NADESHIKO ADENOKOJI.
WATCH FOR SEASON TWO, "GOOD
LUCK GIRL! DARKNESS GLOBES"
COMING SOMEDAY.