- OH, MAN. CAN WE GET A
LITTLE MERCY DOWN HERE?
- SINCE WHEN DOES THE MONK CARE
WHAT'S GOING ON IN THE WORLD?
- SINCE NEVER. I BET HE'S
LOOKING AT PICTURES
OF CHEERLEADERS IN
THE SPORTS SECTION.
- OH, YEAH, SWEET SALVATION.
SEEK AND YE SHALL FIND.
THANKS, BUDDHA.
WELL, YOUNG MOMO'O,
THE ANSWER TO THE QUESTION,
"WHEN ARE THEY GONNA GIVE US
"THE FAN SERVICE EPISODE?"
IS RIGHT NOW.
- Momo'o: SERVICE FOR MOMO'O.
BROUGHT TO YOU BY THE
LETTERS S and M.
- WHY NOT? NOTHING WRONG
WITH A LITTLE VARIETY.
IN FACT, I SAY WE KICK
IT UP EVEN MORE
AND OPEN WITH ONE OF THOSE
MUSICAL NUMBERS.
- HELL YEAH.
- ♪ RISING OVER
THE FEMALE FORM ♪
♪ TOWER TWIN PEAKS PINNACLES ♪
♪ OF HOPE IN ROSY PINK ♪
♪ WE SING LA LA LA ♪
- ♪ I LOVE ♪
- ♪ BOOBIES ♪
- ♪ GINORMOUS ♪
- ♪ HOOTERS ♪
♪ LA LA! LE BOOBIES! ♪
♪ WE SING FOR YOU! ♪
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN!
LET THE SHOW BEGIN!
HAS IT HONESTLY BEEN TWO MONTHS
SINCE YOU WERE SENT TO STEAL
ICHIKO SAKURA'S
HAPPINESS ENERGY?
- I TRUST YOU ARE AWARE OF HOW
DISAPPOINTED WE MUST BE
IN THE TRAGIC AMOUNT OF PROGRESS
YOU'VE MADE ON YOUR ASSIGNMENT?
- YEP.
- HOWEVER, WE ARE ALL
PROFESSIONALS HERE.
WE CANNOT INDULGE
OPTIMISTIC IDEALS.
FROM THIS MOMENT ON,
I EXPECT EVERY GOAL
TO BE REACHED AT AN
ACCELERATED PACE.
- IS THAT CLEAR?
- OH, YEAH.
- EXCUSE ME?
- HELLA POINTS WHEN
YOU CATCH THOSE ONES.
- ( snickering )
- I KNOW WHAT THAT LOOK MEANS,
AND I AM NOT A FAN.
YOU BETCHA. COMING IN
LOUD AND CLEAR THERE, BOSS.
- IF, FOR ANY REASON, YOU ARE
UNABLE TO EXPEDITE THESE TASKS,
YOU WILL LEAVE ME NO CHOICE
BUT TO DEEM YOU INCOMPETENT
AND BRING YOU BACK IMMEDIATELY.
YOUR PUNISHMENT HAS
ALREADY BEEN DECIDED
AND WILL BE ENFORCED
UPON ARRIVAL.
ARE WE QUITE CLEAR?
- UGH, WHY IS IT SO HOT?
THIS WEATHER HATES ME.
GROSS. I'M SWEATY EVERYWHERE.
I NEED TO TAKE A SHOWER,
LIKE WHOA.
- ( cat mewing )
- HEY TAMA KINS.
WHAT YOU CRYIN' ABOUT, BABY?
- Momiji: DON'T TELL
ME YOU'RE ONE OF THOSE
HIGH POWERED
RIVER LORDS, RIGHT?
- WHY IS SHE IN MY BATHROOM?
WHY IS SHE ANYWHERE?
- YOU SAY HUMANS
DID THIS TO YA?
OH, THAT FIGURES.
THEY HAVE NO MANNERS.
LOOKS LIKE IT'S UP TO LIL'
OL' ME TO MAKE IT ALL BETTER.
- I CAN RUB MY CANS ON YOUR...
- WHAT? EW.
- COME HERE, BIG BOY,
LET'S HAVE A LOOK.
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THAT
TEMPERATURE? GOOD?
- ( growling )
- WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
DOING IN HERE?
- PART TIME BATH JOBS. DUH.
THIS IS WHAT FAILURE LOOKS LIKE,
I'M AFRAID.
I'VE NOW LOST
EVERY ITEM IN MY BAG.
I'M LEFT WITH ONLY
ONE THING OF ANY VALUE.
MY PRECIOUS BODY SHALL
BE TRADED FOR FOOD.
- WHATEVER. I JUST WANT TO KNOW
WHY YOU'RE DOING IT IN MY HOUSE.
AND WHAT'S WITH THE
MOUND OF GROSS?
- ( gurgling )
- FOR REAL? THE SOUR THING
BEHIND ME?
LOOKS LIKE YOU HAVE
A REQUEST, ICHI.
MAKE SURE YOU TAKE GOOD
CARE OF OUR KUSARE GOD.
- WHAT?
- IT'S TOTES EASY.
- YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE
TO USE YOUR TITLERS.
- BOOBIES.
- YOU WANT HER TO USE HER JUGS,
BUT MINE AREN'T GOOD ENOUGH,
YOU SON OF A MOOSE.
- BOTH OF YOU GET YOUR MUDDY
ASSES OUT OF HERE, NOW.
EW! ARE YOU SEEING THIS?
IT'S LIKE THE SEWER EXPLODED.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO
TAKE A BATH IN THAT STANK?
SPEAKING OF, YOU'RE SMELLING
PRETTY RIPE YOURSELF, MISSY.
JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE A DEITY
DOESN'T MEAN YOU
DON'T BATHE, RIGHT?
- LOOK, THAT KIND OF THING
TAKES UP WAY TOO MUCH TIME.
I GOT STUFF TO DO.
SO YOU BROUGHT YOUR
FILTHY SPUNK INTO MY HOUSE?
LOOK AT YOUR HAIR. I COULD WAX
AN ENTIRE MINIVAN WITH THAT MOP.
DO YOU EVEN KNOW HOW LONG IT'S
BEEN SINCE YOU'VE SHOWERED?
- ( clock ticking )
- OKAY ARE YOU COUNTING
DAYS OR WEEKS?
- YEARS.
- GET OUT OF MY HOUSE.
AND DON'T COME BACK UNTIL YOU'VE
BEEN SCRUBBED AND DISINFECTED.
- A BATH? OF COURSE YOU
CAN! RIGHT THIS WAY!
- THANKS, RANMARU.
YOU'RE THE BEST.
- HEY, NO BIGGIE.
BE JUST A SEC.
MY POP'S IN THERE RIGHT NOW, BUT
YOU CAN USE IT WHEN HE'S DONE.
- THAT'S FINE,
I DON'T MIND WAITING.
BUT WHY ARE WE
IN YOUR YARD?
- ( blowing air )
- ACTUALLY, I THINK I'M
GONNA PASS THIS TIME.
- WHY? WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- UH, NOTHING. I JUST HAVE AN
ITCH FOR A BATHHOUSE.
- WAIT. ME TOO.
I'LL GO WITH YOU.
- WELL, THAT SURE ENDED UP GOING
AN ENTIRELY DIFFERENT DIRECTION
THAN WE EXPECTED, DIDN'T IT?
A BATHHOUSE. GOOD THINKING
ON HER PART, I GUESS.
BUT, IF SHE'S GOING THERE
THAT MEANS SHE'LL BE AWAY
FROM HER SOMIN SHORAI.
- ( gasps )
- FAMILY TRIP TO THE BATH, HUH?
- ALL THE PIPES BUSTED
IN OUR BATHROOM.
- SPEAKING OF BUSTED,
HEY, TITCHIKO.
- ICHIKO, YOU TURD.
- I DIDN'T SEE YOU OVER THERE.
LOOKS LIKE YOU TWO
HAVE GOTTEN CLOSE.
- WE HAVE, SIR.
- SIR?
- I HAVE A FEELING
THINGS ARE ABOUT TO GO
FROM WEIRD TO
FULL BLOWN SUCK.
- WELL ISN'T THIS A NICE
SURPRISE.
- UGH. I KNEW IT.
BETTER THAN DEALING WITH
THAT STANKY POVERTY HAG.
DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT
PRANCING INTO THE LADIES SIDE,
YOU PERVY MUTT.
I KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING TO HIM,
YOU MONSTER?
HOW CAN ANYONE TORTURE A SWEET,
INNOCENT LITTLE PUPPY LIKE THAT.
- AH SHUT UP.
MIND YOUR OWN BEE'S NUTS.
- WHAT IS GOING ON IN HERE,
KEITA? DID YOU SEE THAT?
THE CUTE LITTLE DOG JUST
TURNED INTO A CRAZY PERVERT.
- STEP RIGHT UP,
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN.
- THAT'S CRAZY.
- KEITA, LOOK.
THERE'S A CAT JUST LIKE HIM.
- OKAY, YOU GUYS
NEED TO CALM DOWN.
- WHOA.
- COOL. I DIDN'T KNOW TAMA COULD
TRANSFORM LIKE THAT, TOO.
- HECK YEAH.
- OH, COME ON.
AM I REALLY THE ONLY ONE WHO
REALIZES WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- SAY WHAT YOU WANT ABOUT HER,
SHE'S GOT SOME PRETTY
NEAT FRIENDS.
- ( exclaims )
FIRST ONE IN.
AWKWARDNESS CAN SUCK IT.
YAHOO.
- ( Ryuta laughing )
- NO RUNNING. I DON'T NEED YOUR
SISTER TRYING TO COPY YOU.
- Ryuta: WHO CARES.
WE'RE THE ONLY ONES HERE.
- UH, RANMARU, ARE YOU OKAY?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- ( gasps ) UH, NOTHING?
- Tsuwabuki: NOW THERE'S ONE
YOU HAVEN'T USED BEFORE.
- HE'S ON THE OTHER SIDE
OF THIS WALL.
IF WE CAN HEAR THEM, DOES
THAT MEAN THEY CAN HEAR US?
WE'RE NAKED TOGETHER
IN THE SAME ROOM.
BODIES KEPT APART ONLY BY
A SINGLE WALL SEPARATING
OUR HEARTS AND LOINS
FROM OUR EYES.
YOUNG HORMONES DYING TO
REACH OUT AND TOUCH EACH OTHER.
STRENGTH FAILED.
- YOU'RE GETTING
BLOOD EVERYWHERE.
ARE YOU FINISHED?
UGH, PLEASE.
YOU DON'T NEED TO BE
EMBARRASSING YOURSELF
OR ME OVER THAT DOUCHE.
- I'VE NEVER SEEN BOOBS
THAT BIG BEFORE.
AMAZING. THEY'RE JUST
LIKE BALLOONS.
- DO IT. DO IT.
- WOULD YOU LIKE TO TOUCH THEM?
- WOULD I EVER?
- OKAY, THAT'LL COST YOU
5000 YEN PER BREAST.
IF YOU DON'T HAVE IT NOW
,TELL YOUR BRO HE'S GOTTA
GET ANOTHER JOB
AND WORK SO HARD IT KILLS HIM.
GO AHEAD. GIVE 'EM A GOOD
SQUEEZE. HE'LL COVER IT.
- ( both laughing )
- I'M SORRY. ALMOST MADE IT.
- NO, I DON'T WANT KEITA TO DIE.
- WHAT IN THE WORLD
DID YOU SAY TO HER?
- I WAS KIDDING.
I WOULDN'T LET HER TOUCH THEM
AND 5000 YEN IS NOT THAT MUCH.
DON'T WORRY, WHEN YOU GROW UP,
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE YOUR OWN
SET, JUST AS BIG AS MINE,
AND YOU CAN PLAY WITH THEM AS
MUCH AS YOU WANT.
- I WILL?
- OF COURSE. I PROMISE.
- MAYBE I SHOULD HAVE
LET HER FEEL
SO SHE COULD TELL ME
IF THEY WERE FAKE.
- CONSIDERING RIKA'S STILL AS
FLAT AS A WASHBOARD,
I KINDA DOUBT THERE'S MUCH
HOPE FOR ME IN THE FUTURE.
- I'M STILL GROWING.
DO YOU HEAR ME?
- ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE.
COUNT OFF.
- UNO.
- TWO.
- RIGHT. OUR DESTINATION IS JUST
BEYOND THIS WALL. FOLLOW ME.
- IS THIS REALLY HAPPENING?
- KNOCK IT OFF YOU GUYS.
- OH, DON'T BE A PARTY POOPER.
- COME ON.
DON'T YOU WANNA SEE WHAT
TITCHIKO LOOKS LIKE NEKKID?
- YOU'RE NOT THE BOSS OF HIM.
- ACTUALLY, I AM.
QUESTION IS.
WHO ARE YOU TWO CREEPERS?
AND EXACTLY HOW OLD ARE YOU?
MY GUESS IS WAY TOO OLD
TO BE ACTING LIKE THAT.
JUST GET IN THE BATH.
( sighs ) IT FEELS AMAZING.
ALL THE STRESS IS JUST GONE.
LIKE IT WAS ALL ONE,
BIG FAT DREAM.
- ( screaming )
- HE PASSED OUT. WAKE UP, KEITA.
- WOW. BOYS ARE ALWAYS
LOUD FOR NO REASON.
- SERIOUSLY. YOU'D THINK THEY
WERE ALL TODDLERS.
HOW HARD IS IT TO SHUT UP
AND SIT IN SOME WATER?
- WANT ME TO WASH YOUR BACK
FOR YOU, ICHIKO?
- THANKS A TON, THAT'S SO NICE.
- HEY, WHAT ARE FRIENDS FOR,
AM I RIGHT?
POVERTY GOD ITEM.
THAT CRAZY LITTLE THING
CALLED WHAT THE WHAT?
THIS TWISTED LITTLE NUMBER
IS DESIGNED TO INFLICT
INTENSE PAIN ON THE VICTIM,
WHILE SUCKING HAPPINESS ENERGY
OUT OF THE WOUNDS.
- HUH?
- ( struggling )
- ICHIKO, LOOK OUT.
MOMIJI'S RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
- NOW THIS IS GONNA
STING A LITTLE.
YOUR HAPPINESS ENERGY IS MINE!
- NOW THIS IS GONNA
STING A LITTLE.
- I'LL SAVE YOU.
( moaning )
- DO YOU EVEN REALIZE YOU JUST
RUINED EVERYTHING, YOU PERVERT?
- WOW. I DO LOVE
A GOOD DOUBLE ATTACK.
- PUNK. WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
IT'S NOT JUST FOR GROWN WOMEN.
MY TWO BABY SISTERS
ARE OVER THERE.
- LET GO. I DON'T LIKE
TO BE ABUSED BY MEN,
YOU SICK, TWISTED PERV.
IT LOOKS LIKE THERE'S
SOMEONE ELSE IN HERE
THAT CAN SURPASS A DEITY.
FAREWELL, MOMO'O.
IT'S BEEN FUN.
- I'M SO NOT GETTING
INVOLVED WITH ALL OF THAT.
- I UNDERSTAND
YOUR DETERMINATION
BUT THIS IS NOT THE
TIME OR PLACE.
- YOU'D THINK AFTER
ALL THIS TIME
THAT YOU'D LEARN TO ALWAYS
HAVE YOUR GUARD UP. LOSER.
NICE TIMING.
I SHALL WITHDRAW FOR NOW
BUT ONLY BECAUSE IT IS
A LITTLE AWKWARD.
ADIOS, BABE.
- HEY, HOLD ON.
- ( grunting )
DAMN.
I HATE THAT SHE HAS FRIENDS NOW.
( gasps )
- NICE ONE, TAMA.
- FIRST RULE OF BATHING.
IF YOU DON'T WATCH YOUR
ASS, SOMEBODY WILL.
- YOU'RE GONNA BE HERE AWHILE.
CAN'T LET YOU OFF THAT EASY.
- HMM.
- I DROP MY TOWEL
AND YOU JUST GAWK.
YOU'RE TOTALLY INTO ME AREN'T
YOU? IT'S OKAY, ADMIT IT.
- THAT'S THE MOST RIDICULOUS
THING I'VE EVER HEARD.
- GOTCHA. YOU'RE TERRIFIED OF
BEING CLEAN, AREN'T YOU?
THAT'S WHY YOU WANT TO
LEAVE SO BADLY, HUH.
COME HELP ME, RANMARU.
SHE HASN'T HAD A BATH IN THREE
YEARS. THIS FUNK IS TOUGH.
- OH, GROSS.
I SEE WHAT YOU MEAN.
HOLD STILL, MOMIJI.
EVERYONE HAS TO BATHE.
YOU NEED TO GET USED TO IT.
- WHERE DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE GOING?
MAY AS WELL WASH YOU
WHILE WE'RE AT IT.
( chuckles )
I FEEL SO MUCH BETTER NOW.
- SHE SERIOUSLY SHRANK.
- ( shrieking )
MOMIJI.
- I'LL TRY PUTTING HER
IN SOME HOT WATER.
- WHAT IS SHE? A RAMEN NOODLE?
- ( water bubbling )
- AND WE'RE BACK.
- NOT GONNA LIE. THAT WAS COOL.
- WELL. I HOPE YOU AT LEAST
LEARNED SOMETHING
FROM THIS EXPERIENCE.
NOW I'M ALL SWEATY AGAIN.
- Bobby: POOR LITTLE GUY.
I CAN'T IMAGINE PASSING OUT IN A
PLACE LIKE THIS.
YOU MUST BE PRETTY MORTIFIED.
BUT I CAN PROMISE YOU ONE THING.
I GOT YOUR BACK, DOG.
I WILL CONTINUE THIS QUEST
IN YOUR NAME.
I TOLD YOU TO KNOCK IT OFF.
- NOW WHAT EXACTLY IS YOUR
PROBLEM, KID?
- I'M THE KID?
YOU'RE SPYING ON GIRLS.
- LOOKS LIKE THEY LEFT, SO NOW
YOU CAN GET YOUR BOOB STARIN ON.
- WHAT? I DON'T WANNA SEE THAT.
- LIAR, LIAR, PANTS ON FIRE.
YOU JUST AFRAID.
I REFUSE TO BELIEVE THAT
A HEALTHY YOUNG MAN
ISN'T INTERESTED IN GIRLS.
- UH, OF COURSE I AM.
I THINK ABOUT THEM
ALL THE TIME, ACTUALLY.
- ( gasping )
- LOOK, I'M TRYING TO SET A GOOD
EXAMPLE FOR MY BROTHER.
SO I DON'T NEED HIM TO SEE ME
OR ANYONE ACTING LIKE PERVERTS.
HE'S BETTER THAN THAT.
- OKAY, KEITA, WE'RE READY TO
GET GOING WHENEVER YOU ARE.
- YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
THEY'RE GONE NOW.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
BE THE ROLE MODEL
AND WE CAN CHECK OUT THE
GOODS NEXT DOOR.
- IT'S NOT JUST THEM.
I DON'T WANT TO.
- WHOA, WHOA, WHOA THERE, SON.
ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE BEING
HONEST WITH YOURSELF?
- POSITIVE. FIRST OFF, THOSE TWO
ARE IN THE SAME CLASS AS ME.
IF IT EVER GOT OUT,
I'D BE MURDERED.
BUT MOSTLY, MY BROTHER
OWES HIS LIFE TO ICHIKO.
- REALLY? IS THAT TRUE?
- NO, THAT WAS LIKE,
FOREVER AGO.
- AND RANMARU, TOO. EVEN THOUGH
SHE DRESSES LIKE A GUY,
SHE'S STILL A LADY AND
SHE SHOULD BE TREATED LIKE ONE.
BESIDES, SHE WOULD
BEAT YOU DOWN...
- I KNEW HE WAS GORGEOUS
AND CHARMING,
BUT I HAD NO IDEA HE WAS
CHIVALROUS, TOO.
- THAT'S CALLED SAVING FACE IN
FRONT OF YOUR FRIENDS.
- THAT DUDE LADY IS
A LITTLE FREAKY TO ME.
I MEAN, WHAT KINDA GUY
WOULD BE INTO HER?
I DON'T THINK IT'S
ALL ATTRACTIVE
FOR A WOMAN TO BE THAT MUSCULAR.
HAVE YOU LOOKED AT HER BOOBS?
CAUSE THEY DON'T BOUNCE AT ALL.
NOT EVEN WHEN SHE'S RUNNING.
THE WORST PART IS THAT
THE FANS NOTICE.
ALL THE MAIL WE RECEIVE IS ABOUT
WHAT A HANDSOME WOMAN SHE IS.
THERE'RE WOMEN WHO WISH SHE WAS
A MAN, SO THEY COULD DATE HER.
I'D RATHER HEAR ABOUT HOW HOT,
GORGEOUS OR STUNNING SHE IS.
- DON'T LISTEN TO THEM, RANMARU.
YOU'RE FINE.
- I GUESS WHAT I'M SAYIN' IS,
I DON'T SEE HOW ANYONE WOULD
WANNA LOOK AT HER.
- ( sighs )
LISTEN, MONK,
YOU GOTTA STOP THAT.
YOU KEEP TALKING ABOUT
MY FRIENDS THAT WAY
AND I'LL HAVE TO...
- IF YOU GOTTA PROBLEM WITH ME,
YO, I'LL SOLVE IT.
CHECK OUT MY FOOT.
HOLY CRAP. WHOA. LOOK HOW TIGHT
AND DEFINED HIS BODY IS.
- NICE CUT THERE, MISTER!
WE'RE FINALLY HERE TOGETHER
BREATHING THE SAME AIR.
IT'S LIKE A DREAM COME TRUE.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU ACTUALLY
FELL RIGHT INTO MY TRAP,
MY LITTLE ANDROGYNOUS FRIEND.
THANKS FOR BREAKING THE WALL.
- OUTTA MY WAY.
- GREAT. THIS WAS NOT WHAT
I HAD PLANNED FOR TODAY.
I LOOK AWAY FOR ONE SECOND AND
THE WORLD FALLS APART,
BUT I CAN'T LET IT GET TO ME.
I HAVE TO REMAIN CALM.
- NEVER FORGET... WHEN LIFE
GIVES YOU SOUR BERRIES
YOU SQUISH THEM UP
AND TURN THEM INTO PIE.
- THAT'S IT! THAT'S WHAT I HAVE
TO DO! THANK YOU, GRANDMA!
- THREE POINT ONE FOUR.
THREE POINT ONE FOUR.
- Ichiko Angel B: ATTENTION ALL
ANGELS. THIS IS AN EMERGENCY.
REPEAT, THIS IS
AN EMERGENCY.
WE MUST COME UP WITH A
RESOLUTION IMMEDIATELY
AND BRING THE SITUATION
UNDER CONTROL.
- WHO HAS IDEAS?
- I SAY WE KILL EVERYONE
AND START ALL OVER.
- NEXT.
- LET'S BEAT HIS
MEMORIES OUT OF HIM.
- BLUSH AND ACT HELPLESS?
- NO. ANY IDEAS THAT
MIGHT WORK?
- LET'S PUT ON A DISGUISE AND
PRETEND TO BE SOMEONE ELSE.
- I LIKE THAT IDEA.
LET'S DO IT.
- EVERYONE, SETTLE DOWN.
- WE NEED TO THINK
OF SOMETHING QUICKLY.
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
- PICK SOMETHING. ANYTHING.
- I'M SORRY, I JUST, I DIDN'T
WANT TO. WELL, YOU KNOW...
I MEAN, I DIDN'T SEE ANYTHING.
- HE'S SO LYING.
- LIES, LIES, LIES, LIES, LIES.
- YEAH, RIGHT. DON'T BELIEVE
ANYTHING HE SAYS. HE SAW IT ALL.
DICK.
- Ryuta: HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
I HEARD A LOUD CRASH.
- Tsuwabuki: IT'S NOTHING.
COME ON BACK, RYU.
- Ryuta: WHY ARE YOU
ALL HUNCHED OVER?
- OH GOOD, YOU'RE STILL ALIVE.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- SOMETHING CAME UP.
- LIKE WHAT?
NEVER MIND. LOOK, I KNOW
YOU'RE GOING TO BE MAD,
BUT I DON'T WANT TO HANG OUT
WITH ICHIKO ANYMORE.
I'M VERY SORRY.
- YOU'RE FINE. I JUST DON'T WANT
TO TALK ABOUT HER RIGHT NOW.
- AND WHY NOT?
- BECAUSE HE'S ALREADY HAVING A
HARD ENOUGH TIME WALKING.
- WHAT THE HECK DOES THAT MEAN?
DID SHE HURT YOUR LEGS IN THERE?
- IT'S NOT THAT. I JUST NEED TO
STAY RELAXED RIGHT NOW.
- HAVE A GOOD NIGHT, TSUWABUKI.
WE'LL SEE YOU LATER, OKAY?
- WAIT. WHO WAS THAT?
- NO WAY.
THAT STUPID POVERTY THIEF.
SHE FREAKING STOLE MY CLOTHES
AND WORE THEM HOME, DIDN'T SHE?
WELL, THANKFULLY EVERYONE'S GONE
OR PASSED OUT.
( sighs )
AM I SUPPOSED TO GO ALL THE
WAY HOME WEARING NOTHING
BUT A TOWEL?
UGH. I JUST WANT TO CRAWL INTO
A HOLE AND DIE.
- ( grunting )
- WHAT ARE YOU DIGGING
A HOLE FOR?
I KNOW IT'S GOING TO
TAKE A LITTLE LONGER
TO FIX THE BATHROOM,
BUT WE DON'T NEED TO GET
ALL PRIMITIVE.
WE CAN STILL USE THE BATHHOUSE.
- WE'RE NEVER GOING TO THE
BATHHOUSE AGAIN.
- I HOPE YOU KNOW
YOU CAN'T BATHE IN THAT.
UNLESS YOU WANT A MUD BATH?
- I THINK I CAME UP WITH THE
PERFECT PLAN, KUMAGAI.
DO YOU WANT TO HEAR IT?
I KNOW THIS IS SOMETHING THAT
WOULD NORMALLY GET YOUR
FUR IN A TANGLE.
BUT, WE'VE BEEN PRESENTED
WITH AN OPPORTUNITY
AND WE'D BE FOOLS
NOT TO CASH IN.
IT'S TIME. LET'S GO.
- GOOD MORNING.
- YEP. WHAT'S WITH
YOUR OUTFIT, DUDE?
- SAYS THE GIRL IN AN
OPEN POLICE TRENCH
AND A SERIAL KILLER MASK.
- IT'S A LUCHA LIBRE.
I WAS FLYING THROUGH THE AIR
AND BREAKING DOWN WALLS
IN FRONT OF TSUWABUKI
AND I WAS NAKED.
I CAN'T FACE HIM TODAY.
- YOU'RE SUCH A FREAKING WUSS.
IT'S NOT THAT BIG OF A DEAL.
SO WHAT IF HE SAW YOU, SAW US,
SAW US, NAKED. HE SAW ME NAKED.
- ( both screaming )
- I HATE IT HERE.
- HEY, YOU CAN'T BLOCK THE
DOORWAY LIKE THAT.
PEOPLE NEED TO GET TO CLASS.
- TSUWABUKI.
- THAT HURT MY EARS.
YOU HAVE WAY TOO MUCH ENERGY
THIS EARLY IN THE MORNING.
- ( crying )
- HE HATES ME. HE WORE
A BAG OVER HIS HEAD
SO HE WOULDN'T HAVE
TO LOOK AT ME.
HE DOESN'T WANT TO SEE
THE CRAZY NAKED GIRL.
- WE SAW HIM NAKED, TOO.
HE'S JUST EMBARRASSED.
GROSS. WHY AM I STRESSING OUT
ABOUT ALL THIS?
WHY SHOULD I CARE
WHAT ANYONE THINKS?
- HEY, GOOD MORNING.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
- AND, YOU ARE?
- WHO AM I? IT'S MOMIJI,
SILLY GIRL.
( giggles )
YOUR FRIENDLY NEIGHBORHOOD
POVERTY GOD.
- HUH?
( screaming )
- Students: THIS WEEK'S...
- Nadeshiko: OH, NADESHIKO!
- ( humming )
- NO, YOUR EYES
DID NOT DECEIVE YOU.
I WASN'T IN THE EPISODE
AT ALL THIS TIME.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"AND WHY NOT?"
PRACTICALLY THE WHOLE STORY WAS
IN A BATHHOUSE AND I'M NOT ABOUT
TO SHARE A SCRUB WITH COMMONERS.
- SHE ALSO WASN'T ASKED
TO BE IN THE EPISODE
AND WE'LL TELL YOU WHY.
IF YOU GOT NO RACK
AND YOU'RE FLAT.
THEN YOU DON'T MAKE THE CUT.
IT'S NOT A SHOW ABOUT BUTTS. OW.
- YEAH, DO THAT SOME MORE.