- ( thunder rumbling )
ALL RIGHT...
THAT'S ALL I HAVE FOR TODAY.
- AND PLEASE MAKE SURE
TO PUT YOUR THINGS AWAY
BEFORE YOU LEAVE, OKAY?
- ICHIKO! YOU WANNA
HANG OUT AFTER SCHOOL?
- HEY, STOP. THAT'S NOT SAFE.
YOU CAN'T MAKE RAMEN
WITH THE ALCOHOL LAMPS.
YOU'RE GONNA KILL US ALL.
- OH. HEY, MAYBE WE CAN STOP
FOR RAMEN ON THE WAY THERE?
- UH, THAT'S A REAL
NICE OFFER, BUT I CAN'T,
I GOTTA GET HOME ASAP.
- YO! WHAT IS UP WITH YOU? HOW
COME YOU KEEP DITCHING ME, ITCH?
THAT'S SO NOT COOL.
- WAIT. WHY DON'T YOU COME
HANG OUT AT MY PLACE?
- ( Ranmaru screeching )
THAT IS THE CUTEST KITTY
I'VE EVER SEEN.
SERIOUSLY, SHE'S
FRACKIN' ADORABLE.
- YEAH, SHE SURE IS.
- OH, WOW.
LOOK AT THOSE EYES.
- HER NAME'S TAMA.
- I WANNA SQUEEZE HER HEAD.
HOW'D YOU GET HER?
- I GUESS IT ALL HAPPENED
ABOUT A WEEK AGO.
SOMEONE LEFT HER OUT IN
FRONT OF MY APARTMENT,
IN THE FREEZING RAIN.
IT WAS TERRIBLE. POOR THING
NEARLY FROZE TO DEATH.
BUT EVER SINCE I TOOK HER IN,
SHE SEEMS TO BE
DOING PRETTY WELL.
- ( chuckling )
AH, YOU'RE JUST SO CUTE.
( incoherent baby talk )
- BABY TALK?
OK, THAT'S CREEPY.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS,
I HAD NO IDEA YOU WERE
SUCH AN ANIMAL LOVER.
IT MUST BE NICE TO BE SO RICH.
- I MEAN, YOU HAVE ENOUGH MONEY
TO KEEP A DOG AND A CAT.
- MOMO'O, NO!
- THIS IS NO FAIR.
I'M THE MASCOT CHARACTER
OF THIS SERIES, DAMN IT.
I WON'T LET YOU TAKE THAT
AWAY FROM ME.
PLUS, I HAVEN'T EVEN BEEN
IN THE SHOW IN A WHILE.
- WHOA, HE TALKS!
- YOU'RE MAKING A
FOOL OF YOURSELF.
- OH, YET ANOTHER THING.
HOW COME YOU'RE SO SWEET TO
THAT DAMN CAT?
ALL YOU EVER DO TO ME IS
TELL ME HOW SMELLY I AM.
- THAT'S BECAUSE YOU ARE SMELLY,
YOU NASTY DOG!
MAYBE IF YOU WEREN'T ALWAYS
HUMPING EVERYTHING THAT MOVES,
- I'D LIKE YOU MORE.
- THIS IS TOTALLY FREAKY.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT FROM ME?
I'M A DOG, I'M SUPPOSED
TO HUMP THINGS.
I GUESS YOU'D RATHER I JUST
LIE THERE SNIFFING MY BUTT.
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- HEY! YOU FOOLS ARE BEING
WAY TOO LOUD!
PEOPLE ARE TRYING TO EAT UP
IN HERE, SO KEEP IT DOWN.
- WELL, WELL LOOK WHO IT IS.
THE MISS RANMARU RINDO.
- HUH?
SEEMS LIKE EVERY TIME
I TURN AROUND,
YOU'RE MAKING A FEATURED
APPEARANCE ON THIS SHOW.
WHICH MEANS YOU CUTTING INTO
MY SCREEN TIME, LITTLE GIRL.
DON'T YOU KNOW YOU
NEED MY PERMISSION
TO BE A LEAD CHARACTER?
- HOLD ON, IS THAT FOR REAL?
- NO, HE JUST LIES ABOUT STUFF.
- ITTY-BITTY-TITTIES...
MAN ARMS...
AND YOU ALL CUT!
IT'S HOPELESS.
- CHANGE!
- WHY DON'T YOU JUST SHUT UP?
YOU JACK ASS!
- OH, YOU CAN'T GET MAD AT
ME FOR HAVING EYES.
MAYBE DRESS UP A LITTLE
SEXIER NEXT TIME.
- OH, HELL YEAH. KICK HIM.
KICK HIM RIGHT IN HIS
SWEET MOCHA BUTT.
- IF YOU JERKS ARE GONNA
DO THAT, GO OUTSIDE.
WEIRDLY ENOUGH, THE BIGGEST
NOISE MAKER ISN'T EVEN AROUND.
SEEMS LIKE SHE'D BE THE
FIRST ONE TO JUMP IN.
- WELL, GUESS I'LL
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
- HEY. HOLD ON ONE SEC.
- HMM? WHAT'S UP?
- I, UH...
- Momiji: IT MAY NOT BE ON
PURPOSE, BUT YOU NEED TO KNOW
IF YOU KEEP ABSORBING HAPPINESS
ENERGY FROM OTHERS
YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE
PEOPLE AROUND YOU MISERABLE.
ESPECIALLY THE ONES
YOU CARE ABOUT.
- IT'S NOTHING,
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
- YOU ARE TOTALLY WEIRD.
SEE YOU.
- WHAT AM I SO SPOOKED ABOUT?
OBVIOUSLY IT'S BETTER IF I TELL
HER SOONER RATHER THAN LATER.
( gasps )
SORRY, TAMA.
BE RIGHT BACK.
- ( screams )
- THAT IS SO GROSS!
- Ibuki: ICHIKO SAKURA?
- WHAT THE HELL, YO?
- I APOLOGIZE FOR
STARTLING YOU.
- THE POOP IS
TALKING TO ME!
- POOP? WELL, THAT'S RUDE.
NAME'S IBUKI AND
I'M THE BATHROOM GOD.
IT'S A PLEASURE TO MEET YOU.
HEY, NOW. WHAT'S WITH
THE NOSE PLUGS?
I GET IT. IT'S THE
SMELL, ISN'T IT?
DO I REALLY SMELL THAT AWFUL?
ARE YOU SURE IT'S NOT
JUST MY COLOR AND SHAPE
THAT MAKES YOU THINK THAT?
WELL, IT COMES WITH
THE TERRITORY.
I AM THE GOD
OF BATHROOMS, AFTER ALL.
- SORRY. YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT'S NOT VERY NICE TO JUDGE
OTHERS BY THEIR APPEARANCES.
- YOU SAY THAT, BUT I DON'T SEE
YOU TAKING THE NOSE PLUGS OUT.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I CAN'T TAKE THIS ANYMORE,
IT'S BEST IF I JUST DIE.
- NOW THAT'S ENOUGH.
WHAT DO YOU WANT FROM ME?
DON'T TELL ME THE POVERTY GOD
SENT YOU HERE.
- POVERTY GOD? NO.
- I HAVE ABSOLUTELY NO IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- YOU DON'T?
- NEVER MIND ALL THAT, PLEASE
JUST LISTEN. AS IT SO HAPPENS,
THERE IS SOMETHING CALLED
HAPPINESS ENERGY
AND THERE IS SOMETHING
CALLED UNHAPPINESS ENERGY...
HOWEVER, YOU, ICHIKO,
POSSESS FAR MORE HAPPINESS
ENERGY THAN THE AVERAGE PERSON.
- YOU CAN STOP RIGHT THERE.
SAVE YOUR BREATH, I GOT IT. I'VE
HEARD THE WHOLE SPIEL ALREADY.
- OKAY, GOOD TO KNOW.
THAT'LL CERTAINLY SPEED
THINGS UP A LITTLE BIT.
- HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- ( flushing )
- OH, COME ON, THAT'S NOT COOL.
HOW COULD YOU FLUSH ME
DOWN THE FREAKIN' TOILET?
- SORRY 'BOUT THIS, MISTER POOP.
BUT WE HAVE MORE
THAN ENOUGH GODS HERE.
- YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
YOU HAVE TO LISTEN TO ME.
YOU POSSESS AN
UNBELIEVABLE QUALITY
THAT SUCKS THE HAPPINESS OUT
OF OTHER PEOPLE.
IF SOMETHING ISN'T DONE,
AND FAST,
YOU'RE GOING TO BRING NOTHING
BUT UNHAPPINESS
TO EVERYONE AROUND YOU.
MAN. WHAT'S THE POINT?
IT'S NOTHING BUT A WASTE.
OH WELL. SCREW THIS. PLOP.
- ( sighs )
- ( mewing )
- THAT POOP GOD SAID THE
SAME THINGS THE POVERTY GOD DID.
- Momiji: ICHIKO, THE TOTAL
AMOUNT OF ENERGY IS FIXED.
IT'S PROPORTIONAL TO THE
NUMBER OF PEOPLE.
IT MAY NOT BE ON PURPOSE,
BUT YOU NEED TO KNOW
IF YOU KEEP ABSORBING
HAPPINESS ENERGY FROM OTHERS,
YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE
PEOPLE AROUND YOU MISERABLE.
- Ichiko: SHUT UP, YOU SOUND
LIKE A BROKEN RECORD.
PLEASE. I GET IT,
I'M THE WORST.
TAMA, I'M HOME.
TAMA?
( gasps )
WHAT IS IT THIS TIME?
THIS IS HER HANDIWORK FOR SURE.
( gasps )
- I HATE HER.
- ( water bubbling )
- UH, MISA?
HOW MANY MORE BATCHES OF
RAMEN ARE YOU GONNA MAKE?
- ( gasps )
- HEY, GUYS, WE'VE GOT COMPANY.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- Ai: COME ON, MISA,
FORGET ABOUT YOUR RAMEN.
WE'VE GOTTA GET
THE HECK OUTTA HERE.
- MY, MY, WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOU, DEAR? YOU LOOK PALE.
WHAT DID SOMETHING IMPORTANT
GET STOLEN FROM YOU?
- ( mewing )
- GIVE TAMA BACK RIGHT NOW.
AND WHO DO YOU THINK YOU'RE
CALLING 'UDDER GIRL', HUH?
- SO YOU STILL HAVE A
HUMAN HEART LEFT
IN THAT BODY OF YOURS. I'M GLAD.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE?
I'M GLAD YOU TOOK THIS CAT IN
OUT OF THE RAIN THE OTHER NIGHT.
THIS CAT I PURPOSEFULLY LEFT
OUTSIDE YOUR APARTMENT BUILDING.
- HUH? THAT WAS YOU?
- YEAH.
LONG, DRAWN OUT FIGHTS
AREN'T REALLY MY CUP OF TEA.
THEY'RE BORING.
BUT I'M GLAD I SPENT AS MUCH
TIME ON THIS AS I DID,
CAUSE IT GOT YOU RILED UP
ENOUGH TO COME SAVE HER
AND MEET ME FACE TO FACE.
NOW THAT YOU'VE GONE
THROUGH IT TWICE,
SURELY YOU'RE STARTING
TO UNDERSTAND.
YOU HAVE TO KNOW
WHAT IT FEELS LIKE
TO LOSE SOMETHING
YOU CARE ABOUT DEEPLY.
THOUGH I GOTTA ADMIT, IF YOU
HADN'T TAKEN A LIKING TO THE CAT
MY BACK UP PLAN WAS TO
TAKE RANMARU HOSTAGE.
BUT I'M GLAD IT DIDN'T
COME DOWN TO THAT,
BECAUSE FRANKLY,
THIS WAS WAY EASIER.
- DAMN YOU. I THINK
I'VE HAD ENOUGH.
IT'S TIME TO PUT
AN END TO THIS.
GET READY FOR A BIG DOSE
OF PAIN, POVERTY GOD.
I'M GONNA KICK YOUR ASS AND
THEN TAKE MY CAT BACK! ATTACK!
- IS THAT SO?
SORRY, BUT I'M AFRAID YOU LOSE.
- THERE. ALL DONE.
- ( gasps )
- DAYSON. THE HEAVY DUTY,
PICKER UPPER, ENERGY SUCKER
THAT DOESN'T EVER QUIT.
IT COST A FORTUNE...
BUT WORTH IT.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
( grunting )
- NOW, FINALLY, IT LOOKS
LIKE I'LL ACTUALLY BE ABLE
TO COMPLETE ONE OF MY MISSIONS.
I'LL BE BACK BEFORE
YOU KNOW IT,
BUT IN THE MEANTIME,
IF I WERE YOU, I'D GET READY.
THE NEXT TIME WE MEET,
I'M GONNA PUT A STOP TO
YOUR HAPPINESS SUCKING
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
- ( grunting ) DAMN POVERTY GOD!
- ( mewing )
HEY, TAMA. JUST HANG ON.
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
DAMN IT. WHO THE HELL DOES THAT
POVERTY GOD THINK SHE IS?
SHE'LL BE SORRY. I'M GONNA
MAKE HER PAY FOR THIS.
I'LL DO WHATEVER I HAVE TO.
( gasps ) WHAT HAPPENED? TAMA!
CRAP. I CAN'T GET IT OFF.
JUST HANG IN THERE, TAMA.
( gasps )
- ( moaning )
ZERO TO OH YEAH IN
ONE SECOND FLAT.
- AH! SHE'S IN MY PLACE
AGAIN WITHOUT ASKING.
TODAY IS THE DAY
WE FINISH THIS!
- NO. PLEASE, DON'T.
CAN'T WE JUST LIVE IN PEACE.
- HUH?
- I CAN'T. AUNT FLO IS
WRECKING MY HOO HA.
- THAT'S NO EXCUSE.
PLUS, I THOUGHT YOU
SAID YOURS WERE LIGHT.
- IT'S THE RED PLAGUE.
- WHOA! LOOK!
- THE GYM.
- WAIT A MINUTE.
THIS IS NOT GOOD!
I WANTED TO TRICK HER,
NOT KILL HER!
- WHAT SHOULD I DO NOW?
THERE'S NO WAY OUT,
THE EXITS ARE BLOCKED.
- Momiji: IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
HAPPINESS IS SOMETHING
THAT SHOULD BE SHARED.
- OH, TAMA. I'M SO SORRY.
WHEN IT WAS SUWANO, TSUWABUKI,
AND RANMARU.
I WAS ABLE TO SHARE MY
HAPPINESS ENERGY WITH THEM.
BUT THIS TIME I CAN'T.
WITHOUT ANY GEAR,
I CAN'T SAVE US.
I CAN'T DO ANYTHING, TAMA,
IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
- I'M SO SORRY.
PLEASE, FORGIVE ME.
- Ibuki: IT SEEMS YOU
FINALLY UNDERSTAND.
ALMOST. YOU'VE STILL GOT
A WAYS TO GO YET.
- WHOA. HEY, YOU'RE THE
POOP GOD GUY.
- BATHROOM GOD.
- RIGHT, LISTEN,
YOU'RE KINDA ON FIRE.
- YES, I DO KNOW WHAT IT FEELS
LIKE TO NOT GIVE A FLAMING CRAP.
WOW, TOUGH CROWD.
YOU COULD AT LEAST PRETEND
TO LAUGH AT MY JOKE.
I MEAN, I KNOW IT'S
NOT THE FUNNIEST LINE
IN THE HISTORY OF EVER,
BUT I'M JUST TRYING TO
LIGHTEN THE MOOD HERE.
- THAT JOKE WAS SO TERRIBLE
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
HEY, WAIT. WHY DID YOU COME
HERE ANYWAY, TO RESCUE ME?
- NO. YOU'RE SO SELFISH,
I WOULDN'T SAVE YOU IF YOU WERE
THE LAST PIECE OF POOP
LEFT ON EARTH.
I'M NOT HERE FOR YOU, ICHIKO.
I'VE COME TO RESCUE THE CAT.
- SERIOUSLY?
- YEP. IF YOU HADN'T FLUSHED ME
DOWN THE TOILET EARLIER,
YOU MIGHT'VE ALREADY KNOWN WHAT
I'M ABOUT TO TELL YOU.
BATHROOM GODS ARE THE DEITIES OF
CHILDBEARING AND CHILD REARING.
OUR ROLE IS TO PROTECT
NEWBORN BEINGS,
AND HELP WITH THE
DEVELOPMENT OF THEIR LIVES.
LONG STORY SHORT, I'VE
COME HERE FOR ONE REASON,
TO TAKE THAT LITTLE KITTY CAT
AWAY FROM YOU.
A NEWBORN KITTEN DOESN'T HAVE
VERY MUCH ENERGY TO BEGIN WITH,
BUT WITH YOU AROUND SUCKING
IT OUT OF HER LIKE THAT,
THERE'S HARDLY ANY LEFT AT ALL.
BUT THIS ISN'T NEWS
TO YOU, IS IT?
YOU HAD TO HAVE KNOWN IT WAS
ONLY A MATTER OF TIME.
YOUR WHOLE LIFE,
EVERY PERSON YOU'VE EVER KNOWN
WHO GOT TOO CLOSE HAS ENDED UP
THE WORSE FOR IT, HAVEN'T THEY?
- YEAH, BUT I DID EVERYTHING
I COULD TO HELP MY FRIENDS.
- HELP THEM? YOU'RE
THE ONE WHO HURT THEM.
CALL YOURSELF A HERO
IF YOU WANT, BUT IT'S NOT TRUE.
DON'T YOU THINK
IT'S TIME TO STOP THIS?
AVERAGE EVERYDAY PEOPLE WORK
THEIR WHOLE LIVES,
FIGHTING TOOTH AND NAIL, TO KEEP
WHAT LITTLE HAPPINESS THEY HAVE.
I DON'T THINK YOU HAVE THE
RIGHT TO WALTZ INTO THEIR WORLD
- AND TAKE THAT AWAY FROM THEM.
- BUT, I...
- OH, WHOOPS. I'VE GOT
DIARRHEA OF THE MOUTH
AND TAMA'S OVER HERE
ACTUALLY DYING.
GOD OF FORTUNE ITEM. THE FUSUKE
BLOWN BLOW DART OF FORTUNE!
- WHERE'D YOU GET
THAT THING FROM?
- I'LL TAKE TAMA NOW, THANK YOU.
- WAIT. WHERE TO?
- JUST KNOW THAT SHE'LL BE SAFE.
AND DON'T WORRY,
THIS ISN'T SOME SCREWY SCHEME
DESIGNED TO TEACH YOU A LESSON.
I MEAN, I KNOW YOU PROBABLY
DON'T TRUST A GUY
WHO'S MADE OUT OF POOP,
BUT GIMME A LITTLE CREDIT.
I'M NOT THE POVERTY GOD,
FOR GOODNESS SAKE.
- WHOA. WAIT,
WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?
I THOUGHT YOU TOLD ME
YOU DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
WHO THE POVERTY GOD WAS?
- ( exclaims )
- WHAT THE HELL DID YOU DO?
- I BLEW WAY TOO HARD,
AND IMPARTED MORE HAPPINESS
ENERGY THAN I NEEDED TO.
- WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN NOW?
- WELL. I'M AFRAID SHE
BECOMES A GOD.
- HUH?
- ( mewing )
- UH, WHAT IS SHE?
- A BECKONING CAT.
- IT DOES LOOK LIKE
SHE'S BECKONING ME.
- THAT'S WHY THEY'RE
CALLED THAT.
BECKONING CATS LEAD
THEIR MASTERS
TO GOOD FORTUNE IN DARK TIMES.
SEE, I HAVE NO INTENTION
OF SAVING YOU.
HOWEVER REGARDLESS OF MY
FEELINGS TOWARDS YOU,
I PROMISE I WON'T TRY TO STOP
HER FROM SAVING YOU, EITHER.
- OH. TAMA.
( crying )
NO, TAMA, WE CAN'T
GO OUT THAT WAY,
IF WE DO, WE WON'T BE
ABLE TO GET DOWN.
YOU'RE GONNA JUMP
OUT THE WINDOW?
- ( mewing )
- I DON'T REALLY KNOW WHY,
BUT I TRUST YOU. LET'S GO.
( screaming )
- ( both gasping )
( both screaming )
- HEY, WE'RE OKAY.
HOLD ON A SEC.
WHAT WERE YOU DOING THERE?
DON'T TELL ME YOU WERE
COMING TO HELP US.
NO, THERE'S NO WAY.
- YEAH. IT'S BACK.
ALL RIGHT.
ACCIO SOMIN SHORAI!
HUH? WORKED IN THE MOVIES.
COME ON.
GET OVER HERE NOW!
CRAZY. WHY THE HECK ARE
YOU COMING FROM THERE?
- ( rumbling )
- ( screaming )
- MAN, CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS?
- SOMEBODY BETTER DO
SOMETHING FAST,
OR IT'S GONNA
BURN TO THE GROUND!
- GROUNDWATER?
- OH, WOW!
- IT'S HOT!
- WHAT IS THIS?
- I THINK, YEAH,
IT'S A HOT SPRING.
- IT'S PUTTING
OUT THE FIRE.
- HOT, HOT.
OH, THAT'S HOT.
- ICHIKO SAKURA.
BEFORE I LEAVE YOU
ONCE AND FOR ALL,
THERE'S SOMETHING
I'D LIKE TO GIVE YOU.
- WELL, BACK TO THE
OLD DRAWING BOARD.
- Ibuki: I'LL ADMIT,
I'M IMPRESSED.
FOR SOMEONE WHO'S
USUALLY NOTHING
BUT A BIG PAIN IN THE REAR END,
I GOTTA SAY, YOU REALLY HAVE
CHANGED FOR THE BETTER
SINCE COMING TO THE HUMAN WORLD.
- OH, IS THAT RIGHT?
WELL, NEVER MIND ME.
WHAT I WANNA KNOW IS,
DID YOU GIVE HER THE
YOU-KNOW-WHAT OR NOT?
- I DID.
- AND I'M ASSUMING
SHE'S STILL IN THE DARK
ABOUT YOU AND I KNOWING EACH
OTHER, AM I RIGHT?
- UH, YEAH, I THINK
WE'RE SAFE ON THAT FRONT.
- WELL, IT WASN'T EASY.
I MEAN, THIS LATEST MISSION.
IT'S LIKE SECRETLY MIXING
PUMPKIN INTO A STEW
IN ORDER TO FEED IT TO A
CHILD WHO HATES PUMPKIN.
MAN, IT'S HARD TO WORK
THESE EPISODE TITLES IN.
IF SHE KNEW I'D PUT YOU UP TO
THIS, IT'D ALL BE FOR NOTHING.
- RIGHT, I KNOW.
YOU WANT ICHIKO TO TRULY
UNDERSTAND WHAT IT MEANS
FOR SOMETHING
TO BE PRECIOUS.
THAT'S THE WHOLE POINT
OF THIS ORDEAL.
BEFORE I LEAVE YOU
ONCE AND FOR ALL,
THERE'S SOMETHING I'D
LIKE TO GIVE YOU.
IT'S CALLED A KEYSTONE, ICHIKO.
AS LONG AS YOU KEEP IT ON YOU,
FROM HERE ON OUT,
YOU'LL NEVER AGAIN
ABSORB HAPPINESS ENERGY
FROM ANYONE ELSE,
AND YOU'LL BE SPARED THE PAIN OF
HURTING THE ONES YOU LOVE MOST.
IF YOU DIDN'T BEFORE,
SURELY YOU KNOW NOW,
THE TERROR OF LOSING
SOMETHING PRECIOUS.
AND THE JOY
OF BEING TOGETHER.
- ( mewing )
- OH, WHAT'S THE MATTER,
KITTY KAT?
DO YOU WANT SOMETHING TO EAT?
- Ibuki: THEN AGAIN.
I DO WONDER.
- Momiji: ABOUT WHAT?
- I'M WONDERING WHY YOU
BROUGHT ME IN FOR THIS,
WHEN YOU COULD'VE JUST
ASKED HER YOURSELF.
IF YOU WOULD'VE BEEN
HONEST WITH HER,
I'M NOT CONVINCED SHE
WOULDN'T HAVE LISTENED TO YOU.
- WHEN I WANT YOUR OPINION,
POOP HEAD. I'LL GIVE IT TO YOU.
- HOW CAN YOU DO THIS
TO ME, POVERTY GOD?
YOU UNTIE ME RIGHT
NOW, OR ELSE!
- THAT'S RIGHT, GO AHEAD AND
TALK TOUGH WHILE YOU STILL CAN.
TRUST ME, LITTLE GIRL, YOU'LL
BE ON YOUR KNEES TERRIFIED
OF THE NEW POVERTY GOD ITEM
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT.
POVERTY GOD ITEM...
THE NEW SWAPPING SWATHE.
BY USING THIS
DELIGHTFULLY WICKED TOOL,
I CAN SWITCH OUR MINDS WITH OUR
BODIES ANY TIME I FEEL LIKE IT.
I'M TOTALLY GONNA MAKE US
SWAP PLACES AND
THERE'S NOTHING YOU
CAN DO TO STOP ME.
TRICKY TUESDAY!
- ( exclaims ) MY BOOBS.
MY BEAUTIFUL BOOBS.
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU PLANNING
TO DO WITH MY BODY,
YOU BIG FREAK SHOW?
- OH AND IT GOES
WITHOUT SAYING,
WHILE I'M YOU, I'M GONNA
DO TERRIBLE THINGS
THAT YOUR REPUTATION
WILL BE RUINED!
- YOU CAN'T. NO!
- BUT BEFORE I DO THAT.
I'LL PLAY WITH THESE THINGS.
LOOK HOW BIG AND
BOUNCY THEY ARE.
I'M GONNA ENJOY HAVING A PAIR
OF PURRING SWEATER KITTENS
LIKE I ALWAYS WANTED!
- STOP IT. YOU FLAT
CHESTED, BOOB-LESS FREAK!
DON'T LEAVE ME HERE.
I SWEAR, IF YOU DON'T COME BACK
RIGHT NOW, I'LL KILL YOU!
- OKAY, I'M BACK.
- THAT WAS FAST. WAIT.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
- THAT WAS SO EXHAUSTING.
HOW DO YOU GET AROUND WITH
THESE THINGS FLAILING ABOUT?
MY BACK IS KILLING ME. I TRIED
WALKING UP A FLIGHT OF STAIRS,
BUT I KEPT TRIPPING
AND FALLING BACK DOWN
BECAUSE I CAN'T
SEE MY STUPID FEET.
EVEN TRYING TO STAND
UPRIGHT IS A CHALLENGE
'CAUSE I FEEL LIKE I'LL
TOPPLE OVER.
AND WHEN I RUN,
THEY SMACK ME IN THE FACE.
I'LL ADMIT, I NEVER REALIZED
HOW HARD YOU SLUTS HAVE IT.
- AND I'LL ADMIT, I HATE YOU!
WHAT ABOUT YOU, BOBBY?
YOU UP FOR A LITTLE SWITCHEROO?
- SWITCH IT UP, GIRL!
- NO, DON'T...
ANYTHING BUT THAT, PLEASE!
YOU FOOL! GIVE ME ONE GOOD
REASON YOU BROUGHT MOMO'O
AND IBUKI TO THE HUMAN REALM!
I'D ASK WHAT THE HECK
YOU WERE THINKING,
BUT IT'S CLEAR FROM THE EVIDENCE
AT HAND THAT YOU WEREN'T!
- YEAH... SORRY.
OH, I ALMOST FORGOT.
I SENT YOU A PRESENT, YAMABUKI.
DID YOU GET IT YET?
- UH.
- WELL, THANKS.
AS FAR AS I CAN TELL,
YOU SEEM TO BE DOING
EXCELLENT WORK. KEEP IT UP
AND I FEEL CERTAIN YOU'LL
COME OUT OF THIS
WHOLE THING JUST FINE!
EXTRANEOUS ROUND!
PART 5!
- ( clamoring )
- WAIT, I'M CONFUSED, ARE THESE
TWO GIRLS FRIENDS OR NOT?
- WHO KNOWS?
- HEY, I'VE GOT
A GREAT IDEA!
TIT-CHIKO! MOMIJI! LET'S MASH
YOU UP TO BE 'CHICHI-MOMI!'.
- WOW, I GUESS
THEY DO GET ALONG.
- Students: THIS WEEK'S...
- Nadeshiko: OH, NADESHIKO!
- WELL, I CERTAINLY HOPE
THAT ALL OF YOU LOVELY,
FABULOUS PEOPLE
GOT TO SEE MY
AROMATIC EXPLOITS THIS WEEK.
BECAUSE THIS WEEK YOU COULD
SEE ME RIGHT HERE. HUH?
( screams )
DON'T YOU GO PUTTING UP FAKE
PICTURES OF MY SUPER CUTE FACE.
IF THERE'S ONE THING
I CAN'T STAND, IT'S POOP!