I wish we could see real stars in Aincrad.
Yeah, but this isn't so bad.
I've never seen a shooting
star in the real world before.
Where I live, the sky's too bright at night.
A city‐girl. That explains a lot.
Oh, come on! Don't even tease me like that!
There's this one spot in my town
that's pretty famous for stargazing.
It's even got a tiny observatory.
Oh, I know!
Let's make a date to go see the stars there someday!
Sure. Someday.
We just have to make sure we survive
long enough to clear this game.
Yeah. And as soon as we do, I'll get you a real ring.
Mm‐hm.
On November 6th, 2022.
the NerveGear, a FullDive virtual reality device,
launched its first game, Sword Art Online.
Its developer, Akihiko Kayaba,
told the 10,000 players who logged in,
they could not log out.
And not only were they trapped, if a player died in‐game,
they would also die in the real world.
Amid growing despair, some took up
swords, hoping to clear the game.
Some became isolated and took their own lives.
While others ended up turning their
swords on their fellow players.
This nightmare continued for
what seemed like an eternity.
Then, on November 7th, 2024,
a heroic player dressed head‐to‐toe in black,
cleared the game and set everyone free. Finally.
Close to 4,000 people died in the end.
But with the death of the game's creator,
Akihiko Kayaba, the nightmare was over.
The players who lived through
it are known as SAO survivors.
And slowly but surely,
they're getting back their lives in the real world.
Um, sorry to bother you folks.
I couldn't help but notice those things you're wearing.
Huh? What, this? It's an Augma!
Welcome to Augma.
Ever since it was made available to the public,
it has quickly become the gadget to have.
Today, we'll look into the Augma,
the next‐gen wearable device.
If you compare the Augma with
its predecessor, the AmuSphere,
you might think since it doesn't have a FullDive function,
it's a step backward, technology‐wise.
But that's so totally not true.
The user's fully conscious while using the Augma
and that opens up a whole world of possibilities.
Isn't comparing the two systems a little
like comparing apples to oranges, though?
The AmuSphere immerses the user in a virtual reality,
while the Augma immerses the user in augmented reality.
You're absolutely right.
And if you wanna talk about safety, the Augma doesn't
come with any of the risks a FullDive rig has for users.
In fact, more and more people have been using
it for exercise and to track health goals.
Now we'll take a look at the
system's newest, hottest game,
Ordinal Scale.
The most exciting feature about Ordinal Scale,
in my opinion, anyway, is the ranking system.
Each player starts with a number that
reflects their ranking in the game.
The more a person plays, the higher their rank's gonna be.
Once you get your rank high enough,
you can unlock rewards outside the game.
Stuff like products and services from partner companies!
Would you look at that!
There's a discount from a big online
retailer and early access to tickets.
There's exclusive shopping sites
and a coupon for a free extra large beef bowl, too!
Kids always go nuts for freebies.
If they're that good in the lower ranks,
imagine what the top rank will get.
When service for the game started,
drones were launched to ease the strain on the network.
They were strange at first,
but folks seem used to them now.
One of the main reasons the game is gaining
popularity is thanks to its mascot, Yuna.
She's the world's first AR pop star and a testament
to how far AI tech has come over the years.
In fact, her mannerisms are so life‐like,
some think she's actually human and not a program.
She's mysterious!
That's probably the main reason she's so popular.
I just started collecting her figures myself...
Uh, Yuna's first live concert
is scheduled for the end of this month
and tickets for it, all 30,000 of them,
sold out almost instantly.
I had to get mine from a scalper
and they damn‐near cost me my condo...
The popularity of Augma and Ordinal Scale
isn't slowing down anytime soon!
All right, we cleared it!
Good job, Silica! Nice assist, Liz!
We all got a hundred points for beating it.
Look! It says we each get a free slice of cake! Sweet!
You guys play games way too much these days.
I‐I never thought I'd hear that coming from you!
Heck, every time we play, we get points to shop at stores.
Might as well play our butts off.
I bet deep down, you wanted to play, too, didn't you?
Well, I love this thing. It's super convenient.
It lets you watch TV anywhere,
it's easier to navigate than a smart phone
and the weather report's a lifesaver.
Best of all, we can talk to Yui whenever we want.
Yup!
You sound like you're totally sold on the Augma!
Mm, I wouldn't say that.
But, hey, they did hand them out to everyone
going to the survivor's school, right?
So,the least we do is take them out for a spin
and see what they can do.
I'm sorry for the wait.
Here are your bonus treats for clearing the game.
Dibs on that one!
The AI's so sharp, it knows what kind of cake we like.
It does a thing they call "Deep Learning".
Pretty thoughtful.
It's even more thoughtful than certain people we know.
I hear it can even tell you how
many calories are in that cake.
Wait up, Liz! Where are you going?
Asuna?
I still can't believe it.
All of us at the survivor's school got
free tickets to go to Yuna's concert.
Going to a concert's kinda weird for a field trip.
I know. Everything about that school is weird.
Yeah, but now you get to see your girl crush.
What? I‐I don't have a crush on her!
Who was belting out her songs at karaoke with Suguha?
You know every line to every song and I'll prove it!
You were great, Silica!
Kirito? You're gonna come to the concert with us, right?
Huh? I wasn't planning on it.
I'm not much of a fan, if you wanna know the truth.
What? You should go, it'll be fun!
Well, I don't know, maybe.
Anyway, I gotta admit,
you can do a lot of cool stuff with this gadget.
Still, I think FullDives are more my thing.
You're kidding.
No. I guess I just got used to living in different worlds.
You doofus. You sound like you wanna go back.
Oh! Speaking of Aincrad,
Do you guys think that rumor about Ordinal Scale is true?
You know, the one about boss monsters
from old SAO showing up in it?
Oh, right. The mysterious event battles.
Really? Is it like some kind of promotion?
I don't know.
I haven't had the chance to check one out yet.
The locations are secret till the last minute, so it's
hard for folks who don't have a car to get there in time.
It'd be awesome to find out, though.
So all we need is a ride? Hmm.
Kirito!
Looks like we made it just in time.
They released the location a half‐hour ago.
And there's already so many people here!
That means there'll be even more by the time it starts.
About time you showed up?
Sweet! You brought Asuna with you!
No, I brought him! He didn't want to come,
but after I beat the others at rock‐paper‐scissors,
he didn't have a choice!
Huh? Yeah, whatever.
Guys, Let's show her how badass we are!
Yeah!
All right! - It's gonna be awesome!
Kirito, it's almost time to start.
Oh, right.
Ordinal Scale , activate!
That's...
The boss from Floor 10 in Aincrad.
Kagachi the Samurai Lord!
He looks exactly like him, doesn't he?
Too bad we can't use our sword skills here.
I wonder if he's gonna use the same attack patterns.
Yuna?
I hope everyone's ready!
It's time to battle! So, start the music!
Uh... Oh, awesome! Yuna's singing!
It's a special stage with a bonus!
I'm gonna piss myself!
How do we beat this thing?
He's frigging huge!
What do you say, Kiri‐dude?
No, wait! Time out!
Time out!
Don't let your HP hit zero! Your rank will get docked!
I know that!
Our guns didn't do jack to it at this range.
No way am I gonna get up close!
Hey!
Come on, you guys! That bonus has our name on it!
I got it!
Nice block!
Tank!
I'm on it!
Eight showed up. Perfect.
Body feels heavy. This isn't like VR at all.
It's coming for you!
Kirito!
Whoa!
Holy crap! It's hard to move!
You're just a little out of shape, is all!
I'm not out of shape!
The hell's he doing?
Watch it, I got the kill‐shot! ‐Huh?
Oh.
Nice one!
Rank 2?
He's making his killer move! Tanks! Follow me!
Nice hit, man! Come on!
Yes! Wait for me!
Move! Retreat!
Right behind you!
All right!
Switch.
Go!
That was awesome!
Yeah!
Congratulations on defeating the boss!
I just boosted everyone's points!
And I have a special reward for
the player who worked the hardest!
Yes!
Oh.
You're this battle's MVP. Congratulations!
See you at the next battle!
Nice job, Asuna.
So that guy's number two?
He's a powerful player, that's for sure.
Dude, my rank shot up from just this one battle.
Look.
Man, those SAO bosses pay out!
If the other users find out,
this game's gonna get crowded!
Huh?
Well, well!
Looks like you barely moved up in rank, Kiri‐dawg!
Like I care. I'm leaving the AR raids to you guys.
Make sure you get the lady home safe.
Of course I will!
Hey, if the kid here gets fresh with you, give me a call.
I'll come save you!
You got it!
Huh? What the heck's an item doing here?
What the...? Oh, it's you.
Ah, so you wanna steal my find, huh?
I don't give a damn if you are ranked number two.
I ain't gonna give it up that easy.
Man! That boss moved the same as the one from SAO.
Wish I could say I moved the same.
After all that running around, my whole body's sore.
Can't believe you guys took it down so quick.
For one thing, Asuna and I fought it before.
Yeah, but still, it wasn't easy. You could tell the
other players weren't used to working as a team.
By the end of it, Kirito was exhausted.
That's only 'cause I'm not used to fighting in AR.
Hmm?
Oh, and you'll never guess who showed up to cheer us on.
You know that girl, Yuna? She gave us a reward
Huh? Yuna was at the boss fight with you guys?
For real?
What's she like?
That was pretty cool, seeing her live.
But like a dumbass, I forgot to put
my name down for one of those tickets.
Too bad you missed out, man.
When they were doing those Ordinal Scale
sign‐ups, I scored myself a pair.
Yeah, I got a pair, too.
You got two?
Oh, come on! Hook me up!
All right, all right!
Get off! Stop begging, I'll let you have one.
Stare.
Yes, Leafa, I'll give you a ticket.
Yay!
Uh, I just remembered,
I have kendo boot camp next week.
Is anyone else as weirded
out about this as I am?
I mean, what's up with an old SAO boss
showing up at an Ordinal Scale battle.
If it were a tie‐in between
games, wouldn't we have heard?
Mm‐hm. But I don't think that's what's going on.
Argus, the company that used to run SAO
, was shut down a while ago.
What about the other players at the event?
Did they know the boss was from SAO , too?
Mm. No, I'm pretty sure most of them didn't.
No one knew its attack patterns,
except us and maybe one or two others.
Switch.
Isn't that the impression you got?
Yeah. Most of them never saw it before.
The thing is, if the old bosses from SAO keep showing up,
it's only a matter of time before folks start catching on.
And those battle events are where the points are at.
Sounds like someone's trying to bring
old Aincrad to the real world. Damn.
So what?
The Augma's nothing like the NerveGear,
so no one's gonna die. It's safe.
Anyway, Yui, see if anything's fishy.
Okay, Daddy!
Heck, if I can hang out with Yuna,
I'll totally go to a battle!
Me, too!
And next time, he'll give me a ride on his bike.
I wish these events would happen at better
times and at places that are easier to get to.
That's what us guys in Fuurinkazan are for!
If any of you ladies need a ride,
just pick up the phone and we'll pick you up!
Yeah, that's what worries us, Klein.
But! Oh, you suck.
Yuna.
What's wrong, Yuna?
What is this thingy?
Proof that everyone loved your singing.
Really? This little guy?
Hmm.
There'll be plenty more where that came from...
after I get my revenge on them.
I'm heading out now, Kazuto!
Okay. Have fun at boot camp.
You gonna change out of those sweats anytime soon?
Yeah, well, I'm just gonna stay home today.
And research some colleges.
That's good, but you should get some exercise, too.
Grab a shinai and go swing it around outside, at least.
Yeah, maybe. If I feel like it.
Don't forget to bring back some of those
Whatever. You know, you should try using the Augma more.
You could win a free gym membership!
Well, see you!
AR's everywhere I look these days.
Link start!
Asuna! Hey.
Hey, you! So, what's going on?
Is Leafa coming?
No. She just left for that Kendo boot camp.
Is she gone for long?
A few days.
Waking up in the morning's gonna be tough.
She's my alarm clock.
Dork!
Even though she's gone, make sure you eat.
Of course! You know, I can cook for myself.
If you say so.
But when you have stuff on your mind,
you tend to forget things like eating right.
Daddy only makes pasta with one ingredient, pepperoncini.
TMI, Yui. TMI.
Kirito, I was thinking about our plans.
My mom said she'd like to meet you one of these days.
Yeah, one of these days. Sure.
Mm.
They postponed another event quest in ALO.
Again?
I just checked and in the last two weeks,
ALO has had a 30 percent drop in logins.
I guess it's because everyone's
busy playing Ordinal Scale.
Yeah, maybe. For now.
But I'm sure they'll come back eventually.
Yeah.
Huh?
Hey, Asuna! Right on time!
Thanks for coming out tonight.
Hope that text didn't wake you up.
Oh, no. I wasn't in bed yet. You caught me taking a bath.
You're missing one of your friends.
Oh, yeah. We sent him a message,
but he hasn't called back yet.
How about you go on ahead,
we'll jump in once he gets here.
Okay.
But you better hurry.
Otherwise, I'm going to scoop
up all your points for myself.
Hey, let's not be greedy!
See you in there.
Okay.
Is everyone ready?
Yeah! Wooo!
It's time to battle! So, start the music!
Crap, Yuna showed up! We gotta get in there!
Is Dale gonna show, or what?
Damn it. That loser still hasn't answered my text.
We better hurry, or we'll miss out on that prey!
Actually, tonight, you're the prey!
What's a boss doing here?
It's a new song!
Aw, yeah!
I'm impressed.
I can see why they were some of
the best in the Assault Team.
But...
I'll teach them the difference between AR and VR.
Oh, yeah! Bring that bonus!
VR never hurt like that, did it?
Son of a bitch! I'm gonna kick your ass!
Come on, don't be like that.
Bastard.
Now let's have some fun.
Here. You dropped this.
Now keep your eyes open.
It's winding up.
It's prepping for its big attack!
You Tanks, draw its aggro!
Okay.
Its killer move is coming.
When you see it hover, aim for the wings!
Huh? Right!
Everyone moves in, once it hits the ground!
You got it!
Here, chickie, chickie!
Fire!
Go!
Oh, shit!
Yo, you were amazing out there.
Nice strategy!
Yeah, you were awesome! You play any other games?
Huh? Oh, uh...
Hello again!
Congratulations!
Oh.
Oh, well. See you later, Asuna.
Lightning Flash Asuna.
Death isn't permanent in Ordinal Scale.
And without the fear of death,
a player's potential is unlimited.
Next time we meet in game,
I'll show you my potential.
Here's the latest on Ordinal Scale,
the AR game everyone's talking about.
Players are telling us that some of
the bosses from SAO 's old Aincrad,
have been showing up in OS' event battles.
The word on the forums is, a player can rack
up a boat‐load of points at those raids.
And not only that, there's a good chance
you'll catch Yuna singing at one of them!
Leveling up and seeing Yuna would be awesome!
Easy now!
As we all know, Sword Art Online was shut down for good.
But I bet you didn't know that there's
been a ton of new interest in it,
thanks to a book that came out last month
called The Complete SAO Incident Report.
Huh. Hmm.
Talk about jumping on the bandwagon late.
I wonder if the book's popularity,
along with the recent spike in Augma users,
are the reasons for the huge drop in logins
on the two big VR games, ALO and GGO.
Do you think people are getting bored with VR?
I have no idea, so let's ask some familiar faces,
who might be able to shed some light
on what's going on in the VR world.
Take it away!
In the next ALO tourney, I want to fight
someone that'll have me shaking in my boots.
Less players means less challenge for me.
Hell, they might as well give me the trophy now.
Yeah, well, you didn't win last time, did you?
This world holds a special place in our hearts
and there's no way we're going to abandon it.
Yes, it's true. There are less
players in Sylph territory now.
We can't hold major events like we used
to, which is a shame.
But if you want to know the truth, I'm not worried.
I'm sure everyone will be back someday.
Why'd you desert me, Fukajiro?
I got a new grenade launcher for you and everything!
You know how hard it is to get one of these?
Where are you,Leafa?
Come back!
Sorry about that.
And now, please welcome our surprise guest. Enjoy!
How's everyone doing tonight?
There's just four days left till my first live concert!
I hope you're all looking forward to it.
Hi, Daddy! Good morning.
Good morning, Yui.
Where are we?
Oh.
This is the battlefield Asuna played on last night.
She's putting a lot of effort into this game, huh?
Yeah, she is.
Is there something special about that day?
Yup. That's when I promised Asuna I'd take
her up to Mt. Doudaira to watch the meteor shower.
That sounds fun! Can I go, too? Can I?
What do you think? Of course!
Goodie! I'm gonna wear something cute!
Back in SAO, we promised each
other that if we got out, we'd...
Hey, Daddy! This would be a great time to
do some fight training for Ordinal Scale.
What?
Mommy said she was worried about
you not getting enough exercise.
Go on, show her how cool you are,
or your marriage will be in trouble!
Ordinal Scale, activate.
This doesn't feel right at all.
There's like a lag, or something.
It's a different physical sensation. That's all!
Practice is the only way to get better!
Maybe if I...
Oh, I'm sorry!
Who are you?
Did you see that, Yui?
Yes.
She didn't have an NPC tag.
She wasn't a player, either.
Then, is she some kind of AR ghost?
No, Daddy. That's impossible.
I guess it is.
It looked like she was saying something.
By the way her mouth moved, I think she said the words,
"Look for...", but that's all I could tell.
I didn't mean to scare you.
I'm sorry I went without you last night.
No, that's okay. I don't mind.
By the way, at that last battle we were at,
you said you saw some other SAO survivors.
Yeah. That one player ranked second.
Really? That guy, huh?
I think he was in the Knights of the Blood Oath. Maybe.
"Maybe".
Yeah, it's like, it's him,
but he's different than he was in SAO.
Back then, he went by "Nautilus"
and I remember he had potential.
I also remember he couldn't go on boss raids with
us, because he was afraid of dying.
Well, he's definitely changed his playing style.
His agility in AR is unbelievable.
Like a gymnast, or something.
Hmm. Did you talk to him?
Mm‐mm. I didn't know how he'd react to seeing me again.
Still we were in the same guild,
so I'm a little concerned about him.
It's hard to drop being second‐in‐command, huh?
Watch it, soldier!
Hey, Asuna,
have you heard any stories about this park?
You know, like, about ghosts.
Oh, my God, would you stop.
You know how freaked out I get,
talking about stuff like that.
I know, I know! I'm sorry.
Anyway, Kirito,
let's talk about how we're going to break the news.
Uh, "news"?
My mom knows something's up with us,
so she's been grilling me about you.
Oh, right, that news. Mm hm.
She's not mad or anything.
But we should figure out how to tell her.
Yeah. You're right.
Daddy! Mommy! I found something out about the game!
I have something to show everyone.
So far, when a boss monster has appeared at an
event, it has always been at 9:00 p. m.
This is the location where Mommy and Daddy
fought Kagachi the Samurai Lord the other day.
And this is the location where Mommy fought last night.
In a few seconds, you'll see the locations
where the other nine bosses appeared.
I'll also superimpose a flattened
map of Old Aincrad over it.
No way!
Every place a boss showed up in OS lines
up with a dungeon from Old Aincrad!
The admin seem to have picked open spaces in the city,
with coordinates that most closely match the dungeons.
With this, we can make certain predictions.
For example, tonight at 9:00, a boss will most
likely appear at the Ebisu Garden Place in Shibuya.
Oh, this is great!
If we know where it's going to be, we can go, too!
Won't your parents mind you're out that late?
Mine won't, as long as I'm hanging with you guys.
They're so weird.
If this was VR, they'd pitch a fit.
Yeah, I bet!
Well, have fun, guys.
I have to work tonight, so I can't make it.
How about you? Are you gonna go to this one?
Nah. I'll pass on tonight.
Oh, jeez! Are you still not used to fighting in AR?
Nope.
Oh, well, suit yourself.
Darn it.
Huh?
All right, ladies!
Let's gear up and show that Yuna chick
how us veteran players like to party!
Yeah!
By the way, where's Klein?
Who knows? He's probably somewhere in Ordinal
, grinding for points, or something.
You know, I saw him last night,
right before the battle started.
But I don't think he ever actually joined it.
They were waiting on one of the
other Fuurinkazan guys to show.
Oh, yeah?
What sucks about AR battles is you have
go to an actual place to participate.
Oh, speaking of going places,
we should figure out when we're all going
to meet up to go see the meteor shower.
Shh!
You know what? We should hammer out tonight's plan.
Okay, so where does everyone wanna meet? Ideas?
Yui.
Yes, Daddy?
I wanted to keep the meteor shower
thing a secret from the others.
Ooh! I'm so sorry.
Eh, it's okay. You didn't know.
Anyway, about the boss location data you got,
could you send it to my cell later on?
Yes! I'd be happy to!
Hi, Kirito, it's me.
Oh, hey, Asuna.
Hang on a second.
That is some plain pasta.
Yeah, I know.
It's the only recipe my cooking app recommends,
so I'm going with it.
Your diet is so not balanced, it's not even funny.
Here's an idea. How about you make
me some of your ragout rabbit stew?
Right, I'll just whip one up.
I know! What if I got some ingredients,
came over and made something like it?
Oh, sure! That'd be great.
Hey, so about that ghost you mentioned earlier today.
Huh?
You asked if I heard about a ghost in Yoyogi Park?
Oh, right.
Anyway, I did some digging.
Some players say they've seen a ghost.
Not in Yoyogi Park, but in other places.
They say it looks like a young girl in a hoodie.
You're kidding me.
What's wrong? Wait, did you see her?
I didn't! But like, maybe whoever saw
it, just saw an NPC instead! Maybe.
Mm. Maybe...
Oh, by the way, I found the tent and sleeping bag.
They look like they're good to go.
That's great!
It's a good thing you have stuff like that.
Oh, don't forget to thank your
dad for letting us borrow them!
Mm. Sure.
I can't wait. This'll be fun!
Bye-bye, Klein. Leader of the Fuurinkazan guild.
We sure had a big crowd last night, huh?
Yeah, I guess we did.
The next one will be even bigger.
Yeah?
Don't tell me you're interested in this.
So many words. It looks boring.
No. It reads like a diary of my memories.
Hm. The swordsman said,
"Once I draw my other sword, the battle's over for you."
He sounds totally cool!
Come on, read the rest of it to me!
I finally found you.
I didn't know you were looking.
Well, you're not a ghost, that's for sure.
Hey, who are you?
Is there something you want me to find?
No, wait!
Hello?
Hey, it's me. About time you picked up.
Sorry. I was on the road. What's up?
I found Klein. He's in the hospital in Yoyogi.
Been there since last night. His arm's all busted up.
What? He get in an accident?
I don't know. He said he ran into some trouble
on the way to one of them Ordinal Scale battles.
That's all I got before he conked out.
Damn.
Let me know when you find out more.
Yeah. You be careful on that bike, man.
Daddy?
Gosh, I hope Yuna shows up to this battle.
Silica, what do you think the deal is with Yuna?
I mean, do you think she's a program,
like what the developer says?
Or do you think she might actually be human?
Well, I'm pretty sure she's not a human.
But she also doesn't seem like an AI, either.
Hey, if you ask me, I can't think of a single human
that can sing with such a crystal‐clear, flawless voice.
So you're saying my voice isn't crystal‐clear, is that it?
You sound good, for a human.
Liz, I'm never going to karaoke with you again.
Oh, come on. I'm sorry.
It's starting.
Is everyone ready?
It's time to battle! So start the music!
Yuna!
We so lucked out!
You ladies ready to get tons of points tonight?
Yeah!
I hate it when I have to be the tank!
Our plan worked!
"Worked"? We almost got squashed!
Hot damn! You girls are kicking all the ass out here.
Come on, slow pokes! Try and keep up!
Hey! Those are our points, buster.
Ordinal Scale, activate!
Daddy?
Shh.
I think I know her from somewhere else.
Your name's Nautilus.
We were in the Knights of the Blood Oath together.
These days, I go by a different name, Asuna.
Eiji?
You play this game really well.
I'm not who I used to be. And you've gotten less intense.
Oh, really?
Yeah. Back then, you were tougher.
I know her.
Going down!
It's almost time.
Move in! Everyone, attack!
What the...?
Is another boss showing up?
Pina!
It's tiny!
Did you come to help us fight?
Silica! This way!
Daddy! That boss is called Dorcel the Chaos Drake!
It lived way up on Floor 91!
Floor 91?
Let me at that thing!
Oh, shit!
Why are you mad at me? What did I do?
I'm sorry‐‐ Ah!
Silica!
Asuna? Come on, Asuna, wake up!
Asuna!
Are you okay?
You dick!
What the hell's your prob...?
You're pathetic.
You might've been the greatest swordsman in VR,
but you're nothing in AR.
Son of a bitch!
Hey, you! Ever hear of game etiquette?
Time's up!
See you later!
Wait! What about the bonus?
Hey, I thought you were gonna help Asuna!
Please kiss me!
Asuna! Are you okay?
Well, this sucks.
Better luck next time.
I'm sorry, Asuna. This is all because I was being stupid.
Can you believe that number two guy
pushed Silica like that? What an asshole!
Uh‐huh. Nice save, Asuna.
That's another reason they made
you second‐in‐command back in...
Hey, what's wrong? Did you get hurt?
Mm‐mm. No, it's nothing.
Want me to take you home?
Mm‐hm. We'll help you up.
Hang onto my arm.
Good night, Asuna. I'll call you tomorrow.
Kirito?
Yeah, what's up?
I, uh, I was wondering if you
still remembered the day we met.
Sure. It was on Floor 1 of Aincrad.
That boss raid meeting?
Yeah. Right. And then, you...
Then you asked me to join your party, didn't you?
Uh‐huh. I still can't believe I
had the guts to even talk to you.
This is so cool. You can already see the lake from here.
No, you can see the lake, I...
Kirito, you shouldn't be out here on your own!
Kirito?
Kirito!
Who are you?
I'm...
A dream.
Kirito.
Why can't I remember?
Are you okay?
What's going on? Can't you sleep?
Why are you sitting in the dark?
Thanks for coming. I'm sorry if I woke you.
It's okay. Did something happen?
This cabin...
About how long would you say we've lived here?
Well, we bought it in SAO,
so it's been two and a half years now?
It has, hasn't it?
Asuna?
What...? I knew it. I can't remember.
What do you mean? What?
Everything that happened in Aincrad.
I can't recall any of it.
The first time you and I met.
All the battles we fought.
Us living here together.
What the heck are you talking about?
You're joking, right?
In the last few hours,
the memories I had of SAO faded away.
There's nothing left now.
I'll have to go through all the data
before I can say for certain what happened.
But by the looks of it,
Asuna's brain seems to have undergone
some kind of limited memory scan.
Limited memory scan?
So like, whatever did this only
targeted her memories of SAO ?
How's that even possible?
I can think of one way, actually.
If she were put in a situation,
which forced her to recall moments in SAO ,
the single neurons connected to
those memories would be identified.
Then by showering the neurons with electron pulses,
the image of each memory is scanned.
In the past few days, there've been multiple
reports of people with symptoms similar to Asuna's.
It could be a coincidence, but I doubt it.
Each patient had something in common.
They all played that AR game's event battles.
Then the Augma's causing it.
I can't be certain of that yet.
Is Asuna going to be all right?
Well, as of right now, I don't see any sign
of actual physical damage to her brain.
My theory is, her ability to
recall her memories was affected
because the electron
pulses degenerated her spine.
Unfortunately, I can't tell whether or not she'll
show any further symptoms until I run some more tests.
Wait, so you're saying
there's still a chance she'll
lose even more of her memories?
I'm sorry, Kirito.
Don't worry.
You can still remember what happened lately, right?
Mm‐hm.
This doesn't mean you're never gonna remember SAO again.
You will, you'll see.
Asuna?
What's wrong, Asuna?
Asuna!
Are you okay?
Well?
I'm sorry, Kirito.
I can't remember anything about SAO.
I remember when we bought this place in
ALO, but not when we first got it.
Everything about SAO 's a blank.
Mommy!
I'm sorry.
I hate that I can't remember the life we had back then.
I'm going to try to find out what's
really going on in Ordinal Scale.
I'm sure I'll find some kind of clue
that'll help you get your memory back.
Mm. Thank you, Yui.
Even if I can't remember it now, this really is
the place we called home back then, isn't it?
Yeah.
I'll go make us some tea.
Oh, I wanna help!
No. I can make it.
The change of pace will do me good.
Now, I'm even more powerful than
Lightning Flash and the Black Swordsman.
Who would've thought?
If it weren't for Ordinal Scale, I'd still be nothing.
Soon, I'll make good on the promise I made her.
Hello?
So how's your arm doing?
Eh, it's not too...
I feel worse about making you guys worry.
Do you feel any, I don't know, different?
Huh?
Do you remember what happened in SAO ?
No. If I try and think about it,
it's like my head's all stuck in this big‐ass fog.
Well, it's not like it was all
fun and games for us, right?
I don't know.
Maybe it's better I don't remember.
I can't wait. This'll be fun!
Welcome to Augma!
Damn!
Launch search for Ordinal Scale rankings.
Hey!
Oh, uh! Sorry.
Let's go, man.
Yeah.
I can't tell if it's a side effect due to a glitch
in the system, or a deliberately designed feature.
If it's the latter and someone did this intentionally,
I'm afraid this is only the beginning.
Let me get this straight.
You're saying that if any of the other
SAO survivors play Ordinal Scale,
there's a chance they'll lose their memories, too.
Just like Asuna?
If I'm not careful, it could happen to me, too.
If I can't remember those two years with her,
will I also forget I love her?
I'm sorry, Daddy!
I couldn't find the player called Eiji.
I used his name and visual data from the last battle,
but the search didn't turn up a thing.
Oh, well...
Don't give up, Daddy.
While you're fighting the boss, I'll be gathering data.
I'm sure I'll find something to go on!
I know you will.
I'm counting on you.
Right.
Well, well! Look who it is.
Huh?
What are you doing here?
You just told everyone not to
fight the bosses and here you are.
I know. But it really is dangerous.
If a boss kills you, you'll lose your memory like Asuna.
I'll be fine.
I'm not an SAO survivor like you guys.
If I don't have those memories to scan,
nothing's gonna happen to me. Right, Yui?
Yes. You should be safe. I think.
Yeah, but we don't know if...
If you're really that worried,
then you'll just have to keep me safe, won't you?
If anyone can keep her safe, it's you, Daddy.
Ordinal Scale, activate!
What the‐‐?
That's Dire Tusk, the boss from Floor 18!
What happened to Floor 13's boss?
I just checked and a total of ten monsters have
appeared at different locations across the city!
They're pulling out all the stops tonight.
Dire Tusk is here, because the
admin shuffled the locations around!
Crap, that's Dire Tusk, all right.
Come on!
It's gonna wind up for an attack next.
Then let's light him up!
Awesome! He's like a sitting duck!
No, get away!
Oh, crap!
Pace yourself!
He didn't show up tonight.
Nice one.
Yeah. Thanks to you.
Take me out for cake and we'll call it even.
How about a coupon for a free beef bowl instead?
Do I look like I want a beef bowl?
I'll settle for a ride home on your bike, cheapskate.
Yuuna?
Hey, wait!
Who are you?
I'm sorry, Daddy.
I was following a clue, but I got blocked by a firewall.
During the battle just now,
I found out that a mysterious program activated
right when a SAO survivor took
on critical damage from the boss.
Son of a...
You want a drink?
Mm‐mm.
Look for...
Of course!
Yui! That girl in the hoodie.
You know which direction she
pointed each time we saw her?
Yes, I have the coordinates.
Bring up a map of Tokyo and show me where they all lead.
They crisscross in Ookayama!
You know what that building is, Yui?
That's where the Touto University of Engineering is.
Why does she want me to look there?
I'll cross‐reference the school's
database and the player called Eiji.
It'll just take a second.
I know this guy.
That's Professor Tetsuhiro Shigemura.
He designed the Augma.
He did, huh?
Based on the evidence, the most glaring flaw in a
FullDive VR device is the FullDive function itself.
When a person has to sever their
physical senses to play a VR game,
that person is taking on
incalculable risks to their health.
True, FullDive tech has been applied to activities
other than gaming such as communication,
browsing, and digital production.
But none of those activities require all of one's senses.
Sight, sound and limited tactile information are enough.
So instead of using a dangerous FullDive device,
one should use an AR device,
which has been proven to be safe and stable.
Are there any questions on what we've covered so far?
Yes. You there.
Professor, would you say AR devices have
certain risks that VR devices don't?
If so, what are your thoughts on that?
Yes, well, are you talking about traffic
accidents, while wearing an AR device?
No. I'm talking about risks like permanently altering
and damaging the user's perception of reality.
FullDive tech just makes a
virtual world seem like reality.
But AR tech alters reality itself.
Don't you think that's dangerous?
I'll answer that question next time.
Class dismissed.
I'll cut right to the chase.
Do you know someone named Eiji?
He's the second rank player in Ordinal Scale.
No.
But he was in your class and he even took your lab.
I've had many students over the years.
Okay, let's try a different question.
Did you know that the Augma is causing
SAO survivors to lose their memories?
Did you know the Augma has a
feature users don't know about?
A feature that scans their brain while they're wearing it?
I didn't know I was going to be interrogated.
Kikuoka told me you just wanted to audit my class.
If the Augma does have a dangerous feature built in,
it won't be long before it's found out.
And once that happens, the Augma's gonna be
banned, just like the NerveGear was.
And you?
You'll end up the same as your former
student, Akihiko Kayaba.
I don't know what you're talking about.
But let's say the Augma has this
brain‐scanning function you described,
why is it bad if someone forgets about SAO ?
In the words of Nietzsche,
"Blessed are the forgetful,
for they get the better even of their blunders."
So now ask yourself, do you think those
survivors want to remember their horrifying past?
If you wish to speak further, make an appointment.
I'm very busy, though,
so there's no guarantee I'll be able to see you.
I didn't know you built robots too, professor.
Thanks for your time.
That's right. Dr. Shigemura has a daughter.
Or rather, had. She died two years ago.
Yuuna?
I'm sure you put two‐and‐two together already,
but I might as well confirm it for you.
The cause of death was the NerveGear.
She was a victim of SAO.
Huh? Why would he do this?
What the hell's he trying to prove?
Well, maybe he honestly thinks he's doing
good by making the SAO survivors forget.
Yeah, well, I can't prove it yet,
but I'm sure the Augma's dangerous to users.
I need your help.
Please, Mr. Kikuoka. Shut down the service.
The Ministry of Economy is tied up with this,
so we have to be careful with how we proceed.
I am looking into everything you've told me.
But I can't move without proof.
A bunch of the Ordinal Scale players are SAO survivors.
And if they fight any of the bosses from Old Aincrad,
you're gonna have a lot more people losing their memories.
I know and I'm doing the best I can.
I checked with the hospital about Klein and his
friends and confirmed their symptoms with the doctors.
But I'm more concerned about their
broken bones than their memories.
You should take your own advice
and don't fight any more bosses.
Your memories are important to me, too.
Don't forget that.
Hey, what's up?
Nothing. I just wanted to hear your voice.
Oh.
Listen, Asuna.
Is it cool if I come over?
Now?
Um, yeah. Or later, if that's better.
No, now's fine.
I'd come to you, but I'm kind of scared to go outside.
No, I get it. I'll be at your
place in about 20 minutes.
I'm in Ookayama right now, but traffic's not too bad.
Sorry. The door was already open.
Heh, why do you sound so nervous? It's okay!
My parents are both at work.
Yeah, but it's my first time here.
Oh, crap. I should've brought your
folks a gift. Like a plant, or something.
Don't be silly! It's fine, I swear.
Come on, this way.
I was talking to someone today and they said survivors
like us are better off forgetting what happened in SAO.
I got to thinking and maybe he's got a point there.
We saw a lot of horrible things happen.
It was scary and sad.
But the memories we have of those two years, good and
bad, are what shaped us into the people we are today.
Everyone's been telling me about
how high‐tech your room is.
It's not what I thought.
In a way, it sort of reminds me
about your place in Selmburg.
I'll go bring us up some drinks and snacks.
Yeah, sure.
Make yourself at home, okay?
Uh...
To the future me.
It's been a long time since I've written in this diary.
These days, I'm worried I'll forget what's
happened to me since I came back to the real world,
so I'll write how I feel now in case I do.
I met Kirito four years ago,
but I only remember the last two.
The moments with him, I can still
remember, are precious, like jewels.
There's a good chance Ordinal Scale will
cause me to forget things more and more.
And that scares me.
But as long as I can keep making new memories with Kirito,
I should be fine.
My calendar says I'm supposed to go to the mountains in
Saitama in a couple of days to watch the stars with him.
But I don't remember the day we
made plans to go there anymore.
I went back and read this diary and from what I can tell,
Kirito said he wanted to give me some kind of present.
I hope he'll forgive me for not remembering what.
I want to get him something,
but since I'm not allowed to have a job yet,
I'm going to use all my points and
whatever I have saved to buy him a gift.
My beloved Kirito. What will I do if I forget him?
What will I do if I forget these feelings I have?
And what if it turns out I can't
make new memories with him?
It scares me to even think about it.
I pray that the person I am tomorrow
doesn't forget the feelings I have for him now.
It's okay. You can read the whole thing if you want.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I love you, Kirito. So much.
Even if I forgot everything that happened in SAO ,
my feelings for you will never ever change.
They won't for me, either. I love you.
Always have. Always will.
I know.
I'm gonna get your memories
back, no matter what. I promise.
You know I won't let you down, right?
Mm‐hm.
Oh, a shooting star.
Well, Eiji, tomorrow's the big day.
I get to be on stage in an enormous
arena and sing for everyone.
Yeah. You nervous about it?
No. Not at all.
I finally get my chance to sing for
a huge audience. How cool is that?
This performance is gonna make
me the world's number one diva.
That's right.
Tomorrow's going to make you the
biggest and brightest star of them all.
Hey! Would you please read some more of that book to me?
Sure. You got it.
This time, could you find the
part in it where you show up?
I wanna hear about you.
I'm not in it.
Huh?
I don't show up anywhere in this thing.
I guess folks like us, the ones who couldn't
fight, aren't worth remembering.
Yes?
You're taking far too long getting this done.
Someone's caught on to our plan. You need to hurry.
Yes. I know that, sir.
I made sure all the pieces are
in place for the final stage.
You're not having second
thoughts about our deal, are you?
Not as long as you hold up your end of it.
I will, sir.
By the way, about Yuna...
Lately, it seems like she has other
things on her mind besides singing.
That's probably her self‐preservation program.
If anything, it's proof the plan is going smoothly.
If you say so.
Yuuna, right?
So where is this place?
Is it a dream? The virtual world?
Dreams and virtual worlds are
the same thing, more or less.
The second you wake up,
the experience becomes a fleeting memory.
I guess.
Here's a thought, maybe it's all just a dream.
Everything like clearing that death
game and coming back to the real world.
And what if, when you open your eyes,
you wake up trapped in Aincrad again?
Did you ever think about that?
I have, but I never wished it was true, not even once.
And by the sound of it, you're an SAO survivor, too.
Are you Professor Shigemura's daughter?
Are you still alive?
Why'd you send me to your dad? What do you want me to do?
Why would your dad wanna steal Asuna's memories of SAO ?
What's the Augma really for?
That song!
All I want is to go on singing. It's all I ever wanted.
And I wanna save Asuna.
So are you gonna tell me how or not?
Getting her memories back isn't going to be easy.
The rank you have now isn't nearly high enough to do it.
Well? Don't just stand there. Wake up.
Whoa, easy! You okay, guy?
Yeah.
What, you fell asleep playing that Augma game?
Seems like everybody's got one of those things these days.
Careful you don't fall on your face.
You wanna know the truth,
I think Silica blames herself for what happened.
I didn't even know.
If only I could've gone to one of those battles.
Klein got himself hurt at one
and ended up in the hospital.
It's probably better you stayed away.
You said it.
Kirito told everyone not fight the
bosses in OS because it's so dangerous.
And then, he goes to fight them by himself.
I sort of helped him on the last one, though.
But then, you know what?
I'm gonna make a video to teach him some kendo moves.
Then he'll cruise through those battles, no sweat.
Mm‐hm. Violence brings siblings together.
Come on!
We're singing the next song together.
We're here to practice, remember?
The concert's tomorrow!
Take the mic and get in here.
I don't know if this is cheering her up.
What do you mean?
It looks like Asuna's having fun.
If you say so...
Dude, you okay?
What's wrong?
Multiple bosses have appeared,
just like last night.
But this time, it's the ones from Floors 20 to 30.
I'm gonna take all of them down tonight.
I can't believe he's knocking down its HP all by himself.
He's a badass.
Jeez! Chill out!
What are you getting so worked up for?
It's only a game.
Move!
It's time for a bonus stage. Good luck, everyone.
We totally scored!
Congratulations.
It looks like you finally learned how to
handle yourself in this game, Black Swordsman.
You bastard!
Instead of Yuna rewarding you, I will.
Wow. Yuna's more popular than I thought.
Ugh. My throat's sore from karaoke.
That's what you get for overdoing it.
Silica, thank you for yesterday.
Oh, sure!
Oh, man. Wish Klein and Suguha could be here.
Wait. Where's Kirito?
He said he was going to stop by the restroom first.
Okay, I'm here like you wanted.
You're gonna give me her memory
back, or do I have to take it?
What's the rush, Black Swordsman?
You called yourself Nautilus back then.
Cool name for a guy who wouldn't
fight, 'coz he was too scared of dying.
I'm called Eiji now!
Guess I can't escape my past.
I'm surprised you remember a little runt like me.
Actually, I don't remember you. A friend did.
Hmm? A friend, like Asuna, I bet.
It's not enough you have her,
you probably want Yuuna, too.
What are you talking about?
Never mind.
You think you're so cool.
You know, there's a reason I'm ranked second in this game.
Do you really think you can beat me?
I won't know until I try.
Besides, it's not like you're number one.
Ordinal Scale, activate!
I wish I could change things.
I used my position as chairman
of Argus' board of directors,
to get Yuuna a NerveGear and a copy of SAO.
I was just trying to make my daughter happy.
But in the end, it was
my stupidity that killed her.
Yuuna!
Hah! I can see how everyone believed you'd clear SAO.
You've got some moves! Wish I could say
the same about you. Second rank my ass!
People only remember the players
who fought on the front lines.
But Yuuna and me? We didn't fight,
so we get treated like we didn't even exist!
Wait, you guys were together in SAO ?
That's right!
And I was with her at the end. I watched her vanish!
I hated myself for being so weak!
The girl I loved was in danger and I
couldn't lift a finger to save her!
Her brain had become so damaged
by the effects of the NerveGear,
it was impossible to save her.
But if I could acquire the memories of her
from the other SAO players and find a way to combine them,
the Deep Learning function would do the rest.
And it could give my daughter new life, as an AI.
The numbers in the Ordinal System are absolute.
Whoever is ranked number one becomes immortal.
After all, that's how you designed it, Kayaba.
Yuna, is it? It sounds like
"una", the Latin word for "one".
Aincrad was controlled by a
system using cardinal numbers.
Ordinal Scale is controlled by
a system using ordinal numbers.
A system I originally developed for
SAO, but discarded early on.
It seems you resurrected it, doctor,
and developed a new game.
The man I used to be would've done the
same, had I been in your place.
But now, doctor,
the man I've become believes in something greater.
An existence that can transcend the system itself.
Who cares if we take away everyone's memories of SAO ?
We're doing them a favor!
Let's see how good you are without this!
Goddamn you!
We all suffered back then.
But I won't lose to a guy that rejects the
past, because he thinks he suffered more.
Are you gonna give me Asuna's memory
back, or do you wanna keep going?
That was so fun!
It's too late now.
Practically every SAO survivor is upstairs.
In a few minutes,
we're going to start scanning the brains of
every survivor and take their memories of SAO.
Their memories of that hell.
And then we'll bring Yuuna back to life.
Huh? What're you talking about?
Like I said. It's too late now.
And you can't stop it.
Okay, so here's what I learned from Kamura,
the company that manufactures the Augma.
The drones flying inside the stadium
are equipped with a special function.
According to my source, they can boost
the output of the Augmas wirelessly.
So, what does that mean?
It means if they run that brain scan inside the stadium,
we might be dealing with something worse
than just partial memory loss.
Holy shit!
You said it.
The scan could permanently damage the brain and
might even kill people, just like the NerveGear.
I'll get the professor.
You get everyone to take off their Augmas.
Hopefully, they'll listen to you.
Oh, my God!
Is this part of the show?
Let us out!
Open the door!
Asuna!
Asuna! You okay?
Kirito!
Damn it. Looks like Kirito will have
to handle things on his own in there.
Come on!
Yuuna?
Please, Dad. You have to stop this now.
No. You're not quite ready yet.
But I don't want to come back to life.
Of course you don't.
You're still an AI and that's what your
self‐preservation program is making you say.
It won't be long now, so just be a good girl and wait.
But, Dad...
The AI crawler is collecting
all the data from the players.
She's almost done.
It's her final task. She did a fine job.
You have to stop this!
If you run a high‐output scan inside there,
those people might not just lose
their memories, they could die!
That is enough, Yuuna!
I would happily sell my soul to the devil,
if it meant I could bring you back to life.
I swear I'd... do anything,
even if it meant I ended up like Kayaba.
All I want is to get you back in my life.
Step back!
He's not making it easy for us.
That camera's recording. Find out where it's connected.
That should keep you busy for a while, Kikuoka.
I'm sorry, sir. I lost to one of the players.
But you can go ahead with the brain scan on the crowd.
I can't wait to see Yuuna again. The way she was.
You still have one last task to finish, though.
What?
You have to give me your memories of Yuuna as well.
Huh?
Of all the players in SAO,
you were the one who spent the most time with her.
What did you expect?
Besides, if you can't even
master the equipment I gave you,
what use are you?
What? But what about our deal?
You said you'd make it,
so I could be with Yuuna forever!
Farewell.
Yuuna!
Help me, Kirito!
If we don't stop this, everyone here is going to die!
Once the average of their emotive counters passes 10,000,
a high output scan will activate and destroy their brains!
I'm on it!
Everyone! Take off your Augmas! Now!
Take them off, or you'll die!
It's no use.
My dad put the bosses in the other events, so everyone
here would fight, thinking it's part of the game!
What am I supposed to do?
Go to the place we met yesterday.
That was Floor 100 in Old Aincrad!
Go there and beat the boss!
It's our last hope. Sit down.
I'm going to unlock the Augma's FullDive function now.
You can FullDive with the Augma?
The Augma's just a version of the NerveGear
with limited functions. Now get going!
I'm ready!
You guys...
Let's do this.
Yeah!
Good luck, Daddy!
Yui. Guard your mom.
Right!
Kirito!
Don't worry, this won't take long.
We're the only chance these people have
but I'm gonna need you to wait here.
Kirito...
Keep that safe, till I get back, okay?
Link start!
No way!
So this is Floor 100, The Ruby Palace!
Can't believe after two years,
we finally get to take a crack at it!
Agil!
So you're the last boss of SAO , huh?
Let's go!
Switch out!
Switch!
Shit.
No way.
Oh, man. How do we beat that thing?
I'm sorry, Asuna.
I'm the reason your memory was stolen.
My father's collecting the other SAO players'
memories of me from when I was alive in Aincrad.
He's using the old bosses to force the survivors
here to remember their fear of dying in SAO.
Then he'll run a scan on their
brains to extract the memories.
If that happens, it might end up
damaging everyone's brains permanently.
It might even kill them!
Oh, my God!
No, don't!
If I take it off his head, he'll be saved.
But then, what about the other players?
They're still in danger.
Yuuna, you died in SAO, because you were
brave enough to leave the safe zone.
You fought a boss and tried to clear a floor, didn't you?
I can't sit here and do nothing.
Yui? I'm going to help Kirito and the others.
Okay, Mommy. I'll join you in a little bit.
Link start!
Oh, no!
Silica!
Kirito!
No!
Crap!
Asuna!
I got you!
It's my fault! You lost your memories because of me!
No, stop blaming yourself. It's okay now.
Asuna!
Hi, guys. Sorry I'm late.
You okay to be here?
Mm‐hm. I'm ready to fight. I'm not afraid anymore.
Good.
Kazuto! Sorry I'm late!
Daddy, Mommy! I brought everyone else, too!
This is gonna be fun!
Stay sharp, general!
Ha! We rule in VR!
Skeena Guail!
Guy‐sah Oru‐muru!
She's a big lady!
They're here, too?
Yay!
Time's running out!
Hit it again!
Don't just stand there! You've got work to do!
What the...?
Pina!
I loaded up your saved data from the SAO server.
I thought you'd be more comfortable this way.
I also brought your gear, Sinon!
All right! Let's do this!
Yeah!
Hurry! Block it!
You and me, Asuna!
Right!
Damn it!
Switch!
I know what skill to use.
Now you really have cleared the game, Kirito.
Kayaba?
You only have one thing left to do.
It's Yuna!
Why is this happening?
I was so close, Yuuna! So close!
Don't worry, Dad.
No matter what, I'll always be in your memories.
Forever and ever.
You sounded great up there, Yuuna.
Thanks a lot.
The data for my primary body
was based on the resource script
of the boss from Floor 100.
Its language engine is what allowed me to move around.
But the boss was defeated and its
saved data will be initialized.
So now I have to say goodbye to you.
No way.
It's not a bad thing.
I got to sing in front of a huge audience,
so my wish was fulfilled. I couldn't be happier.
Before I go, I have to give this back to you.
Your fear of death is what
caused you to lose your memories.
But you overcame it and fought anyway.
I'm sure everything will come back to you now.
You remembered my wish, Eiji. Thank you.
The AR idol, Yuna, is making headlines again.
During her concert at the New National Stadium,
several boss monsters from Ordinal Scale appeared.
The promoters of the show said today
that it was a surprise event for the fans.
In other game‐related news,
Kamura Incorporated, the company behind the Augma,
revealed that their head of development,
Dr. Shigemura of Toto Institute, has decided to step down.
Bet you're glad to be out of that hospital.
Yeah, how's your arm doing?
Ow! Nah, I'm kidding, it's fine.
But I'll be sticking to VR games from now on.
But you got to meet more girls in AR.
Eh, it's no big deal. Nobody meets
their dream girl in games, anyway.
You better pray my wife never hears you say that.
Yo, she gave up her ticket for your broke ass.
Ow! What's your problem?
Apologize!
Um, guys, I brought something back for everyone.
Where was this boot camp you went to?
Shimane.
The place we stayed didn't have computers.
If I didn't smuggle in my Amusphere,
I would've died from boredom!
Eh...
By the way, where's Kirito and Asuna?
They said they had other plans tonight.
Anyone know what they're doing?
Oh, who cares about them.
If they're not here, they're missing out.
Some friend.
I get discharged and he can't come by for a drink?
He can suck it.
On second thought, you can buy your own drinks tonight.
You all owe me for that ticket.
You greedy... You got that ticket for
free, you cardboard‐sword dealer!
Oh, whatever.
At least I got ALO. Now that it's hopping
again, maybe I'll meet some new hotties.
Nope.
You were right, it gets dark up here.
Yeah. Can you see, Yui?
Yup! I can see just fine, Daddy!
The color balance is skewing a little green, though.
For a while there,
I didn't think we'd get to come here.
Oh, and in the end, I left without telling my mom.
You what?
You're kidding, right?
I'll talk to her when we get back.
Do you remember what we promised
each other back in Aincrad now?
What, to go stargazing?
Well, yeah. That was part of it.
I'm kidding. I remember.
You said if we ever got out, you'd give me a real ring.
Here. For you!
Um.
It's not fair if you're the only one
handing out presents, so I got you one.
Thank you.
This time, put it on my finger. And this time, for real.
Look! A shooting star!
Wow!
Amazing!
Why all the mystery, Kikuoka?
What did you bring me down here for?
I appreciate you getting the charges against me dropped,
but it's time you told me what this is about.
Actually, doctor, I want to talk about the future.
I've been keeping a close eye on your research.
And now, I feel like I've seen
how far a top‐down AI can go.
But I have my sights on a different kind of future.
You're the head of the Shigemura Research Lab.
Your students included Akihiko Kayaba and Nobuyuki Sugou.
So I know what I'm about to show you will interest you.
Kikuoka, what is that?
Welcome to Rath.