Ugh...
I'm so sick
of this heat.
It isn't even pleasant
to eat outside anymore.
Yeah, I know
what you mean.
But at least we have that
really strong sunblock
to put on... right?
You did put the sunblock
on before coming outside,
right, Sissy?
Huh...? Why would I?
Are you a dermatological
idiot...?
Ultraviolet rays are
the skin's enemy...
You don't want
your beautiful,
creamy white skin covered
in freckles, do you?
But we won't let that
happen, now will we...?
Just hold still while
I rub this over
every last inch
of your body.
Uh, no thanks.
Come on, there's no
need to be shy, Sissy.
I only want to look
after your health.
I promise, this will be much
easier if you let me just-
-Knock it off!
-Shirai?
Oh, hi there, Wannai.
And Awatsuki, too...
What's up?
Actually, we wanted
to ask you a favor.
[Music]
Swimsuit modeling?
Yes... The swim
club is involved
with this swimsuit
manufacturer...
They've been insisting
we do this for them.
Apparently, it'll be in
the upcoming issue
of their web catalog.
The older girls in
the club are all busy
competing in
a swim meet...
Which means we're the
only ones available
to participate.
This is perfect...! We
have to help them out, Sissy.
Hmm...
Me wearing a swimsuit
and modeling...?
It doesn't sound like
something I'd be good at...
I don't know...
Of course. We
totally understand.
Thanks, I'm sorry-
I thought better of
you than this!
These poor girls are
in desperate need
of our assistance...
Yet you refuse to
volunteer your time?
How uncharitable!
I'm tearing up...
it's so tragic!
Hey...! You wanna chip in?
All right. If you don't
think I'll be too bad at it,
I'll help you out.
That's the selfless
Sissy I know!
I'm so glad!
Yes, thank you! We
really appreciate it!
Excellent...! I get to
spend a whole day with Sissy
in a swimsuit!
I gonna have to pick out a
really sexy bikini to model...!
Yes... I'll have
her salivating!
I know there are dirty thoughts
going through your head.
I give!
I didn't know it was
such a big business!
It's exciting and
intimidating
all at the same time!
Uiharu!
It's great that you were
able to get your friends
to come along,
thanks again!
It was no problem.
With something like this,
the more the merrier,
don't ya think?
Eh, so after seeing us,
are you sure you want us
to play swimsuit models?
Don't worry so much.
Modern fashion designers
have come up with
all sorts of ways to make
even underdeveloped bodies
look more appealing
to the eye.
Thank you for your
support, Shirai.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Who is she?
She's the manufacturer's
general manager.
Thanks for coming today.
It's gonna be great...
Uh... weren't there
two more coming?
More models?
Well, hello, Shirai.
Ugh... I know that voice.
Oh, my, look at all the
people who are with you!
Is this a social
studies field trip
for school, or something?
Oh, hi there, Kongo.
And Konori's here, too!
What do you have to
say for yourself?
Why are you wearing
that outfit?
The school rule dictates
that we wear our uniforms
even on days off.
Or have you
forgotten that?
For this afternoon
at least,
I am no mere student of
Tokiwadai Middle School...
I am here as a model...
Naturally, I
dressed as such.
A model...?
They asked you, too?
Huh...? You don't
mean... are you-?
Did you come for the swimsuit
modeling as well, Konori?
Yeah. I ran into a
classmate at the gym,
and she asked me if I'd be
willing to come today...
What about you guys?
We've got some friends
in the swim club,
and they asked
us to help out.
It's obvious that none
of you have done anything
like this before...
I'd be delighted to give
you a pointer or two.
From a pro...
I've been modeling ever
since I was a little girl.
The thunderous applause
echoing off all the walls...
the cheers
screaming my name!
I can still hear their
ardent admiration, even now!
Give me a break. I
bet the only person
cheering for you
was your mother.
Now... shall we get
down to business?
Will you show me to
the changing rooms?
Uh... sure...
Right this way.
I must be dressed in a
suit that flatters my curves.
Is that girl an
acquaintance of yours?
She's more like somebody I
wish I wasn't acquainted with.
All right! Everybody
please choose
whichever swimsuit
you prefer.
Okay!
Hey, look... what do
you think of this?
Wow... that's a
really pretty one.
Oh...! This one's
really cute.
I think I found
one I like, too.
Hmm... This doesn't
look that great...
and I don't care
for this one... Hmm...
Haven't you decided
on a suit yet?
It seems like you could
use some tutoring.
Why don't you allow me
to select one for you?
I don't need your
help, thanks.
Halter--top suits are best for
those with a nice bust...
and then there are
triangle--top bikinis,
which always work well,
whether you have
the goods or not.
I said no thanks.
Now go away.
It's obvious which
one you'll need.
You have my sympathy.
I look forward to sitting
you down and having a nice,
long chat one
of these days, Kongo.
Wow, look what
Misaka found.
It's so cute!
Oh, yeah. Frills and polka--dots
work so well together.
No, you've got it wrong...
I don't want to wear
this one or anything...
I'd love to see you in
that one...! It's perfect.
I know it'll look
adorable on you!
I agree...! What's the
harm in trying it on?
I don't know...
I don't think it's
the right fit.
Don't be like that.
Give it a chance!
It'll look great.
No doubt in my mind!
You really think so...?
Well, if you guys insist,
I'll give it a shot.
Oh, nice... I take it you
prefer designs that look more
child--like, Misaka?
No...! Of course I don't.
I was just browsing...
Here... this is what I want...
I'll just take it over
here and try it on.
Um... what's wrong...? Was
it something that I said?
Why do I have to be
so embarrassed
about the stuff I like?
I... I feel practically
naked wearing this thing.
We're all girls
here, Uiharu.
There's nothing
to be shy about.
Plus that looks
great on you!
It does? Really?
A bikini divides the eyeline
between top and bottom...
but a one--piece shows off
a woman's entire figure...
so they only flatter
truly slender people.
Oh... Is that swim
club knowledge?
Do you have any
other pointers
for picking out
a suit to wear?
Well, let me think...
sarongs are an option...
they are, of course,
fashionable...
and they're also useful
for covering the lower body.
It's not like I was
trying to hide anything.
I just thought
it was cute!
Sorry for taking so long.
I am a little disappointed
that all the designs
they had were so
tame like this.
But given that these are
off--the--rack swimsuits,
what more can
a girl expect?
I don't know what to say.
We probably shouldn't
be surprised.
Uh... individuality's
important in a model.
It sure is.
Modest as it is, I'm
sure this must be
driving you crazy, Sissy.
I know it'll be difficult,
but please, try to resist!
I don't think I'm gonna
have a hard time with that.
Oh, look at you girls...
Is that all you're
working with?
Well, what do you think...?
Impressive, huh...?
I'm working the
"sexy and exotic" angle.
I expect rave reviews.
It's the ultimate swimsuit
experience for the audience.
That's a snake!
-I think it's cute!
-Her name is Ecaterina.
Oh, look at that.
What a pretty python.
You do realize it's a snake
not a dog... Don't you?
Would you hurry up and
put that away already? !
Oh, why?
Don't you want to play
with this little cutie?
Pretty snake! Pretty, pretty,
pretty, pretty snake!
What do you think, Shirai.
Surely you're not scared.
What...? Me...?
I think it's just a
tasteless stage prop.
It's a little bit tight...
but it's all they had...
They don't carry
larger sizes.
Oh, wow!
It's nothing but
an empty room.
This is where we're
going to be shooting?
It's so bare.
This high--tech studio
digitally creates
any number of
different settings.
Wow, that's amazing...!
I can even touch it.
It's the latest in
Academy City technology.
Oh... I was just wondering-is
the person shooting us
going to be a man?
Yeah... now that you mention
it, that's a good question.
Even if he was a
professional,
it would still be kinda...
you know? I can't
stand amateurs...
Don't you people get it? The
whole point of modeling
is to be seen at
your sexiest.
All the photography
is automated.
The camera will never be
inside your field of view,
so you don't have
to worry about it.
Just act naturally, okay?
[Music]
She said to act naturally
and nothing about that
looks natural to me.
Come on, Sissy. We need
to play our parts, too.
What parts do you mean?
Oh, you know...
You're the sexy beach babe
I apply suntan lotion to.
Not this again...!
I said no...!Ahh!
Aww! Just a little, please?
You'll like it!
Go away!
-Rub--a--dub--dub!
-No, no, no!
I get it now. That's
totally natural for them.
Yeah, that's
Misaka for you...
She always sets
a great example.
What do you guys think?
Should we follow her cue?
Yeah!
W--where are we now?
Wherever it is, it's
incredibly cold.
When the scenery
changes in the room,
the temperature changes, too?
That is high--tech.
I think this may be
taking it a little far.
We're supposed to be
relaxed and natural
in the middle
of a blizzard?
That's what makes
a real model...
Whatever happens,
you get the job done.
Serves you right for
being such a show--off.
Ow! Hot!!
From too cold to too warm.
Way, way too warm.
Why'd they program
in such extremes?
Water! Water!
Not this much water!
Like I said, what's with
all the extreme weather?
If they want to
put us on a boat,
can't they at least
make it comfortable?
Not bad...! A
prize barracuda!
Sorry... I think that's
just a really big tuna.
Is not!
Maybe you should let
her have her fantasy...
I'm sure she
doesn't want credit
for something
she didn't do.
Oh, I guess we're
off the boat.
Wow... the stars
are beautiful...!
And over there!
Looks a lot
like the Earth!
Huh?
Great, we're on
the moon, now? !
Well, at least
it's pretty.
Yeah. Very pretty.
Hey, you guys, look...!
What's that over there?
I'm sorry. Please hold
on a moment...
We need to make some adjustments
and change the scene.
Great. What are we
in for this time?
A campsite?
I'm sorry.
We're experiencing some
technical difficulties
with the cameras...
We should have it
taken care of soon...
In the meantime, why don't
you take a short break?
So, what do we do now?
Oh, by the way, the
food there is real...
Feel free to cook something
up if you want to.
Cook something up using
this stuff...?
What should we make?
With the number of people
and the ingredients we have...
We need to make
some curry!
Some of us can
work on the curry,
and the rest can do rice.
I'll be on team curry!
Yeah, me too, please.
All right. Why don't
I take the rice.
If you're making rice,
Sissy, that's what I'm doing!
Ugh... please...
curry is such a boorish,
unsophisticated food.
What are you talking
about? It's delicious.
You really don't
like curry?
I'm betting you just have
no idea how to make it.
Please! Don't be
ridiculous...!
I have a recipe for
the best curry.
It's been passed down
through the Kongo family
for generations!
Oh...? What kind
of curry is it?
An authentic
family recipe?
I'd love to try it!
Yes, please
make it for us!
Well, since I'm
stuck here anyway,
I suppose I can make do
with whatever plebian
curry dish you all prefer.
We can make a normal
curry and your dish...
We've got lots
to work with.
That's a great idea!
Okay let's do it...
yeah? ! Well...
if you insist,
I guess we can.
Hooray!
All right... everything's
settled then...
We'll go and get
the rice started.
Right!
Be ready for
something amazing!
Um, excuse me, Kongo...
Oh...! Yes?
Would you mind
if we joined you?
We'd love to see
how it's done.
Uh... certainly,
if that's
what you want.
Shall we get started
cooking ladies?
First... why don't we...
uh... peel these onions?
Sure!
Stupid thing.
It's broken?
This isn't
working, either.
I know!
This is what I call
induction cooking!
Don't talk to me.
I have to concentrate,
or it's gonna boil over.
Could you do
this one, too?
What...? Don't tell
me there's more!
You get a lot less onion
after all that peeling, huh?
So, what are we supposed
to do with this?
Oh... well, we, uh...
That's what those things
on the side of the plate are!
Out of the whole
entire onion
they only use this
one tiny part? ...
It must be a precious
ingredient for all that work.
Well... feel like you're
learning some things?
Yes!
Thanks...
I mean that.
This is a great
experience...
It's so nice of
you to teach us.
It's embarrassing
to admit...
but neither one of us has
ever made a curry dish before.
It's an honor to learn
from someone so talented.
Now the carrots...
Do we cut them into
quarter--rounds?
Huh...? I think for curry,
they're supposed to
be in chunks.
But quarter--rounds will look
more appealing on the plate,
and besides, they'll cook
faster at that size.
Oh, Uiharu, don't you
know anything...?
The key to a good curry
is that the vegetables are
neither too big nor too small.
When we make curry at
home, we chop the veggies
up smaller so they
blend in with the sauce.
No, no, no!
You've got it
all wrong...!
You want the vegetables
to be large enough
to add some substance.
Making it taste good
is the bigger concern.
It tastes just
fine my way!
Let's settle this.
The vegetables should be cut
in bigger chunks, right?
No, chopping them
up is better, right?
Okay, now I 'm confused.
They're grating the corn?
Tomato skins, interesting.
They're pretty hard
to peel, aren't they?
And now we're
adding seaweed?
Also unexpected...
and difficult
to cut up, too.
We leave the peel
on the tangerine...
And slice it
into rounds...
Ah...! I got
juice in my eye!
Ow. That doesn't
sound like fun.
I wonder what the finished
product will be like.
I'm just excited about
trying the first curry
I've ever made!
The ingredient choices
are all so unique!
I never would've thought
of adding burdock root.
Or strawberries...!
Ah... all this cooking
is making me hungry...!
I can hardly wait!
What's wrong?
What is it?
Um...
The truth is...
well...
You see, I...
I've never actually made this
curry recipe before, okay?
In fact, it's
not just this...
I've never done
any cooking.
I'm sorry...
It would have been too
embarrassing to back down
after what I'd said.
Well, in that case...
we can ask the others to
tell us how to make it.
Yeah?
I'm sure they
wouldn't mind.
Do it, Sissy...
do it, Sissy.
You can do it,
yes you can...!
Do it, Sissy...
do it, Sissy.
You can do it. Yes, you can!
Yeah! Time to eat!
Here we have
chicken curry!
Which is accompanied by
a lovely seafood curry.
Looks great!
Okay, everybody
ready to eat?
Absolutely!
Mmm... It's delicious!
You know, you really
can still taste
the little vegetables.
It's nice to have big
ones in there, too!
I'd say we did a pretty
good job, wouldn't you?
Yep. I couldn't agree more.
This is great, isn't it?
It was worth every
bit of effort.
Y--Yes.
See?
It tastes better because
we all worked together
to make it.
You know, you seem
like a nice person...
What's your name again?
Oh, um... I'm Mikoto Misaka.
Misaka? . . . That
sounds familiar...
Well, in any case...
I've decided to give
you the opportunity
to become my friend...
How does that sound?
Uh, that sounds great...
Thanks a lot.
Sorry for the delay.
The system is
up and running,
so we'll resume
shooting now.
Huh...? Already?
Oh, you can
continue eating...
I think we can get some
great shots of that.
Mmm... that was fantastic!
I'll model anytime if
we get to eat like that.
It really was
a lot of fun.
I'm so glad you all
had a good time today.
I suppose eating
peasant food
isn't so bad every
once in a while.
You did have seconds.
Hey... where's Misaka?
Where'd she run off to?
Let's see here...
No, that's not it...
Maybe this one?
This bathing
suit is adorable!
Now then...
Woo.hoo!
-This is so much fun!
-That looks like Zapper...
but what is she doing? Weird.
I'm ready for
my close--up!
[Music]
Who's there...? You
would dare to assault
Mitsuko Kongo of
Tokiwadai Middle School?
Um, I hate to
break it to you, Kongo,
but you're not actually
in the next one.