[Music]
You know what
we should do?
We should go see
a movie today...
What do you think?
A movie? Yeah, maybe.
Here, this looks like
a good one, doesn't it?
It's called "Caught
Between Love and Youth."
yeah, sounds okay...
I guess I like a romance flick
as much as the next girl.
Oh, really?
You don't sound all
that interested.
I don't care one
way or the other.
We both have the day off.
I thought we could do
something together.
Hey...! It looks like
they're having some kind
of summer festival on the
rooftop over at Seventh Mist.
Oh...? My guess is it's
just some silly event
designed to
amuse children.
We won't know for sure
unless we see it, will we?
Uh... well, I mean...
it might be nice
to try something new
every once in a while.
Oh, I see what it is...
This is what you're
really interested
in checking out,
isn't it, Sissy?
It's not...!
I couldn't care less
about some stupid thing-
No need to be ashamed, Sissy...
You can tell me
if you like Gekota.
It's all right.
-I told you, I don't care-!
-Sorry I'm late!
I hope you haven't been
waiting for too long...
I missed the first bus.
No, no, don't
worry about it!
We only just got
here ourselves.
Hey, Saten's not
with you today?
Oh... well, you see...
Man! Extra classes
on a day off...?
That's a dirty trick
for them to play.
Yeah... and it's not
just our middle school
that's doing it, either.
They're calling
students together
from all over to participate
in some special
workshop for the day.
-A workshop?
-That's right...
I don't know what makes
it special, though.
Well, special or not, it's
bad luck for poor Saten.
Such a beautiful day
to be stuck in class.
[Music]
This is it... at
least I think so.
Let's see here...
Hey...! Ruiko!
Akemi! Mu! Mako!
Hey, guys.
What's with making us
climb all these stairs?
I'm exhausted.
Don't be such babies.
We just got here.
Yeah, well...
It was a whole
lot of steps!
This way, then.
Honestly...! This
is the worst...
Going to some school on our
day off to take extra classes,
and for what?
It's not like they're
gonna teach us
how to raise our
ability levels.
That would be too
easy, wouldn't it?
Normally, I'd be sitting
by the pool right now.
And what about you...? You
were planning to hang out
with Uiharu today,
weren't you?
Well... What
choice do we have?
What're we gonna
do with you,
not even putting up a fight?
Oh, come on...
You won't even
complain a little?
You're hopeless.
Hey... we've got a long
day ahead. Be nice!
Well, the quicker
we get started,
the quicker it'll end.
Let's hope so.
They really did
pick people
from all different schools
for this, didn't they?
It sure looks like it.
That may be the case.
But this is still
a lousy turnout.
It's so much easier to
doze off in class
when there are more
people there.
What's with
the long faces?
You all look like your
puppies just died.
Why did we come to this
thing, anyway, Boss...?
It's so lame.
Well, we're here, so
you might as well
quit your griping you got it?
Yes, I'm sorry.
-I didn't hear you!
-Scary...
They look like they're
in high school.
Quit staring!
They'll notice us.
No, no problems here.
Please, just take it easy.
Yes... got it.
Okay, kids,
that's enough...
Let's all get inside now.
Yeah? Who're you
supposed to be?
I'm your teacher
for today.
Our teacher? !
I'm Komoe Tsukuyomi and I teach
the morning class here...
If you want to
smart off to me,
I will happily extend
the lessons even longer.
One thing is paramount
if you wish to further
develop your abilities.
And that's the achievement
of Personal Reality.
Today, we're going to go
back to the basics
and really explore exactly
what that phrase means.
Personal Reality involves
the development
of a reality unto oneself,
separate from that
which may be accepted
as true reality...
As we study this concept,
we must also look at the
quantum theory and the
uncertainty principle
postulated by Heisenberg.
We must study
theoretical physics
because Personal Reality
and quantum theory
have something in common:
both are rooted
in probability.
Okay, unless anybody
has questions,
that should conclude the
morning lecture...
I'm sure you'd all like
a nice, long lunch break,
but please don't be late
to the afternoon class.
It's for your own
good, I promise.
Ugh.
I thought lunch
would never come...
Hey... massage my
back, would you?
Do I have a choice
in the matter?
That feels so good!
You're becoming
an old lady.
Oh, shut up.
We've been here
for so long.
I can't believe the
day's only halfway over.
This is seriously
draining.
Yeah, it is...
oh, now that you
mention it...
don't we have to go to
physical training
this afternoon?
We sure do.
Oh... and what's even worse you
guys know the teacher
they put in
charge of it...?
From what I hear, she normally
does this with Antiskill.
-Eh? !
-That is bad...
I bet she's gonna make us run
some really harsh drills.
I wanna go home!
Well... sitting around here's
not gonna help anything...
We might as well eat
while we still can.
What is it?
I forgot to bring
lunch with me.
Everyone else
has the day off.
Hey, it's me...
No, they're not open...
I'm gonna go out
and grab something. ...
Don't worry about it.
Hey, Saten.
So... long time no see...
Jufuku, remember?
Oh... uh... hi Jufuku...
Are you taking the
workshop this afternoon, too?
Yeah, I am.
Sorry, I didn't
notice you.
I didn't really want
to be noticed...
Have you forgotten my
Dummy Check ability...?
It comes in handy when
you don't want people
to realize you're there.
You made yourself
disappear?
No... My level isn't high
enough to manage that...
but I do have a knack for
making things seem less present.
Oh... I get it.
Uh... Saten?
Huh? ... Yes...?
What is it?
I wanted to say thanks
for always answering
the letters I wrote you...
I really appreciated it.
Oh... sure...
no problem...
I did promise I would.
But, uh...
Well... it would mean a lot to
me if you would write the
next letter first...
maybe?
Uh... Well...
if I get a chance...
It might sound silly, but
I sleep with the postcards
you send me tucked under
my pillow every night...
I like feeling
close to you,
even if it's only
in my dreams.
That's... very sweet.
You know... I'm so glad
I came today...
I was really dreading
coming to this stupid
"special" workshop...
But it turns out I
was wrong, though.
Since I got to see you.
Hey... you... you know...
um... if you feel like it,
maybe we can eat
lunch together.
Oh... I can't...
I forgot to bring one, and
the cafeteria's closed...
So I'm gonna have to go
out and pick something up.
That's okay...
I mean, I actually packed
way more than I can eat today.
You're welcome to have
some if you'd like.
Oh... thanks, but-
Wow! You're sure
you don't mind?
Not at all.
Please help yourself
to whatever looks good.
Okay, thanks a lot.
You made this? It's delicious!
You think so...?
I'm glad to hear it.
You know...
It felt really awkward
sitting in that classroom...
almost like I should be
ashamed or something.
Why do you say that...?
We're all in the same boat.
Well... That's kinda the
point, isn't it?
They've gathered together
a certain type of people.
I wonder if there will
be more workshops...
for people like us.
Maybe...
but even if there
are more of them...
There's nothing
we can do about it.
There's nothing we can do.
It's hot out here.
I can't believe they're
making us work out in this.
Isn't this some
kinda abuse?
Can you do anything
but complain...?
You think whining's gonna make
it any cooler...? Huh?
Sorry Boss!
Seriously scary.
What did I tell you earlier?
Don't stare at them!
Okay, look
sharp, people...
In case you
haven't guessed,
I'm your physical
training teacher,
Miss Yomikawa...
Nice to meet you all.
Nice to meet you
too, Miss Yomikawa.
All right, that's
enough of that.
Why don't we get started
with an endurance run?
-Ugh! -That sounds awful!
-Are you serious? !
-It's too hot! No way!
Not up for testing
your limits?
Slow down, Ruiko.
You should be conserving
your strength.
I don't get why we're even
doing this in the first place.
It's not fair.
What's the point in making
us run until we drop...?
Torture?
Hey, you three!
Stop dragging your feet...
I know you can go faster.
When you don't think
you can run any farther,
then raise your hand.
She's enjoying this.
Keep moving!
Yomikawa runs her classes
like a drill sergeant...
Hang in there, kids.
You can do it.
Get through this...
and you may overcome
something greater.
Run!
Get up...! On your feet!
I can't do it.
I can't...
You giving up?
Yes, ma'am. I give up.
All right, make this
last lap a sprint.
Huh? !
I said, sprint!
Just hang in there.
You're almost done now.
Okay, very good...
How about going
for one more lap?
I can't run anymore.
Get up.
Get up and give
me one more lap.
You call this training? !
I certainly do.
How can you...? All you're
doing is putting her
through the ringer!
Why not go ahead and
call this what it is...
It's punishment...!
Admit it, lady!
The whole point of this
so--called workshop
is to punish us!
It's nothing of the sort.
Then why do you
have us running
until we're too
exhausted to move?
The point is to teach you
how to overcome your limits...
Look at him.
He was the first one
to raise his hand...
yet he's still running.
When you convince yourself
you can't do any more
you're finished...
Even though you may still
have some strength left
that you're
just unaware of.
Her, for instance.
So sure she couldn't
go one more step.
Until she ran
another lap...
Where do you think
the strength to run the
additional lap came from?
The same applies to
developing your abilities.
What I wanted to teach you
today is not to decide
so quickly what
your limits are.
Oh, please!
Don't give me that crap!
She's down!
Are you okay, Boss?
You think we
won't go after you
because you're a teacher? !
That will be all.
Class dismissed.
You're running away?
Time's up for today.
Everybody hurry
back inside!
Hey, Ruiko!
Come on! Hurry!
Quick, before
you get soaked.
It should clear up by
the time we're done here.
Aww, man...
after the last class,
they're gonna make us
take an ability test...
We know how that
one's gonna turn out.
"When you think you
can't do any more,
-you're finished!"
-Dead on...
Always nice to hear
another empty pep talk.
You know...
maybe that punk
girl was right earlier
and this workshop doesn't
have anything to do
with education.
Like I said: punishment.
First we all
slip into comas,
and then they force us to
take these stupid classes...
I wonder what'll
be next...
They could at least have
been straight with us.
Why didn't they
come out and say
we're being punished instead of
pretending it's a workshop...?
I mean, come on...
was what we did
even that wrong?
Who wouldn't want to
level up so easily?
In this world, you gotta
take every advantage you get.
Yeah, you've got
a point there.
It's not right to cheat.
Um... Ruiko...?
We all cheated,
so it's only natural
that we're being
punished for it.
My, aren't you a
good little girl?
You idiot!
Why did you challenge
her like that?
Aren't you scared of her?
Yes... Terrified, actually...
Her eyes are like daggers.
Even so... you didn't
back down one bit...!
I swear I could see sparks
when their eyes met.
Me, too!
Then there was
that popping sound!
I think that was
just thunder, guys.
I know what I heard.
Sparks or not...
what Ruiko said was right.
It was wrong
of us to cheat.
It was.
It appears that some of
you may have jumped
to the wrong conclusion.
So before we continue, I
want to clarify something.
Please understand
this workshop
was not intended as a
punishment for students
who used the Level Upper.
Certainly, your actions
were far from laudable.
It would've been better
had you resisted
the temptation
to use that device
to augment your abilities.
However... we do
not want you to feel
a disproportionate
sense of shame
or remorse for
having done so...
As far as punishment goes,
I'd say slipping into a
coma should suffice...
That's a far more harrowing
experience than a workshop.
You've already paid for
your transgressions
the hard way...
So, instead of feeling
guilty or bitter,
why not make the most
of all you've gone through?
The Level Upper gave
you a taste of power
that you've never had before.
However, that power didn't
come from some device.
It was already inside
you, waiting to come out.
As I'm sure my friend Miss
Yomikawa would tell you...
"You convinced yourselves
you'd reached your limits,
but... you overcame them."
Okay then.
With that said, we'll
begin the last class
of the workshop...
I want you to think about
using the Level Upper...
Close your eyes if it
will help you focus.
Concentrate on the time
you used your power.
As clearly as you can,
remember every aspect
of how it felt.
Now, I want each of you
to try to achieve
your own Personal Reality...
or at least
reinforce the footholds
that you already
have in place.
A new reality...
my own reality...
Concentrate.
So, anyway...
he told me to study up
on "Personal Reality,"
but I just don't get the
concept, you know?
Maybe it has something
to do with the power
of our own belief...
The way we shape
the assumptions
we make about the world.
I'm sorry...
I came so close...
So close to
losing something
far more important to me
than some stupid ability.
I couldn't take it...
I was so tired of
not having any power.
And finally, it
didn't matter anymore
what lengths I had
to go to to get it.
I understand.
But this doesn't
have to be it.
You'll be fine,
Saten... I know you.
You're too stubborn
to give up easily.
Don't stay here and let
yourself be defeated.
You are not defective.
There's nothing
wrong with you.
So... don't give up!
Okay, everyone!
We're going to
finish up the day
with a quick
ability test...
Go ahead and pack up your
stuff and follow us, please.
So, how did you
guys do on the test?
My numbers were
actually up a little.
No way! Mine, too!
But our levels are
still the same as ever.
I know...! Let's go do
something to celebrate
the workshop being over.
Good idea.
Hey... you coming
along Ruiko?
Oh... I don't know.
Let me think.
No... sorry...
Go ahead without me.
I've got something I
need to take care of.
Like I thought.
It's from Jufuku.
I'm so glad we got to
spend time together
again today, Saten...
It was really inspiring.
Seeing you go lap after
lap in the endurance run...
And the way you stood your
ground with that scary
high--school girl when
everybody else was afraid to...
Watching you be brave
gave me more courage.
I'm gonna try to learn
from your example...
I'll stop moping about
things I can't change
and be strong like
you, instead.
I don't think I'm
all that strong.
Of course I wasn't
going to do that well...
For now... ...
-I'll just keep trying. ...
-I'll just keep trying.
Oh... hey...
how's it going?
Pretty good.
All right! Done for the day.
It's time to go home.
All finished, Saten?
We wanted to come
by and pick you up.
How did it go?
What was the hold up...?
You took so long
coming out of there,
we thought you'd
already left
and headed for home.
You should have
seen it, Saten.
Without you, we weren't
able to decide
on a single thing to do.
Yeah? Then what've you
been up to all this time?
So, Saten...
how does going to
the movies sound?
Huh? Forget that.
They're having
some kind of event
on the roof at
Seventh Mist...
-Doesn't that sound fun?
-Well, I...
Do you really want to
see Gekota that badly?
I told you, that isn't it!
So, you see, we've been
split between two ideas.
We spent the whole day at
the restaurant talking it over.
And... you want me to pick?
It's the movie, right?
Hey, Kuroko! No fair!
Okay...! I say we
go to the pool!
Eh? !
But that wasn't
one of the options.
All right then. Why
don't you decide Uiharu?
-Huh?
-Seventh Mist, right?
No, the pool!
[Music]
What...? Armed gunmen are
hunting down espers?
This is the work of the
gang known as Skill Out.
What should we do,
Konori...? Konori...
did you hear me?