A Level Six esper?
Yes.
That's what you
will become, dear.
You will be the
very embodiment
of Academy City's
greatest dream.
Oh, Grandfather...!
How amazing!
Will that really happen?
Yes.
Today... we lay the
groundwork... dear.
Yellow Marble leader
reporting in, ma'am.
We have arrived.
Now commencing
installation.
Brown Marble leader,
how are you coming along.?
Is the blue car
following you?
Right on schedule.
Then it's time to put an
end to these foolish dreams.
I'm tired of waiting.
Let's move right
to the finale.
Just you wait.
When I get my
hands on you....
What was that?
Come on...
Is this really
your idea of fun?
Just a fancy little
trick I wanted to try.
What are you doing?
Why the hell did you
choose now to interfere?
Well, say something!
Dr. Kiyama...!
Those trucks are only decoys!
The children
aren't inside them!
They're not there...?
But...
-Come on, Saten, hurry.
-Calm down, I'm going.
Hey, wait...! What do you
two girls think you're doing?
Watch it. You're squishing me!
Just sit still!
I'm going to be
your navigator.
Now, get in...!
You want to save
the children, right?
Okay, get ready, Sissy!
If you guys wanna fight,
I'm happy to play along.
Helicopter, huh?
I think you're
about done here.
Ugh. I recognize that
ability all too well.
I think you can
relax, ladies.
The cavalry is here.
Try not to be too
intimidated by my ability.
"Aero Hand" will make
swift work of our opponents.
That was good timing!
Go on. We can take
care of things from here.
You go catch up with
Kiyama and the others, Sissy.
Kuroko.
All right, then.
But you had
better catch up.
Or you'll answer to me!
Who would dare
to assault me?
I am Kuroko Shirai
of Tokwadai,
partner of the
great Railgun!
Hold on! That phrase sounds
suspiciously familiar...
Konori! On it!
We're ready now.
Let's do this!
[Music]
I have to say...
This is rather
unexpected...
I never thought we would
team up for a fight.
We can use this opportunity
to settle something:
Whose ability is
the greater one.
Shortly after the
other squad moved out,
Antiskill surveillance picked
up something interesting.
They recorded two
transport vehicles
posing as civilian trucks
departing MAR headquarters.
-Most likely...
-Those are the real transports.
I can't believe I fell
hook, line, and sinker
for that madwoman's
amateur trick.
We need to hurry...!
It looks like the transport
has already reached
its destination.
Where is it?
An unused propulsion
system laboratory
in School District
Twenty--Three...
Take this exit
on the left.
Oh... Good work, Doctor...
Of course, I wouldn't
expect anything less
from an opponent like you.
Hold on tight!
That's what will make killing
you such an amusing task!
Hold on, Konori.
I've got this!
Hey... what made
that thunk just now?
Come on, come on!
I want to see you run like
your life depends on it.
Which, of course, it does.
Better keep moving!
I know that voice.
So do I.
That evil witch.
Hey... That's Misaka.
Uh... what are you
doing out there?
Quick, you need
to go faster!
Yes, I kind of
noticed that.
I'm sorry.
About before...
I was wrong, I know that.
I suppose I can't
really blame you.
In your position, I would
have done the same thing.
I'll make up
for my failure.
I'll beat her...
I will!
My attacks were deflected!
Did you really think your little
shocks would work against me?
All right, then.
Take this!
I know about
that trick, too.
Impossible!
I've done my homework,
you see.
I'm up to date on everything
they have in the databank
concerning that
ability of yours.
Including the especially
interesting fact
that your railgun's range
is only fifty meters.
I'm getting sick
of this woman.
Take the next
turnoff on the left.
What's that?
Tch... I missed...
Oh, well.
The targets are headed
your way now, Green Marble.
Crush them.
We're under attack!
Take care of it!
There's no way you're
getting past us,
so you shouldn't
bother trying!
Yes, that's right.
We've managed to gain
control of all ramps
from this point forward.
Sorry, but we're being
harried from above, too.
This is the most we can
do for you right now.
Why is Antiskill
helping me?
Never mind that.
Just hurry up and get
to those children!
Why am I surrounded
by incompetents?
Very well. I'll take
care of it myself.
Huh...? Again?
Hold on tight up there!
It's a lost cause.
Give up, already!
You don't stand a chance!
It doesn't matter how hard
you try or how fast you run.
You might as well
pack up and go home.
You're never gonna be
able to save those brats.
I'll make sure of it!
I won't stop.
I swore that I
would revive them!
I have to try!
A teacher doesn't give
up on her students
just because
things get tough!
I would never
expect you to.
No matter what happens,
I'll make certain
you get to them.
That's why I'm here.
And I promise you, I'm
not gonna give up, either!
Little fools.
You don't have any
cards left to play now.
Just roll over and die!
Misaka! Misaka!
Ha! Another pathetic
attempt...!
I know all of your
attacks, remember?
Nothing you can do
will surprise me!
Oh, really?
I wouldn't be so
sure about that.
Kuroko!
On my way!
Yes, I can fire coins.
But that isn't all.
I'll show you the full
extent of my power!
What the...?!
How rude.
Teleporting away without
warning like that.
Shirai, Misaka!
You guys terrified us...!
Are you okay?
Yeah, we're fine.
Don't worry.
You saved us.
-I want to...
-Hold on.
Don't say it...
Let's wait until after
we've saved the children.
Right.
Well?
Can you figure it out?
Almost there.
The security on this
is pretty tight.
How annoying.
This would be a lot easier
if you hadn't taken out
every single one of them.
Oh, yeah...? How was
I supposed to know?
I figured they would have
left at least one person
inside to guard it.
Got it!
In this facility,
there's only one area
where power consumption
is especially high.
The lowermost block.
I found you!
Haru'ue...!
Can you hear me?
Wake up!
We came for you...!
All right...
where's the control
panel for this?
Hold on...
I'll go look over there.
Great, thank you!
Not long now.
We'll get you
out of there.
What is it...?
What's the matter?
No, that sound again!
It can't be.
But it is.
You pesky, meddling brats.
Oh, no.
It's her!
This is to pay you
back for earlier!
Shirai, Misaka!
You okay?
How dare you?!
What was that?
Ah... that felt good.
You think you can get away
with making me look like a fool?
Her again!
You're using
Capacity Down!
Misaka described
it to us before...
The sound it emits
only affects espers!
This is Capacity Down?
What's your point?
Knowing what it does isn't
going to protect you from it.
She told us that you'd
upgraded it, though.
That the speakers were a lot
bigger than they were before.
Too big to be
moved easily.
That's right.
It wasn't easy to do,
but I've placed them
throughout the facility.
Would you care to go around
destroying them one by one?
It still has to have
a control center.
And its size limits
where that could be.
I know a little about this
building's structure.
From what I can tell...
the power center must be
back where we just were.
The central control room!
Uiharu...
You might be right.
But what does
that matter...?
There's nothing you
can do about it now.
Ugh. Do all little girls
talk as much as you?
You should thank me.
I'm about to show you
something amazing.
The culmination of
years of research.
The completion of
the ability crystal.
How can you?
I don't understand.
You're a victim
in this, too.
Your own grandfather used
you for his experiments.
He made your ability
run out of control.
And yet here you are.
You're wrong.
I'm no victim.
I'm Academy City's
ultimate dream.
This seed of greatness
was born thanks to me.
And I intend
to let it bloom.
It can't be.
That vial.
It contains
the First Sample?
Using this, I am finally
going to create a Level Six.
-Hah!
-A Level Six.
-No way.
-Oh, yes.
This young girl
is about to become
the first esper in Academy City
to reach Level Six.
The power of the other
children will flow into her!
You can't do it!
Not Haru'ue!
Under specific wavelengths,
she has a reception
ability above her level.
It was truly a stroke
of luck to find someone
whose ability can resonate
with the crystal like hers can.
High--level Telepaths
are quite rare, after all.
Why them?
Why use these same
children again?
Why are they always the ones
who have to suffer the most?
It's not so bad.
They probably won't
even feel a thing.
I'm just going to
borrow the realities
they've created
inside their minds.
You're talking about
Personal Reality.
You can call it
whatever you want.
Shall I explain
the process to you?
Essentially, I'm extracting
the neurotransmitters
that control activity
within the brain.
Particularly those which
make them runaway espers
and fusing them
with the First Sample.
By doing so, I will
create an inhibitor
for the ability crystal.
And it will be
perfected at last.
The old geezer never
could figure it out.
He spent all his time
applying minor changes
that were
ultimately useless.
And now...
only one step left.
Don't do it!
Why not?
Do you realize
what will happen?
If you do this, and
the children awaken
while still in their
runaway state.
Then Academy City
will be hit
by an unprecedented
wave of poltergeisting,
and it will be destroyed.
So what?
That's fine by me.
"Someone who attains
the power of God
while still inhabiting
a mortal body."
Creating such a person is
the whole point of this city!
And once that's done,
there's no real reason
for Academy City
to remain standing anymore.
Careful.
You're going to
get yourself hurt.
Dr. Kiyam...
Just lay there and be quiet
like a good little girl.
Please, Saten!
Please hurry!
Come on!
Where is it?
I have to find that
Capacity Down thingy!
You said something
interesting before.
I can hear her.
That Skill Out members
weren't my lab rats.
Well, you were just one
word away from being correct.
They aren't my
only lab rats.
No, you are all my lab
rats, don't you see?
Would you prefer a different
analogy? Very well.
Academy City is
my breeding farm,
and all you children
are my livestock.
Misaka... hang on...
I think it's time to
put you down, though.
What the...?
What was that?
I don't give a damn if
you think we're lab rats.
Don't forget.
Rats have sharp teeth!
That sounds like.
Thank goodness! Saten!
There's another one
of you brats here...?
How is she still standing?
I'm not going
to tell you twice.
Keep your hands
off my friends!
-It went away!
-Damn it!
Fine, then.
Looks like it's time
to change tactics.
Fortunately, I have a plan B.
I'm going to blow you
and this whole place away!
I built this
particular weapon
after carefully
analyzing your ability.
It's even more powerful
than your railgun.
Honestly, first laboratory rats,
then livestock.
How bitter and pathetic
do you have to be
to think so lowly of
other human beings?
You may be a Level
Five Electromaster.
In this town, however,
you're nothing more
than a bunch of data.
That's right!
Just a bunch of data
with two legs
and a smart mouth!
That's where you've
got it all wrong.
The people of Academy City
are so much more than that.
Anything is possible
in this place.
Here we can
achieve greatness.
In a way that we
couldn't anywhere else.
So you see.
You think you're
human beings?
You're just samples.
That's what Academy
City was made for!
I'll stop you...
for the sake of my city!
That was nice work.
You saved all
our lives, Saten.
Is that it?
Yes.
The program is complete.
And now.
Go on, it's all right.
Banri spoke to me.
She wanted me
to tell you.
"I trust you, teacher."
Teacher...?
You look tired...
Why do you have those dark
circles under your eyes?
I... I've just been very busy.
There was so
much work to do.
Oh, yeah.
And you know what...?
Your hair's longer.
It's her, though.
That's our teacher.
It's Miss Kiyama.
She's here!
My children are all awake.
Hey, Erii.
I want to thank you...
for hearing my voice.
You're a true friend.
Yeah!
All right...
can I finish
saying it now?
Thank you so much.
[Music]
How can I describe it best?
A battle of singular heroism!
Of course, it didn't
take long for Shirai
to lose her nerve
and run away...
but I wasn't about
to let that stop me.
I stood firm, facing
the enemy head--on,
defeating them easily.
Wow! Then you were the
one who finally put an end
to all the dreadful
poltergeisting
that was happening?
Oh, was it really
you, Kongo?
We should have known!
When is it coming?
Any moment now.
Aw, man, I can't wait!
So, where are they?
Uiharu and the others.
She said they would be
along in just a minute
and we should go on ahead.
They're running later
than I thought, though.
I hope they make it.
This is a special day.
We have to hurry!
I don't want to miss it!
Misaka, Shirai, it's
unlike you to be late.
What's gotten into you?
Honestly! Of all days, Sissy,
this is the one you
choose to sleep in on?
Shut up...!
You were sleeping every
bit as soundly as I was!
I have to admit,
I'm kinda surprised.
I would never have
expected Misaka
to come up with
something like this.
What are you
talking about?
It's sweet and generous
and thoughtful,
just like Misaka is.
Yeah...
I don't think
I'd go that far.
Hello, Shirai?
Oh...? You haven't
gotten there yet?
No, I don't need anything
from you guys right now.
Just calling
to let you know
that you--know--who's
regained consciousness.
We've begun
interrogating her,
but I don't think she's
going to give much up easily.
Yeah, I agree.
All right.
Thanks for
letting me know.
What is it?
It's going to be
a long time before
we have a full account
of Therestina's crimes.
Hey! What are we
doing standing around?
We need to hurry!
Look...! Up there!
-Hey, it's here!
-Look, there it is!
Where?
-Look!
-That's so cool!
Okay. One, two, three...
Ready, go!
We just wanted to say...
Happy birthday
Miss Kiyama!
Rest up and get
well soon, okay?
-We'll do the same!
-I can't wait to see you again!
Me, neither!
Bye for now, Teacher...
Thank you so much!
We love you!
[Music]
There's never a dull
moment, is there?
Not in this city.