Oh, hi there, Tesso.
Still hard at
work, I see...
even during
summer vacation.
Yeah, I still had some loose
ends that needed tying up.
Quite the busy little
bee, aren't you?
Yeah...
Ah! It's that late already?!
You have to work at your
other job today, too?
And I need to hurry!
See you later!
Have a good day!
Well, be careful
out there.
Ow--ow--ow!
I really don't
have time for this!
No I'm serious.
Be very careful.
Oh! The train!
Wait for me!!
Why do these things
always happen to me?!
[Music]
Sorry, I know I'm late!
No kidding.... You're
good and late, aren't you?
R--really sorry.
Students get restless when
they're on summer vacation...
Judgment has a hard time
maintaining discipline
in the city on their own,
so we've been called in
to assist whenever we can.
You're late. Now get over it
and pull yourself together.
Right... I will.
I'm sorry.
Honestly.
Yes, Yomikawa...
A robbery?
Roger that......
Make up for your mistake
by doing well today.
Got it?
Yes!
Can you help me,
please, Yomikawa?!
All of you,
just stay back!
Come any closer
and I'll kill 'er!
Forget about me...
Take him down.
-What should we do?
-Keep quiet!
Let me have that.
Ma'am?
Don't think I won't do it!
Excellent!
I'm in the zone!
Well, that was a
pathetic display.
Huh?... She got the all--time
high score. That's impressive!
It wasn't too shabby,
I'll grant you that.
But... Wait 'til
you see me go!
Come on.
The hostages had
been rescued,
so you let your guard down...
Look where that got you.
I didn't think
he'd move so fast.
Excellent!
I did it!
You beat my high score?
That's incredible, Saten.
Good job!
Well look at that. It's
almost time for school curfew.
Yep, just about.
Go in there
and do your job.
Make up for your mistakes
by working hard, remember?
Oh... right.
This time I'm gonna
hit it like I mean it.
Oh, so now you're saying
you didn't give it
your all last time?
Please, don't get carried away
and start kicking and stuff.
Oh...! I didn't
know I could!
But you shouldn't.
That would be cheating.
Hey... that's it for today.
Time's up. It's going to be
school curfew any minute now...
You four should hurry
on back to your dorms.
Oh, hey...
I recognize her.
You're those girls...
We were in a tight spot,
and you helped us. Thank you.
I should be thanking you
for all the help you gave us.
You know, you look a lot
skinner than I remember.
If I had to guess,
I'd say it's due to exhaustion.
Oh? I don't think so...
No, she's right.
You're as pale as a ghost.
You should take better
care of your skin.
You guys over in Antiskill
must have it really rough, huh?
Yeah, that's the truth.
What do you say?
Want to give it a try?
It's an excellent
stress reliever.
I don't think so.
I'm still on duty.
Who knows, it might do
wonders for your skin, too.
Well... maybe I could
play just one game...
Games aren't in your
job description...
Now, get moving, girls.
Back to your dorm rooms.
It's the scary teacher
from the workshop.
Come on, move
it...! Curfew!
Everybody outta here!
You heard me.
Go on.
Huh?
That's Konoe.
Friend of yours?
No, not really.
He does go to our school,
but we don't know
him all that well.
He's kind of the
unapproachable type, you know?
Ow! That really hurts!
What's the matter
with you, Tesso?
Oh, the hot water stings the
spots where I got scraped up.
I'm not talking
about that...
I wanna know what was the
matter with you today...
First you were late, then
you got yourself taken hostage,
and then you were manipulated
by a group of young students.
Yeah...
I can't say you were always
the best Antiskill officer,
but today was a
particularly poor showing.
I know. Sorry.
Well... Whatever
else happened today,
a nice, hot bath is
always a great way
to finish a long day of work.
Yeah, it sure is.
Komoe thinks so, too.
Isn't that right?
Hey, Pops, an
order of gizzards!
Here ya go.
Hard--drinking
as ever, huh...?
Well, here's to you!
-Now, Tsuzuri Tesso!
-Uh... yes?
Listen to me!
Your problem is
that you're a wimpy
little insect...
You gotta hold
your head high.
Sometimes you gotta give
life a hard smack in the face.
A good, hard smack!
That's right. Sometimes a
girl's got no other choice.
Ah! That's enough!
Hey, Pops. How 'bout
some liver steaks?
Here ya go.
A hard smack... huh?
I will try harder.
Today's patrol is from
Area A through D...
Let's split up
and get to it.
Are you ready, Tesso?
Yes!
Let's see...
That way is north,
so that means...
Where did you get separated
from your mommy, little one?
Nothing is going
right today.
It's that boy.
Here I go.
You there.
Have you looked
at a clock lately?
It's almost curfew...
You need to pack it
up and head home.
Hey, are you
listening to me?
Gekisho 9!
I wouldn't think they'd
have an old classic game
like this in
Academy City.
It sure takes
me back, though!
I used to play
this a lot...
They never did come
out with ten, did they?
K.O.!!
Anyway, enough of that.
It's time for
you to get going.
Hey, you...!
Pig's trotters,
please, Pops!
Here ya go.
Let's add on some shrimp cakes
and bamboo shoot sashimi, too.
Here ya go.
-Hey, Tesso...
-Yeah?
You know, if something's
bothering you, I'm all ears...
It's okay,
you can tell me.
Oh, goodie! Are we
talking about boys?
Thank you, but nothing's
really bothering me.
Oh, really? Then why do you keep
screwing things up all the time?
I dunno. Sorry.
How does it go...?
Something along the lines of
"Gather ye rosebuds
while ye may."
She's right, Tesso.
Your life shouldn't
be all about work.
Maybe what you
need is a hobby...
Do something you enjoy
every once in a while,
and you won't be
so burned out.
Something I enjoy.
Like what?
Summer's the best time for a
young woman to find herself!
Cut loose!
Run wild!
Anything goes!
The sky's the limit!
Yeah...! Go nuts!
Go nuts, huh?
Yes, you're right. Thanks.
Good!
Pops, give us
something special.
Here ya go.
Um, Komoe...
there's something I've been
meaning to ask you for a while.
Okay, shoot.
Uh... what kind of
restaurant is this, exactly?
You're gonna be late again...?
What in the world
are you doing?
Well, you see...
I haven't gotten my term
evaluations filed yet.
What? Those are
supposed to be finished
before summer
vacation starts!
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Geez, what am I
gonna do with you...?
All right, you don't
have to come in.
Get your work done so this
doesn't happen anymore.
Yes ma'am!
One more thing... the next
time we go out drinking,
it's your treat.
Right!
All done!
It's a lot later
than I thought.
Something I enjoy...
well...
K.O.!!
You rely too much
on the big moves.
And you should
really balance
your offense and
defense better too...
If your attacks
aren't well--defined,
you're better
off not making them.
Aren't you...?
I used to be really
into this game...
You mind switching
out with me?
Watch this... All you do is
just press the start button...
Then hit these like so.
Come on...! Bring it!
A hidden character?
Cool, huh...?
Unfortunately this guy's
not all that good, though.
Why are you showing
me all this?
Because I enjoy it...
The game.
You like it, too...
Don't you wanna know
all the secret stuff...?
Besides, look at this guy.
He's kinda cute.
Nope, not even a little.
Are you sure about this...?
Being Antiskill, and all.
I've got the day off.
My schoolwork is
all done, too.
I thought it might be nice
to cut loose and relax
for once, you know?
Now then... Let's see
if I've gotten rusty
after all these years.
Komoe's calling.
Yes, hello...? What...?!
There's an emergency
involving Yomikawa?
Uh, yes... okay...
but...
Yomikawa needs my help...
I know... but still...
Jamie!
Sorry, would you take over?
Oh! And the Jamie ending
is totally awesome,
so make sure you
watch it, okay?
All right, I'm here!
Uh--oh... I think
I drank too much.
This is the emergency
that you needed me for?
Yes. Thanks for coming.
Isn't it a little
early for this?
Exactly how much did
she drink, Komoe?
Between the both of us,
we had about two gallons.
Hey Tesso...
are you enjoying yourself?
How in the world could
I be enjoying this?
Well... what about
the rest of your day?
Huh?
And yesterday...?
And the day before that?
Oh... aside from this,
it's been basically
enjoyable, I guess...
I mean, I've been busy
with work and all...
I make it a point to
enjoy myself every day.
With all the different
students in this city,
life's never dull.
Yeah.
Just recently,
for instance,...
this poor young girl blew
the roof off my place.
Huh?...
She destroyed your roof?
Yes, she did.
But it's all right.
Because I love every
one of my students...
no matter what mistakes
they might make...
and what about you, Tesso?
What is it that you love?
Right.
Today, we've got
areas I through L...
-Let's split up, and...
-That sounds perfect. I'm on it.
I'll start by
patrolling area L.
She's pretty
fired up today.
Come back here!
Stop there, you...!
What kind of automaton
monster are you?!
-Give it back!
-Hey there!
Um. What school do you go to?
I'm not a student here...
I'm a holy sister!
Okay, so...
What you're saying is
you dropped a donut,
and it was picked up by
the cleaning robot?
Exactly! And I'm well
within my rights.
Toma told me about
the regulation
you have known as the
"three second rule."
I know what you're
talking about,
but I don't think the rule
applies on the street.
Ah...!
Hey! Give me back my
donut this instant!
Oh. Uh, hey wait!
Oh... kay...
Huh?... I'm sorry, miss, but...
All of them.
All of them?
Okay, let me get
this straight...
That girl was
adamant about
buying all the hamburgers
the restaurant had?
Hey.
Can you tell me what
school you go to?
Kirigaoka Girls'...
But I'm on
break right now.
For lunch, right?
And why do you want
so many hamburgers,
if you don't
mind me asking?
They taste incredible...
I must have them all.
Okay...
sure...
Maybe this is too
much for me...
No! I can't give up now.
Forward, march!
What's the matter?
A special necklace
that I had... it's gone.
A lost necklace...?
Describe it.
It has a photo inside.
Oh, it's a locket, then.
What's a locket?
That's what you
call a necklace
you can put a
photo inside of.
What?! Kids don't
call it that anymore?
It's a necklace.
A necklace. Right...
So, uh... did you
lose it around here?
Maybe. Who knows?
Okay. We'll start here.
I'll help you
search for it.
Not there either.
Earthquake!
Hey, was that
an earthquake?
Huh?... Was it...?
I didn't notice.
Oh. Never mind then.
I found it.
You did...?
That's fantastic!
I'm glad it's not
gone for good.
Yeah... Oh, by the way,
can you tell me what
school you go t...
What good am I if I
can't even help some girl
find her locket...?
Is this really the
best that I can do?
She sure is late, huh?
What could she be up to?
Let's do this!
Huh...?
It's another Jamie.....
All right, you don't
stand a chance!
Ready... Go!
This guy's pretty good.
Lariat, huh?!
K.O.!!
Round 2.
Yeah, take that!
They didn't used to call me
Jamie's Empress for nothing!
K.O.!!
I did it...!
We're even!
Final round!
I'm gonna take this match.
Just watch!
Got 'im!
Time to say goodbye!
K.O.!!
You lose.
I guess I have gotten
rusty, after all.
Oh, well...
For a while there,
I was on fire.
Jamie's Empress, is it?
What? Oh, no! You heard that?
No kidding...?
You really did what I said
and played until you
saw Jamie's ending...?
No wonder you're so good.
Aw, man, I really wish
they would come out
with a Gekisho 10.
They never will not with
an old game like that.
Well, if they do, I have no
doubt I'll beat you on it.
What?
Nothing.
I'll look forward to it...
Your Imperial Majesty.
Didn't I tell you to
forget you heard that?
You can just
leave me here.
What are you
talking about...?
It's past curfew...
A middle--schooler
can't be out on his own.
It's okay.
My place is right over there.
Oh...
Bye.
Um...
Thanks a lot.
-Yes-?
-Where are you?!
You didn't even call!
If you're not coming, the least
you can do is let us know!
Yomikawa worries
about you, Tesso.
Well, I wouldn't say
"worry," exactly...
Anyway... remember
what I told you.
-It's your turn to buy...!
-All right, Pops...
Today I'll take the
entire pig's head!
You'd better hurry
up and get down here!
Yes, ma'am! Coming!
He transferred?
That's what we heard.
It does seem strange,
going in the middle
of summer vacation.
You're right...
It does.
The school he's
transferring to.
What was it called, again?
Zasso Academy Junior High.
I don't recognize
the name at all.
I think I'd remember it.
Zasso is a weird
name for a school.
Here's the thing...
Zasso is a game--making company.
They're the ones who
established the school
in the first place.
They make games?
Yeah, they're famous
for those Gekisho games
that were real popular
a while back.
Oh... I think I
have heard of those.
So then, is the whole
purpose of the school
to train future
game creators?
From what I've heard,
the real technical stuff
doesn't start until
the high--school level...
I wonder why he picked
Zasso, though...
I mean, they're
kinda washed up.
Are they really?
That surprises me...
They made some of
my favorite games.
Yes, but you're a
big dork, Uiharu.
What is it, Tesso...?
You're acting strangely.
Oh, nothing.
All right...
I expect all of you to get
back home before curfew!
Right!
Yes!
I'll do my best!
What's come
over you today?
Come on, let's go...!
Area E is next, right?
No, it's F.
Oh, is it...?
All right, then!
[Music]
When I was a little girl,
my mom always told me
"Drink before you speak."
Wait, that wasn't it...
"Think before you speak?"
"Drink before you leap?"
Whatever.