[LAST ORDER]
"Are you okay?"
asks Misaka Misaka,
concerned by all the blood.
[ACCELERATOR]
Thank Goodness.
[LAST ORDER]
Huh?
You'll be okay. Thank goodness.
Thank goodness, for real.
[ACCELERATOR] There's no
denying that this world
is cold and harsh.
Sometimes it seems to be filled
with malice beyond all hope.
However, if you
make the decision
to stretch out your hand
and struggle and struggle
and struggle some more,
you'll find there's light ahead.
This world is cruel, but it's
not so desperate a place
that one cannot reach out and
snatch a ray of that light.
[groans]
As much as Misaka hates to break
up your oh-so-touching reunion,
there are one or two other
things that could use
your attention right now.
Like the war, for example.
Doesn't exactly look like it's
headed for a happy ending.
[ACCELERATOR]
The light is converging around
that giant heap in the sky.
If it discharges
toward the ground,
the outcome won't
be good for anyone.
Yeah, well, screw that.
[gasps]
[ACCELERATOR]
Misaka Worst!
I'm gonna go put a stop to that.
Can you keep the kid safe?
[MISAKA WORST] Well, I guess
nothing's changed, has it?
"What are you talking about?"
says Misaka Misaka,
worriedly posing a question.
"You aren't going to run
off somewhere, right?"
asks Misaka Misaka,
hoping you say no.
[ACCELERATOR]
You don't have to worry.
I'll put an end to this.
[LAST ORDER]
"No.
I want us to be together
forever and ever,"
says Misaka Misaka, begging you.
I understand.
Truth is, I wanted us to
be together forever, too.
[gasps]
[ACCELERATOR]
I see.
So, this is what
it's like to fight
to protect something
precious to you.
Great, there's
another light now?
What in the world
could be going on?
Toma Kamijo.
Are you up there now?
[FIAMMA]
What is this?
The necessary output should've
been reached by now.
There should've been enough
destruction on the ground
to meet the
strategic conditions.
So how is it that my path to
victory is not yet assured?
[KAMIJO]
Let it go.
[gasps]
Come on. It's past time
to give up this fantasy!
You're done, Fiamma!
What?
[groans]
The animosity that's plagued
the earth is decreasing?
But why?
[INDEX] Warning. Chapter
eighty-eight, verse one.
Irregularity in main body
during search operation.
Gravely negative effect
on operational
efficiency developing
due to over-susceptibility
to external stimulus.
[gasps]
This is the English Puritan
sorcerers' doing!
Bad luck.
[laughs]
All I need to do is buy
five to ten seconds.
In that time, I'll forcibly
reset the grimoire library.
I don't care if the high load
burns out all 103,000 volumes.
I'll do what I must to flush
away the enemy before me!
[yells]
Here I am, trying to maximize
the miracles and blessings
of the Son of God, all to bring
this phenomenon about,
but this bastard
shows no regard.
[FIAMMA] It's not about
good luck versus bad.
That's just another blurry
distinction that this boy
has the power to
trample under his foot.
If you believe that
yours is the only way,
that you alone can save
the people of this world,
then I'll start by laying waste
to that pathetic delusion!
[LESSAR]
Excuse me!
I thought you might like to know
that Sasha and I have already
escaped in the container.
[LESSAR] You should hurry
and get out, as well.
There's not much time.
The Star of Bethlehem is
about to start falling.
This is it, then.
Hey, come on. We're going.
[FIAMMA]
The remaining escape containers
probably won't be of
any use at this point.
At best, it's a question of
finding an individual-sized pod
that will work.
Only one of us is going to make
it out of this place alive.
Looks like it.
Are you sure?
Like you said, I haven't
exactly invested a lot of time
looking at the world and getting
to know the people in it.
[KAMIJO]
That's true.
But, hey, now you'll have
the chance to do it.
[engine roaring]
Misaka!
[MIKOTO] Hey, can't you
set down anywhere?
[MISAKA 10777] "Shaking incident
to the fortress's fall
will be too intense, so we
cannot get any closer,"
explains Misaka, patiently.
"And if we were
able to set down,
our chance of escape would be
virtually zero," says Misaka.
Okay, fine. Just keep us
as level as you can then.
I'm going to drag
that idiot over myself.
Just go! Forget about me!
Oh, shut up. There's no
turning back at this point.
Not yet.
Huh?
"The shaking has exceeded
the designated value,"
says Misaka, warning you.
"If we get any closer,
we could collide."
[MIKOTO] Please have buttons,
or a belt, or whatever--
anything to let me reel
you in with magnetism!
Huh?
[INDEX]
Toma?
[gasps]
[KAMIJO]
Index.
Why didn't you escape
when you had the chance?
The same reason as
your magical item.
I needed to stay
because I have to take care
of the whole fortress, too.
[KAMIJO]
I'm sorry.
This whole time... I've
been hiding something.
And honestly, I wasn't sure
whether it was really
the right thing to do.
I feel terrible about it,
but I've been lying to you
for a long time now.
There's no guarantee
that I'll ever come back
from the Star of Bethlehem.
So I'm going to tell you
now, while I still can.
See, the truth...
The truth is, I've lost--
[inaudible]
[INDEX]
That's okay.
Whatever happened,
it doesn't matter now.
Nothing does, as long
as you survive this
and come back your usual self.
I will come back.
And when I do, I promise...
...I'll get on my knees.
I'll apologize to you in person!
[KAMIJO]
Fifty point nine megahertz.
You should be able to connect
with the speakers here.
Contact the English
Puritans for me.
Tell them I need help.
See if they have advice
on how to bring
the Star of Bethlehem
down safely.
Not like this.
The item--I won't be able to
leave this place of my own will.
I guess not.
You head on back
ahead of me, okay?
[INDEX]
Toma.
[KAMIJO] So I need to destroy
the elevating magical items
that are keeping the Star aloft.
And that'll change the
location where it will fall?
[STIYL] The items are
in 20 different places.
If you destroy three of them,
numbers three,
nine, and thirteen,
then it should come down
somewhere in the Arctic Ocean.
[KAMIJO]
Got it.
You know, her
consciousness was there
on the Star of
Bethlehem earlier.
Couldn't you have resolved
this situation easily
by using her knowledge then?
You know what Fiamma
put her through.
You think I'd let her
suffer a minute longer?
[yells]
[SISTER 10A] Third magical
item confirmed destroyed.
[STIYL] Strange. There's
something huge out there.
Telesma? What's it doing there?
It looks like Misha Kruezhev
is advancing toward
the Arctic Ocean!
[gasps]
[SISTER 10B] Reading a line of
telesma between the two.
Reciprocal interference is
definitely being generated.
What now?
I mean, it can't be a new power.
So, is she trying to restore
herself physically?
[KAMIJO]
What do you mean?
[STIYL] Misha Kruezhev
presides over water.
If she uses the polar ice cap,
including special
symbols and emblems,
her power will
become even greater.
But there's a possibility that
if she tries to elicit
too much power,
the very body that Misha is
composed of will explode,
and a great deal of
telesma will be released.
[STIYL]
How do we stop her now?
We weren't even sure we
could stop the old Misha,
and that was with an
organized response.
[SISTER 10A]
The Star of Bethlehem.
It's deviated from
its earlier course!
[STIYL]
What?
Don't tell me. He's--
[KAMIJO] Sure, the world as
we know it may perish someday.
But... it doesn't have to be
a tragic ending like this.
I'll fight to keep
that from happening,
and no one can
tell me it's wrong!
Damn. I can't find anything.
I need something.
A bargaining chip to
negotiate with them.
Hamazura, we need
to get out of here.
They'll be coming for us.
[HAMAZURA]
I know. Just a few more minutes.
[MUGINO] Use my blood
as an insurance policy.
[BOTH gasp]
[MUGINO]
The fourth-ranked DNA map.
As long as all three
of us are carrying it,
we should be able to
keep them in check.
Mugino.
[HELMETED WOMAN]
Honestly.
You really are a great
deal of trouble.
Who are you?
[HELMETED WOMAN]
Your ally.
Perhaps you'll recognize
me from my work
up the chain of command?
What is it she always says?
[HELMETED WOMAN] "It's always
like this with you."
My top-priority objective
is Riko Takitsubo.
It's a relief to secure her.
[HAMAZURA]
Takitsubo is your priority?
[HELMETED WOMAN]
You mean you didn't notice?
I suppose you were
a bit distracted.
When you fought those
masked assailants,
Riko Takitsubo affected Shizuri
Mugino's personal Reality.
Are you saying--?
[HELMETED WOMAN]
She is already indicated as such
on the Parameter List,
but she has the potential
to become something
extraordinary
known as the "eighth."
If her evolution continues,
she could eventually become
capable of providing all
of Academy City's functionality
entirely on her own.
A so-called
"Academy Individual."
[HAMAZURA]
Hold on.
You're telling us you
knew all this already?
That no matter how hard we try,
there are those who
are fated to succeed
and those who are
doomed to fail?
[MUGINO] Takitsubo and I
have gone down this road
on our own and faced
the consequences.
But Hamazura isn't like us.
If he'd been given a fair shake,
then things could've
turned out differently.
Mugino.
[HELMETED WOMAN] Not the
reaction I'd expect from you.
Tell me, when did you start
sympathizing with weaklings?
[MUGINO]
Shut up.
It's okay.
The three of us are still ITEM,
and that's not something
I'm ever gonna regret.
So it's okay!
[gunshots]
[HELMETED WOMAN gasps]
Hamazura, you all right?
Yeah, thanks to you.
You guys timed that perfectly.
[HELMETED WOMAN]
Why?
We're not in Academy
City anymore.
I may be a Level Zero,
but out here I was able to
rely on the help of others
in order to survive.
[HELMETED WOMAN] Reinforcements
will be here soon.
Nothing about the
situation has changed.
I know that.
[HAMAZURA]
Now, then.
What you mentioned earlier,
this "Parameter List."
[HAMAZURA] You're going
to tell me everything
you know about it.
I'll show you just how
cruel a person can be.
So long as they can excuse it as
protecting the ones they love.
[MALE PILOT 26A] This is the
recovery team. Target secured.
Now heading to the rendezvous
point with the main unit.
What did you do with the kids?
[MALE RESEARCHER 26A]
Another unit has them.
I want you to give me
your word, right now.
There'll be no more hiding
behind the kid or the Sisters.
You can do your own dirty work.
Do not toy around with a single
one of their lives any further.
And that goes for other
people like me, too.
I won't permit you to force us
to do jobs for the
underworld anymore.
[MALE RESEARCHER 26B]
You don't seem to understand
what's going on.
Huh? See, now that's where
you're wrong, Goggles.
You're the one who doesn't
seem to understand.
[MALE RESEARCHER 26B] Hey. His
switch is turned off, isn't it?
[MALE RESEARCHER 26C]
Uh, yeah, it should be.
[MALE RESEARCHER 26A]
Double check it.
[MALE RESEARCHER 26B gasps]
This isn't a negotiation,
a suggestion,
a trade, or a request.
It's a triumphant return,
you sons of bitches.
[banging]
[FIAMMA]
No. It can't be.
Aleister Crowley?
[ALEISTER] It's good to see
I'm well known enough
to be recognized
outside of my tank.
[FIAMMA]
But why?
You may not have understood
what you were doing,
but you went after that right
hand a bit too enthusiastically.
If only you'd seen Imagine
Breaker as nothing
but an extraordinary tool for
negating extraordinary powers.
Unfortunately, you got a glimpse
of its true nature, didn't you?
That's a loose end
I can't allow.
[FIAMMA] What do you mean,
"its true nature"?
I'm sure you must have guessed.
And though your plan
may ultimately
have been unsuccessful
how is it any different
from Academy City,
a world with a certain sort of
power enclosed within it?
I see, so in my own way,
I've actually managed
to come close
to touching the truth at
the heart of the world.
I can tell from the
look on your face,
all of my recent efforts
have been futile.
Yours isn't the
expression of someone
who truly wishes
to save the world.
He stood, and he fought.
And in that moment,
he was utterly untouchable.
[ALEISTER] I really don't think
that's going to work.
It isn't a question of
whether or not I can do this.
I have to.
I won't let you trample
what he fought to protect!
Do you know where your
failure really lies?
I will tell you.
You thought you could explain
that right hand and Kamijo,
the Purifier of God,
with no more than the
church of the cross.
How very foolish.
I'm reading something here.
This wavelength, I recognize it.
It belongs to Aleister Crowley!
[LAURA]
Oh. So he is alive.
Well, then, seems things are
about to get very interesting.
Chairman of the
governing board. Aleister.
You seem to be enjoying this.
[AIWASS]
Yes. I find it quite pleasant.
Or, to be more precise,
I'm delighted that this pleasant
time will be prolonged.
He has done surprisingly well.
It was less about purging me
and more about making a shift
into a different domain.
I think you would be better off
if you spent a little bit more
time getting to know humans.
Underestimate them, and you
just might find yourself
stabbed through
the heart someday.
[AIWASS]
What are you saying?
Humans are such
delicate creatures.
I suspect my heart
is entirely safe.
That said, if one of them
actually did manage to wound me,
well, can you think of
anything more fascinating?
[gasps]
[SILVIA] Hmm. It looks
like he's still alive.
[OLLERUS] You don't want your
life to end like this, do you?
Tell me everything
you saw and heard.
Who're you?
My name is Ollerus.
I was almost a Magic
God once. Came close.
But then I was unseated
by the One-Eyed Othinus.
A wretched sorcerer.
I have good news.
We have looked
over the conditions
presented to us by Academy City,
and have agreed to a seat
at the conference table.
So, as of this moment,
I declare that all hostilities
are officially at an end.
This decision was reached with
the cooperation of all parties,
and it is my sincere hope
that it will be recorded
in the history of a
future world at peace
as having been correct.
Huh...
You know, you've got
awfully good luck
for somebody who
claims it's rotten.
Toma Kamijo.