[LAST ORDER]
Jeez!
I asked you to let me out here.
So why don't you drop me off?
Asks Misaka Misaka
protesting as hard as she can
with her hands on her hips.
I've already been
paid to take you
to a specific destination.
No unscheduled stops.
[LAST ORDER] Misaka steals
this chance to run away!
Hold on, Miss! Please!
--[TAXI DRIVER 04A sighs]
--[horns blaring]
[tapping]
'Scuse me.
It looks like you might
be having some trouble.
[UIHARU]
Let me see.
What was her name again?
Hey, Crazy Haired Girl!
I'll have you know
Misaka's alias is Last Order,
says Misaka Misaka
with fists in the air!
[UIHARU]
"Lost child?"
I think we might
want to look over there,
says Misaka Misaka
making a prediction.
I have a tickling feeling
in this part of my head,
she says with confidence,
adding some important
and fascinating
sensory information.
Yeah, okay.
So, who exactly is this lost
child we're looking for?
[ACCELERATOR]
End of the line, huh?
Good enough. Get lost.
[CITIZEN 04A sighs]
Looks like it's still
a few more kilometers
to the satellite antenna.
I'll have to walk from here.
[SARAKU]
Well, well, well.
Looks like I found
your weakness, didn't I?
If I can keep you from
accessing your switch,
you won't be able
to use your ability.
Who are you?
Are you with BLOCK?
Guess again.
[ACCELERATOR grunts]
I'm not from BLOCK. I'm MEMBER.
[DOCTOR] It would be a shame
if we were to lose one of our
level fives.
You're either with
GROUP or ITEM.
The question is which one?
Neither, actually.
I'm from MEMBER.
[BABA laughs]
Teitoku Kakine and Accelerator!
We got two level fives
at the same time!
That just proves
MEMBER is the greatest!
[gunshot]
[SARAKU grunts]
[ACCELERATOR]
So you're a teleportation esper,
but you can only attack
others from behind?
Wow, that is one
piss-poor ability.
[SARAKU yells]
You can't even
activate your ability
until you calculate
where somebody else
is going to be located.
It's like you're controlled
by your own power.
And this is coming from
the guy who's dependent
on an electrode.
[WORKER 05A]
Hey! What are you doing?
[WORKER 05A gasps]
[ACCELERATOR]
You lack aesthetic.
You don't understand
the values of a villain
or what it means to be evil.
[SARAKU yells]
[ACCELERATOR]
This gun's aim must be off.
The precision of my power
is a far cry better
than this mess.
You can run if you'd like,
but you better
believe my next move
will be to obliterate you.
I can see you
trembling with fear,
so go ahead and run, you swine.
But first, I'd like to
teach you something
about aesthetics.
This is what a real world-class
villain looks like,
you son of a bitch.
[DOCTOR] Allow me to introduce
you to a modest little invention
I call "mimosa."
What you see in the air before
you are ultra-tiny grains
of a reflective alloy
designed to react
to specific frequencies.
They're attached
to bacteria in the air,
and depending on
how they're manipulated,
they can slice through
concrete or even pluck out
human cells one at a time.
It was during the winter
when I was 12 years old
that I gave up all
hope in the arts.
At the time, I had a passion
for European architecture.
But I found it overwhelming.
I couldn't wrap my head
around the time and manpower
required to create
just one work of art.
Now I much prefer
mathematical formulae.
They are fully functional
without a waste of energy,
and they have the poetic
beauty of a haiku.
[DOCTOR groans]
Just like when you were twelve,
feel free to give up all
hope again right here.
[BABA panting]
Damn it!
[XOCHITL]
What's wrong?
The Doctor and Saraku!
They've got me locked in here!
What am I supposed to do now?!
[XOCHITL] I have my own
opponent to go after.
I don't have time to clean
up your mess. I'm sorry.
Wait, don't hang up!
[gasps]
[BABA]
What's going on?
Hey! Let me out! Please!
Can you hear me? Help!
[UNABARA (YAMATE)]
All right.
All I really need to do
is destroy that computer.
[TESHIO] There's been some
activity in the twenty-third
school district.
Several Antiskill officers at
the site were taken down.
The subject appears
to be heading toward
the ground antennae.
What do we do?
Ha!
We just wait and hope
that they're successful!
[UNABARA (YAMATE)] These
guys couldn't be after...
...control of the optical
weapon that's mounted
on the Hikoboshi II satellite?
They want to paralyze
Academy City's
surveillance capabilities?
Time to go.
There are five thousand
mercenaries on the other side
of that wall, waiting for
orders to charge in.
Seems pretty heavily guarded.
Can't we just muscle
our way in there?
No.
If anything happens, unmanned
attack helicopters will rush in.
The latest six-wing model.
If they spot us,
we'll be up a creek.
In about another ten minutes,
the patrol rotation will switch.
This is a crucial gap time
right now because
the aerial surveillance
is suspended.
What is it, Yamate?
Are you worried?
[UNABARA (YAMATE)]
Five thousand mercenaries.
I wonder where exactly
they're planning to attack.
There's no point
in holding back now.
What the--?
[SAKU]
Yamate!
[alarm blaring]
[ARMY gasps]
[ARMY yelling]
[SAKU]
Up there!
Scatter!
[TETSUMOU screams]
We have to grab the
mercenaries and get out of here!
I can't believe five thousand
troops wasn't enough!
I should've known it
was gonna be impossible
to try and stop all of them.
Venus's angle and
my obsidian knife
are in perfect alignment.
Accelerator!
You just let the intruders
waltz right in here.
What kind of useless
idiot does that crap?
I managed to use my
Spear of Tlahuizcalpantecuhtli.
It cut the intruders
down to a hundred.
That's not useless.
How nice for you. That reminds
me of an expression I know.
"A miss is as good as a mile."
We can't stop the operation,
not after all of this.
All right.
How 'bout a question?
Do you know where BLOCK
is currently heading?
Yeah.
They're going to a juvie hall
in the tenth school district.
Why would you even consider
attacking a place like that?
It wasn't about
the place, exactly.
Our target was Move Point.
We were investigating.
And we received intelligence
that some of her friends
were being held there.
We figured we'd capture them,
and then use them to
negotiate with Move Point.
To get into the
building without windows.
[MERCENARY 05A]
Yes.
BLOCK figured out that Move
Point was the secret guide.
Since it can't be
destroyed from the outside,
we were assigned to learn
how supplies were delivered,
and use that information
to blow the building
up from the inside using
synchronous composite bombs.
Is that so? Interesting.
Do you even know who's
standing in front of you
right now?
No! You can't be!
[yells]
Time to go. Are you ready?
Check it out.
It's the world's one and only
esper internment facility.
They've installed
AIM jammers in there,
so you know what that means.
Yep, sure do.
It means none of us
will be able to use
our abilities inside.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] It's not
that you can't use them.
But it's possible they
could spin out of control.
[ACCELERATOR]
Well...
Sounds like it's best
for us to refrain
from using ability mode.
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Makes sense now.
I wondered why it was
so quiet around here.
Looks like every one of these
guys killed themselves
with their own weapons.
[XOCHITL]
There you are.
[ACCELERATOR] If you're here,
then that must mean
you're with BLOCK.
Not true. I'm from MEMBER.
I was just using those guys.
Etzali! The reason
I did it was to find you!
This girl is Xochitl.
She's an Aztecan sorceress
from my organization.
The one I used to be in.
A sorceress?
You filthy traitor.
I abandoned everything
to come here today
and dispose of you.
I don't care about the rest.
You guys go ahead.
I'll stay here and
clean up this mess.
I can't believe we're
cornered here like this
while BLOCK's inside.
You guys need to
hurry it up and get going.
I move the slowest
out of all of us,
so I'll stay here
and hold them off.
Tsuchimikado. Make sure
you've got Musujime's back.
Let's get movin.'
[TESHIO] Won't we get
hurt when the blast goes off?
[SAKU]
Not at all.
It's rigged to direct the
explosion into the door.
There're 38 kids
being detained here.
So it's really not gonna
make any difference
if we blow up one
or two of them.
You didn't mention that before!
Heh. Don't tell me you've got
a soft spot for these kids
all of a sudden.
[gunshots]
[ARMY yelling]
What a bunch of morons.
Stop!
I haven't finished
packing the explosives yet,
which means the results
could be unpredictable.
I'm afraid I can't
guarantee the kids' safety.
Don't you dare
touch that detonator.
Awaki Musujime,
the famous Move Point.
That saves us some time.
Tell me something, GROUP.
The incident on September
30th sure was something, huh?
You learn anything from it?
What are you talking about?
I know I certainly
learned a lot.
I always thought Aleister
controlled every corner
of this world, but he doesn't.
It turns out there's a way to
get out from under his thumb
and places to flee where his
authority isn't recognized.
So you're traveling to
the new world on the backs
of others?
Honestly, that's not something
I'd brag about if I were you.
Nothing wrong with
hoping for a Heaven
or a paradise that
doesn't exist for us yet.
It's something we all
have in common--
[TESHIO]
That's enough.
[SAKU]
Huh?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Don't move!
What are you
trying to pull here?
Believe me when I say
I have my own reasons
for wanting Aleister dead,
but I will never take hostages!
I'll keep roughing
you up personally
until I have the information!
[TSUCHIMIKADO grunts]
[MUSUJIME yells]
[MUSUJIME gasps]
This is how a pro does it.
We don't need magic
abilities or cute one-liners.
[MUSUJIME yells]
Just years of experience
and fundamental tactics.
We rely on rational methods.
[XOCHITL]
Tell me, Etzali.
Does it look different
when it's that close?
[UNABARA]
She takes control of the weapon.
And then uses it to kill
the enemy without getting
her own hands dirty.
I guess you could say
it's like a suicide spell.
[UNABARA grunting]
You dropped something.
Aren't you going to pick it up?
What happened to you?
You shouldn't even
know about spells
with this kind of power.
No, wait.
Didn't you take the
position to never be involved
in violent acts?
Tell me what's
going on with you!
And what the hell is
happening in the organization
right now?
[XOCHITL chuckles]
A macuahuitl? No way.
[XOCHITL yelling]
[XOCHITL grunting]
A weapon like that is
not very becoming of you.
Then let's see what
it says about you
and what you've become.
You, who abandoned us.
And now you just want
to hide your face
and undermine the peace?
[UNABARA yells]
You're finished!
[XOCHITL grunts]
You lured me in!
[UNABARA] The Aztecs have
no way of processing metal
into their weapons,
which means your sword really
isn't as sharp as it looks.
So if I was willing
to be cut to the bone,
I could actually stop it
with my own limbs.
Like I said earlier.
That particular weapon
doesn't suit you.
I have no desire
to take your life.
Please go somewhere
and disappear.
[MUSUJIME yells]
We can stop as soon
as you're ready to share
the service route for the
building without windows.
Tell me.
What's got you so
angry with Aleister
you'd be willing to go this far?
Like so many others,
I've experienced serious
tragedy in this city,
and I deserve to find out
if he was involved in it.
I want answers. That's all.
Trust me, I know what
it's like to be fixated
on finding out the
truth about something.
But... Nothing he'd say
would provide peace of mind.
You would be suspicious
of any answer he gave you.
Is that so?
Then how do you find peace?
[MUSUJIME] The trauma
I've sustained is keeping me
from transporting myself,
and I can't shoot her or
fight hand to hand either.
[MUSUJIME]
Right.
It's because this is
my constant mindset.
If I don't change it, I'll never
be able to protect anyone.
You're gonna use it?
Yeah, and I hope you're ready,
'cause I'm gonna go all out.
[MUSUJIME]
I'll overcome this.
I can overcome this.
I can overcome everything
about these infuriating scars!
[TESHIO grunts]
Pretty bold. Good job.
I know it's unfortunate.
But this is the
kind of leadership
that's expected
of me these days.
Xochitl. What in the world?
If you ever try to compensate
for lack of abilities
with a grimoire,
this is the kind of
thing that can happen.
You could learn from me.
What? You mean you read one?
[XOCHITL]
No. It's worse than that.
What are you saying?
That you've fused with
the original grimoire text?
You tried to gain more power
by making it a part of you?
Any spell that distorts
your own body will fail!
You had to have known that much!
Sure, but it doesn't matter
as long as I'm still able
to kill you while
it's consuming me.
If I do it before I die,
then the organization's
goal is achieved.
The organization that I knew
was already terrible enough.
But what the hell's been
happening while I've been away?
You won't die. I won't let you.
The original text will
display its knowledge
to anyone who desires it.
I'll have to visualize
it consuming me.
And that should allow me to
draw it completely out of her.
Of course there's no precedent,
so if I fail, it'll kill me.
[FRIEND 05A]
I always believed in you.
FRIEND 05B] I knew trusting
you was the right call.
Thank you so much for coming.
[FRIEND 05C]
It's enough that you're here.
[FRIEND 05D]
Okay, go on. Get going.
You're sure about this?
I am. It's for the best.
[ACCELERATOR]
Damn, you're slow.
Guess it's about that time.
Back into the darkness.
[punching]
[FRENDA grunts]
[KAKINE]
Come on.
Damn, you're pretty tight
lipped for someone
who's got no chance
of leaving here alive.
Looks like I might just have to
start cleaning a little house.
[FRENDA]
No, please don't.
Fine, I'll tell you everything.
[KAKINE]
Wow.
You've got a pretty
cushy base here, huh?
[KAMIJO]
Those who have power survive.
White wings spit upon
conventional principles,
and sneer at common knowledge.
Next time, "Super-espers."
When science and
magic cross paths,
a story is born.