[KAMIJO] Academy City:
a city of science,
with a population
of 2.3 million.
I'm Toma Kamijo,
a level zero student there,
which means I'm powerless.
At least, that's what they say.
But I discovered I've
got a mysterious ability
in my right hand
that can cancel out
any other extraordinary powers.
And as a result of this gift,
happiness, divine favor,
and anything that
might actually be good
keep their distance from me.
What is this,
some kind of penalty game?
Aren't we overstacking
the deck, here?
One day, a nun
fell from the sky
onto my doorstep.
Her name's Index, and she's
memorized 103 thousand books.
Shortly after that,
I was attacked
by a flame-producing sorcerer,
got chased around by
some lady with a katana,
and hung out with the
city's strongest esper,
who can manipulate vectors.
I was also dogged
by Mikoto Misaka,
a level five Zapper,
and then a bunch of girls
who looked just like her
surrounded me.
With all of the crisscrossing
between science and magic
I've seen, it seems
like there's trouble
stirring throughout the world!
And no one knows why!
The Roman Orthodox Church
and its Right Seat of God
are going worldwide.
But it still doesn't make sense!
Hey, Tsuchimikado!
You know something, don't you?
I'm begging you, man,
just tell me!
What is going on
in the world right now?
And who's going after what?
[INDEX] ♪ Bath time!
Bath time! I love baths. ♪
♪ Bath time! Bath time!
I love baths! ♪
♪ I love bubbles in the
shower and I love baths! ♪
Sphinx!
You have to hold still or else
I won't be able to clean you!
[SPHINX growls]
[INDEX] If you run away, you'll
miss all the delicious dinner
Toma's bringing home
for us tonight!
[INDEX]
Wow.
Look how dry you're getting
without any magic!
The science in Academy City
is amazing, isn't it?
[door opens]
[INDEX]
Hi! Welcome home, Toma!
'Bout time.
We were getting so
worried about you!
Do you have any idea
how late it is?
Sphinx thought you
weren't coming back!
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
'Kay! I do!
What's for dinner?
[KAMIJO]
Yeah. About that.
[INDEX]
Huh?
I couldn't exactly go shopping
today because, well...
I think I kinda lost my wallet.
Okay. So we're not eating?
[KAMIJO]
Hey, come on.
Maybe you should just
try thinking about it
as a healthy fast.
I've heard that going
without food for a while
actually makes it
taste even better.
[INDEX]
Toma!
[INDEX growling]
--[INDEX] Gah!
--[cracking noise]
[KAMIJO]
Rotten luck!
[KOMOE]
Okay, listen up.
I promise not to get angry.
I need all of you to be
honest and explain to me
why you would do
something like this.
She asked you a question.
Yes, ma'am!
It's kind of
complicated, though.
Okay, Pierce and I
were debating whether
the black or red
bunny girl was hotter.
We were almost settled.
But then Tsuchimikado butted in
saying the white bunny girl
was clearly the hottest,
which is just total nonsense.
And what about you?
Which bunny suit do you like?
Uh...! Are you serious?
I was the one trying
to get these three idiots
to shut up about it!
Right, and how
did you do that?
Don't you think
you may have taken it
a little too far?
Not to mention
a little too soon.
We never even
reached a conclusion.
For the record,
I stand by my position.
Even A-cups look great in white!
Oh, come on!
You're just saying that
'cause you like anything
having to do with loli!
Stop! Gross!
There are better things
to talk about!
[whistle blows]
All four of you
are responsible.
So after school, you'll all meet
behind the gym to pull weeds.
Do I make myself clear?
[GROUP]
Yeah.
Thanks a lot. This sucks.
I wanted to go to the mark-down
sale at the supermarket.
Hey. You can blame
it on Tsuchimikado.
He's a moron.
I shouldn't even
be part of this.
Wait. Where'd he go?
Did he just take off?
Yeah, makes sense.
No. I'm on it. Okay.
If you clean up after.
Those kids.
One thing is for certain.
They'll never change.
You're right about that.
Wow, are you still
working on those gloves?
They're such a pretty color.
Are they going to be
a present, Miss Oyafune?
[SUAMA]
Huh?
No. That's just silly!
Why would anyone start a
Christmas present this early?
I'm just taking it slow.
Because I want to,
not because it's really hard.
[REPORTER 01A] Late last night,
in the industrial city
of Toulouse in
the south of France,
a local religious group began
a large-scale protest movement.
It's having a serious
effect on traffic
and even various buildings
are currently blocked.
This series of demonstrations
against Academy City
and the reprisals toward
them are fueling concerns
that the conflict between
the Roman Orthodoxy
and the center of
science is beginning
to escalate faster than
previously expected.
It's so hot!
[ENGINEER 01A] Yeah.
Thanks for doing this, though.
I can't believe there
are so many people
interested in seeing
an interception weapons
show today.
During the week in the
middle of the afternoon?
I know, and this is with
limited admittance, too.
All hell will break
loose when we open
to the public tomorrow.
Oh, wow,
look at that, Shirai!
It's a fifth generation tank!
Oh! And over there
is an independent
shoulder-launched
missile system!
Omigosh! Are those
state-of-the-art powered suits?
So cool!
This is the best day ever!
I'm glad you're
enjoying yourself.
Can't wait to see what's next.
What is the deal?
He hasn't even sent
me one single text.
Did his thumbs fall off?
[KUROKO]
Hey, Sissy!
Okay, there's something
bothering you.
You've been
fidgeting like crazy.
Oh. I'm fine.
There's just way too
many people here.
[KUROKO] I know.
It is pretty intense.
Not only is it more
elaborate then usual--
it's also quite ostentatious.
I find it interesting
that they've never asked
any of us in Judgement to
work security before today.
I know, right?
I bet it has something to do
with those demonstrations.
Seems like they've been
itching for a chance like this.
Meaning what?
You're making
way too much of it.
But I'll admit, things are
getting kinda weird
around here lately.
I completely lost track of time.
We gotta get going. You ready?
Yeah. Sure.
[KUROKO]
I'll see you later, Sissy.
[UIHARU]
Take care.
Bye. Be careful, guys.
[phone buzzes]
Great. Nothing.
More false alarms.
[KAMIJO]
Damn it.
Figures those jerks
would bail on us.
[FUKIYOSE]
Some friends you've got there.
I've got a question.
Considering that the October
midterms were cancelled...
Why are you still
spending all your free time
studying instead of relaxing?
I should ask you why
you're not still studying.
With midterms cancelled,
our entire grade
is going to be determined
by the final exam.
Doesn't sound like
any of us can relax.
Uh... Guess not.
And no, you may
not borrow my notes.
Ha! Oh, well.
There's more to life than
just high school, ya know.
I never said there wasn't.
You act like I don't do
anything else but study.
What else can you do?
Bet you've never
seen a girl like me
throw a forkball pitch.
I could play baseball,
I'm just not interested.
Cool...
In fact, if you want,
I'll prove it to you
right now using this ball.
You might wanna
prepare yourself!
Wait. You're serious?
Do you even know me?
When have I ever
not been serious?
[KAMIJO] Right, good point.
Okay, I'm ready for ya.
You sure?
Because I don't want
to see you wussing out
when smoke comes flying
your way at 150 kph!
Wait! Stop, Fukiyose!
Why, what's wrong?
[KAMIJO]
Your skirt!
[KAMIJO grunts]
I'm so sorry! Are you okay?
That was just
a regular fastball!
[INDEX]
Still?
I wish you'd find
a way to forgive me
and put this behind us, Sphinx.
[SPHINX meows]
I'm genuinely sorry
for making you
take a shower with me. 'Kay?
[doorbell rings]
Oh. Hi, Maika!
It looks like I'll be
living next door again,
so I thought that I'd say hello!
I'll also be doing
a lot of cooking,
so feel free to come
over and eat any time!
[INDEX]
You mean it?
Hey, Sphinx!
Where're you going?
Oh, no!
Your door!
Keep an eye on
the place for me!
Please wait!
Slow down, Sphinx. Please!
Sphinx!
Hello. What have we here?
On your way home? Are you lost?
[SPHINX meows]
It's okay. There we go.
[INDEX]
Come back, Sphinx!
Is this your kitty?
Yes, his name is Sphinx.
Right, boy? Let's go home.
[SPHINX growls]
Oh, goodness.
Yeah, we got into a little
bit of a fight earlier.
He ran away and
made me chase him.
[MONAKA]
Is that so?
I haven't even eaten today.
I think I'm about to pass out.
[groaning]
You poor thing!
That's terrible.
Thank you so much!
So good!
Would you like to try a bite?
[SPHINX meows]
It looks like you two
have patched things up.
Like that?
I think you're right.
Ooh, that scarf!
It looks so nice
and cozy! Is it?
Why yes, it is.
And guess what?
My daughter made it for me.
So now what...
It says to knit two stiches
on the next row.
My word.
I never would've thought
making gloves was this hard.
Is there a shortcut? [gasps]
Ugh! Seriously?
Is anyone here?
[KAMIJO]
Hello?
Oh, hey, is it okay if I...
If I leave?
[KAMIJO]
I'm so sorry!
I thought I was gonna die.
[KAMIJO]
Oh, man.
I don't know how I
managed to survive that.
It's pretty late.
I'm sure Index feels
like she's starving.
I'll stop at the supermarket
on my way home.
[MIKOTO]
Take that!
For real?
Are all the vending machines
here going on strike?
"Only fools rush in where
angels fear to tread."
"Let sleeping Zappers lie."
[MIKOTO]
Hold it!
You saw me struggling
and you're just gonna
walk away like that?
Please forgive me!
Mr. Kamijo has had a
long day of weed-pulling.
His simple mind cannot
solve one more problem.
He needs to go home and rest.
Have a good night!
[MIKOTO]
Oh, no, you don't!
Tell me why you
didn't respond to the text
that I sent forever ago?
What text?
I don't think I got it.
Let me see your phone!
[KAMIJO]
Hey! Come on! Not cool!
That's my personal information!
[MIKOTO]
What? Are you kidding me?
You can't text me back,
but you've got plenty of time
to take selfies with my mom?
Um... It's not like that.
[MIKOTO] Oh, and you
have her number saved.
Great!
[KAMIJO]
Now that I didn't do!
So, what?
It just jumped in there?
No. I have no idea
how that happened.
Look, Ms. Misuzu was
pretty wasted, though,
so maybe she thought...
[MIKOTO]
"Ms. Misuzu"?!
It's bad enough that you're
hanging out with my mother,
but keeping her contact info?
Hang on. It's not...
You disgusting jerk-wad!
[KAMIJO grunts]
Ugh! You're just as
contemptible as ever!
It's no big deal!
She got drunk and grabbed
my phone, that's all!
And I had Index with me.
You can ask her.
She saw everything
that happened.
[MIKOTO growls]
Anyway... The sun's
almost down already.
I don't want you to miss
curfew on my account.
Yeah, right.
I don't need you
to keep track of my life.
I'm out. But only because
the checks have been getting
stricter lately.
Also... Watch your back.
There's major trouble
brewing around here.
Yeah. Thanks.
[MIKOTO] I don't know
what's going on,
but I know something
happened on September 30th.
Everyone is fighting.
So many people are getting hurt.
Someone's behind this,
but they won't show their faces.
Do you have any idea--
[MIKOTO]
What a jerk!
[MONAKA]
Ah. So.
This young boy you live with
cooks all your meals
for you every day?
Yep! It's delicious!
Toma makes the best food ever!
[MONAKA]
Toma?
[INDEX]
Yeah!
And is this Toma a nice boy?
Nice boy? I dunno.
What do you think, Sphinx?
[SPHINX meows]
[INDEX]
He says he's probably nice.
Oh? That's good.
[phone buzzes]
[MONAKA]
Um, will you excuse me?
Yes? Yes.
I understand. Yes, thank you.
[MONAKA]
I have to be going now.
It was lovely to meet you.
Thank you for chatting with me.
[INDEX]
Oh, goodness no, thank you!
For the all the
yummy food you gave us!
Right? Tell her, Sphinx!
[SPHINX meows]
[INDEX] Have a good night!
Bye-bye!
I'm so sorry.
[KAMIJO]
What she said is true.
Ever since the
Kazakiri incident,
there's been trouble
stirring all over.
Maybe I should swing by
Tsuchimikado's apartment
after I get home.
Excuse me!
[MONAKA]
Not at all.
I'm the one who should
be apologizing here.
No way.
It's my fault.
I bumped into you.
[MONAKA]
I'm not talking about that.
I mean for all the trouble
you're about to go through.
Poor boy.
[KAMIJO gasps]
Let's go have a chat.
About all the
unrest taking place
around the world right now.
[KAMIJO] You said you
want to talk about it.
But I don't know how
much there is I can say.
There's a huge problem here
that needs to be solved.
Your input is quite necessary.
Oh, yeah?
And who exactly are you?
Monaka Oyafune.
Sound familiar?
I work for Academy City.
I'm a member of
the Governing Board.
Wait, the governing board?
You're kidding.
You don't believe me?
Well, it's just that
scarf you're wearing.
I figure that somebody
who's on the board
could afford something
a little nicer.
[MONAKA gasps] I'll have you
know my daughter made this scarf
for me as a gift!
I will not allow you
to insult it!
Whoa! Okay!
I take it all back!
But, uh, as far as that
problem you mentioned,
there aren't exactly
any definite reasons
or causes for it.
So no one can really
take action, right?
[MONAKA]
Yes.
But if there was a
definite cause or reason,
I'd want to know.
[KAMIJO gasps]
[MONAKA] That's the main reason
I thought it would be good
to talk to you.
Maybe you have something
but don't know its importance.
Something that the state
heads and United Nations
don't have.
What are you talking about?
[MONAKA]
Your right hand, of course.
You don't mean...?
[MONAKA]
Yes, I do.
You want my Imagine Breaker?
So then...
Whatever's causing this
unrest is really powerful.
That's right.
But what's happening
right now isn't a result
of September 30th.
I'm afraid it goes
far deeper than that.
Whether or not the
protests were their doing,
the Roman Orthodoxy's
making use of this confusion.
Instead of attacking
Academy City directly,
they're turning their
attention to the world
that has come
to rely on it so much.
Undermining science
on a global scale.
[KAMIJO] So, let's assume
the Roman Orthodoxy
is currently on the move.
I wouldn't know
where they would be
or what kind of tricks
they would use.
I don't see how
I could help you right now.
If they tried to pull
something again, then, maybe.
[MONAKA]
Right. As for that...
He can explain it
better than I can.
Tsuchimikado?
Did you have a nice chat?
We're not quite finished,
but it should be enough.
I think I'll let you
handle it from here.
Sounds good.
[MONAKA grunts]
What the hell?!
Are you crazy?!
Snap out of it!
You bastard!
[KAMIJO]
Damnit, Tsuchimikado!
[MONAKA]
Please.
Please, don't.
Don't hold this against him.
It's not him.
It's because of me.
My actions don't align with
the governing board's agenda.
[KAMIJO]
Huh?
[MONAKA] They want to
increase hostilities
and destroy religion.
Science's counterpart.
As it's represented by
the Roman Orthodox Church.
You have to put a stop
to all of that insanity.
That's the reason
I chose to contact you.
You have the ability
to defuse the situation.
I know eventually they
will learn I spoke to you.
But if I were to try to escape,
my family would most likely
bear the brunt
of the punishment.
And so, to keep
my loved ones safe,
I asked him to punish me.
Don't say any more.
I'll take care of the rest.
You've done exactly
what you needed to do,
so don't you worry.
They're gonna be just fine.
I need you to
remember that, okay?
Well, what do ya think, Kami?
Ready to go?
Yeah, all right.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] First we'll head
to the 23rd School District.
From there, we'll have
to fly to France.
Our objective is a
Roman Orthodox magical item,
the Document of Constantine.
Also known as the Document of C.
That's gonna be the
key to resolving this case.
Ready, Kami? Here we go!
What? You mean right now?
[KAMIJO yelling]
[yelling continues]
[KAMIJO] After dropping
into a foreign city,
I'm reunited with Itsuwa.
Magical items? Geoducts?
Do you really even
need my right hand?
Next time,
"The Right Seat of God."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.