[HAMAZURA grunts]
[HAMAZURA]
Come on.
Where are you, Takitsubo?
Damn it. Help me!
We have to dig her out of here
before the enemy finds us.
I can't do it on my own!
Why should I help you?
It's freezing out here,
and she's still nowhere
near her full strength!
We need to get her warmed up!
[MUGINO]
Tch.
Hamazura, I've had
enough of your whining!
[screaming]
[MUGINO]
Ugh... My head.
Damn those ability crystals.
Curse their stupid side effects.
So dizzy.
Be careful! We don't know
where she's buried.
Quit attacking me
and start digging!
[MUGINO]
Ugh. What's your problem?
The way I see it,
I gave you a head start.
It's hopeless!
I need someone gentle as a lamb,
not this rabid tiger who's
looking to devour me!
Huh?
Hey, look. Here's your
sweet little lamb now.
Huh?
No way!
[HAMAZURA]
Takitsubo!
Not right now. That comes first.
[HAMAZURA]
Uh?
Dark Matter?
[yelling]
No. That isn't Dark Matter.
And they're not Academy
City espers, either.
[HAMAZURA]
Huh?
[ATTACKER 25A] Esper powers
are a lot like flames.
Humans are the only ones
who can control flames.
But simply brandishing
them is no better
than being a caveman
swinging a torch.
Civilized people use
flame to forge iron.
This is the same thing.
[HAMAZURA]
So that's it.
They failed to fashion
Mugino into a weapon,
so they're here to retrieve her.
What's the next plan?
To turn her into a blast
furnace or something?
[gasps, yelps]
[HAMAZURA] Do you realize
what you've just done?
That bottle you broke
was the last hope
for negotiating
with Academy City!
It's the biological weapon
that Russia was going to use
according to the Kremlin
Report protocol!
Now you've infected us, too!
[ATTACKER 25A]
Huh? Damn it!
Ha! I'm kidding.
That was actually just
a bottle of club soda.
[ATTACKER 25B]
Ugh. Sneaky bastard!
[HAMAZURA yells]
I think you may be forgetting
something pretty important.
Mugino's probably still
got some blasts left.
Two or three, I'd say.
[ATTACKER 25C]
You're bluffing.
We're not gonna fall
for another stupid trick.
Oh, no? That's a shame.
Let's see if you're
still that confident
a few seconds from now.
[gasps]
[ATTACKER 25C]
What the--?
Shizuri Mugino?
The fourth-ranked
allowed somebody else
to help steady her aim?
I don't believe it.
So, you were planning
this trap the whole time?
Yeah. Thank you for
stepping right into it.
[ATTACKER 25C] Who knew
you were capable of this?
Me? I'm not.
But... ITEM is!
Take that thought
to hell with you.
[gunshot]
[ACCELERATOR]
Damn it. This is crazy.
It's so far beyond abnormal--
even the thought of
analyzing it is ridiculous.
Does this mean that the
very makeup of the world
is being transformed?
What do I care?
How's it coming?
Have you gotten the
data from the song
that purged Amata
Kihara's virus yet?
Yeah, in the Misaka Network,
a fairly shallow end.
Misaka does have the song,
but she can't render it
with her current specs.
The breathing technique and
internal resonance it requires
are not exactly normal.
It would be more efficient
to output the song
as electronic signals instead.
Music notes, pseudo-audio data,
or surround amplitude graphs?
Which one would you prefer?
All of 'em. Right now.
Being stingy's something
a third-stringer does.
You really can be demanding.
Then again, I suppose you're
more charming that way.
It's going to take more
than just this song
to get anywhere, right?
Wasn't there something
about converting
the specialized parameters?
I can manage it.
As long as I have this.
Is this your way of
making fun of Misaka?
Sure hope you're
not trying to say
that creepy, occult-reeking
contract with the devil
has the necessary parameters
hidden within it.
No, I'm not.
Here, as far-removed from
Academy City as we are,
there just happens to be
a handbook lying around
with the solution in it?
It's almost like hunting
for a quest item
in a game or something!
[ACCELERATOR]
I told you, it's not that.
Whether it's high-level
security encryption,
or a secret code embedded
in an ancient diagram,
it all boils down to
the world of numbers.
The roots remain the
same no matter what.
I digitized all the
necessary data,
then put the puzzle
together inside my head,
and I should've been able
to solve it that way.
Misaka thoroughly enjoys hearing
the frustration and
displeasure in your voice
when you're forced to admit you
failed to accomplish something.
[ACCELERATOR]
I can't solve the puzzle.
There's still a piece missing
in the math portion.
It's like some other form
of law's been mixed in,
which is the reason I've been
dredging up every last bit
of knowledge stored
away in my mind
to the point of exhaustion.
And then dredging up
some more, over and over.
And that's when I suddenly
realized something.
I already had some information
placed inside of me
that I didn't
comprehend at the time.
It happened not too long ago.
Sometime during the battle
between the water angel
and the science angel.
But I must have understood
it all on my own
long before that moment,
that some kind of unidentified
law was in effect.
Establish an imaginary
vector grid
that can process
these incongruities.
Back trace from the vectors
right in front of you
to highlight the laws that
have been put in place.
Once a single line of
this unique physical law
had been input, the
substance of the parchment
would immediately stand out.
But that's not what
was important.
What matters is that
once I solved the puzzle
using the clues I found,
the Aiwass vectors lodged inside
of me would begin to act.
They would've been able to
chip away at this deduction.
It's as close to realistic
as it's going to get,
and it's on the same level
as the Big Bang Theory.
In other words, it's done.
I've acquired the parameters
I need to save the kid.
From now on, I'm the one
who will turn the tables.
[ACCELERATOR] I made a promise
long ago that I would become
the ultimate villain
who would rescue her.
I fought all those sons
of bitches to the finish,
and a great darkness
swallowed my soul.
But... this fight is different.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
I can save her.
So there's no longer any
reason for me to be a villain.
[ACCELERATOR]
Tch.
Let's do this.
[ACCELERATOR]
The question is what am I?
Am I good or evil?
Am I a man or a monster?
Am I ruled by science or magic?
[ACCELERATOR]
Maybe that's the answer.
What I am... is something
that cannot be defined
by any other word than "me."
[explosion]
Why bother? How can
you hope to stop me?
Your power only works to
neutralize other powers.
All you are is an adapter--
a mere anchor for that hand
until the designated time.
You're nothing more
than a potato vine
that falls back into the
earth after the harvest!
Heh.
[KAMIJO]
You still don't get it, do you?
Remember what you said?
That the power of your right arm
varies according to the
strength of your opponent.
You decided you wanted
to try stimulating
its maximum power.
You thought starting World War
Three would do the trick.
You wanted to fuel
the people's hatred.
That way your enemy
would be clearly defined,
and the rest would
be smooth sailing.
But have you ever
thought about this?
What if you're wrong?
What if there isn't
as much hatred
in everyone's heart
as you think?
Then you wouldn't
be able to summon
the amount of power
you're imagining!
You're operating under
a false assumption.
The four fundamental
elements were about to be
permanently disrupted.
Lucky for the entire world,
I stepped in and restored them.
The war that I started is
not ending any time soon.
The larger conflict springs
from all the smaller
thorns in people's sides,
spreading out all over the world
until there is nothing left.
Resource shortages.
Racial conflicts.
Religious differences.
Food shortages.
International conflicts.
Environmental destruction.
They are all results of
the evil man creates.
Like that's some
great revelation!
That darkness lurks
in man's true nature.
There may be some
malice within me
that I'm not ready
to admit is there.
However, there's more to
human nature than just that!
Like what?
[KAMIJO]
How can you say flat-out
that people's inner workings
are only one-sided?
Even if it's true,
and everyone you meet has
a dark side buried within,
how can you declare
that's all there is?
We don't have to have a reason!
People don't have to explain.
They believe in fighting
for those they love,
and that's all there is to it.
I, myself, have been saved
by that power, so I know!
All this without any reason?
That sounds like the kind of
logic that only applies to us.
If there was a nuclear missile
about to be launched
right in front of you,
no one could do
anything to save you
without a key to stop it.
So why would they bother?
'Cause they don't need a key!
That's only one way
to resolve the situation!
Anyone can fight
if they want to!
Even if the rest of the world
turns against them.
When it involves someone
they care about,
they'll risk their own
lives to protect them.
I'm going to get
Index back from you.
And that's not all.
I'm gonna put a stop to science
and magic fighting each other.
And to the nations of the
world destroying one another
over World War Three.
It's all going to end right now!
[FIAMMA] In the middle of
such a large-scale conflict?
You honestly believe you'll
somehow emerge victorious
without any losses?
Yes, I do!
I know it's hard
for you to fathom,
but I believe in the
strength of humanity!
[ALL gasp]
This has turned into
something greater than war.
What's happening to our world?
Damn!
You saved my life.
Huh? Wait. But we're
on opposing sides!
You saw what's happening, right?
We can't think in terms
of war right now,
or who's on what side.
Both sides need
to work together.
We need Academy
City's firepower.
Roger that.
[SOLDIERS gasp]
It doesn't matter to me one bit
if you are British, French,
Russian, or from Academy City.
All able-bodied soldiers
need to pitch in!
We're about to launch a full-on
support strike together!
Let's go!
It's time for us to show them
that enough is enough
with an attack that's of
the people, by the people,
for the people!
We're gonna blow the roof
off this place, baby!
[BRITISH SOLDIER 25B]
Uh. Wh-Who are you, exactly?
A sorcery society known as
"Dawn Colored Sunlight."
How very foolish, Fiamma.
[VASILISSA] Cannibal old lady
of the one-legged house,
please grant this
frail, yet sincere,
young girl your strength.
Lend her enough of your
overwhelming witch's power
to muddle this sick, treacherous
abomination into a pulp,
and create a more perfect
world for all of us.
[KRANS]
Hm?
Hi there! If it isn't the
head of the Russian Church.
Good news!
I've come to rescue you
from the devil's castle.
Forgive my surprise.
I didn't expect there
would be anyone
who would still
see me as Patriarch.
Not when all of my
power's been lost.
[giggles]
There's still something that
could use your assistance.
That fortress.
Did you know that it
was cobbled together
from the requisite
parts of cathedrals
and churches of the cross
from all around the world?
But just because they
were gathered together
and placed in the same spot
doesn't exactly mean
it's a perfect fit.
Spells from both
the Russian Church
and the Roman Orthodox Church
are what's responsible
for keeping it in place.
So if we could
break them down...
Yeah, I get it.
You're asking me to release
the spells on the fortress.
Well, since you brought it up.
One moment. As you
mentioned before,
the Roman Orthodox Church must
be involved in this as well.
Have you taken steps to ensure
their cooperation
with your plan?
Everything's okay
as far as that goes.
I'm not sure what
you've been told.
But the truth is, that
group isn't as corrupt
as everyone thinks.
So what do you say?
Would you be so kind,
my dandy gentleman?
As I'm no longer the pope,
I'm not sure how
much I can help.
[VASILISSA] I'm speaking to
the person who I believe to be
the true head of the
Roman Orthodox Church.
Both in name and in fact.
Very well, then.
If it means saving the people,
I will commit Roman Orthodox
power to this strategy
and assist you in
stopping Fiamma.
But you should know,
the spells that are in use
on the Star of Bethlehem
are likely not limited to those
of the Roman Orthodoxy
and the Russian Church.
Of course I've thought
of that, silly.
Indeed, the final key...
...is the archbishop of the
English Puritan Church.
[VASILISSA] So should we
do rock-paper-scissors
to see which one of us will
be contacting that vixen?
These aren't fatal wounds.
You'll be okay, so try
to keep it together.
[MECH SOLDIER 25A]
Who are you people?
That isn't important.
What matters is we're here to
alleviate harm done by the war.
Even if we're only able to
help one soldier at a time.
[popping]
[ALL gasp]
[groans]
[STIYL]
That was just a mirage.
A pretty common trick.
[gasps]
Warning. Chapter forty-seven,
verse eighty now activating.
Psychological effects present,
causing severe physical
and mental restraint.
Redirecting spell effect
into dummy location
and prioritizing security of
back-calculation abilities.
You're still a library
of 103,000 grimoires.
I never expected that would
be enough to contain you.
Even so, it doesn't matter.
If that confounded boy
is finally able to bring
an end to this madness,
it will be a win for all of us.
[footsteps]
Very well. As you wish.
Our quota appears to be filled,
so you will have your reward.
Meanwhile, I will do
everything I possibly can
to help retrieve the
grimoire library.
[yells]
What now?
Why isn't this going
the way I wanted?
[FIAMMA yells]
[LESSAR] The English Puritans,
the Roman Orthodox Church,
and the Russian Church
have all begun
breaking down the Star of
Bethlehem's joint spell.
We're just about to climb into
an escape chamber over here.
There aren't very
many of them left.
You have to work
faster than that!
It's all over, Fiamma.
Your right arm as well
your ceremonial site,
the Star of Bethlehem,
they're both losing power now!
If it was truly your
desire to save the world
more than anything,
then you would be ecstatic
to see the people's goodwill
winning out over evil!
If you don't see it that way,
then your fantasy has
already been shattered!
I know that I'm at a
disadvantage in this situation.
And with the way things stand,
I find it unlikely that I'll be
able to continue as planned.
[chuckles]
So I'll have to
make some changes.
[gasps]
[FIAMMA] This is actually the
outcome that you've invited.
[KAMIJO]
What do you mean?
[FIAMMA] You see,
the earth was originally
supposed to be
transformed in stages.
However, all of the
goodwill you rave about
has prevented that
from happening.
As a result, an unnatural
distortion has developed
between heaven and earth.
Which means all that's
left for us to do now
is to wait patiently for
the accumulated telesma
to come plunging
down from above.
Honestly, even though
this is not the route
I had originally anticipated,
as long as the earth ends
up inundated with light,
the outcome is all the same.
Do you know what's
really going to happen?
If that tremendous
amount of power
starts to run amok
uncontrollably,
it could cause all of human
civilization to be destroyed!
[FIAMMA]
That's true.
And it would be quite a
shame for you, wouldn't it?
As for all the goodwill
you speak of,
despite how much may
be burgeoning forth
amidst this war, an overwhelming
power will crush it from above.
This divine punishment
will sweep down
on the fruits of mankind,
wiping them from the
face of the earth.
Great change is
born out of pain.
And just as the destruction
of the Tower of Babel
once severed the
ties of humanity,
I will use the animosity
brought about by this
to pick up the broken
pieces I see before me
and once again draw
upon tremendous power!
Damn you, Fiamma!
[FIAMMA]
I'm afraid your preferred way
of saving the world
is overruled.
You're too late.
I've already won.
[KAMIJO] There is still
something left for me to do.
I'm sorry.
I promise... I will return soon.
Next Time, "Son of God."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.