[LAURA]
What's the matter, Stiyl?
I'm giving you a chance to
do something about this.
If you're not interested,
let me know, because I will.
I don't need you to tell me.
I know what to do.
I've been doing this job
for a long time now.
[INDEX]
Hostile identified.
Now conducting analysis
of available spells.
Searching construction
of suitable local weapons.
[KAMIJO] He went out of
his way to get this ready.
In order for Fiamma
to accomplish what he has
set out to do,
he must need this
Star of Bethlehem here.
Which means that
if I destroy it,
I'll be able to do damage
to Fiamma, as well.
[FIAMMA] Let's see, I've got the
angel medium Sasha Kruezhev,
the magical item to remotely
control the 103,000 grimoires,
the Star of Bethlehem,
the ceremonial site,
and your right hand
fit to wield my power.
It would appear that I've
acquired everything I need.
I say it's high time to ask
the supporting players
to leave the stage.
Charge forth, Archangel Gabriel.
Obliterate everything.
No way.
So the reason he abducted
Sasha was to enlist the power
of an archangel.
I guess I'll just have
to smash that angel up
until she's immobilized!
[grunts]
[KAMIJO]
Sasha Kruezhev?
[FIAMMA] The Star of
Bethlehem is not yet complete,
but the moment I set
Sasha Kruezhev in motion
was the moment my
victory became undeniable.
All I need now
is that parchment.
Simple fix.
Why don't you
retrieve it for me?
There's no reason
to show mercy to them
just because they're weak.
Go claim it with everything
you have, and don't hold back!
[ELIZALINA]
That completes her treatment.
All of the toxins that
I found inside of her
have been successfully removed.
Scientific efficiency
is quite distasteful.
I have little faith
that it will change.
Have you guys seen
that big mess outside?
What the hell's goin'
on out there, damn it?
It's Fiamma's work.
I didn't think he'd touch
the four elements.
[TAKITSUBO grunts]
Be careful!
You're so light.
Hamazura, you suck.
Is something wrong?
[HAMAZURA] I'll fill you in on
everything later, but for now,
let me just say this.
You're gonna be all right.
So, what do we do now?
Our main objective:
negotiate with Academy City.
We're going back into Russia.
We'll find what we need there.
But you...
You're still recovering
from being sick.
You can stay here if you want.
Really?
Tell me how to wake you up.
With a kiss or a
smack on the head?
If those are my options,
I should try leaving
you behind more often.
[HAMAZURA]
What's that?
This is bad.
The Russian army might
be planning to use
a bacteriological weapon
near that village.
You think they'd do that?
A secret silo.
It was abandoned
during the Cold War.
But it's close to that location.
There's a manual to keep
it safe from enemies
called the Kremlin Report.
What should we do?
Find it?
[TAKITSUBO] The Elizalina
Alliance of Independent Nations
will be suspected of
assisting the villagers,
and of trying to acquire
information on how
the nuclear facility works.
So the orders are to stay away.
They can't be serious.
Listen. I can't--
I can't leave Digurv and
the others in the lurch.
I don't want to abandon them.
I get it. I'm coming, too.
[HAMAZURA]
Takitsubo...
After everything those
people did for me,
I owe them my life.
I'm ready.
I want to fight for them myself.
[HAMAZURA] You're not going
to change your mind, huh?
I'm not. Are you?
[ELIZALINA]
How can this be?
Is that an angel?
We're looking right at
the core of the mystery
that me and the kid were forced
into being involved with.
If we can find a way
to control that thing,
it would be the breakthrough
that I need to save her.
You have to go.
They're coming soon.
Huh? Who's coming?
And why are they
coming after me?
The castle isn't
quite completed yet.
The parchment in your
possession is proof of that.
Think about it.
Fiamma went so far as using
the army to get his hands
on that document, so it
must be critical to his plans.
[ACCELERATOR]
Yeah, I get it.
If I have it, that proves
he hasn't been able
to gather all of the essential
pieces together yet.
If I had to guess,
I'd say he's missing some
important information,
and that will bridge the gap.
He probably wants to pair it
with Index's magical grimoires
to achieve his maximum effect.
Index, huh?
That's yet another connection
to some mysterious set of laws
neither I nor the dark
organizations of the world
know the full scope of.
That damn Level Zero bastard.
Just how many steps
ahead of me is he?
That's why I feel
you're in danger.
Even if you were to turn over
the parchment right now,
you could still be captured
and pressed for information.
[ACCELERATOR]
I wouldn't give them up.
What if they end up being
the essential key I need?
I might finally have
a way to free Last Order.
Okay, got it.
Misaka will retrieve
Last Order right away.
But Misaka could
really use a weapon.
What for?
Misaka appreciates your
generosity in helping her.
In return, she would strongly
advise that you give
the Russian Army a wide
berth for the time being.
[chuckles]
What exactly does
she mean by that?
Are you going to do
something foolhardy?
No extra charge.
You're welcome.
[KAMIJO]
Is that really you?
[SASHA]
Question one, if I may:
How is it that you have
come to know my name?
Hmm...
To be honest, I'm not really
sure where to begin with that.
[KAMIJO grunts]
My first answer:
I have determined
that I did not receive
a favorable response from you.
By way of further explanation,
I suspect that you are
here to capture me,
seeing as how I fled
from the ceremonial site.
No, I promise, I'm not!
Do you know who that angel is?
I thought she was you,
but that's obviously wrong!
You think it's possible
that Fiamma has used you
to summon another angel?
Please tell me.
I'm trying to stop him.
My second answer:
By the time I had awakened,
the ceremony was already over.
The ceremonial site was
built with an odd focus
on the element of fire.
[KAMIJO]
The difference is
this angel isn't living
inside Sasha's body
like what happened
at Angel Fall.
It's completely exposed.
However, if he used
Sasha to summon Misha,
the two of them
could be connected.
And that means...
[SASHA]
By way of further explanation,
the angel represented
by fire is Michael,
but the angel waiting on
the battlefield now is Gabriel.
Which is to say,
the water element--
[gasps]
I could be wrong.
Not seeing anything.
Damn it.
And there's no change in Misha.
Guess it's not gonna work.
[KAMIJO grunts]
Question two, if I may:
Do you possess the
same soul as Vasilissa?
What the hell are
you even talking about?
My third answer is this:
I do not believe ceremony
alone could control
a powerful angel.
However, to explain further,
there was one magical
item I'd never seen before.
Which item?
Specifically, a staff.
One with a cylindrical
magical item at the top,
small enough to
hold in your hand.
[KAMIJO] I wonder if that's
what he was using earlier
to remotely control Index.
If it is, he could be using
it to control Misha Kruezhev
as well.
[ACQUA]
Gabriel.
Archangel who signaled the
Annunciation of the Son of God.
He was also known for
exacting divine punishment
upon the city of wickedness.
It makes sense.
This is why Fiamma's
head became so swollen.
I wonder if he's forgotten.
Perhaps it would be
beneficial to remind him
all that I preside over
in the Right Seat of God.
Have you ever seen a more
divine power than this?
[PIETRO]
How glorious!
The victory of the
Roman Orthodox Church
has been assured.
Once the papal conclave
has been assembled,
I will become the next pope!
Cardinal Pietro Yogdis!
The public has begun
to advance on us!
We will temporarily postpone
the papal conclave.
Absolutely not!
The conclave will proceed!
But Your Eminence!
Mobilize some of the
Roman Orthodox units
to put them down!
[WARRIOR MONK 22A]
Impossible!
I can't do that, sir!
We cannot turn our arms
against our own people!
The Roman pope is among them!
Our own pope is doing
all he can to calm them.
He's managed to quiet
the rioting somewhat.
They are now on their
way into the Vatican.
There are so many of them.
We have no way of
stopping their march.
[WARRIOR MONK 22D]
We can't.
Not this man.
Our pope has chosen his course.
Who are we, then,
to stand in his way?
[PIETRO]
No... No...
No!
I am going to be the next pope!
He must die!
We have to kill him!
[ROMAN POPE]
You need not worry.
[PIETRO gasps]
I no longer identify as
the Roman pope you rival.
I am here as Matthai Reese,
just an ordinary believer
with a desire to put an end
to this war and protect
the citizens I love.
You what?
[ROMAN POPE] That which we need
to save our world from ruin
may lie beneath the
Basilica of San Pietro.
There is a vast library there
that the English Index
Librorum Prohibitorum
was once directed to,
and you're going to
give me access to it.
That library may be
the best hope we have
of countering Fiamma's attack.
I appreciate your hard work
and all that you've done
to keep the flock
of two billion together
during these trying times.
You can rest assured
that you will have my vote
in the papal conclave
when the time comes.
Please allow me to
support you however I can
in your path forward.
Remember, the goal in
this fight is to ensure
your survival.
Keep that in mind, and no
matter what challenges arise,
don't get yourself killed.
[PIETRO crying]
[SOLDIERS yell]
[MISHA] You are next.
The next one. Next time.
He is next.
[CARISSA]
What a tragedy.
It's disheartening to learn that
one of God's precious pawns
is no better than a
monster such as this.
[FEMME FATALE] A princess
is expected to represent
her nation.
How about being a
little more circumspect
regarding your actions?
Although...
I suppose I don't have
much room to talk
if I'm here beside you.
We're facing a grave situation.
The enemy is armed
with an item that boasts
a level of refinement
comparable to Curtana.
I'd even dare to
suggest it surpasses it.
Isn't there a
weapon-nullifying spell
you know how to use?
Unfortunately, this
is out of my league.
[CARISSA] And what is
Necessarius waiting for?
Can their saint not engage her?
[KNIGHT LEADER] I believe she
views treating the injured
as her first priority.
She sees combat as
nothing more than a chance
to offer her services
to those in need.
[FEMME FATALE] That shouldn't
come as a surprise.
She is a Puritan, after all.
I don't need you to remind me.
You ready for this, Frenchy?
After all the hard work
required to funnel
France's power into Durandal,
I couldn't be more
ready to finally use it.
[CARISSA] Let's see what
this monster is made of.
How humiliating for you
to learn that I have
the same level of
power as an archangel
concentrated right
here in my hand.
You should know
that the manifestation
of Misha Kruezhev
has been confirmed.
Therefore, we are expecting
you to uphold your end
and help us battle
Academy City's top forces.
First, we'll destroy the
unmanned units' command center.
[FIAMMA laughing]
Let me make sure I understand.
You have the archangel
of water at your disposal
and you want me
to damage a building
as the first attack?
[NIKOLAI]
What are you trying to say?
[FIAMMA] Just that it makes
sense now why you got no further
than bishop.
I'm surprised that you
would honestly think
someone like me would
use his own resources
for the sake of a lowly
mass of Russians.
Why, you--
Look, Fiamma, you must
know that you are
fundamentally mistaken
about something.
The Right Seat of God
does not have the ability
to use spells in the same
way that typical sorcerers do.
Isn't that the whole reason
you had to use 200 sorcerers
in the creation of
that floating fortress?
But did you ever comprehend
that those same sorcerers
are my pawns?
With just one word
from me, your fortress
would disintegrate.
And how would you handle
that, Fiamma?
[FIAMMA laughs]
If that's the best retort
you could do after giving it
serious thought, then it's
a wonder you even made bishop.
There's a good reason I went
to the trouble of acquiring
the remote-control magical item
for the 103,000 grimoires.
Hold on! You can use them?
You're able to use powers
other than those
of the Right Seat of God?
[FIAMMA] For me to become
the Person Superior to God,
I must have separate powers.
And so, while it pains me to
end our fruitful partnership,
your usefulness to me
is at an end.
Thus, I will now be disposing
of your 200 sorcerers.
Don't spend too much
time dwelling on this.
Seek to find the glory
in your defeat.
Damn it!
[yelling]
[MISHA]
Air precedence sword.
[MISHA] Wind precedence
ground and human.
[FEMME FATALE gasps]
Do you have any
idea what that was?
I couldn't even make it out.
Gabriel is known
as a message bearer.
She's diverting our
instincts and foresight.
Rely only on your
five primary senses.
Using your sixth sense will
throw your timing off.
[MISHA] You are not effective.
Not effective.
You are nothing.
The more we fight her,
the more she seems to be
relishing the battle.
You're the one who encouraged
her with that sword of yours.
[CARISSA grunts]
What's taking so long,
you barbarian?
Isn't your Curtana
supposed to be chock full
of the same amount
of archangel power
as the beast we're fighting?
Speaking in terms
of simple volume,
we seem to barely
have the upper hand here
if you haven't noticed.
We're matched in power,
but her technique is stronger.
Stop, you idiot!
[CARISSA]
I understand it now.
This is a military campaign
employing archangelic forces.
And this is the true
reason for the revolution.
Why did I force my people
into something so ridiculous?
[FEMME FATALE gasps]
[CARISSA]
I know how this looks.
It does stand to reason that if
my Curtana Second fragment
is destroyed, then my power
would be diminished.
However...
I never claimed there
was only one fragment!
I am a princess who put her
entire country on the line.
It'll take a lot more than
this to get me to tap out.
[MISHA]
The damage has been confirmed.
Over.
[CARISSA] How long do
you think it will take before
this ridiculous battle is over?
That depends on how
far they have to run
before they're considered safe.
If the other side of the
world isn't far enough,
then it will be sooner
than we think.
Such confidence.
Is that truly
the way you see me?
[MISHA] I will begin by
pressing the attack,
then smashing the enemy
into unrecognizable pieces.
All right.
I think it's about time to put
our backup plan in motion,
don't you?
I'd prefer if you didn't place
things we need in there.
Speaking as a fellow woman,
I find it disturbing.
Attention all
military on standby!
Launch the surface-to-air
missiles immediately!
I doubt that will be enough
to bring such an entity down.
I'm just buying time.
Get the wounded as far away
as possible while we can.
[KAMIJO] Why exactly is
there a monorail here?
Not that I don't appreciate
efficient transportation.
[SASHA]
My fourth answer:
I do not know why
you are asking me.
The Star of Bethlehem
is the star that signaled
the arrival of the Son of God.
Could this Fiamma person
be trying to recreate it
with only artificial means?
Um...
What the--?
[KAMIJO]
Misha Kruezhev!
Not good!
Question three, if I may ask it:
What is going on?
[KAMIJO]
Is that Hyoka Kazakiri?
[MIKOTO] There's no way
I'm not getting involved
after coming this far.
The issue now is getting close
enough to actually do something.
[MISAKA 10777]
"Big Sister,
what is that strap thing with
a frog hanging from it?"
asks Misaka, filled with
confusion and curiosity.
What do you mean?
Oh. His name is Gekota.
I got him during a
cell phone promotion
that I went to
with an idiot once.
[radio static]
"Interception of a
Russian transmission,"
Misaka reports responsibly.
"It has indicated that
a large-scale attack
is currently being carried
out against that fortress,"
says Misaka, offering
further explanation.
That's not good.
NU-AD 1967.
What does that mean?
"It's the name of the
weapon being used
to attack the fortress,"
Misaka explains,
answering your question.
[MIKOTO]
Yes, but what is it?
"A former Soviet
tactical nuclear warhead,"
reports Misaka with certainty.
[KAMIJO] Kazakiri and
Accelerator face off against
the archangel.
But not even they can stop her.
At that moment, he steps
forward, ready to do or die.
Next time, "Fuse=KAZAKIRI."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.