[TATEMIYA]
Damn it all!
Hey.
What are you doing
huddling on the floor
over there by yourself?
He said...
He said thank you
to me even though...
I did nothing to help him.
I couldn't protect him
at all with my magic,
and he thanked me.
I was thinking about his power,
and how I always thought
it was so amazing
even before I'd met him.
But I was so wrong.
It's not like that.
He can't rely on
any defensive spells.
There's no restoration
spell that can heal
even a single scratch.
He truly fights with
just his physical body.
All I could do was watch
as he was beaten.
He doesn't have any magic.
Yet he goes on living
like it's nothing.
Divine punishment should
be raining down on me.
This isn't how it should be!
You've gotta be kidding me--
this is the kind of girl
he stuck his neck
out to protect?
The man you owe your
life to is laying there
black and blue and
you're saying all you can do
is sit here and cry about it?
He threw his life away for you
and you don't lift a finger?
How do you think
he'd feel if he knew
he risked his life for nothing?
Do you hear me?
Absolutely nothing!
[ITSUWA gasps]
[TATEMIYA] Acqua of the Rear
will definitely be returning.
And while you're sitting
around doing nothing,
the clock will continue
to count down.
Every second you waste dwelling
on your own useless
regret and guilt
is time we could've
used looking for a way
to protect him.
Don't throw away
someone else's entire life
just because you've got
some problems to work out!
I'm sorry.
You want to apologize to him?
You want to make
it up to the person
you were supposed
to be protecting?
Do you want to
send him back home
and into the light of day?
Then get up and fight!
Prove to him that you're
the best woman out there
and that he was right
to risk his life for you.
He can't be moved
by your tears or accept
your apologies
if he's not alive.
Of course, if you
would prefer to repent
from in front of his grave,
then stay behind.
If not, we must fight.
Honestly.
It's unacceptable to
see someone in despair
right in front of us
and not have the ability
to extend a hand to help him.
Therefore, there's only
one thing left for us to do.
[ROMAN POPE] So you've
decided not to kill him
and have settled on
taking his right arm?
I was told the Right Seat
of God never deviated
from their policies.
You'll find no deviation here.
The boy's uniqueness
is focused in his right arm.
If we can take it from him,
then the threat he poses
will be removed.
[ROMAN POPE] I've heard
that the boy in question
does not yet know God.
And If I'm being honest,
I must admit
that I am opposed
to killing him.
Though Vento laughed
at me when I told her that.
I don't exactly
know what it is
you're expecting of me,
but I am nowhere
near as virtuous
or as philanthropic as you are.
If the time comes to
kill him, then I will.
And that's all there is to it.
They're dispersing fine
particulates into the air.
It looks like they're being
used to break down matter.
[alarm blaring]
[SAFETY OFFICIAL]
Attention: A low-oxygen alert
has been issued
for the entire third level.
Everyone, please take
shelter in your designated
building and do not
leave until instructed.
I repeat.
A low-oxygen alert
has been issued
for the entire third level.
[ROMAN POPE]
Have things taken a wrong turn?
[ACQUA] Feels more like
a trial run to probe
my combat abilities.
However, I don't sense
any human presence.
These are likely
unmanned drones.
I doubt they would've
been able to get so close
were that not the case.
I am the Right Seat of God.
I am a saint in whom
dwells the Power of God.
If any of you dare
to stand in my way,
then brace yourselves
accordingly.
[phone rings]
[ORSOLA] Hello?
Are you there, Miss Sherry?
I do hope I've called
the correct number.
[SHERRY]
Huh? Yeah, hello, Orsola.
Friendly reminder,
bulk waste is picked up
on Mondays and Fridays now.
[SHERRY]
Thanks. Get to the point.
Yes.
I've been investigating
the Right Seat of God
and Acqua of the Rear.
[SHERRY] Yeah, I heard
about that this morning.
What did you find?
It seems that before he was
known as Acqua of the Rear,
he was actually poised
to become an English knight,
if you can believe that.
[SHERRY]
Huh?
Sounds like Acqua of the
Rear has been confronted
by a squad of
unmanned powered suits
on the third level.
If he could be stopped
by mass-produced units,
we would have it all too easy.
Are we heading out?
Not yet.
We'd just be charging in
there blindly if we left now,
and I think we all know
how that would turn out.
We need to wait
for the perfect time.
Meanwhile, we will prepare
ourselves and our weapons
as best we can,
and we must craft
an optimal strategy.
[ITSUWA] Please just wait
another three hours.
It takes a little more time
to re-sharpen a blade
and make it strong
enough to fight against
a monster like that.
[TATEMIYA gasps]
What do we do now?
Why'd you have to
fire her up like that?
I had to.
Should I have just let her
sit there like an empty shell?
[ITSUWA]
Tatemiya, sir.
I'm gonna be just fine.
Can I ask you to please
let me focus for a bit?
Uh, of course.
[phone buzzing]
[ORSOLA] Oh, my, would
I happen to be speaking
to Mr. Tatemiya?
Oh, wow!
It's so comforting just
listening to your voice!
I am terribly sorry, sir,
it appears I've dialed
the wrong number.
--Goodbye.
--[TATEMIYA] No!
Don't hang up!
[ORSOLA] I have new
information regarding
Acqua of the Rear's past.
His real name is William Orwell.
He has no mercenary affiliation
in the region of England.
His principle combat
record involves
astrological brigade support,
the mission to terminate
the Orleans Order,
and the Third Princess
of Britain rescue mission.
Heh. All of those
are battlefields comparable
to the worst of nightmares.
[ORSOLA]
Because of his achievements,
he was on track to receive
a British knighthood.
But then one week
before his investment,
he mysteriously disappeared.
And naturally once
he'd resurfaced again,
he had become a known
enemy of England.
[ORSOLA] Not only was
he a strong fighter,
he also supplied knowledge
of medicinal herbs
to impoverished regions.
He showed them how
to use roots for food,
and many now
regard him as a sage.
[TATEMIYA] In other words, he's
not just a mindless savage--
he's a brilliant beast,
tough in body
and soft in thought.
[ACQUA]
They've fallen back then?
They seem surprisingly
intelligent.
Let's see...
There are still nineteen
hours until the deadline.
Have you come to
a decision yet?
Well, when you make a demand
as impossible as this one,
it tends to eliminate the need
to put too much thought into it.
You currently stand to
have two billion members
of the Roman Orthodox
Church as your enemies.
You have the chance
to avoid that for the price
of one arm.
I would think someone
with your intelligence
would call that a bargain.
The Roman Orthodoxy
is not our enemy.
It's people like you who
regularly go out of their way
to exploit and prey upon
those who earnestly
believe in God.
[ACQUA] Does this mean that our
negotiations have broken down?
[TATEMIYA] Is there anything
else it could possibly mean?
Don't forget that I am a saint.
I also possess a vast
amount of power as part of
the Right Seat of God.
If you truly understand
what that means,
and you still insist
on fighting me,
I will use this opportunity
for a demonstration.
I will prove to you that
battles are not won or lost
by good or evil, but by
strengths and weaknesses.
The least you can do
is try to force me to use
--one of my last--
--[ITSUWA grunts]
[TATEMIYA]
Um... Uh, Itsuwa?
I didn't even make it
through my sentence.
Couldn't you wait until
I'm finished speaking?
Whatever you have to say
to us can wait until later.
And that's only if your
jaw is in any condition
to still help you speak.
It may not be after
I've shattered it
and beaten you to a
thoroughly bloody pulp!
I don't believe this.
Sounds like Itsuwa's
completely snapped.
This is because of what
you said, Deputy Pope.
Oh, please.
A girl in love will
go to war with anyone
who threatens her,
including God.
[ACQUA]
I see.
How extraordinarily
gallant of you,
but I would prefer
to see you back up
such strong words
with bona fide actions.
[ITSUWA]
Is that so?
Well rest assured, there's no
need to worry about that.
You can reduce us to shreds.
But we'll still beat
the crap out of you!
And we won't stop until you
regret what you've done!
We're taking it that far?
You appear to have prepared
yourself substantially for this.
[ITSUWA]
Of course I have.
This spear has been treated
with fifteen hundred
layers of resin.
It symbolizes the rings
of age within a tree,
and the form of its hidden
spell is the fertility
of plant life.
You've done well
to ready your weapon
in such a short amount of time.
I'm impressed.
[ITSUWA grunts]
[ACQUA] And what's more
surprising is that even though
you're slow, you're still able
to keep up with my speed.
[ACQUA]
Interesting.
I see you're augmenting
each other's motor skills.
It's almost as if you
have experience fighting
against a saint
as powerful as me.
But you're still too slow!
[FEMALE VOICE 8A]
You killed me.
[FEMALE VOICE 8B]
You're a killer.
[MALE VOICE 8A]
You killed me, too, didn't you?
[FEMALE VOICE 8D]
You killed all of us.
[ACQUA]
I see. So that's what this is.
In case you haven't guessed,
the form of this spell
is a murderer's punishment.
Each wire is a redefinition
of an individual's lifeline,
and the spell penalizes
whoever breaks them.
It's very strong,
and no defensive spell
from any cultural
region can stop it.
It denotes negative resentment.
[gasps]
[ACQUA]
My attribute is Gabriel.
And to a certain extent,
I can perform the esoteric rites
of the Holy Mother Veneration.
As for acts of restriction
such as severe provisions
dealing with sin and evil,
they're meaningless against me.
What?
Would it have been
so difficult to wait
until I finished
what I was saying?
All right.
I suppose this just adds
to the thrill of the chase.
Wow, he's here already?
[ACQUA] The bodies of the Right
Seat of God are almost angelic.
So they cannot perform
magic used by normal humans.
However...
The Holy Mother veneration
spells that I possess
can effectively remove those
bindings and conditions.
I am both saint and
Right Seat of God.
I can command both
human and angelic spells.
So do not put me,
Acqua of the Rear,
on the same level as the
rest of the Right Seat of God.
Where's Acqua?
[ACQUA]
Over here.
[ITSUWA grunts]
[ACQUA]
Well, now.
Don't you think it's time to
bring an end to these warm ups?
We've both taken up
arms against each other.
There's no reason for us
not to exchange blows.
[ITSUWA]
That's true.
However, I'm not
necessarily fighting alone.
Doesn't matter. Let's go.
[GROUP yelling]
[GROUP grunts]
[ITSUWA]
[ACQUA]
Your moves are fine.
But your rhythm
is starting to lag.
[USHIBUKA. TATEMIYA yell]
Tell me... Girl.
How much longer do
you think you'll last?
Don't try to move.
You won't be able to.
We collect magical notation
from everyday items.
Then reconstruct them
for use in our spells.
Notice the pattern at your feet.
In case you were wondering,
it's blocking your
movement magic.
Tatemiya! Gather the others!
It's time for our sure bet!
Here it goes.
[yelling]
Take this!
[ITSUWA]
Saint Breakout!
Because saints possess
physical characteristics
that are very similar
to the Son of God.
They're able to generate
the same kind of powers
as the Son of God.
Using Saint Breakout
disrupts the balance
of those characteristics,
and when saints
lose that balance,
they don't lose their powers,
but they do lose
control of them,
and they can no longer move.
The Amakusa Church
once lost a saint
who left her home
out of fear of her own
power and strength.
After that happened,
every one of us took a vow.
Beyond our grueling efforts
to support her as a saint,
we must also help her
confront the problems
she found threatening.
Our solution was born
in the creation
of what we call
the Saint Breakout.
It's a specialized attack
spell specifically used
in battles with saints.
[ACQUA]
And a fine spell it is.
It's too bad I'm not
just an ordinary saint.
If I were, I might've
been finished right here.
Unfortunately for you,
a saint is only
one part of who I am.
I am also the Right Seat of God.
[ITSUWA grunts]
[GROUP yelling]
[ACQUA]
This is pointless.
Even after combining
your forces and planning
such a strong strategy,
this is where you end up?
At least you still
have a little time left
before your deadline.
I'll give you a choice.
Either find a way to get
me the young man's arm,
or become a stain
on the road right here.
Then you leave me no choice.
Very well, then.
Looks like you get
to continue living.
[ORSOLA] It appears that William
Orwell has used an explosive
amount of power as a saint
since his days as a mercenary.
Currently, he wields power
in the Roman Orthodoxy's
organization,
the Right Seat of God.
He also had another name.
A sorcerer's moniker
he crafted for himself.
Flere Two-One-Zero.
Flere is a Latin word,
the infinitive "to weep."
His style of fighting
appears to be self-taught,
but his method of moving
around during combat
involves a spell that
uses water as a teleport.
Obviously, there's
a common thread here.
If the name "Acqua of the Rear"
is associated with
the four archangels,
it would fall under Gabriel,
and its attribute would
be water, so it fits.
Heh. I see, so that means
he's at a height normal humans
can't reach no matter
how hard they try.
[ACQUA] I've heard that the
Amakusa Church once had a saint
among them whose
philosophy was to kill
using only a single
strike of the sword.
However, I also heard
that this particular saint's
disposition was that she
absolutely hated fighting.
Do you have the nerve
it takes to fight me?
[KANZAKI]
Well, that's interesting.
Apparently, I'm a
more childish person
than I ever
thought myself to be.
I was taught anger
was one of the seven sins,
but I refuse to lose
any sleep over it.
I won't let his
resolve be for nothing.
That alone is enough
motivation for me.
You don't need to
worry about my nerves.
Let's go.
Single Flash!
[ACQUA] Talent alone can be
profoundly cruel, can't it?
Even though we both
use the same method,
our results are
vastly different.
[KANZAKI]
Not true.
My foundation is
entirely Amakusan,
and my teachers are
all of my friends.
Therefore, I cannot permit you
to denigrate them in any way.
Moreover, if someone
is conscious
of how much power they have
and yet still ruthlessly
brings it to bear
against an ordinary
high-school student,
then it doesn't matter
if they're a saint.
Such a person has lost any
right to look down on others.
I'm not impressed.
Even a foot soldier will
unwittingly encounter a tank.
It's the way of the battlefield.
And if he's not prepared,
he'll be crushed to pieces.
That's just your
way of thinking.
That's right, and you
and your comrades
are the ones who
stepped onto my territory.
Or, was the boy
perhaps unknowingly
dragged into this
by someone else?
If you knew he was
just an ordinary person,
then why did you
use your saintly power
against him?
And why would I tell you
my reasons for fighting?
[ACQUA] Show me yours first,
Saint of the Far East!
I want to know that those
are more than just words.
I want to see your
reason within your sword.
See if you can show me
what it is without words!
[KAMIJO]
Where am I?
Oh, man.
What happened to me?
[KAMIJO]
That's right.
The fight against Acqua
is probably still going on.
I'm sorry, Index.
I'll apologize to you later.
But right now,
just let me do what
needs to be done.
[KAMIJO]
A shot exerted by the chosen one
blows dignity to bits.
After all the despair,
will the Priestess's cries
get through?
Next time,
"Holy Mother Veneration."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.