[ITSUWA]
Seriously?
The key to a
long-distance relationship
is in whether or not
the couple remains
in each other's memory.
"Steal his love Special?"
Tip number one:
"A stronger woman's charms
will overwrite his memory"?
The sexy fallen angel outfit!
So then the whole thing
was an all-out mental,
technical, and physical
boob tactic?
Well... It's hard to
compete with the Priestess.
I have to turn things around!
[gasps]
That product I heard about.
The Great Fairy
Revealing Maid outfit!
[ITSUWA gasps]
What am I even saying?
I could never wear
something that revealing!
[KNIGHT LEADER] As for the
events happening in October,
I believe the most suitable
one will be the ball
held at the Queen House.
Though the social class
might be a bit dodgy.
Wait just a minute,
Knight Leader.
Going to those kinds of
soirees and balls with you
sort of has the
implication of being a date.
I assure you,
I was simply responding
to your request that I instruct
you in English behavior.
I had assumed you were
starting to explore
how to live like a lady.
Wherever did you hear
something like that?
Hmm... Well, that's interesting.
So the bit about the fallen
angel sexy maid was false?
[KANZAKI gasps]
No, but I was only...
I would not consider
such conduct to be ladylike.
[KANZAKI coughs]
Well, anyway.
Can you tell me what's
happening with the Eurotunnel?
We don't know when
it will be restored.
[KANZAKI]
How unfortunate.
I've been hearing that
tensions with France
have been rising, too.
I'd say that's accurate.
They seem to be having
trouble convincing the hawks
in Parliament to forgo
their anti-French
pre-emptive strike.
We also have a number
of domestic organizations
who are wanting to take
advantage of the chaos
to stir up unrest.
[KNIGHT LEADER]
Enemies without and within.
We've both got a lot
to consider right now.
[MIKOTO] That was a completely
ridiculous thing for me to say!
Listen.
I know all about it, okay?
I know you have amnesia.
I can fight too, you know.
I'm serious!
I can be of help to you!
[MIKOTO yelps]
[whining]
Oh, hey, Zapper.
I don't mean to interrupt.
What're you doing?
Just the usual,
not that it matters.
You know, kicking
vending machines. Hmph.
Right. Okay.
So, how are you doing?
Are you over your
injuries already?
Yeah, close enough.
So you, uh...
I guess you really did
find out, didn't you?
I'd appreciate it if you
wouldn't tell anyone else
if that's all right?
Yeah. Sure.
And about this vending
machine-kicking hobby you have.
Maybe be a little more
discreet if you're gonna do it
in public while wearing a skirt.
You're being unusually
quiet about this.
[MIKOTO]
What is happening right now?
Why am I so uncomfortable?
My heart feels awkwardly cozy.
Um, hey...
[MIKOTO yelling]
[KAMIJO]
Was that necessary?!
What is going on
with Misaka lately?
Wait. I hope this
doesn't mean Index
will be acting
out of sorts, too.
[TV ANCHOR 10A] The fallout from
the explosion in the...
And Index is exactly the same.
Toma, what are you making
us for supper tonight?
A cup of yakisoba.
It's been a long day.
A long day how?
Give it a minute.
It'll be ready soon.
[pounding noise]
What... What was
that loud noise?
Uh, don't worry about it.
[splattering]
[INDEX]
Toma...!
You're the biggest
klutz that's ever lived.
Here, this one's for you.
It's yummy.
[KAMIJO yells]
[phone buzzing]
Yeah? What's going on,
Tsuchimikado?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Hey, Kami!
This is kind of a
long conversation.
Is now a good time?
Actually, no,
I just witnessed a miracle.
Keep it short, would ya?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Sure, I can do that!
In short, get yourselves
to Britain right now.
Wait, why?
[BOTH gag]
[KAMIJO]
What is this?
Knockout gas?
[INDEX] Do I want beef or fish?
Do I want beef or fish?
I know you're excited
about the food.
But could you please
try to keep it down?
[INDEX growls]
Hey, you never explained
why we had to drop everything
and go to Britain right away.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I was told they
were in some huge
magical trouble over there,
so they thought it'd
be best to call you in
as a state official.
And I'm sure there was
a reason they wanted me
to come with you,
but I don't know what it is.
Know what I just remembered?
We're getting airplane food!
What time is it gonna be here?
Sometime after nine
o' clock, I'd guess.
We got the later meal
because it was cheaper.
It's better than getting
on that plane
that Tsuchimikado sent for us!
[INDEX growls]
[FLIGHT ATTENDANT] Due to the
impact of the Eurotunnel...
So does that mean we're
not in Britain yet?
I think they said France.
I heard them talking
about this on the news to--
Look!
Do you see that man out
there in the work uniform
eating a big sandwich?
It's not fair!
I want to eat something too!
[whines] I'm so hungry.
[FLIGHT ATTENDANT]
Excuse me, sir?
Yes ma'am?!
What seems to be
the trouble over here?
There's no problem.
We're okay!
[laughing]
[KAMIJO]
I have to wonder, though.
Is it worth it to transport
daily necessities on a plane?
These particular
items are coming from
overseas countries.
So apparently there
are a lot of things
they cannot always
procure in Britain.
From what I can
tell on this flight,
I get the impression the
container includes liquid foods.
Liquid foods?
[FLIGHT ATTENDANT] Yes.
I don't know what it's called,
but there's a disease
that renders those affected
unable to eat solid food,
so they get their nutrients
from liquid options.
Nutrients. Food.
Airplane. Inflight.
Do I want beef or fish?
No, beef and fish!
Beef and fish!
[KAMIJO] I told you it's
either one or the other!
[FLIGHT ATTENDANT] I'll bring
you something right away!
[MUSSET] Damn, the seat
was taken by someone on
the waiting list.
What do I do?
Is my food ready yet?
It's been a while.
What the--?
Isn't that door
supposed to be closed?
Does that mean you saw it?
[KAMIJO grunts]
Captain. Emergency.
What do you mean, terrorist?
I mean that we've
received a warning
from the control tower
that a member of
a French anti-English
organization
has managed to board
the plane somehow.
And if certain demands
aren't met right away,
the plane and everyone
on it will crash and burn.
[KAMIJO]
Seriously?
Yes, these terrorists
are demanding
that the major airlines'
customer management systems
be destroyed.
Their goal is to
completely eliminate
all of the routes into England.
The blood spatter
you saw earlier
came from one of my colleagues.
We believe the terrorist
was responsible for that.
Wait a minute, you're
not trying to suggest
I'm the culprit here, are you?
No, of course not.
No one was thinking that.
Do you think just the
two of you can handle
finding this criminal?
Seems like you'd need
as much help as possible.
I'll back you up.
I don't want this
chaos to keep spreading.
Last thing we need is
an amateur milling around
on his own.
Could you take
responsibility for the lives
of five hundred passengers?
[CAPTAIN 10A]
Go ahead and toss him in.
Damn!
What the--?
It doesn't seem like
Toma could've gone very far.
Damn it!
How did the connector
get broken?
If I can't feed the crash
stabilizer the disrupt program--
[INDEX]
Did you say "crash?"
What are you doing with that?
[MUSSET] You know what's
nice about knives carved
from animal bone?
They don't set off airport
security metal detectors.
Get up.
If you give me any
trouble, I'll stab you.
[footsteps]
[MUSSET]
Get in there!
Unless you'd rather be stabbed!
--[INDEX yelps]
--[KAMIJO] Is that Index?
Damn it!
[KAMIJO grunts]
[KAMIJO yelling]
[INDEX gagging]
[KAMIJO grunting]
[MUSSET grunts]
[KAMIJO]
Hold it!
[INDEX coughs]
[KAMIJO]
Index!
You again! Hey!
Tell me what the hell
just happened here!
[CAPTAIN 10A] So he's
attacking the passengers now.
Damn.
What is this terrorist
trying to do?
"The crash
stabilization device."
What do you mean?
I think Index overheard
that guy saying it.
This aircraft is
built with sensors
that can auto-detect the
shocks from a belly landing.
It will instantly shut
down all the engines
to prevent an explosion.
So then, if that malfunctions...
The aircraft would crash.
I get the gist of
what happened here.
And I'm sorry we
couldn't get to you
before that creep did,
but I'm glad it didn't
end up worse than this.
I don't want to risk
the passengers' lives
by sending them into a panic.
I can't have them
making assumptions.
So we'll have to keep
you sequestered for now--
You've gotta be kidding me!
Risking passengers'
lives, my ass!
I stayed in this closet
and did everything
you jerks asked me to,
and look what happened!
My friend was assaulted
and could've been killed!
And now you want me to wait
here until he comes back?
The witnesses are the
ones in the most danger!
[KAMIJO]
Where is he?
Where did he go?
[KAMIJO]
Damn it.
I could spot him right
away if he'd just
do something suspicious.
[KAMIJO]
All right.
[alarm ringing]
Does anybody know
what's going on?
What's with the alarm?
Are we losing altitude?
[COPILOT 10A]
No sir, the alarm was sounded
from a manual button
in the cabin.
[COPILOT 10A]
Emergency, Captain!
[CAPTAIN 10A]
Great, what is it now?
I don't know, damn it,
but I'm losing control,
and I can't do this alone!
Can you come back here?
[COPILOT 10A]
The fuel gauge!
It shouldn't be
dropping like that!
My only guess is there's
a hole in the tank!
At this rate, we're not
gonna make it to the airport!
Worst case scenario,
we'll need to prepare
for an emergency
landing on a highway!
Captain, instructions?
Damn it! Just hold on,
I'll be right there!
It sounds as if
that illusion you set up
is finally starting
to have an effect.
Creating an illusion with
just the gauge reading
is much simpler
than it may seem.
So they're not
landing at an airport.
You're going to force them
down on a country highway
with few buildings nearby?
Yes, unless of course
you'd prefer to have
it explode in the city
or a residential area.
Where can they make
an emergency landing?
It would have to
be a major highway
that leads from
London to Scotland.
Let's see...
Between Kendal and Carlisle.
[LAURA] Then we'll need to
block the pertinent highway
as soon as we can,
and shut down all the roads
that feed into it, as well.
I don't mind that you're
speeding things along,
but what are you going
to do if that airliner
breaks up in midair?
If that happens, we'll
have to at least recover
the List of Prohibited Books,
who is currently aboard.
And we'll be able to
catch at least one person
on the ground.
Speaking from the
bottom of my heart...
I hope you die an early death.
[LAURA chuckles]
What's going on?
We're losing altitude now.
Not good!
[MUSSET]
Increase our altitude!
Unless you want me
to kill all your passengers,
you'll regain
altitude immediately!
[CAPTAIN 10A]
I can't.
At this rate, we won't make
it to Edinburgh Airport!
In fact, it's very possible
the engines themselves
could explode!
[MUSSET]
Damn it! I'll kill you!
Listen very closely.
If you don't regain altitude
in exactly three minutes,
I'll kill every
passenger one by one!
[LAURA]
Well, this is unusual.
What do you mean?
It appears that the airliner
has gained altitude.
I assume this means they've
aborted their landing.
Archbishop,
there's an emergency!
We've identified a
large-scale obstruction
coming from Scotland.
Obstruction? What kind?
[SISTER 10B] It appears that our
illusion is being intercepted
by a third party.
It's being nullified from
within Britain of all places?
This oversight is entirely
on you, Archbishop.
Yes, I understand that.
Just to be safe,
I'd like to put things into
place with Sky Bus 365.
Be sure we have everything.
All right.
I'll need a transport.
The altitude.
It's been restored.
[KAMIJO]
So this is where you've been!
You're mine!
[MUSSET grunts]
You have a problem with that?
[CAPTAIN 10A]
Attention passengers,
we are safely headed
for Edinburgh Airport.
We are terribly sorry
for any inconvenience
this has caused you.
Is something wrong, Toma?
I don't understand. Why now?
Why did he wait to act?
Wouldn't it be
because he was looking
to create a problem
over British airspace?
[KAMIJO]
If he had done it right away,
he could have given himself
more time to negotiate
and still shaken
Britain up a bit.
He's gone now.
So it doesn't matter
anymore, right?
Should we still be
worried about him?
There has to be a reason
he waited until the end
of the flight to cause
any kind of disturbance.
There's still another one.
The cargo hold!
He waited until we were
finished loading cargo
at the airport in Paris.
Then he attacked.
And that's because he
was waiting for his buddy,
who was tossed
on with the cargo.
He was waiting for insurance.
Is there only one way to get in?
Uh, yes.
This stowaway terrorist
is most likely armed.
So that means we
shouldn't charge him
right after opening the door.
[FLIGHT ATTENDANT] But there
aren't any other ways in or out.
Could we use that air duct?
[FLIGHT ATTENDANT]
No way.
It's not like in the movies.
There's not enough space
for a person to get through.
No, it's just right.
What are you going to do, Toma?
There were coffee
and tea bottles
in the free drinks
station, weren't there?
Do you think you could
bring me some of those?
But I need you to make them
as hot as possible first.
Negotiations must have failed.
Not my problem. I'm bringing
this plane down either way.
[EIKER]
Is that tea?
[KAMIJO]
Hey there, terrorist!
Ever heard of thermal expansion?
[KAMIJO grunts]
[EIKER yells]
[KAMIJO yelling]
I'll take this plane down!
Back off!
Thanks to the
Eurotunnel explosion,
our great France has
been forced to sustain
some massive losses!
And that's why we
will stop at nothing
to make sure they
suffer the same damage!
We're not just blocking
their land routes,
they'll lose their
air routes, too!
Forget about whether
it's Britain or France
who's at fault!
Allies like you shouldn't
be fighting each other!
Did you know those are
all full of liquid food?
France is sending it to sick
people in Britain for relief!
They're trying to help!
Isn't that the relationship
Britain and France have?
There are still idiots
wherever you go.
I'm not willing to let
these idiots off the hook
just because you
say they're mixed in
with some good people.
No, don't!
[EIKER laughs]
[STIYL]
For crying out loud.
Ever the amateur, I see.
[KAMIJO gasps]
[EIKER grunting]
[STIYL] It's ten minutes
to Edinburgh Airport.
I think he should be able
to survive for that long.
[EIKER gasping]
For heaven's sake, you're
supposed to be watching over her
in some fashion or another.
I'd appreciate it if you'd at
least show that much resolve.
Hang in there.
[RADIO HOST 10A]
Now for an update.
The jumbo jet Sky Bus
365 has just landed
at Edinburgh Airport.
Didn't expect that. Sounds like
the plane landed safely.
And at the airport.
Well, yeah, but only because
of the stealth transport
that was sent in using
Academy City's technology.
I think Britain may be
stretched to the limit.
Whenever I channel any
magic, my body starts
to get tingly all over!
Put on your game faces.
It looks like we're
about to break up
the very paradigm
that is Britain.
[KAMIJO] Multiple threads
intertwine around
ceremonial accouterments.
The true purpose of the
sorcerers known as "New Light"
is revealed.
Next time, "British Labyrinth."
When science and
magic cross paths,
a story is born.