[door opens]
[AOGAMI]
Bad news!
The school store is
all sold out of bread!
And the cafeteria is packed!
We're too late.
How could this happen?
Um...
It's my fault for asking the
teacher a dumb question.
We must act.
Or we'll have to
endure afternoon classes
with empty stomachs.
[AOGAMI]
We can't!
We're still growing
boys and girls
in need of nourishment!
That would just be cruel!
[STUDENT 07A]
What now?
[STUDENT 07B]
We get food from someplace else.
[STUDENT 07C]
But...
Do we dare?
It's the only way.
All right, everyone!
Make a break for
the convenience store!
[CLASSMATES]
Yeah!
[FUKIYOSE]
Let's keep our numbers down.
If we all leave school at once,
the teachers will notice.
We need to be quiet,
and we need to be quick.
This operation is a
race against the clock.
[KAMIJO]
That's for sure.
If they're already sold out of
lunches when we get there,
then all of this is
for nothing, right?
[phone vibrates]
[STUDENT 07A]
A Team has failed to escape.
[STUDENT 07B]
B Team is eliminated.
It's up to you. Good luck!
[KAMIJO] Damn it!
We're the only ones left!
[horn beeps]
[KAMIJO]
Saigo?
I bet he's not forced
to go hungry!
Let it go, Kami!
If he catches us now,
it'll mean everyone's lunches!
Oh, crap!
Sorry. I'm going.
[AOGAMI]
Huh? [grunts]
Hey, what are you doing?
Come back!
[AOGAMI gasps]
[yells]
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
He's coming!
Our best bet's to split up.
[KAMIJO]
Uh... Right!
Oh, of course
he comes after me!
[KAMIJO]
Huh?
No, you don't!
[KAMIJO]
Wait! No!
Hold on a second, Itsuwa!
[ITSUWA]
Huh?
I really am sorry!
I thought it was a
Roman Orthodox plot.
Oh. No, it's okay.
Saigo's really tough.
They say he once
caught a giant boulder
with his bare hands.
He'll be back on
his feet in no time.
[ITSUWA]
Well, that's good.
But still, could I have
been any more useless?
Hey, you were totally useful.
[KAMIJO] So, what brings
you here, anyway?
[ITSUWA]
Huh? Oh.
[KAMIJO]
Hey, what are you doing?
Okay.
Tell me, does the name
Acqua of the Rear
sound familiar to you at all?
Uh, yeah.
He's with the Right Seat of God.
I think.
I met him when I was
fighting that Vento woman.
You see, the thing is,
he's issued a challenge
to the English Puritan Church,
and to Academy City, too.
[KAMIJO]
What kind of challenge?
In the next few days,
he's going to pulver--
I mean, stage an
attack on Toma Kamijo.
What? But why me?
[ITSUWA]
Isn't it obvious?
You're responsible for thwarting
the Roman Orthodox Church's
darkest schemes,
over and over again!
You're making it
sound bigger than it is.
Come on. I'm a high schooler.
[KAMIJO]
Honestly.
First there was
the front, then the left,
and now the rear, too?
Are they ever gonna
give it a rest?
Well, if they're targeting me,
then they must have too much
free time on their hands.
According to the report,
he's extremely dangerous.
He's also said to
possess saintly powers.
Um, okay.
[ITSUWA] But you have
nothing to worry about.
Even if Acqua were to attack,
I promise your life
wouldn't be in danger!
So, why exactly are you here?
To save you!
I'm your bodyguard now.
Night and day!
[USHIBUKA]
Damn it, Itsuwa.
She's got the perfect
opportunity to go on the attack,
and it's all "business this"
and "business that."
Not only is it a shameful waste,
it looks like she's not
even aware of the weapons
she's packing.
[KOUYAGI]
What do you mean, weapons?
Why, I'm referring to
the "Undercover Bra
Busters Theory"!
Interesting hypothesis,
Your Holiness,
but is there any basis for it?
[ISAHAYA] If you're just
making random predictions,
then you're better off saving
them for the horse races.
[chuckles] The "Itsuwa
Massage Operation"
that I conducted yielded
promising results,
and I believe you'll agree
they support my theory.
Her shoulder stiffness
index was forty.
However, factoring in
clothing and equipment
to calculate the load
on her shoulders,
a stiffness index
greater than thirty-seven
can only be explained
by one thing!
So you mean...
Yes. Something's
causing that stiffness.
And thus, my "Undercover
Bra Buster Theory"
is proven.
[USHIBUKA]
Huh?!
[TSUSHIMA sighs]
That said, however,
if I wish to explore
this theory to the fullest,
I'm going to need a new tactic.
[KOUYAGI] But you know Itsuwa,
she's never gonna make
the first move.
Which is why I've come up
with a super-secret plan.
Are you ready?
I call it "Operation Field
Sharpshooter Free Kick"!
[MIKOTO]
I can't believe he has amnesia.
For how long now?
What the--?
[KAMIJO yells]
[ITSUWA gasps]
[GROUP cheers]
[MIKOTO]
Listen up.
I've got enough unpleasant
stuff on my mind already.
I don't need any additional
stress right now, okay?
They're gone?
[ITSUWA]
Um, are you all right?
[KAMIJO]
Yeah, I think so.
Just a little dazed is all.
Really? Come on!
Oh, Misaka.
[MIKOTO] How long were you
planning to keep your face
buried in there,
you disgusting pig?
Get back!
[KAMIJO]
No! Stop! Let's go!
Hey! I'm not done with you yet!
Toma...!
You wanna tell me what
you're doing with Itsuwa
of the Amakusa Church?
[KAMIJO]
Oh, um...
The thing is, well...
What's the best way
for me to explain this?
There's a problem.
The Right Seat of God is after--
[KAMIJO yells]
Look, I'm the one who
Acqua's going after, right?
So we don't really need
to tell Index, do we?
Itsuwa?
Yes, I heard you!
Loud and clear, don't worry.
Oh, sorry.
That hurt?
[ITSUWA]
N-No.
It's fine.
[KAMIJO gasps]
[KAMIJO]
What the hell is going on here?
Is there some kind of
sinister power at work,
trying to make Index so angry
that she can't function?
Um...
Hey, Index. Can you hear me?
I'm not really sure
what's happening,
and I can't believe
I'm asking this,
but will you please bite
me before you explode?
If you bleed off some of
your anger little by little,
I think it will reduce
the chances of my head
being bitten off entirely.
[ITSUWA gasps]
I know!
I have the perfect thing
for your sweet little kitty.
Premium-grade bonito!
Wait, did you go shopping?
But when?
Yes. I may be here
acting as your bodyguard,
but that doesn't mean I'll
just help myself to your food.
I wouldn't want
to be a freeloader.
Wait. What? Hey!
Why do I feel like
there's been an enormous
shift of some kind?
If you think hard,
I bet you'll find the answer.
Who is it that's left me
to do everything around here
and not once pitched
in to help with even
a single chore?
Right. I see.
And I'm sorry about that.
I'll try harder--Wait!
Why are you trying
to change the subject?
You'll find all the pots
and saucepans right here.
Spices and stuff there.
Great!
[KAMIJO] I don't know
why she's doing this,
and I'm not even gonna ask.
Thank you, Itsuwa,
from the bottom of my heart!
Amazing!
Somebody else is cooking,
and I managed to avoid
getting bitten by Index.
Could this day get any bett--
[KAMIJO yelling]
[KAMIJO]
A girl making me dinner.
What's with that
dopey smile on your face?
You look like you've just
witnessed some kind of
miracle being performed.
[ITSUWA]
Oh, no, please don't.
The chikuwa isn't ready yet.
[INDEX] Sorry, I hear
what you're saying.
But I can't stop
my mouth from eating!
[KAMIJO] Don't stand between
a man and his dream!
[INDEX yells]
See that?
That's what crashing
at someone's place
should look like.
Index...
I'm curious, is there a reason
you do nothing but eat, sleep,
and watch TV?
What time is it?
I think the rerun of Magical
Powered Kanamin Integral
is about to start soon!
You need to do some work
around here from now on!
Get up and clean the bathroom!
[INDEX]
Okay.
[crash]
[MAIKA]
I smell it. I can smell it.
No way! No more weirdos!
There! In that miso soup!
[ITSUWA gasps]
You've added in
dried scallop powder
as the secret ingredient,
haven't you?
What? How did you know that?
My own mother doesn't even
know my secret ingredient!
Now to try it.
What flavor!
I can't be here anymore!
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Hey! What's going on?
Why are you throwing out
my white cream stew?
[MAIKA] Because it doesn't
come close to being as great
as the miso soup I'm
about to make for us!
[yells]
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Okay,
but there was nothing wrong
with that stew!
Why do I feel like
I know that voice?
Oh, uh...
Listen, keep yourself sane
and don't pay attention
to those nutjobs.
--[explosion]
--[INDEX screams]
[KAMIJO]
All right.
How did you break the tub
with just a sponge and cleanser?
Well, you told me to
scrub it hard, so I did.
Maybe I did too good of a job?
That's not it.
You poured all of that
concentrated cleanser
into the hot water inlet!
But isn't that what
cleanser's supposed to do?
Clean stuff?
[KAMIJO] Not if you burn the
inside of the hot water heater
and nearly cause a fire!
Um, sorry, but I think I
have an idea that might help.
For a change of pace, maybe
we could go to a bathhouse?
A bathhouse?
[KAMIJO]
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean for you to pay
the rental fee for the bike.
[ITSUWA]
Don't worry about it.
I've got plenty of money
to use for things like this!
[INDEX]
Hey, Toma,
why do I get the feeling
that there's more
to our seating arrangements
than you're admitting?
Huh? What are
you talking about?
The sidecar's the most
comfortable seat on the bike.
So poor old Kamijo
rode in the back
and let you sit there
in the spirit of ladies first.
[KAMIJO]
Whoa!
With Academy City
this empty at night
and the road conditions so good,
I might just accidentally
start speeding.
[KAMIJO] Whoa!
You're definitely speeding!
Slow down before you kill us!
[INDEX gasps]
Toma, look up there!
It's the biggest jungle
gym I've ever seen!
[ITSUWA]
The 22nd School District
was developed underground,
so it can't rely on
wind or solar power
like other districts can.
They had to build
those power stations
you see above it.
Plus, it uses so
much electricity
that there are other power
generating provisions
laid out all over the district.
[KAMIJO] So this spa
resort we're going to...
What level is it on?
[ITSUWA]
Let's see.
It's supposed to be
on the third level.
Wait, hold on.
A bathhouse underground?
Really?
Yep, apparently so.
Should be interesting.
The 22nd School District's
divided into
ten underground levels,
and we're headed to the third.
Oh.
[ITSUWA] Looks like the
third level is up ahead.
[INDEX]
Oh...!
The roof of this level is
actually an enormous screen,
like you'd find
in a planetarium.
It's set to display the
night sky in real time.
[INDEX]
It's beautiful!
Is this entire place
really underground?
It looks like there's a river
over there, and even a forest.
You gotta admit,
Academy City really is amazing.
Look, you can see it from here!
That's it!
[MIKOTO]
Ugh. This is so annoying.
Here I was worried about him,
and what does that
idiot go and do?
[MIKOTO]
One adult, please.
How many times
do I need to come?
That's really all I'm getting?
I have to say, they're
not making it very easy
to collect stamps.
I wonder if I could
get two stamps
if I bring Kuroko
with me next time.
Bring me, Sissy!
Nope, forget it.
I'll collect them all on my own!
[CHILD 07A laughing]
[MIKOTO] Huh? What the heck do
you think you're doing here?!
Shh! Bath time is quiet time!
[INDEX] You don't need your
towel in the water, you know.
Right.
[MIKOTO gasps]
Wait! You're the girl
that idiot clung to
because of the soccer ball!
No! It's not what
it looked like!
You see...
It was an accident.
I was just lucky that my
breasts happened to be there.
It wasn't like I planned it.
[MIKOTO] I wonder if
either of those girls know
about that idiot
and his amnesia.
I mean, he'd probably tell
them sooner than he'd tell me.
Not that I care
one way or the other!
Why am I getting so
upset about somebody
so obnoxious?
[sighs] He really is nothing
but a nuisance.
[INDEX] Uh-oh, looks like the
short-haired one is going under.
We have to save her!
Aw, man. that's really hot.
I should've gone
with iced coffee.
[ITSUWA]
Enjoying the evening breeze?
It's nice, huh?
[KAMIJO] It's so easy to
forget you're underground.
In that case, do you
want to take a little walk?
[KAMIJO] Sure. Wait...
But what about Index?
[ITSUWA] Last I saw
she was running around
in the all-you-can-eat section.
She was?
Well, then I guess we
don't have to worry
about losing her.
You know, this really
is an amazing place.
How many times have
you been here before?
This is her big chance.
There's definitely
a nice mood happening.
Well, Your Holiness.
What do you wanna do now?
What? About the
evening date operation?
No. I mean about
Acqua of the Rear.
Oh.
We've received reports about
him from Academy City, but...
[USHIBUKA]
I know. It's hard to believe.
It would be strange
for all three factions
to be scrambling.
And over someone like Toma
Kamijo, you know what I mean?
I get the feeling there
must be some information
that we're still unaware of.
[USHIBUKA]
In other words,
if we're serious about
protecting this guy...
Then yeah.
Chances are good we've still got
some investigating left to do.
[TATEMIYA]
The streets have been cleared.
How could I have
let this happen?
I'm pretty sure we've been had.
[KAMIJO]
I was wondering...
Where are the rest
of the Amakusa folks?
[ITSUWA] You may not be
able to see them right now,
but they're there.
Most likely watching
us from a distance.
It's too bad the priestess
couldn't be here.
It would be like having a
one-woman army on our side.
[KAMIJO] Oh, yeah? Kanzaki's
really that incredible?
[ITSUWA]
Of course she is!
She's one of not even twenty
saints in the whole world!
Any trouble you may have,
the priestess can
resolve instantly!
Oh, really? That's impressive.
Well, I guess she did
fight that archangel--
you know, the Power of God.
[ITSUWA]
She fought an archangel?!
[ITSUWA] I know that I'm not
supposed to let my guard down,
but I just...
[KAMIJO]
Itsuwa? Is something wrong?
No! Nothing!
I mean, everything's
fine, really!
I was just noticing that
there don't seem to be
very many people around.
And would you just look
at that beautiful view!
[KAMIJO]
Yeah, I know.
This is what Academy City
looks like at night.
It feels a whole
lot more deserted
than it should be, though.
Hey...
[ITSUWA, KAMIJO gasp]
[ACQUA]
I gave you a warning.
You had plenty of time
and a number of options
before you.
And yet, this is
the path you chose.
The one you decided it was
worth risking your life on.
[ITSUWA]
Isn't that...
It's Tatemiya's!
[ACQUA]
I truly want to know.
Were you honestly incapable of
finding a better alternative
--than this?
--It's Acqua!
[ITSUWA gasps]
[KAMIJO]
Itsuwa!
[ACQUA]
Our world is being disrupted.
I've come to eliminate the
source of the disturbance.
Is now the best time
for you to be concerned
about others?
[KAMIJO yells]
[ACQUA] Do you honestly
believe one of you
has the ability to
challenge me and win
when your entire organization
combined could not?
I still have my pride.
I must fight!
[ITSUWA yells]
--[KAMIJO] Itsuwa!
--[ACQUA] Your right arm.
If you will offer it to me,
I'll let you leave this
place with your life.
No, screw that!
I see.
Well, in that case,
I'll have to give you
a little more insight
into the reality of things.
[ITSUWA]
Kamijo!
Hold on!
Please stay with me!
I'll heal you with my
restoration magic!
[ITSUWA]
It isn't working.
Are you finished yet?
Hmm. I guess not.
I'll have to crush
you both together.
[KAMIJO]
Thank you, Itsuwa.
Because of your
restoration magic...
...I'm starting to feel
a little bit better now.
Please don't!
[KAMIJO yelling]
I admire your courage.
[KAMIJO yells]
[ACQUA]
I'll give you one day.
You may take that time to
consider my earlier proposition.
Cut off your own right
arm and deliver it to us.
If you do that,
I will let you live.
I'll wait for one day.
[KAMIJO] Saintly power
shakes the world's surface,
thundering to the lower levels.
After everything is plucked
apart and strength is used up,
what sort of strike
does Itsuwa make?
Next time, "Saint Breakout."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.