My friends, it is our
responsibility to fight
to defend the world and
every person living in it.
Right now, there is
environmental destruction
happening all over.
Petroleum and fossil
fuel shortages
are only the tip of the iceberg.
We now know that this is
the result of Academy City's
peculiar brand of
science and technology.
Unless we can find a way
to stem the sedition
of this unregulated technology,
we can say for certain.
Every living thing on this
planet will be exterminated.
Academy City needs to enact
a total freeze on all projects
they are carrying out around
the world immediately.
Furthermore, we demand
that they disclose details
of their state-of-the-art
technology to us!
Are you kidding?
[RUSSIAN PRESIDENT]
All we want is peace.
If they reject our proposal,
then we will have no choice
but to declare Academy
City an evil entity.
They are not attempting
to integrate with the world.
They're exclusively concerned
with their own interests
as they expose all
other living creatures
in their environment to danger.
This cannot be tolerated.
We will give them until
October 19th at midnight,
Moscow Standard Time,
to provide an answer.
If by that time we have
not received a response,
we'll have just one option.
We must assume that
their intent is hostile
and commence an
invasion immediately.
And no weapon
will be restricted.
[HAMAZURA]
We have no other choice.
Stay calm.
I absolutely will not
hurt the cashier.
Everything I need
is inside the register.
The gun is only a prop.
This is a stick-up!
Hands above your--
I mean it, guys. Hands up!
[CASHIER 18A whimpers]
[gunshots]
Hamazura?
Well, the cashier
was so grateful to me
for saving her life in there,
she gave me this to say thanks.
"Where are we?"
asks Misaka Misaka,
as she looks at these
strange surroundings.
We're on a train.
[LAST ORDER chuckles]
It's you!
It's been so long since
I've seen your face.
[ACCELERATOR]
How did this happen?
And for what reason?
Why does the kid have
to go through all this?
[crash]
Are they coming after us?
"Just don't start fighting
again the way you did
before, okay? Please?" asks
Misaka Misaka, staring at you.
Really? All right,
fine, I promise.
[ACCELERATOR]
I'm tired of you scrap heaps!
I'm only gonna ask you once
to stop getting on my nerves!
[INDEX]
Yes. I am the magical library.
I am affiliated with
Necessarius, 0th Parish
of the English Puritan Church.
My name is Index.
[KAMIJO] I have to destroy that
remote-controlled magical item
as soon as possible.
But never mind that.
Lessar, what the heck do you
think you're doing out here?
[LESSAR]
Don't worry.
I didn't come by order
of the British Royal Family,
nor do I have a grudge against
this Fiamma of the Right guy
or anything of that nature.
I was just thinking that
if it's not exactly
in the best interest
of the country of Britain
for you to die out here,
then the very least that
I could do is show up,
be charitable, and provide a
much-needed support system.
Makes a lot of sense to me.
If you had somebody with
you who spoke Russian
and could interpret,
it might make things easier.
I'm less concerned
with why you're here.
It's more of a "how," as in
"How did you find out I
would be sneaking into Russia
in the first place?"
What's this face?
You're feeling guilty about
not being fair to Index
because she's currently lying
helpless in the cathedral
in London, aren't you?
You're worried she'll find out
you had a secret rendezvous
with the first woman
you had a chance with.
Well, have I got
some good news for you.
I, Lessar, am not
wearing any leggings
under my skirt right now.
Only my undies!
Great. You know, that
information does absolutely
nothing for me. How am I
supposed to respond to that?
[LESSAR growls]
Like a normal person!
Get over here, jerk!
Lift my skirt up and forget
that previous woman!
You know what?
No one in the world would
blame me if I slugged you
for what you just said to me.
[KAMIJO] Follow what's out of
place and we'll find Fiamma.
Out of place?
Take the map, for example.
It has military
information on it,
but someone like me
was still able to buy it.
Ah, so you mean...
That's right.
They don't want anyone
to think it's important.
They've deliberately
lowered their security level.
Don't you think that's strange?
[LESSAR gasps]
[AGNESE] The deployment
has been completed.
A mixed force of both
puritans and knights
is currently on the way out.
I'd like to avoid any
engagements wherever possible.
I'm afraid France
remaining passive
under these circumstances
is not realistic.
They may be acting as the
Orthodoxy's advance force
or moving for their own reasons.
It's impossible
to say at this point.
Their animosity with
Britain is long-standing.
They won't sit this out.
[AGATHA] Interference from
France is confirmed!
They're on their way.
Please be on the lookout.
[AGNESE gasps]
[FRENCH SORCERERS yelling]
[KANZAKI] If they manage
to get through here,
they'll have a straight
shot into London.
[KANZAKI grunts]
[KANZAKI] We're at a
disadvantage aboard ships
that are stuck in place.
And being down here in the salt.
[CARISSA] What good will
it do for you to break down
at this point?
You are the fighting force
defending Britain, after all!
[FRENCH SORCERERS gasp]
[FRENCH SORCERER 18D]
It's Second Princess Carissa!
[KANZAKI yells]
[FRENCH SORCERERS yell]
Fiamma found a way to
get his magical materials
to the base.
He must've created a
secret route somewhere.
It's just as I predicted.
What's wrong?
Aren't you feeling
a little hot?
I'm not.
Aren't you kinda cold?
[LESSAR groans]
This is hopeless.
I'll just have to
unbutton my shirt
and flap my skirt at you!
What is your deal?
I don't understand why
you're behaving this way.
It's weird!
I'm trying to seduce you,
so just respond already!
The British need
more advance forces,
and that's where we come in!
Now just bowl me over
and get the deed done
like a good little soldier!
[KAMIJO]
Right.
So she's one of those girls who
just blurts out strings of words
without knowing what any
of it actually means.
As someone a bit older,
it's my responsibility
to tell you.
The things you're saying
could be really dangerous.
You need to be more careful.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
I read you loud and clear!
And now, if you're
finished lecturing me,
I'd like to explicitly
demonstrate exactly
how serious I am!
--[BOTH gasp]
--[crash, clatter]
You and I need to have a
serious chat when this is over.
Russian soldiers?
Or are they sorcerers?
Yep.
I think it's safe to assume
they're with the Russian Church.
They'll spot us
if we stay here. Go.
Crap!
[FRENCH SORCERER 18H coughs]
He's not dead, right?
No, but killing him
would've been a lot easier.
[FIAMMA]
It's necessary.
This is called a "space."
Now, what that means is
both coordinates and volume
are crucial.
And if you were to ask me,
I would say it's even more
important than Moscow.
You have to look at it from
Project B'Tselem's perspective.
Wait, that's--!
[FIAMMA] I'd like the
results of the survey.
Right away, please.
You wouldn't want things
to end up with you
as a bishop, would you?
What are you doing?
Stopping you from making
a scene so all the soldiers
on the base won't come running.
And you probably shouldn't
charge straight in from here
if you actually want
to reach Fiamma.
Yes, yes,
you're such a good boy.
So it's the Elizalina Alliance
of Independent Nations.
Fascinating.
Well that definitely explains
why I couldn't find
Sasha Kruezhev after searching
all over Russia for her.
Damn it, we were so close!
Let's get moving.
We need to get to Sasha
before Fiamma does.
If we can do that, it'll give
us the perfect opportunity
to set up a surprise
attack for him.
[KAMIJO] The Elizalina Alliance
of Independent Nations.
[TAKITSUBO]
It's okay.
I'm fine, really.
Don't worry about me.
Let's hurry and get moving.
You're fine, huh?
No one would call this normal.
An adverse effect
of the ability crystal.
What do I do?
[tapping]
Your friend looks like
she needs a doctor.
Oh, yeah?
Who are you?
[DIGURV]
How 'bout a "give and take."
My village recently ran out
of fuel for our generator.
So let's trade.
If you share some of
what you've got left with me,
I'll show you and
the girl to our doctor.
Deal?
[PRESS SECRETARY] We will not
impose any coercion upon
the Japanese government.
However, we are also
under no obligation
to defend anyone other
than our own allies.
[REPORTER 18A] So if the
government pressures
Academy City,
you'll remove the rest of the
country from the protective
umbrella of satellite
missile interceptors?
[REPORTER 18B]
Is that supposed to be a threat?
[LESSAR] There's something
I've been meaning to ask you.
What's up with that strappy
thing on your phone?
Huh?
His name is Gekota.
I don't know much
about him personally.
A fancy mascot like that
and you don't know anything
except his name?
I think there's a girl
wrapped up in this somehow.
Okay.
You know...
Maybe we should talk
about this later.
So this is the Elizalina
Alliance of Independent Nations.
And that's Elizalina,
the one the Alliance
of Independent Nations
is named for.
She's the holy woman
who went on a mission
to make several Russian
states independent.
She was also responsible
for unifying them.
I understand that Fiamma
of the Right is on his way here.
Uh, yeah, prob'ly.
Wait.
So you already know
who Fiamma is
and what he's capable of doing?
[ELIZALINA] I may not
be very skilled at it,
but I am a sorceress.
He's a primary figure
behind this war,
or, perhaps I should say, behind
an invasion of my homeland.
I would like the
chance to defeat him.
However...
I will by no means have the
lives of our Alliance's citizens
lost as a result
of any fighting.
It's simply not worth it.
[LESSAR] Are you saying
we can do what we want?
Well, no. I'm not.
Your objective is the
same one as Fiamma's.
Sasha Kruezhev.
Which is to say that we--
I'm gonna guess you're
sending us out of the country
along with Sasha.
And once we arrive there,
you want us to carry out
an operation against
Fiamma, is that right?
And it doesn't bother
me if you consider me
to be a cold-hearted person.
No way.
You're not gonna get any
judgment from our end.
I mean, we're using
you to find Sasha.
In fact, I think we can all be
grateful you didn't immediately
handcuff us
without talking first.
[ELIZALINA] We may be
operating on different scales,
but you also have those
you're trying to protect, right?
Yes, and she was almost
taken away from me
because it took me
so long to realize it.
There might be some
time left if I act now.
So, what do we do?
[FIAMMA] A strategy
session at this stage?
[ELIZALINA gasps]
Well. It's too late.
Incoming!
[LESSAR, ELIZALINA grunt]
Huh.
It's quite difficult to take aim
when dealing with sizes
that are this great.
[KAMIJO grunts]
Wow, where did that come from?
Do you know what
kind of attack it was?
That's Fiamma.
Now, for the real attack!
[KAMIJO, LESSAR gasp]
[KAMIJO grunts]
Imagine Breaker!
That's too bad.
I thought perhaps you
had learned something
from dealing with
Britain the Halloween.
How disappointing.
[ELIZALINA grunts]
[LESSAR coughs]
[FIAMMA]
I see.
Apparently, your wall was
too hard to easily break.
No! Bellagi! Rongier!
Oh, come on.
Don't sell me so short.
[BELLAGI, RONGIER yell]
Fiamma!
Well if it isn't the main dish.
The one that needs to be
properly prepared before eating.
[KAMIJO]
I could use my right hand.
But I don't know if I'd really
be able to guard against
every one of his attacks.
What if I just stay on
the defensive and guard?
Would I still be able
to help Index?
[FIAMMA]
Stay out of this.
[LESSAR yells]
[KAMIJO grunts]
Take your best shot!
You know why I'm
fighting, don't you?
[FIAMMA]
What's this?
Why are you offering yourself
up to be defeated first?
Very well.
[KAMIJO grunts]
[KAMIJO coughs]
[FIAMMA]
Did you know
that as a basic principle,
modern sorcerers,
as established in
the nineteenth century,
dislike taking
collective action?
What are you getting at?
[FIAMMA] That there is someone
here about to be killed
right before their eyes.
And that's not all.
Hundreds, if not thousands
of innocent civilians
are involved.
And they will all be
killed by the invasion
that's about to take place.
So tell me if this makes sense.
Under these circumstances,
could a powerful sorcerer
sit idly by in hiding?
[SASHA yelling]
That's Sasha Kruezhev!
Today must be my lucky day.
[SASHA grunts]
[FIAMMA] I never thought
it would be possible.
How was it so easy to
achieve both objectives?
[FIAMMA]
There's a familiar face.
[VENTO] I'm not particularly
obliged to help these people
in any way.
However, you need to
quit disrupting the
Roman Orthodox Church!
I think enough is enough,
don't you?
Too bad I happen to know
you aren't able to use
your trademark
Divine Retribution.
And for some reason
you think that's all it takes
for me to quit?
Of course.
They went and got attacked
before I could get here.
But who'd level a
military base like this?
Looks like it's been
thoroughly wiped.
[chuckles]
That's an easy riddle to solve.
Academy City, obviously.
Is this what they were after?
What's in there that's
worth dying for?
How interesting.
So this is an operation
on the same level
as my recovery mission.
I'm not seeing a lot
of results just yet,
but maybe this has
something to do with that
"other set of laws."
Or whatever that son of a bitch
Aiwass was talking about.
That cryptic freak didn't
exactly give me much to go on.
[FRENCH SORCERER 18K]
Freeze!
[ACCELERATOR]
Hmm?
[FRENCH SORCERER 18K]
You from Academy City?
[ACCELERATOR]
I don't believe we've met.
You must be the ones who
attacked the military base,
right?
Never mind, don't care.
I'll take you all out quickly.
[ACCELERATOR]
You don't mind, do you?
[PILOT 18A] Now approaching
the slated assault zone.
Russian Airbase 740.
[CONTROL TOWER 18A]
Copy.
What's your drop status?
[PILOT 18A]
Ready to release.
[MISAKA WORST]
Yoo-hoo, I'm here to kill you.
First Ranked.
[KAMIJO] The Third Season
has been unleashed.
An expression of 10,031
people's vengeance,
condemnation, and hatred.
Retribution arrives
in the worst of forms.
Next time, "Misaka Worst."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.