[KAMIJO, FLORIS panting]
Are you okay?
It looks like we managed to
successfully get away from them.
Uh... huh?!
Successfully?! If you mean
despite plunging into the water
and bouncing all over the
place while spinning around,
then sure--what a success!
Hey. We're still here.
We're alive, aren't we?
And safe, safe!
Huh? You think we're safe?
That isn't the issue here!
[horse galloping]
Are those horse hooves?
They found us!
Oh, it's you.
[KAMIJO]
You're the third princess.
[AMAKUSA MEMBER 13A]
I've located the third princess.
[TATEMIYA] Outstanding.
Hurry and escort her here.
[AMAKUSA MEMBER 13A]
The thing is...
So you're saying the
Imagine Breaker is with her?
What on earth could possibly
be going on over there?
Tell me, have you ever
heard of the Norse warrior
they call Thororm?
He used magic,
and allegedly had the power
to cancel out the sharpness
of his enemy's swords.
Wait, you can't mean...
[KNIGHT LEADER]
Taking a page from this legend,
I've formulated a spell that
zeroes out the attack force
of anything I might
recognize as a weapon.
That is, after I took a brutal
sneak attack at Dover long ago.
[ACQUA grunts]
[KNIGHT LEADER]
Zero out!
That again?
I zeroed this out earlier.
Does this mean you're running
out of tricks already?
History is currently
on the move.
Unless you can turn back time,
it is abundantly clear which
leader has what it takes
to be the most beneficial
to the country!
So why cling so tenaciously
to that powerless
and pathetic Third Princess?
You still don't
understand, do you?
[KNIGHT LEADER]
It can't be.
It just can't be!
The three animals
on the coat of arms.
The royalty, the knights,
and the puritans.
The fields of blue symbolizing
England, Scotland, Wales,
and Northern Ireland--
the entirety of Great Britain.
Are you serious?
Do you truly not see the
absurdity of a plan like that?
You want to strive
for a perfect harmony
within the body of the United
Kingdom with the queen
and the three sisters,
and without anyone else
there to support you?
As I said before...
Why talk when you can fight?
A true warrior
acts on his beliefs
rather than
speaking about them.
[KNIGHT LEADER screaming]
[ACQUA yells]
Zero out!
[KNIGHT LEADER]
He launched that himself?
But once I've noticed it
and recognize it as a weapon,
it's over!
Zero out!
[KNIGHT LEADER]
Is there enough time?
Zero out!
[KNIGHT LEADER] How many
hidden blades do you have?
Imagine meeting the
same fate as Thororm.
In the same way ten years ago,
being bested by
another sneak attack.
[ACQUA] Well, I am a shameless,
washed-up mercenary scoundrel.
I can fight with wild abandon
in a way you stiff
knights never could.
But as fate would have it,
I do not have a blade
in my possession
with which to
kill an old friend.
[KNIGHT 13A]
The captain! Fall back!
[KAMIJO] I've got a nasty
feeling that won't go away,
but I'm not gonna get
anywhere unless I keep moving.
Luckily, the Amakusa are
guarding the Third Princess now.
[KAMIJO gasps]
Quite a devil of a face
to come across once again.
It's Acqua?
But how?
He's still alive.
Is that Index?
If rescuing her is your goal,
then get it done quickly.
In some ways, the danger here
is greater than in London,
though the city
has already fallen.
[CARISSA] Huh. The Knight Leader
has been vanquished, has he?
You're causing me so much grief.
I'm overwhelmed, honestly.
And functioning without
my vanguard means
I'll just have to deal with
you bottom feeders myself.
Not to worry,
your grief will end soon.
Because your coup d'état
is about to come to an end
right here and now.
I advise you not
to underestimate me.
I have the Curtana Original
in my hand right now,
so don't you forget it!
[KAMIJO]
Whoa...!
Now, ordinarily, this is
something that separates
the United Kingdom from
the rest of the planet.
That is to say,
it manages and governs it.
But by applying
its special attributes,
it can do this as well.
When you cut through
three-dimensional matter,
its cross-section
becomes two-dimensional.
And if it's two-dimensional,
the cross-section will
become one-dimensional.
In the same way, if you
cut through a dimension
of space higher than
three dimensions,
its cross-section is
put out into the world
in three-dimensional form.
In other words...
I hold the power to produce
cross-sectional wreckage
of this level any time I want.
It's a pan-dimensional
fragmentation spell.
However, there is
a drawback to it.
This spell makes it way too
easy to put an end to things.
So it's just not as
fun as it could be.
Damn.
I need some time.
Keep her occupied.
While you do that,
I'll smash her item
with my right hand.
[CARISSA]
Oh, how frightening.
If I recall correctly,
your patented move
was called Imagine Breaker,
was it not?
In that case, allow me to
show you an applied technique.
It's perfect for it!
[KAMIJO grunting]
[KAMIJO yelling]
[KAMIJO]
Damn it! What now?
Hold on, Index!
[ACQUA] Grab onto me,
unless you'd prefer to die.
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
[ACQUA]
Here. Catch.
Thank you.
But why'd you save us?
I had to.
The one who was
responsible for the union
between the Roman Orthodoxy
and the Russian Church
is called Fiamma of the Right.
Wait, Fiamma of the Right?
That is correct, and he
has a plan in place
that relies upon two things:
your right arm
and the wisdom of the
List of Prohibited Books
needed to fully
exploit its powers,
which left me no choice.
Make sense?
Saving one of you
without the other
would make the plan ineffective.
Fiamma would be sent
into a panic if he lost
both key elements.
And that in and of
itself would carry the risk
of even more senseless
destruction spreading.
So here we are.
I have no other choice
but to destroy the scourge
within the scourge.
However, the need arose
to quickly put an end
to this petty quarrel.
A quarrel that spun off
of the actual scourge
before I ever had a chance
to attack, you see?
Wait, a petty quarrel?
You mean the coup d'état?
I don't understand.
Can it be stopped?
Carissa and the knights' new
order relies solely on Curtana.
Which means they're
more vulnerable
with only one true weapon.
But striking at weaknesses
is not how I operate.
I don't have to trick anyone.
I challenge my opponents
upfront, out in the open.
[gun fires]
[KAMIJO]
Acqua of the Rear. Damn.
Index! Are you okay?
Are you hurt anywhere?
Toma, are you the one who
rescued me from the knights?
You'd think so, right?
I only wish things had
worked out as easily as that.
Oh!
Well then, that must
mean you came here
with yet another girl
you've known for ten seconds.
You'd think so, right?
I only wish things had
worked out as easily as that.
I'm glad to see you're
still your usual self.
Um... Toma, I'm hungry.
Will you feed me?
Maybe too much your usual self.
[aircraft approaching]
[KAMIJO] Prevent Curtana
Original from functioning?
We received a report
that the Second Princess
has just returned
to Buckingham Palace.
It can be assumed
that the reason for this
is because Curtana Original's
power is too great
and therefore unstable
and in need of fine tuning.
Then now's our chance.
With Knight Leader defeated,
the alliance is fragile.
The knights and
the Second Princess
were only ever united
by mutual interest.
If we can eliminate Curtana,
then this coup d'état
will fall apart.
Acqua did mention something
about how the knights
and the princess were
vulnerable because their plans
were centered solely on Curtana.
Do you think shutting Curtana
down is really a possibility?
There's a subway
under Buckingham Palace.
[KANZAKI] There was a backup
system created in a rarely-used
underground branch line.
A special car with magic
cast on it is standing by.
It will activate should
Curtana ever get out of control.
Essentially, it's a failsafe
put into place in order
to check the sword's power.
We believe Carissa returned
because she needed
this system to counter
Curtana's growing instability.
[KANZAKI] We plan to use
this to our advantage.
We'll forcibly disrupt Curtana
Original via the subway,
and then expend a tremendous
amount of magic power
from the English Puritan's
aerial fortress
to cast a large-scale
flash spell.
This should stimulate the
sword to run away with itself.
I see.
I mean, I don't
really understand
the exact theory behind it,
but if you say it works,
then I'm all in.
I apologize.
I didn't expect that,
and it's quite a relief to
know we have your support.
The truth is, you see,
there are very few people
who'd be able to
carry out this mission.
[MIKOTO]
I wonder...
What is going on
with this restaurant?
I just came in here
today by chance.
It's like touring
Big-boob country!
Wait a minute!
If everyone in here looks
that way, then maybe there's
something in the food
that makes you grow!
[phone buzzing]
[coughing]
[MIKOTO] Seriously?
What does he want?
Why in the world would
that idiot be calling me?
Yeah, hello?
[KAMIJO]
Sorry to bother you, Misaka,
but I need to sneak
into a subway.
Do you know how to open an
electronic shutter door lock?
[MIKOTO]
Ugh.
[KAMIJO] Sorry to bother
you, Misaka! But I need--
I heard you,
but I was ignoring it!
Get a clue, you idiot!
Okay, tell me:
Why do you need to break
into a train station?
And where are you, anyway?
[KAMIJO]
London.
[MIKOTO]
Huh?
Do you have any idea
what kind of crazy hoops
you'd have to jump
through just to get out
of Academy City?
[MIKOTO] But then again,
wasn't he in France earlier?
[KAMIJO] I know it sounds
weird, but I'm in London.
And I really am staring
at a shutter door
that I need to get through.
You'll need to tell me
what kind of lock it is.
[KAMIJO] You know, the fact
that we've made it this far
so easily confirms that
the strength of London's
security network is stacked
more towards magic.
Yes, so it would seem.
Oh, well, Index and I are
disconnected from magic,
so we won't set anything off.
But you're a British
princess, aren't you?
I am, which does mean I've
acquired a certain level
of education as a member
of the royal family.
But as far as magic goes,
I refused to obtain
any knowledge or skills
that could be applied
toward violence.
Sorry. I can't help.
I was asking because
the subway partition
has to be opened by
someone with royal blood,
so I thought you
could give it a try?
Ah! Well, I don't have
much experience,
but if Index will help me,
I will certainly do my best.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
Hey, Toma,
I'm detecting some sort
of marking in this area
that was created using magic.
If I had to guess, I'd say it's
probably so sorcerers
who maintain a magical item
can keep track of this location.
Oh, yeah?
What are those?
[INDEX]
Toma!
Stay back there. I'm serious!
That magical item is
based on the construction
of the Mökkurkálfi
used to fight Thor!
It's a fabricated clay
giant from Norse mythology!
[KAMIJO grunts]
Damn it! Did I get him?
[KAMIJO]
Come on! Really?!
This is bad... I can't move!
Toma!
[VILIAN yelling]
[VILIAN] This trap is probably
simpler than it seems.
I bet my sister could
set it with less magic
than she holds
in her little finger.
No matter.
That's not the issue here.
If even the smallest amount
of force will harm those
who are trying to support me...
[KAMIJO gasps]
[VILIAN]
I will resist it!
I will resist it
to the bitter end!
I'll do whatever it takes!
C-A-O!
M-Y-R-A-T-T-R!
You must obey the one who
bears the blood of royalty!
I demand you open up at once!
[KAMIJO]
Thanks. You saved me, Vilian.
I can handle it from here.
I'll stop him
for good this time!
[KAMIJO yells]
We did it.
[phone buzzing]
[ITSUWA] Oh, thank
goodness I got through!
Itsuwa? Is that you?
[ITSUWA]
The mission was a success!
Thanks to Princess Vilian
releasing the lock
on the magic partition,
we found the special car
and were able to access
its power source!
But that's why I'm calling.
[KAMIJO]
Huh?
[ITSUWA] You have to get
out of there right away!
[CARISSA coughs]
[CARISSA] Somehow,
I managed to contain it.
[KNIGHT 13B]
Princess Carissa!
Don't worry. I'm fine.
This was an attack
from Coven Compass.
Recover the railway
car and reseal it.
[KNIGHT 13B]
Right!
[TATEMIYA] I'd say things
went quite well overall.
Curtana's power has
been dampened at last.
Now we just wait for
the countercoup forces
we called in to
start assembling.
Then we charge the palace.
Once we have control of Carissa,
the coup d'état will fall apart.
Almost done. Which means...
Which means what?
[TATEMIYA chuckles]
You can't take what's not yours!
Ugh! I can't believe
you ate my meatball!
I did not!
[AGNESE]
Light salad is not an option!
We still have to fight,
so don't eat too much!
[SISTER 13A] More food!
I demand you give me more,
no questions asked!
[TATEMIYA] You know what we
have to do before a big battle.
You and I must fortify
our bellies, of course!
[KANZAKI]
Aren't you going to eat?
I was, but everyone's
fierce determination
to stuff their
faces distracted me.
Oh, come on!
You need a break!
Let me take over for you!
Uh, no thanks.
It's really not a good time.
See, we just got done fighting
and I was sweating a lot,
so I'm afraid my
outfit might be smelly.
Then I've got the perfect
Cinderella mission
for you, Itsuwa!
[ITSUWA]
Huh?
[TATEMIYA]
Ta-da!
Looks like opening
night for the premier
of the Great Fairy
Revealing Maid outfit!
Tatemiya, why would
you bring that horrible
doomsday weapon here?
[TATEMIYA] And Priestess,
you'll be please to know
I also carefully saved your
precious bridal outfit.
I never asked you
to do that for me!
Why would I even
need that thing?
Oh, really?
Does that mean you
have something better,
like a hyper-fallen-angel
sexy maid outfit?
Wow, you go above
and beyond, don't you?
[KANZAKI]
I do not!
Sister Agnese.
The far east denomination
seems to be saying something
about not letting good
breasts go to waste.
I see. So who among our camp
would be the most effective
in serving as a
counterargument for this?
You can count me out for sure.
There's no way I'm doing
something like that!
I saw this and instantly
thought it would look lovely
on you, so I brought it here
along with that pedestal.
I never asked for either!
Don't you judge my goth outfits!
[ORSOLA]
Then you leave me no choice.
I will wear it so it
doesn't go to waste.
You idiot! Stop that at once!
[KNIGHT LEADER] It appears that
Curtana Original was overloaded.
Was that your doing?
Well, no.
But my guess would be
that it was the work
of magical specialists
within the country.
[KNIGHT LEADER]
I see.
And as a result, the knights
are on the verge of collapsing.
Is that so?
If it is, it can be set aside
with your return, can it not?
Are you having second thoughts?
[KNIGHT LEADER] I offer you a
warning before you leap into
the jaws of death.
In our fight earlier,
I could only control
one fighting pattern at a time.
As a result,
I was defeated by you.
Second Princess Carissa
and Curtana Original
are equipped with
each of these patterns.
She can produce an attack
that cannot be avoided,
blocked, or countered.
If you truly mean to bring
her down, be prepared.
[ISAHAYA]
Deputy Pope!
Coven Compass has arrived
at the designated coordinates!
Attention! The time
has come at last!
Ready to go?
You bet!
[RIMEA] Oh, dear, it appears
that we didn't make it in time.
[ELIZARD] I Can't believe
they left us behind.
And they made me run
into my calculating
oldest daughter whom
I had no desire to see.
How rude to call me calculating.
Why not refer to it
as an intelligent,
level-headed decision
made in the event
that Carissa slipped up
and released Curtana Original's
full power.
A matter of self-preservation?
That is what calculating means!
Keep going, horsie.
I've got important business
to take care of back in London.
So, have the arrangements
for that flag been made?
The one in the British Museum?
I would say we are about
halfway to completion on that.
Not many would recognize
it as a magical item
after being mixed in with
the other general artifacts.
Now if Charles Conder
from the museum does exactly
as we discussed,
and I fully expect him to,
then it should prove to be
quite useful to us, indeed.
[ELIZARD] My word, with the
fate of the United Kingdom
on the line, they're charging
into the final showdown
without so much as a plan--
just their pluck and their guts.
Bloody fools!
Well, well.
I must say, your tone
doesn't match the smile
on your face...
Dearest mother.
[KAMIJO] Are men powerless
in the face of overwhelming
military might?
No, they're not.
Everyone fights for the
United Kingdom tonight!
Next time, "Heroes."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.