[INDEX] Chapter eight,
verse twenty-five.
Commencing purge of humans
who may hinder remote
access operations.
Completed.
Innocentius... disperse!
[screams]
Chapter ten, verse three.
Confirming effectiveness
of executing spells.
Determining that halting
all hostile elements
of vital activity is
consistently the recommended
and most effective
solution available.
[yells]
[INDEX]
Chapter eleven, verse two.
Identifying effective
destructive force.
Determining that a
rapid-fire chain of attacks,
without allowing full
time to recover,
is currently the best
known strategy.
Not good!
Um. Question three, if I may:
What's going on?
[KAMIJO]
Is that Hyoka Kazakiri?
Seriously? Why is she here?
Uh. Question four,
if you don't mind:
What is it, exactly?
Oh, her?
That's Hyoka Kazakiri.
She's a friend of mine.
A friend of yours, huh?
[KAMIJO] Well, actually, I'm not
sure why she's here, but...
...I'm definitely
going to find out.
[KAZAKIRI yells]
[MISHA] You must return. You
must return. You must return.
Return to the location
immediately.
Find the correct
coordinates for heaven
and take the original path
to the proper meeting place.
Return to the
location immediately.
[KAZAKIRI] Must be a
different form of power
lodged inside of that thing.
[MISHA] Return. Necessary.
Perform. Operation.
Fiamma. Utilize. Interests.
Contact. Plan. Collaboration.
I'm giving you a fair warning--
if you intend to hurt
my dear friends
over something like this,
then I will have no choice
but to use every drop of
strength I have to stop you.
[MISHA] Damage. Disregard.
Priority. Return. Correct.
Location. Obstacle. Evil.
Synonymous. Judgment. All.
[MISHA]
Capture.
Necessary. Information.
Parchment. Obtain.
[grunts]
Looks like the scent of this
parchment is so strong
it's attracting flies.
Detecting an incoming disaster.
And Misaka predicts
this one to be worse
than a natural hurricane.
What now?
There's a difference between
natural and manmade.
Only one strikes with
the intention to kill.
And personally, I'm much
happier with an exact target.
It gives me an outlet,
so I don't have to waste my
time being weighed down
by anger I can't
seem to channel.
Don't forget you've got
the kid in the back seat.
Be careful and keep her safe.
Jeez, come on. Seriously?
Don't you know that's what
Misaka is the worst at?
You know, you're pretty damn
lucky I've got a need for you.
Your potential usefulness is
the only thing keeping me
from ending your life after
a dumb joke like that.
Yeah? Perfect!
Then Misaka did something right!
A Russian
bacteriological weapon?
Are you absolutely certain
that's their plan?
'Fraid so. It's
because of the silo.
They don't want
Academy City to get it.
You have to leave,
it's dangerous here.
[VILLAGER 23A]
What do we do?
Call everyone from Academy City
who's stationed in our village?
[HAMAZURA]
No.
If they were to make
any big moves,
the Russian army might
speed up the operation.
We're going to have
to do this alone.
Then I'm coming with you.
[HAMAZURA]
What if something happens to me?
Who will come back here
to protect the villagers?
[TAKITSUBO]
You ready, Hamazura?
[HAMAZURA]
Yeah.
[DIGURV]
Hamazura!
Don't get killed.
I'll try.
Bye.
Be careful, okay?
[HAMAZURA]
Yep!
[gasps]
Well, we can't say this
thing doesn't work.
Those wings you're
controlling are constructed
from aggregated
A-I-M diffusion fields.
Who are you?
I'm quite impressed that
a powerful monster
such as yourself has
the mental capacity
to conduct an interview
with me right now.
Be straight with me--
the scent of this thing brought
you here, too, didn't it?
Tch. What a cocky bastard.
Is that supposed to
be an introduction?
What?
I'll have to deal
with you later.
I have a feeling that
the key element I need
to save the kid is,
unfortunately,
in the hands of that other
monster down there.
Maybe I shouldn't use the
term monster so loosely.
You guys aren't
as bad as Aiwass.
[MISHA] Preparing, preparing,
preparing, preparing,
preparing, preparing.
We're at range and set to go.
Our preparations... complete.
[gasps]
[MISHA]
Command. Sweep. Drop.
[choking]
Damn you.
[ACCELERATOR]
What the hell was that about?
One blast wasn't
enough for you, huh?
Well, screw you, then.
I can't afford to risk
dying because of you.
Not when justice for the
kid hasn't been served.
I won't rest until I end
the cause of her pain.
It doesn't even matter to me
if I can defeat you here or not!
You've given me a reason to
try, and that's all I need!
[MISHA]
Second wave attack is now ready.
We have 30 seconds to sweep
before we redrop the fuel.
Second wave attack is now ready.
Is that really all you've got?
If neither one of you has
the strength to stop me,
then I guess, my Sweeps
will blanket the world.
[FIAMMA]
Long time no see, Acqua.
Are you still claiming to be a
corner of the Right Seat of God?
Or have you given up
and gone back to making
your way as a mercenary?
[ACQUA] It doesn't matter
how you label me.
As long as I'm in a position
to put an end to your tyranny.
[FIAMMA] Oh, really?
And how would you do that?
You can't be that ignorant as
to how this war got started.
I may be the one who
pulled the trigger,
but a bullet doesn't fire
without a little gunpowder,
now does it?
[ACQUA] I see, and you feel
that's reason enough
to turn an archangel loose
on innocent people?
[FIAMMA]
Are you going to stop me?
Then ultimately, your solution
is to resort to force.
However, your power
is not strong enough
to control an archangel.
You have my blessing to continue
trying to fight the
good fight, of course,
but I do think watching
from the sidelines
would be more advisable.
[ACQUA]
Is that so?
In that case,
allow me to use a method
that doesn't rely on force.
[FIAMMA]
What did you do?
Wait a minute.
[ACQUA]
It seems you've forgotten.
I am Acqua of the Rear.
Member of the Right Seat of God,
known as the darkest
organization
within the Roman Orthodoxy.
And he who presides over
the archangel Gabriel.
How dare you try that!
[FIAMMA] You took the
telesma inside of you?
[ACQUA] If I were to siphon
the water element
telesma into myself,
one could only imagine
what would happen
to the Archangel Gabriel,
as it's the source of its power.
[FIAMMA]
You must be out of your mind.
[ACQUA] It's not a
difficult task, you know.
After all, the nun you tried
to use from the Russian church
was able to do it.
[FIAMMA]
You idiot.
That's only because
she had the grounding
and tolerance required
to begin with.
[ACQUA] You're completely
missing the point.
If someone like her can
do it, then so can I.
That's all there is to it.
[FIAMMA]
Whatever you say.
Go ahead and try.
But keep in mind
that you're only
putting your own life at risk
by doing something so foolish.
[groaning]
[yells]
[chuckles]
He managed to take roughly
half of her telesma,
but there's plenty available
for me to prevail.
Therefore, your life
will be lost for nothing.
[FIAMMA]
Kill him, Misha Kruezhev.
Bastard.
[yelling]
[KAMIJO] The timing of Misha
Kruezhev's appearance
is notable.
It was after the Star
of Bethlehem popped up.
If Fiamma was able
to utilize the power
of archangels this whole time,
he could've completed
his goal of destruction
without ever needing to start
World War Three, but he didn't.
It wasn't until this appeared.
The Star of Bethlehem is what
enabled him to summon
and sustain that
powerful archangel.
That makes things
easier to understand.
Let's see.
I bet Misha's life support
is somewhere in here.
And once I find it, I'll
smash it with my right hand!
[gasps]
That wasn't enough!
What else do I have to do, huh?
[MISHA screams]
It's a mass of energy.
Stop, or you'll explode!
[ACCELERATOR] I don't care
if I'm a fair match
for this thing or not.
That isn't the issue here!
I am not going to make
this decision for you.
Call it arrogance or
whatever you want.
You're the only one who can
decide if she's worth it.
No one else can tell
you what to do!
[ACCELERATOR]
She is worth it.
I can't lose her. I will
fight to protect her!
I don't even want to
think of another option!
I've made up my mind.
If keeping her safe
means risking my life,
I'll dive head first
into this nightmare,
and finally face my reality!
Hey, don't let me
fall back there!
[yelling]
[ACQUA]
I think that's good enough.
As long as we find a way to
eliminate the archangel Gabriel,
the war will shift dramatically.
Fiamma, you will soon
see that you've placed
too much confidence
in your own strength.
You battle alone.
You've forgotten that
people will join hands
with like-minded strangers
to fight a great enemy.
You don't understand
that the choice
can be made for one to
hand over the torch of war
to others who share
a common goal.
Indeed, much as I once did.
Death will find me soon.
I will take the archangel
down with me.
As long as it provides a
future full of joy for others,
I will be fulfilled.
[HAMAZURA]
Damn it!
Come on, stay with us!
Can you hear me?
What happened to you?
Takitsubo! He needs first aid!
[ACQUA]
No, don't bother.
I won't survive in any case.
You shut your mouth!
[ACQUA]
Please, go. Leave me here.
The goal for my life has
already been accomplished.
Any effort you make to
keep me in this world now
will only slow you down.
[HAMAZURA]
Oh, come on!
What am I supposed to do about
all the people waiting for you?
Aren't they part of everything
you've spent your entire
life fighting for?
You've done everything you can
to have masses of
people follow you,
and they're still here!
If your only reason for
fighting is something so lame
as stepping in front of
a crowd of citizens
with tears in their eyes
and seeing smiles
appear because of you,
then you're not done!
So, it's time! Get up!
Get up, hero!
[yelling]
That's how it is? You're
not going to cooperate?
Well, fine. Screw you, you
worthless piece of crap!
Thanks to Gabriel's
perceptive skills,
I've acquired the information
I need from the parchment.
Almost there.
[KAMIJO gasps]
[yells]
Sasha, no!
[FIAMMA] You like making
things difficult, don't you?
I guess I'll have to
complete this ritual
sooner than I expected.
You think I'm going to allow
you to proceed that easily?
The people have conquered
your archangel.
So no matter how
you choose spin it,
the scales have
tipped in our favor!
I wouldn't exactly say that.
[FIAMMA]
The angel's defeat matters not.
Her role came to an end
the moment she changed
the night sky to my liking.
The Star of Bethlehem
now flies alone
in a telesma-filled,
incomplete sky,
as part of a ceremony to
reconfigure the four elements.
[KAMIJO]
What? What are you trying to do?
This is all just a
means to an end, see?
What really counts
is my right arm.
Everything comes down to this.
Fire, water, wind, and earth.
By controlling these
four elements,
I would be gaining a tremendous
amount of magical power.
However, I am being held back
by the distortion of elements
in the world at large.
And proper power is something
that can only be exercised
to its fullest
in a proper world.
It's finally time.
Time for you to learn what
proper power really is!
[gasps]
[HAMAZURA] Damn it.
There are too many of 'em.
Hamazura.
I think they're spreading
the microbes using a timer.
We should probably wait
here for them to leave.
Yeah. Right.
Promise me. No crazy stuff.
I promise.
[HAMAZURA]
Crap! We've been spotted!
Great. What do we do now?
[engine roars]
[HAMAZURA]
An Academy City plane?
[SOLDIERS scream]
[VOICE 23A] Hey! I know
there's somebody down there!
If you're a goodwill volunteer,
I'd like to shake your hand.
I'm a charitable man, myself.
Why would Academy City attack?
[VOICE 23A] If you think you're
protecting the Kremlin Report,
we caught wind of it, too.
And we're here to
thoroughly incinerate
any biological weapons!
[BOTH scream]
Takitsubo! Where are you?
Answer me!
Takitsubo!
"Have you regained
your composure?"
asks Misaka, sincerely.
Yeah. But this is
so far beyond bad.
Especially if they use nukes
on something that high up.
Do you have any idea
where the launch site is?
[MISAKA 10777]
"According to the transmission,
it is a location
roughly 70 kilometers
from our current position,"
answers Misaka.
Well, sounds like we'll
have to steal some wheels.
Remind me, do you know
how to drive a car?
[KAMIJO]
Right arm power and knowledge
of the List of Forbidden Books.
After Fiamma masters both,
his attacks won't allow
me to strike back.
Is the power to save the world
what he's really after?
Next time, "Index."
When science and magic cross
paths, a story is born.