[TERRA]
Well, well, well.
What is the matter?
Why ever did you stop?
Please amuse me some more.
[TERRA]
Precedence!
The motion of the
spear will be lower.
The air will be higher.
[ITSUWA gasps]
[KAMIJO yells]
[KAMIJO]
Crap, I missed!
[grunts]
I'm still alive?
But how?
Was that attack different
from the previous one?
[ITSUWA]
Flour? Is it symbolic?
Meant to signify
the flesh of God?
Oh, my.
Even an easterner
like you can tell that?
By any rationalization,
there is no way
a mortal man would be
able to kill the Son of God.
And yet, the legend says
that it was His fate
to be crucified by
mortals in order to take
the original sin of
man upon Himself.
To that end,
there was an alteration
to the order of
precedence performed
between man and the Son of God.
It is this esoteric
procedure of changing
the order of priority
to fulfill mythology
that is my technique--
It's called
The Light's Execution.
That's it.
He prioritized a spear
made out of flour
over the outside wall,
which is why it had
such a destructive force.
And because the air
had priority over the spear,
Itsuwa's attack was
stopped dead in its tracks.
Is this the power of
the Right Seat of God?
So in the face
of that technique,
all the strengths and weaknesses
of any opponent
become irrelevant.
Oh, dear, you're
looking troubled again.
Either try to find a way
to defeat me or run away,
but don't just stand there.
I am going to give
you ten seconds.
I expect you to
use it to come up
with your plan of attack.
[chuckling]
That is, assuming there
is one that actually exists!
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
In ten seconds, I could come up
with at least three plans!
Precedence.
Magic is lower,
and skin is higher.
[KAMIJO gasps]
Tsuchimikado!
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Sorry to keep
you waiting so long, Kami.
Ha! I hope you're not going
to tell me that that was your
big breakout strategy.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Unfortunately
for you, I've got you cornered.
This next move
will be checkmate.
[TERRA laughs]
Do you really think you
can fight me with that toy?
Precedence!
Bullets are lower,
skin is higher!
Heh, it's like I said.
You've been checkmated.
[CROWD yelling]
I didn't need this.
[TERRA] I see, so that's how
it's going to be, Aleister?
There's just a regular
spellcaster using
the Document of C
in the Papal Palace.
It would be quite bothersome
if they were attacked
by a large-scale military force.
So you leave me
no other choice.
Hold it! [yells]
Are you okay?
Come on, Kami, we gotta
head to the Papal Palace, too.
They're from Academy City,
those powered suits.
But they weren't supposed
to make a move.
We need to go
after Terra right now.
At this point,
the Right Seat of God
is about to wage an all-out war,
so if we want to stop
the Document of C,
we have to do it now or
we're gonna lose our chance.
Why would they target us?
You guys go on ahead
to the Palace. Leave.
I'll stay here and deal with
these Academy City idiots.
You'll be okay?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Yeah, it's not
like they're entrenched enemies
or anything.
I think I can find some
room for negotiation.
Now go!
Damn it!
[ITSUWA] Looks like they're
knocking out rioters
and removing them from
town in those balloons.
Tsuchimikado wouldn't
pull something like this.
Are we just supposed to
accept this kind of violence
as a way of doing things?
It doesn't look like
there's anybody here.
I have to wonder.
Where did those
powered suits come from?
[ITSUWA]
Huh?
And what the hell is Academy
City planning to do with them?
Hey, Misaka?
Is this a good time?
[MIKOTO]
Are you kidding me?
You can't send a single text
and now you're calling
out of the blue!
What do you--
Can you look at the news?
Either TV or internet?
I need you to check and see
if there's anything going on
in a city called Avignon.
Huh? Are you serious?
Avignon is all
they're talking about.
Jeez.
They're saying a religious
group made weapons
of mass destruction and
violated international law.
Apparently, Academy City
is helping to carry out
a mopping-up operation.
Wait, where are you right now?
Hello? You're, uh, cutting out.
--What the--?
--[MIKOTO] Hello?
[KAMIJO]
That sound... It's gone now.
Itsuwa, did you...?
[ITSUWA yells]
[TERRA]
Well, this is a fine mess.
While trying to stop
the chaos of the riots,
you create an even
larger disturbance
and get caught up in it.
I suppose we're
seeing just how serious
Academy City is about this.
He has the Document of C!
[laughs]
The ordinary caster
enacting the spell
was being targeted
by Academy City forces.
So I thought it prudent
of me to recover this first.
I am not able to
perform mortal spells,
and average spellcasters
hold me back.
Therefore, I think it would
be wise to cut things short.
You think I'm gonna
let you walk away?
Suit yourselves.
You can stay here and fight
to your heart's content.
After all, I much prefer
to keep things interesting!
[TSUCHIMIKADO chuckles]
You blockheads have one job,
so make yourselves useful.
And act as a shield!
That's not the kind of side
effect you can ever really
get used to.
Now wake up, ya' bastards!
Smash it all up so we
can go home laughing!
[TSUCHIMIKADO grunts]
I surrender.
You can do whatever
you want with me.
Go on.
Let's see what you're
capable of, shall we?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Wondering how I did that?
Those H-S-P-S-fifteens
are equipped
with fancy new stand-alone
auxiliary drive units,
which is a mixed blessing.
See, they're still prototypes
with a lot of bugs left to fix.
When you give it any
contradictory conditional input,
its decision-making
functions freeze.
What's worse--for you at least--
is that the onboard
databank functions
are overdeveloped.
So if one suit malfunctions,
all of them are affected.
And now, you've all been
stopped in your tracks.
Those are Academy City's
supersonic stealth bombers--
H-S-B-zero-twos.
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
What are you thinking, Aleister?
It'll take more than that to
eliminate the Document of C.
Or is there another
trick up his sleeve?
Operation A
objective accomplished.
B is next.
Get your parachute.
[ACCELERATOR]
Don't need it.
So now they're opening
fire on the outside, too.
[BOMBER TECH 03A]
Commencing Operation B.
[ACCELERATOR] Heh. With just
three kilograms of iron sand,
these Earth Blades could
slice up all of Eurasia.
You've cooked up quite an item.
[BOMBER TECH 03A]
Isolating operational area.
Switching to aerial bombardment.
There's a change of plans.
The target is the
Papal Palace, right?
Then concentrate your
main attack there first.
But we can't.
[ACCELERATOR]
Change it now!
There are several
types and levels of "evil,"
you know.
And a truly world-class villain
will never target the
lives of innocent people.
[KAMIJO] You have no intention
of handing it over nicely,
do you?
Now Precedence.
The air lower. Flour higher!
[KAMIJO gasps]
Stay here.
[TERRA]
Precedence.
Blade lower. Skin higher!
[ITSUWA, KAMIJO yell]
[TERRA]
Precedence.
Flesh lower. Flour higher!
[TERRA]
Is that all you've got?
Looks like I have a
leg up on you, literally.
And you've finally
exposed yourself.
That spell has a weakness.
There was something unnatural
about what you just did.
Is that so? How troubling.
It's unfortunate that you won't
have any time to make use of it.
[TERRA]
Precedence.
Ceiling lower. Flour higher.
--[ITSUWA yells]
--[KAMIJO] Itsuwa!
[TERRA] Well, I suppose
that's to be expected.
Damn you!
[TERRA]
Imagine Breaker.
The name raised my expectations.
But I never imagined
it could be so flawed.
Had you restored
its original capabilities,
you might actually
have been able to defend
that sorceress.
[KAMIJO]
What are you talking about?
Oh, my. You really don't know?
But how is that possible
when by all rights,
you should have--
You haven't by chance forgotten
anything you shouldn't have?
[KAMIJO]
Why, you...!
[TERRA]
Does that mean I'm right?
And have you been keeping
this memory loss hidden?
But for what reason?
Maybe your sorceress
friend knows?
I bet it would be fascinating
to discover why
you've lost your memories.
[KAMIJO]
I won't reveal it.
For her sake.
I've made it this far
without telling anyone!
Well, I suppose
it doesn't matter
since you're about to die.
[KAMIJO]
I won't let him get to me.
I have to figure out what
his spell's weakness is.
[TERRA] Oh, no, does this mean
you won't be coming for me?
In that case...
[TERRA]
Precedence.
Stone lower, skin higher.
[KAMIJO]
Now how could that be?
You deflected Itsuwa's spear
and Tsuchimikado's spell.
So why couldn't your
Precedence defend
against a simple wallet?
Now that I think
about it, it's strange.
Even after taking a
direct hit from that blade,
Itsuwa and I are still alive.
You've got no reason
to hold back on us,
or allow us to escape.
Which makes it all very simple.
It's not that you
decided not to kill us.
It's that you couldn't!
The spell won't work on more
than one target at a time!
Or am I wrong?
There are still some kinks
to work out, you're right.
But what good is
knowing that gonna do?
It's going to take a
whole lot more than that
to successfully defeat
Terra of the Left!
Terra!
[TERRA]
Precedence!
The floor lower, flour higher!
[KAMIJO grunts]
What is your reason for
taking things this far?
To drag a whole city
in like this?
You really think it's worth it?
[TERRA] Ha, I believe
Academy City is to blame
for the majority
of this commotion.
Which reminds me of
something I've been wondering.
Is mankind currently
worthy of the ultimate goal
set by Church of
the Cross followers--
The Holy Kingdom?
And that's the extent?
That's your salvation?
I don't believe the God
of Roman Orthodoxy
spread his teachings to
give rise to this conflict!
[KAMIJO] If you're going
to redefine salvation
just to gratify yourself,
then allow me to lay
that fantasy to rest.
Right here and right now!
[KAMIJO yelling]
[TERRA]
Precedence!
You're just too slow!
[TERRA]
Why, you damned heathen monkey!
Precedence!
Body lower, flour higher!
[KAMIJO]
You can cut the body.
But I guess you just
couldn't cut the shotgun.
Ya know...
It really is the most
sorry excuse for a power!
You aren't that strong at all.
Just some jerk pretending to be.
All while hiding in
your comfort zone.
Itsuwa and I can hold
our own on the battlefield.
No way in hell are you stronger!
[KAMIJO gasps]
[TERRA laughs]
Look at that.
It seems your Imagine Breaker
is incompatible with us.
Honestly.
It almost feels as though
our efforts are being rejected.
Aren't you going to ask?
About your right hand's
Imagine Breaker?
[KAMIJO]
You know about it?
[TERRA chuckles]
If you're asking
me for confirmation,
then it would seem you
really have lost your memory.
It's fairly simple to explain.
Your Imagine Breaker
is actually--
[KAMIJO grunts]
What the--?
[TERRA yelling]
[KAMIJO]
Terra!
[ACCELERATOR]
Jeez..
If I don't find anything
in the next ten minutes,
I'm out of here.
You guys can keep searching
after it cools down a bit.
[LIDVIA] Now that they've
eliminated the original sin
that binds them to humanity,
they are searching for a
method to become like angels.
[STIYL] All right, and what
does that have to do
with the Right Seat's name?
The word "right" in this
sense means Equivalent.
The angels Lucifer
and Michael were a pair,
until one defeated the other.
And thus obtained the
power that allowed them
to sit on the right,
or equal, side of God.
So then you're saying
that their ultimate goal
is to attain the place
occupied by Michael?
Well, no. That is...
They want the seat,
but it's not their endgame.
Once they possess that
power, they can use it
to transform from angels
into something more.
Or so they seem to believe.
"La persona superiore
a Dio." Or "Kamijo."
[ACQUA]
I hear Avignon has been torn up.
But you seem to be
all right, Terra.
A-ha.
As long as the attacks
are all the same type
or are delivered one at a time,
my Precedence serves
me quite well.
I also heard the
Document of C was lost.
Yet, despite that failure,
you seem to be in good spirits.
[TERRA]
Acqua.
I'm sure word has
reached you by now,
but I've heard the Russian
Church has officially decided
to ally with us.
Our foothold for
the invasion of Japan
is about to become a whole
lot stronger with their support.
We should consult
with Fiamma of the Right
to decide how we need
to deploy our forces.
[ACQUA]
Very well.
But before we do that,
I need to have a word with you.
I've heard some disturbing
rumors I'm hoping
you can clarify.
These reports are saying
you're using children
and tourists in Roman
suburbs to improve
the alignment of your spell?
Oh, yes. Of course.
Is that really something
to fuss over, though?
It works.
I'm sure.
I just thought you were
supposed to be representing
salvation for all people
of the world equally.
[TERRA]
I'll have you know.
I've only ever used heathens
as my test subjects.
They've been a blessing,
thanks to their contribution,
I've discovered new
improvements and realignments
that my Light's
Executioner needs.
[ACQUA]
But first...
I'm afraid there's
something more pressing
that needs to be done.
[ACQUA grunts]
[TERRA groaning]
[ACQUA] Just so you know,
there is absolutely no way
God will ever choose
you as one of His own.
He knows everything
you've done, Terra.
You can ask Him all about it
yourself at Final Judgment.
[ROMAN POPE] This is the
Basilica of San Pietro.
As a member of the
vaunted Right Seat of God,
one would hope you would
have better manners
than to destroy it in the
presence of the Roman pope.
[ACQUA]
I apologize.
Tell me.
What is the next move
you're going to make?
[ACQUA] Vento is unable to act,
and Terra's been purged.
So that leaves only
one course of action.
And what could that be?
You're planning to attack Japan
by way of Russia as Terra said?
[ACQUA] This incident
has taught me something.
Civilians should not
stand on the battlefield.
Only soldiers need
to cross swords.
I see.
You're saying it will be you.
As a member of the
Right Seat of God,
and one who bears
the qualities of a saint,
you will step up.
Acqua of the Rear.
[KAMIJO]
You know about it?
[TERRA laughs]
If you're asking
me for confirmation,
then it would seem you really
have lost your memory.
[MIKOTO]
What's going on?!
Amnesia?
Him?
[KAMIJO] In a city on the
verge of its law collapsing,
an organization lurks
in the darkness.
Who will slip through
the tangle of outcry
and bullets to survive?
Next time, "The Dark
Side of Academy City."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.