[MP] When did you
last replace your shaft?
After the mop up, sir.
That was six days ago.
Right. She's clear.
Okay, you're good. Who's next?
I'm with squad 42.
Christa Lenz, sir!
[MP] Well, let's take a look.
[CADET] So now we can
actually get in trouble
for killing Titans?
Yeah, it's crazy, but they
were valuable test subjects.
I know that. What I
don't understand is why
they're trying to find
the killer among the cadets.
[CADET] Right, we're
worn out enough as it is
[CADET] from cleaning
up the battlefield.
[CADET] Who'd have the energy?
Guess someone hated
lookin' at those Titans
even more than I did.
Mm. The sad thing is they
may've actually helped
the Titans more than anything.
All that knowledge lost,
and for what, someone's
personal revenge?
It just doesn't
make any sense.
Well, it might sound dumb,
but I'm glad they did it.
Before I'd actually seen
a Titan, I was convinced
I wanted to be a Scout
and take 'em all on.
[CONNY] Now I never wanna
lay eyes on one again.
[CONNY] And today, we have'ta
pick which Regiment to join.
[CONNY] Jean. Are you
really gonna do it?
[crying]
[JEAN] I guess regret's
the order of the day.
[JEAN] Right about now, we're
all wondering why the hell
[JEAN] we ever
put on this uniform.
[JEAN] Standing here,
watching our friends burn.
[JEAN] How could we possibly
think anything else?
Sorry, Marco.
[JEAN] I don't even
know which of these bones
[JEAN] are yours, anymore.
[JEAN] If I hadn't
become a soldier,
[JEAN] I would've never had
to worry about who's next.
[EREN] So, you're tellin'
me it's better to just
[EREN] cut our
losses, is that it?
Let all the death and
destruction be meaningless?
[JEAN] We have to fight. I know
that's the right thing to do.
[JEAN] But I also know I'm not
a suicidal maniac like he is.
[thuds]
Huh?
Promise me you're not gonna
take this the wrong way.
[MARCO] But I don't
think you're a good leader
[MARCO] 'cause you're strong.
I think it's 'cause you
know what it is to be weak.
[MARCO] You're one of us.
You're scared out of your
mind, just like we all are.
It makes you
alert; sympathetic.
[JEAN] So, what
am I going to do now?
Hey guys. Question for you.
[YMIR AND CHRISTA] Huh?
So have you decided yet?
Which regiment
you're gonna join?
I've made my choice.
It'll be rough, but--
Dammit. I'm gonna
join the Scouts!
[Jean crying]
Ah, hell. Hey, Annie.
You think Jean meant it?
[CONNY] You think
he's serious about
[CONNY] signing
up with the Scouts?
Wait. Jean said that?
Who cares?
So you're sticking
with the MPs, huh?
I'm really startin' to think
I might go that way, too.
Tell me something.
If someone ordered you
to die, would you do it?
[CONNY] W-What? Of course not.
Well, then my advice
is do what's best for you.
[ANNIE] And what
about you, Armin?
[ARMIN] Oh, uh,
I think I might.
If the situation
truly called for it.
And I knew that my
sacrifice might save others.
[ARMIN] Not that I'd want to.
So, you've decided then.
[ARMIN] Mm. I've planned to
join the Scouts from the start.
[CONNY] Come on.
Not you too, Armin?
[ANNIE] I'm impressed.
For a mouse, you've got guts;
[ANNIE] I'll give you that.
Uh. Thanks, I guess.
[ARMIN] You know,
I'm beginning to suspect
[ARMIN] you care
more than you let on.
Huh?
[ARMIN] It's just, the way
you're trying to discourage us
[ARMIN] from the Scouts,
you're looking out for us.
Is that why you're
joining the MPs?
I bet you think you can
do some good there too, huh?
No, not really.
I just want to live.
The only person I'm
looking out for is myself.
[GUNTHER] After that whole
inspection, they didn't turn up
one person who used their
ODM gear without permission.
So who could'a done it?
Beats me. And right now,
I'm more concerned with
the recruitment
drive tonight.
How many cadets are
crazy enough to join
the regiment with
the highest casualties?
Hey, Eren! You
know if anyone in
[GUNTHER] your class is
thinking about joining us?
Yeah, there're a few.
Or, at least, there were.
I'm really not so sure now.
[GUNTHER] Fall in!
[LEVI] Make ready, people!
We're going on patrol.
[BOTH] Yes, sir!
Good morning, captain!
Reporting for duty!
[LEVI] Eren.
You will stay within
[LEVI] ten meters
of me at all times.
The only reason that you're
out of your cell is because
I'm keeping an eye
on you. Understood?
Yes, sir!
[LEVI] Let's ride!
[LEVI] Hyah!
♪
[nervous chatter]
[ARMIN] Jean! You're
really set on the Scouts?
Yeah.
Whoa, are you serious? I
mean. Aren't you terrified?
Huh? Of course I'm scared,
I'm not an idiot here.
[CONNY] Uh. Then why are you--?
[JEAN] Because I am
scared of the Titans.
[JEAN] And I want to
do somethin' about it.
Huh?
[JEAN] But listen, I
understand that joining
the Scouts isn't for everybody.
I won't guilt trip you.
Unlike a certain
suicidal maniac.
Eren, huh?
Guess he's already been a Scout
for a while now, hasn't he?
[SOLDIER] Cadets! Fall in!
Head over to the platform!
Time to make your
choice! Move it!
At the end of the day, there's
nothing that anyone could
say to persuade you
into risking your life.
[JEAN] Same goes for me.
So believe me when I say
this decision is all mine.
[ERWIN] Good evening.
[ERWIN] I am Erwin Smith,
Commander of the Survey Corp,
[ERWIN] also known
as the Scout Regiment.
[ERWIN] Today, you will
choose your regiment.
Let's cut to the chase
here. The Scouts need you.
We need all the
warm bodies we can get.
[ERWIN] After the recent Titan
attack, you now know first-hand
[ERWIN] the horrors of
which they are capable.
[ERWIN] As well as the
limits of your own skill.
[ERWIN] However...!
This battle's
aftermath gave humanity
a new chance for victory.
I refer to Eren Jaeger.
[ERWIN] After selflessly
risking life and limb,
[ERWIN] he has proven,
beyond a doubt,
[ERWIN] his unwavering
loyalty to our cause.
Hope lives in him.
Eren didn't just help to
deter the Titan invasion.
He's offered us a means to
discern the truth
of their origin!
[various chattering]
[ERWIN] Intel suggests that
the cellar of Jaeger's home
[ERWIN] in Shiganshina
holds a vital secret
[ERWIN] regarding our enemy.
[ERWIN] We will form an
expedition to find this secret.
[ERWIN] Find it.
And use it to break free
[ERWIN] from the Titans'
tyrannical hundred-year reign
once and for all!
[gasping]
The cellar, huh?
[CADET 1] Things have
progressed this far?
[CADET 2] If we can figure
out what makes 'em tick,
[CADET 2] we can hit
'em where it hurts!
[ARMIN] I know the Scouts
desperately need recruits,
[ARMIN] but going public
with this is out of line!
[ARMIN] Maybe it's a
ploy. A covert strategy?
[ARMIN] Question is
if he's baited the hook,
[ARMIN] who does
he intend to catch?
[ERWIN] Before we can
reach the aforementioned
[ERWIN] cellar in Shiganshina,
[ERWIN] another problem
must be dealt with.
We must first
retake Wall Maria.
Of course, this is much
easier said than done.
[ERWIN] And now
that the gate at Trost
[ERWIN] has been
rendered inaccessible,
[ERWIN] we'll be forced
to stage future operations
[ERWIN] from the Calanath
District, further east.
Thus, the battalion route
we've spent the last four years
[ERWIN] establishing is now
completely useless to us.
[ERWIN] Over the course
of those four years,
[ERWIN] we've incurred
losses in excess of 60%.
[ERWIN] 60% in four years.
[ERWIN] That's a
horrifying figure.
[ERWIN] One month from now,
we will conduct a recon
mission outside the walls.
Recruits from
among your ranks
will be expected
to take part.
[ERWIN] I estimate a
third of them will die.
[ERWIN] After four years,
most will be dead.
[ERWIN] But those who
endure will be amongst
[ERWIN] the most
capable soldiers alive.
Now having heard this
dismal state of affairs,
[ERWIN] whoever still wishes
to put their life on the line
[ERWIN] and join
us, remain here.
[ERWIN] But first ask yourself.
Can you give your heart?
[ERWIN] Can you give
everything for humanity?
[worried reactions]
[ERWIN] That is all.
[ERWIN] Those wanting to join
other regiments are dismissed.
[DARIUS] Commander!
I think that you may've
overly intimidated
the cadets, sir.
[DARIUS] None of them
are gonna stick around.
♪
[JEAN] Dammit! C'mon,
I've already decided.
[JEAN] Stop making me
feel like such a fool.
[SASHA] If I don't leave now,
[SASHA] I'll have to
go through it all again.
[CONNY] I left my village.
The MPs were the whole point.
[CONNY] I wanted
Mom to be proud.
to be treated right.
[CONNY] Everyone
respects them. Period.
[JEAN] But there's
no going back.
[JEAN] Not
after you've seen it.
[SASHA] Seen
them up close, and--
[CONNY] Seen
how they eat people.
[yell]
♪
I ask you, if you were
ordered to die, could you do it?
[CADET] We don't
wanna die, sir.
Of course. Let us
hope that you don't then.
You who stayed,
you are now one of us.
Allow me to welcome
you to the Scout Regiment.
This is a genuine
salute, soldiers!
Together, we give our hearts!
Sir!
Everyone.
Joined the Scouts.
This is so stupid.
This is scary!
I just wanna go home.
Ah, man. What the hell?
If you're gonna keep
crying, then don't stay.
Those of you standing here
have worked through your fear.
You have proven
yourselves courageous.
[ERWIN] Each one
of you has my respect.
♪
[JEAN] Attention!
[MAN] I'm Section
Commander Ness.
And this girl is
my horse, Charrette.
Fair warning. Charette is
rather partial to pulling hair.
So I'd watch out if
you don't wanna go bald.
We're glad to meetcha.
[NESS] Hey,
stop that, ya freak!
Can I get a
hand here, you guys?
[NARRATOR] Our training
began in earnest the next day.
[NARRATOR] However, the lessons
were rarely combat-oriented.
[NARRATOR] With an emphasis
on memorizing Commander Erwin's
[NARRATOR] long-range
scouting formation.
[NARRATOR] Despite being
such a precisely detailed,
[NARRATOR] meticulously
calculated formation,
[NARRATOR] Eren
Jaeger's position was
[NARRATOR] somewhat
less than clear.
[NESS] You rookies
will be here.
[NESS] between the
wagon defense squad
[NESS] and the
Scout support squad.
[NESS] You will
run spare horses
[NESS] as well
as relay signals.
[GUNTHER] Our Special Ops
squad'll be positioned here,
[GUNTHER] on standby.
Behind the center rank.
So we'll be
pretty far back then.
[GUNTHER] It's the safest
position in the formation.
[GUNTHER] The supply
wagons don't even
get such fine treatment.
Our goal this time around is to
simply leave, then come back.
Today's expedition will
serve as a sort of test run.
[GUNTHER] To see if we've
got a shot at getting you
[GUNTHER] all the
way to Shiganshina.
Understood. Either way,
I still don't really know
how to use my ability
or if I can even control it.
Eren. Do you understand
what the Commander was
asking you about back then?
[EREN] Huh?
Who do you think
the real enemy is here?
What did he mean by that?
What do you guys think?
Not a clue.
Well, if I told you
that I knew what he meant,
I'd be lying to
you. That said I--
[GUNTHER] It's entirely
feasible, that this operation
has an alternate goal.
And yet, the Commander
has decided it's best
to withhold it from
the rank and file.
If that's the case,
leaving and coming back
[GUNTHER] is all we need
to concern ourselves with.
[GUNTHER] Have faith
in the Commander.
I will.
[GUNTHER] Today's training
has concluded. Return to base.
Whoa. I don't believe it!
Oruo! May I be excused to
talk to my
friends for a minute?
Fine. Just don't
take too long.
Hey Mikasa! Armin!
Eren!
Man, am I glad
to see you guys!
Eren. Have they
mistreated you in any way?
Like subjecting you
to any cruel experiments,
or some sort
of mental anguish?
[EREN] No. N-Not at all.
That pipsqueak took
things way too far.
I will make him
pay for it one day.
[EREN] Hold on.
You mean Captain Levi?
[CONNY] Hey! Eren!
[SASHA] Long time no see!
[EREN] Oh, hey guys.
You're all here!
[EREN] Whoa, wait.
If all of you are here,
then does that mean--
You're saying that you
guys all joined the Scouts?
Well, yeah. Why
else would we be here?
[EREN] Of course. So then
Jean, Annie, and Marco
[EREN] went to the
Military Police then?
[EREN] Wait a sec.
You joined, too?
Marco is dead.
He what? Wait,
what are you saying?
Marco's not dead.
You're just kidding
around, right?
I wish I could tell you
he died nobly or heroically.
Truth is, I don't even
know how he went out.
[JEAN] He died alone. There was
no one there to see it happen.
Marco's dead.
[NESS] Alright,
rookies! Form up!
Your uniforms are here!
♪
[EREN] So then,
you guys are really...
Yes. We will be in the
upcoming operation as well.
Hey. Eren. I heard that while
you were in your Titan form,
you intentionally
tried to crush Mikasa.
You mind telling us
what that's all about?
You're wrong. He
thought he was just
swatting a fly, nothing more.
[JEAN] I wasn't asking you.
Oh, by the way. That cut on
your cheek looks pretty deep.
Just how did you
get that, again?
Apparently it's all true.
When I was a Titan I--
I tried to kill Mikasa.
"Apparently?" As in
you don't remember
whether you did or not?
So basically, you
can transform into a
14-meter tall monster
at will, but when you do,
[JEAN] you don't actually
have full control over it?
Not yet. But that's right.
Do you hear that everyone?
What a fine situation this is.
Our lives and the fate of all
mankind rest on his shoulders.
[JEAN] I'm guessin' we'll
probably all end up like Marco,
[JEAN] dead well before
Eren even knows it.
Stop it! What's the point
in chastising Eren now?
Just give it a rest.
[JEAN] Listen, Mikasa. Unlike
you, most of the rest of us
aren't willing to
just throw our lives away
for him on a whim.
[JEAN] We need a
reason. The truth.
We want to know what we're
laying our lives down for.
[JEAN] Otherwise,
we might hesitate
[JEAN] when
the time is at hand.
[JEAN] What we want is
a guarantee from Eren.
[JEAN] Show us what you're
worth. Prove it to us.
[JEAN] We're asking
you to make us believe
[JEAN] that you're
worth dying for.
[JEAN] You think
you can do that?
If you can, then we're
with you. All the way!
[EREN] Right.
[GARRISON] Commander.
The time approaches.
[GARRISON] Titans in the
vicinity have been lured away!
[GARRISON] Gate opens
in thirty seconds!
Awesome, it's the Scouts!
See that symbol? They call
it the Wings of Freedom!
[GIRL] So cool!
[DARIUS] This is it! The
day has come for humanity
to take another step forward!
[DARIUS] Now let's
show those Titans
[DARIUS] exactly
what we're made of!
[cheering]
[GARRISON] Open the gate!
[ERWIN] Forward!
[ERWIN] It's officially begun.
The 57th Recon Mission!
Scouts, move out!
[NARRATOR] The Scout
Regiment takes up its
[NARRATOR] long-range
scouting formation,
[NARRATOR] and begins to
make progress beyond the wall.
[NARRATOR] Their efforts,
however, come to an abrupt halt.
[NARRATOR] A new
foe presents itself.
[NARRATOR] An enigmatic
Titan displaying intelligence.