[ERWIN] It's officially begun.
The 57th Recon Mission!
[ERWIN] Scouts, move out!
[ERWIN] Intel suggests
that the cellar of
[ERWIN] Jaeger's
home in Shiganshina
[ERWIN] holds a vital
secret regarding our enemy.
[ERWIN] That's our destination.
[NESS] You rookies
will be here. Between the
[NESS] wagon defense squad
and the Scout support squad.
[NESS] You will
run spare horses,
[NESS] as well
as relay signals.
Beyond that will be
uninterrupted Titan territory.
We'll be more
or less on our own.
[GUNTHER] The only thing
to fall back on out there is
[GUNTHER] Commander Erwin's
long-range scouting formation.
[GUNTHER] The special ops
squad will be positioned here.
[ARMIN] We're not
dealing with an Abnormal.
[ARMIN] This thing's
showing intelligence!
[ARMIN] Like the Colossal.
[ARMIN] Like Eren!
[ARMIN] It's a human being
wrapped in a Titan body!
[JEAN] The moves on this one,
she's like a damn athlete!
[JEAN] We are so screwed!
[JEAN] What? She's
protecting her weak spot?
[JEAN] Damn it!
There's nothing I can do.
Jean! Don't let that
suicidal maniac die in vain!
[JEAN] Why did she stop?
[ARMIN] She did it!
She's the one who killed him!
[ARMIN] I told him the
right wing was suicide
[ARMIN] but he
went along anyway!
[ARMIN] And how he's
dead, thanks to her!
Oh no.
Odds are that bought the
platoon more than enough time.
I say we follow suit,
and get outta here!
[ARMIN] What? Wait. No.
[ARMIN] She's--
She's going for Eren!
[whistle call]
[REINER] Where'd they get
this? How old's your gear?
[ARMIN] Don't worry about it.
[ARMIN] It came off like it's
supposed to, so it didn't break.
[ARMIN] Should still
be in decent shape.
All right. That's
something, then.
Still down a horse, though.
Not an ideal situation.
[whistle call]
We can't get movin' again
until Jean's ride shows up.
[JEAN] Just my luck.
[JEAN] Reiner's horse comes
back like an old lover.
[JEAN] Why the hell's
mine gotta go AWOL?
[whistle call]
[JEAN] Damn it.
We can't afford to
[JEAN] stay out in
the open like this.
[JEAN] If worse comes to worse,
[JEAN] one of us'll
have to get left behind.
[JEAN] What are we supposed
to do? Draw straws?
[JEAN] Armin's hurt. Reiner's
too big to ride with safely.
[JEAN] Maybe I should
just take my chances
[JEAN] horse-retrieving on foot.
Dammit!
[JEAN] How messed up
is it that we might even
[JEAN] have to
even consider that?
[JEAN] Out of the
frying pan, into the fire.
[JEAN] It's what we get for
narrowly escaping death.
[whistle call]
[shaky breath]
[REINER] Armin.
[REINER] You with me?
I guess your head's still
a little shaken up, huh?
Um. I might still be
a little foggy, yeah.
It's okay. The
choice isn't gonna be
any easier with
you thinkin' clearly.
[REINER] One of us is
gonna have to stay here.
[REINER] We need
to figure out who.
Wait a sec! I mean
shouldn't we at least
fire off a smoke signal first?
If everyone kept
going straight, Row Four,
Squad Three ought to be in
close proximity to us by now.
Well, that's the emergency
signal, but who knows?
I doubt anyone's
gonna see it and think,
"Hey, somebody must
need an extra horse."
Armin. Listen. We
only wait three minutes.
If no one shows, we
have to decide who stays.
[ARMIN] It should be me.
But, if I'm going to be
left out here in the open,
I need you to relay a message.
If possible, give it
only to Commander Erwin.
[JEAN] Hang on, Armin!
[JEAN] Looks like you'll be
able to tell him yourself.
Someone answered
the call! Hell yes!
They've got two horses in tow!
Huh?
[JEAN] Whoa, that's--
[JEAN] It's Christa!
Hey guys, you alright?
[JEAN] Well, damn! That's
my li'l runaway! [chuckling]
[JEAN] Easy, Buchwald.
It's okay. I forgive you.
[CHRISTA] Poor thing.
He ran to me like
[CHRISTA] the devil
was on his tail.
[CHRISTA] So did
you guys fight a Titan?
Oh, no! Armin, your
head! You've been hurt!
[ARMIN] It's nothing. Promise.
[REINER] I'm impressed
someone actually answered
[REINER] our distress signal.
Well I wasn't far away, so.
That and I found the horse.
A lot of people wouldn't have
risked the trek over here.
You're as noble as
the steeds you tame.
We're all in your debt.
It was nothing.
I'm just-- I'm just
glad that you're all okay.
What would we do without you?
[ARMIN] She's an angel.
[JEAN] A goddess.
[REINER] One day, my wife.
[CHRISTA] Okay. I suppose we'd
better rejoin the formation.
[JEAN] Yeah! They'll order
a retreat any minute now!
[JEAN] I'll just say it.
I'm glad we survived,
[JEAN] but heading
back after only an hour?
[JEAN] Not really something
to be proud of, if you ask me.
[JEAN] And while we're on the
subject, is anybody else curious
[JEAN] why she's headed
away from the command squad?
[CHRISTA] She?
[JEAN] Green smoke?
[ARMIN] Looks like we're
not heading back after all,
[ARMIN] just changing course.
Yeah, but that
doesn't make sense!
What the hell? Is Commander
Erwin out of his mind?
Every one of us
has the authority
to declare the mission failed.
Why isn't anyone speaking up?
Is the command squad too
far ahead to see their signals?
Possibly. But either way,
I think our course is clear.
Assume command's got this.
[LEVI] Smoke signals. Green.
[LEVI] Oruo, pass it on.
With pleasure, sir!
[EREN] Things seem to be going
pretty smoothly for the moment.
[EREN] Still. I wonder
how it really is.
[EREN] My gut tells
me the frontline's
[EREN] already
taken a serious hit.
[MAN] Reporting, sir!
[MAN] An oral message! It
appears the right-wing spotters
have been wiped out!
[MAN] The early warning
network is compromised.
[MAN] One of you will need to
relay the message down the line.
You heard the
man, Petra. Go on.
Sir!
[EREN] The right wing? That's
where Armin's positioned!
[EREN] Still. He wasn't
with the outliers.
[EREN] He and the others
were more toward the center.
[EREN] Surely the Titans
haven't made it that far in?
[EREN] Black smoke?
An Abnormal!
Eren. Fire the signal.
Yes, sir.
This is a disgrace.
Lotta good the formation does
if the bastards can
bore into it that deeply.
[EREN] So close. Too close.
[EREN] Just under
that smoke, someone--
[EREN] someone's fighting.
[DARIUS] Damn it.
I'm right in front of you!
Look down, you monster!
Now!
[DARIUS] We've got you now!
You're clever, but I'd like to
[DARIUS] see you defend
all three weak spots at once!
Cut the Achilles'
Heel! The spinal cord!
Whatever brings the
bitch to her knees! Attack!
For the soldiers you've killed!
We're gonna
make sure this hurts!
She jumped?
[SOLDIER] Put me
down! Put me down!
♪
[DARIUS] I have
to tell the others!
[DARIUS] She can't be allowed
to take anyone else by surprise!
The platoon will be decimated!
[frightened yell]
[SOLDIER 1] An Abnormal?
[SOLDIER 2] This far
in? Let's take it out!
We can't let it
make any more headway!
[SOLDIER] Well if the right
wing's been all but annihilated,
[SOLDIER] why in the
hell aren't we retreating?
Don't know!
Commander's orders!
Just keep the
message moving left!
[SOLDIER 1]
So what's the story?
[SOLDIER 1] How
far's the commander
[SOLDIER 1] gonna
let us run off course?
[SOLDIER 2] Your guess
is as good as mine.
[SOLDIER 2] We should
be heading south, not east.
This is crazy. We'll run
right into the damn thing!
Yeah. And look up ahead.
[SOLDIER] Just what we need.
[ERWIN] Titans
have used this path.
Lack of vegetation's
a giveaway.
It should be a
cinch for the wagons.
[ERWIN] Inform everyone behind
us. Only the center wagon
[ERWIN] defense squad
is to enter this forest.
[BOTH SOLDIERS] Yes, sir!
Excuse me, sir. It looks
as though the center rank
is heading straight
into the forest.
Won't we run smack dab into
the trees if we follow them?
We'll go around.
Um. Yes, sir!
[JEAN] You're kidding me.
[JEAN] We on a
sight-seeing tour now or what?
[JEAN] How much further they
want us to stray off course?
[JEAN] This is ridiculous!
Bizarre. But so be it.
Commander Erwin must
have something in mind.
Perhaps the situation
compels him to improvise.
That gives me a
lot of confidence.
Maybe he's looking
for a nice, shady spot
to throw all the rookies
a celebratory picnic.
Uh. I rather doubt that.
Lighten up. Point is,
I'm praying he doesn't
[JEAN] intend for
us to camp here.
[JEAN] Not with that
Female Titan on our ass.
[JEAN] We'd be sittin' ducks.
He's got to know that.
Yeah, we're just passing through
on the way to somewhere else;
no one in his right mind
would make us stop here.
[SQUAD CAPTAIN]
All soldiers, halt!
Alright, rookies! Listen up!
[SQUAD CAPTAIN] We're
assuming intercept position
[SQUAD CAPTAIN]
within the trees!
[SQUAD CAPTAIN] Unsheathe
and find a perch!
[SQUAD CAPTAIN] If any Titans
attempt to enter the forest,
stop them, whatever it takes!
Uh... Excuse me, sir?
What exactly is the--
[SQUAD CAPTAIN]
I've given you an order!
Okay. What the
hell's going on?
So. Hey. Only the center rank
is going into the forest then?
[CONNY] What about
the formation?
Apparently it's breaking up.
[MIKASA] The path isn't wide
enough for the side ranks.
[MIKASA] We have to go around.
It's the only tactical option.
Even if it means
we're useless as spotters.
But couldn't we have just
avoided the forest altogether?
The commander misread a map and
realize it too late, or what?
No clue. Maybe we're
here to shake the threat
that's been on our right.
The trees make a decent
cover, I suppose. Maybe.
[JEAN] Do you believe this B.S.?
[JEAN] Am I the only one who
wonders what happened with
[JEAN] the whole "logistics
base," thing? Or why we didn't
[JEAN] go galloping home after
the Female Titan showed up?
[JEAN] Why're we suddenly
all playing birdhouse?
[JEAN] Oh wait, no.
I know the last one.
[JEAN] No, Titans allowed in the
center rank's nature retreat.
Fool. He's got no
idea what's going on.
He'll hear you.
What do I care? He's
not explaining anything
to the ones risking
their lives. Look at him.
He acts all
calm and in control,
but you can
see he's petrified.
What do you mean?
They say when officers in the
field are deemed incompetent
by their men they
can be relieved of duty.
Or in more extreme
cases, they can die from
mysterious stab wounds to
the back. I suppose there's
all kinds of accidents
that could happen out here.
Hold on. Whatever you're
thinking of doing...
Look, I'm just talkin'.
The whole situation's screwed
and I need to vent, alright?
I'm not gonna start a mutiny.
Well, not yet anyway.
[JEAN] Just answer me this.
You agree with this strategy or
is it a bunch of crap? Really.
[JEAN] 'Cause you look like
you know something I don't.
Well, um.
[SQUAD CAPTAIN] 5-meter
Titan approaching!
[ARMIN] Why did the commander
opt to bring us here?
[ARMIN] I can't make sense
of it. What was he thinking?
[ARMIN] No. That's wrong.
[ARMIN] That's not the
question I should be asking.
[ARMIN] The real puzzle is this:
[ARMIN] if the Female Titan
is in fact pursuing Eren,
[ARMIN] does Erwin know?
Is that why we're here?
[EREN] Captain! Captain Levi!
[LEVI] What?
C'mon, sir! We're in a forest!
We won't see a Titan 'til
it's right on top of us!
The center rank's
totally cut off!
Something's coming up
on the right, isn't it?
[EREN] So what are
we supposed to do?
[EREN] Avoid Titans
or defend the wagons?
Quit whining and move
on from the obvious already.
Neither of those
is an option anymore.
Wha--? What are
you talking about?
Haven't you noticed
what's arond you?
Take a look at
these big ass trees.
[LEVI] Perfect environment for
ODM gear, wouldn't you say?
[LEVI] Take my advice, Eren.
Calm down and use your head.
[LEVI] The best survival
tool is your brain.
[EREN] Yes, sir!
[EREN] He's right. I'm new to
this, so virtually everything
[EREN] about it's gonna
throw me for a loop.
[EREN] Simple answers
are for children.
[EREN] Only way
to learn is by doing.
[EREN] If I want to
cut it with these guys,
[EREN] I've gotta stop
cryin' to be spoon-fed.
Doesn't make sense.
What are we doing here?
There's gotta be a reason.
[ORUO] I mean they know,
right? They gotta!
[EREN] Huh?
[EREN] Wait. Are we
all in the dark here?
[EREN] What the hell's
going on? Really?
[EREN] Does that mean,
even Captain Levi's clueless?
[ARMIN] Break it down
to its simplest elements.
[ARMIN] If the Titan
really is after Eren, then...
[ARMIN] there's only one
reason for our being here.
[ARMIN] Commander Erwin knows,
and he intends to confront her!
[JEAN] Armin.
[JEAN] Bear with me.
Our orders are to
[JEAN] keep Titans
out, right? Right?
[JEAN] So, I mean. We don't
actually need to fight them.
[JEAN] Yeah? Am I wrong?
♪
[EREN] Black smoke!
[ORUO] It's right behind us!
Damn thing's been on our
ass since we came in here.
[LEVI] Blades drawn. Now.
[LEVI] It'll happen in the
blink of an eye. Be ready.
♪
Go! Move it!
[GUNTHER] Holy shit!
How the hell are we supposed to
pull evasive maneuvers in here?
It's catchin' up!
Captain! Engage the ODM gear?
[PETRA] Captain?
[SOLDIER] Where you goin'?
[PETRA] Rear Reinforcements!
Captain! Your orders!
It's dangerous!
Let's take it out!
[ORUO] Tell us to engage, sir!
I'll cut the bitch!
[EREN] Stupid creature!
[EREN] You're racing full
speed to your own death!
[EREN] You're chasing
the best damn team of
[EREN] Titan-slayers
in existence!
[EREN] Captain?
Captain!
[ORUO] We need your orders, sir!
[GUNTHER] She's gaining on
us! Let's just take her out!
That's the whole reason
we're here, isn't it?
Right, sir? Captain!
[EREN] Your
orders, sir! Please!
Everyone cover your ears. Now.
[ALL] Huh?
[NARRATOR] The Female
Titan's chase leaves a trail
[NARRATOR] of
bloodshed in its wake.
[NARRATOR] Eren flees in
horror, watching as his comrades
[NARRATOR] die
right before his eyes.
[NARRATOR] The chaos
forces a decision.