[LEVI] Blades drawn. Now.
[LEVI] It'll happen in the
blink of an eye. Be ready.
Go! Move it!
[GUNTHER] Holy shit!
How the hell are we supposed to
pull evasive maneuvers in here?
It's catchin' up!
Captain! Engage the ODM gear?
[PETRA] Captain!
[SOLDIER] Where you goin'?
[PETRA] Rear Reinforcements!
[grunts]
[screams]
Captain! Your orders!
It's dangerous!
Let's take it out!
[ORUO] Tell us to engage, sir!
[GUNTHER] She's gaining on
us! Let's just take her out!
That's the whole reason
we're here, isn't it?
Right, sir? Captain!
[EREN] Your
orders, sir! Please!
Everyone cover
your ears. Now.
[ALL] Huh?
[high pitched ringing]
Was that an acoustic round?
Remind me, what is our mission?
Is it to simply act on impulse
in the heat of the moment?
[LEVI] Let me answer that
question for you. It's not.
This squad's mission is
to keep this brat alive,
whatever the cost.
Don't forget it.
[EREN] It's not
just to police me?
We keep pushing forward,
on horseback. Is that clear?
As a bell, sir!
But for how long? We
can't keep running forever!
She's right on
top of us as it is.
If we don't do something soon--
[EREN] No!
They keep coming!
They're all gonna die unless
we turn around
and do something!
Eyes front! Stop
lookin' behind us!
Seriously?
Keep pace with the group!
Maintain top speed
or we're all dead!
Eld, please! Help
them! If the Levi Squad
can't stop this thing, then
who can? Those men need us!
[EREN] Another one!
[EREN] Damn it,
he didn't have to die!
Come on,
there's still one left.
We can save him
before it's too late!
Do as you're told,
Eren! Eyes forward!
How can all of you just ignore
what's happening back there?
Are you tellin' me to
abandon my comrades? Is that it?
Damn it, yes!
Stop whining and do as
your captain tells you!
[EREN] Why are we
letting people die?
[EREN] If this is part
of some bigger picture,
[EREN] why can't
someone explain it to me?
"Ask not the reason why,
ask but to do and die!"
You'd understand
what that meant
if you weren't such
a useless greenhorn!
[ORUO] Now stifle it.
Behave like a soldier!
[EREN] No.
[EREN] I can do
this without them.
[EREN] I don't need
to rely on anyone else.
[EREN] I'm a
squad all to myself!
No, Eren! Stop!
You're only permitted
to assume Titan form
when your life's
in extreme peril!
That was the agreement!
You swore an oath!
[PETRA] Eren!
[LEVI] I wouldn't blame you.
Do as your
conscience dictates.
But Eren, listen.
You are not inherently evil.
You're ability to change
doesn't make you a monster.
That said, it could
be the other way around.
How're you supposed to
know where to draw the line?
Whether you lose control
or freely give it up.
Maybe it's the same.
And slaughter every
Titan that crosses my path!
[LEVI] Look, Eren. We don't
agree because our experience
[LEVI] brings us to
opposing views. That's life.
[LEVI] At the end of the
day, there's no reason
[LEVI] to go
against how you see it.
[LEVI] The choice is yours.
You can trust yourself.
[LEVI] Or you can trust
the people willing to
[LEVI] put their lives
on the line for you.
I don't know which way
is better. I never have.
Should I act on my own
instincts, or put myself
in the hands of my
comrades and trust them.
Either way,
there's no guarantee.
In the end, you
choose what you choose.
If afterwards, your regrets
are at a minimum, good for you.
[PETRA] Eren!
Trust us.
[LEVI] Good news. There
may be a way to stop you
[LEVI] without killing you.
[EREN] Sir?
[LEVI] In your Titan form.
We may have some
middle ground after all.
A fail-safe if you will.
The method I've come up with
will only leave you mutilated.
Well, at least in theory.
Depends on individual skill.
Essentially, we
cut the entire nape
[LEVI] from the body,
with you inside.
Your arms and legs'll
be severed halfway down
in the process,
but you'll survive.
[LEVI] As a matter of fact,
they'll probably just grow back,
[LEVI] lizard-style.
Creepy little bastard.
Hold on a sec.
I'm not really
sure how they do it.
I mean, they might but
maybe it's not worth
the risk that they won't.
Oh, I see. You're
only up for this
if there's no risk
involved whatsoever.
[EREN] No...
Then be prepared.
We're in the same boat.
If you go on a rampage you
could kill us. So we're even.
Yes, sir. Seems
perfectly fair to me.
[HANGE] Just to be clear,
I have the go-ahead, right?
We can't afford not to run
tests. So yes, you're good.
Just try to keep him from going
rogue right out of the gate.
[HANGE] Oh, not to
worry. I have a plan.
[HANGE] Eren. I know you're
still a mystery to yourself,
[HANGE] but we learn as we go.
[HANGE] Knowledge is always
worth the risk. I believe that.
[HANGE] You ready
down there, my dear?
[HANGE] When
we're good to begin,
[HANGE] I'll fire
off a smoke signal.
What happens after
that's entirely up to you.
Ready when you are, Commander!
If the boy loses control,
this well should hold him
'til he wears himself out.
If not, we'll go with
Levi's method. Perfect.
[EREN] Alright.
[EREN] It's been a while.
Since Trost, actually.
[EREN] I've got to
keep a hold of myself.
[EREN] The Levi Squad's
well within their jurisdiction
[EREN] to kill me
if I lose control.
[HANGE] Hmm.
I don't understand it.
Perhaps he missed the signal?
Perhaps. Or perhaps
we're just naive to
expect he can
turn it on and off.
[LEVI] Eren! Enough!
We're done for today.
Did something
go wrong down there?
I'm sorry. I don't
think I can do it now.
You're telling me the
bite wounds on your hands
show no sign of healing?
None, sir.
No offense, but you're not
much good to us in this form.
If you can't change, our plans
for Wall Maria go up in smoke.
Pull it together.
And yes, that is an order.
Yes, sir.
C'mon, don't lose heart,
kid. You'll get it.
Maybe, I don't know.
[ORUO] Well, that's one
hell of a way to learn
[ORUO] you're more
human than suspected.
Look at it this way, it's
a lot better to find out now
than in the field. Back
to the drawing board, huh?
He's right. No such
thing as being too careful
when so much is ridin' on you.
[EREN] How-- How can
they all be so damn calm?
[EREN] Are they
actually relieved
[EREN] I can't
turn into a Titan?
Is everything okay?
[EREN] Yeah.
[struggling]
[SOLDIER 1] What the--?
[SOLDIER 2] Titan steam?
What the hell's
going on over there?
[struggling]
Dammit why now?
[LEVI] Calm down.
I'm sorry, Captain.
I-- I don't know how I--!
The situation is
complicated. Now, calm down.
[HANGE] Please be
what I think it was.
[Hange excited shouting]
[ELD] Eren! What the hell
do you think you're doing?
Sir, please.
No one gave you permission
to transform, did they?
I said calm down--
Answer the question,
Eren! What got into you?
Leave it. Explanations
can come later.
First thing's first.
You need to persuade us
you're not hostile like
your life depends on it!
Huh?
[GUNTHER] Prove
it or we kill you!
The burden of
proof is yours, kid!
So much as twitch an arm
and I'll lob your head off!
This is the first and
only warning you'll receive!
[ORUO] I can end
you in a heartbeat!
[ORUO] Do you
understand me, boy?
Oruo! How many times
do I have to say it--
Captain! I need you to
step away. You're too close!
Right now, I believe
you're the ones
who need to step away. Do it.
Why on earth--?
A gut feeling!
Eren better say something!
[EREN] I don't--
[ORUO] Don't try anything cute!
[GUNTHER] Prove
you're not hostile!
[ORUO] Now!
[EREN] Seriously, I don't--
[ELD] This is serious!
We will kill you!
[ORUO] I'll do it!
I swear to god!
[ELD] Are you with us or not?
[GUNTHER] Can you not hear me?
[ORUO] That's it! He's dead!
Be quiet! All of
you just be quiet!
Eren!
I wanna touch the arm!
Pretty please
with sugar on top!
Let me touch
this glorious thing!
I don't think that's
such a good-- Wait, no!
[HANGE] Argh! Son of a bitch!
[HANGE] That mother is
hot when there's no skin!
[HANGE] This is the best
day in the history of science!
[MOBLIT] You're a maniac!
You hear me? A maniac!
Are you not burning
up? What's it like?
How is it connected
to your hand?
Oh you have to show me!
I really, really wanna see!
[EREN] Wait, yeah. I should
just be able to pull it out.
[EREN] Come on!
[struggling]
Are you ignoring me?
Don't try anything stupid!
[Eren stuggling]
[HANGE] No! What are you
doing? That's too soon!
I wanted to put
it under the knife!
[heavy breathing]
Sorry, Captain.
So you feelin' okay or what?
[heavy breathing]
[EREN] Not... exactly... No...
[EREN] That was quite a
wake-up call, let me tell ya.
[EREN] 'Til their
blades were drawn,
[EREN] I had no idea
how little they trusted me.
And what did you expect?
A suspicious nature
was the top of my criteria.
[LEVI] Traditionally, you're
not considered a real Scout
[LEVI] 'til
you come back alive.
But out there, there's always
so little intel to go on.
So many uncertainties
and unknowns
it's a miracle any
of us come back alive.
[LEVI] You have
to be reactive, quick.
[LEVI] Hit the ground running
while anticipating the worst.
That doesn't make
them heartless, though.
They're not just a
bunch of mindless machines.
Whatever that might've
looked like out there today,
I can promise you that
every single one of
them was conflicted.
[MOBLIT] Captain Levi.
[LEVI] Hm?
[MOBLIT] Section Commander
Hange would like a word, sir.
[LEVI] Man. How long of a
shit were you taking, anyway?
[HANGE] Oh, long enough
to get the job done.
[HANGE] Thank you for asking.
Meeting the brass can
do a number on your bowels.
But enough about that.
[HANGE]
Feast your eyes on this.
[EREN] That's the spoon, right?
[HANGE] The very one.
Your spontaneous Titan
arm erupted into being
while holding it. Like so.
Resting between the
thumb and the index finger.
The world operates on chance,
so coincidences are expected.
But this begs something more.
This utensil wasn't warped
by the heat or by the pressure.
Any thoughts on the matter?
Uh... All I know is
that I went to pick it up.
When I did the arm
came out of nowhere.
[HANGE] Interesting.
This might explain why you
couldn't change in the well.
I'm certain of it.
[HANGE] Slaying Titans.
[HANGE] Blocking cannon fire.
[HANGE] Lifting big rocks.
[HANGE] In each instance
before assuming Titan form
[HANGE] seemingly at will, there
was a distinct goal in mind.
I believe it's
possible that self-harm
isn't the only catalyst
of transformation.
It appears as
though a clear objective
is a crucial
ingredient as well.
I think you might
be on to something.
This last time was a lot like
the time with the
cannon ball. But I--
[EREN] I transformed
into a Titan
[EREN] just to
pick up a damn spoon?
[EREN] That's insane.
So, uh. What I'm getting
out of this is what you pulled
wasn't something
you did on purpose?
No, sir.
[sigh]
[gasp]
What the--? What the
hell you think you're doing?
[GUNTHER] Ow.
'Kay, that hurts like a
son of a bitch. Damn, kid.
I'm impressed you
can sink your teeth in
that deep without shrieking.
We made a judgment
call today and it was wrong.
Consider this our
way of apologizing.
That is if you can find it
in your heart to forgive us.
Huh?
We have to make spur of
the moment decisions, okay?
Make the best call we
can with what we know.
It's our job to
keep you in check!
The fact is we were scared.
That's no excuse, I know.
You've every right to be upset.
But-- All that aside,
we're doomed if we
can't trust one another.
Just as you are
if you can't trust us.
[PETRA] Eren.
I'm asking you.
[PETRA] Trust us!
♪
[LEVI] Eren! C'mon!
Make up your damn mind!
I'm with you!
[SOLDIER] No!
[EREN] Forgive me!
[GUNTHER] Target
is accelerating!
Just keep moving!
We'll outrun the bitch!
[EREN] Outrun it?
Are you kidding me?
[EREN] We keep riding with
our backs to her like this,
[EREN] we'll be crushed
before we know what hit us!
[EREN] No.
We're at death's door.
[EREN] We've seen our
comrades die left and right.
[EREN] And we're
still moving forward.
[EREN] They trust the
captain, and he trusts them.
[EREN] That's
what this is about.
[EREN] That's why they
can all keep moving.
[EREN] I-- I need
to be a part of it.
[EREN] I need to trust
them, like they trust me!
[gasps]
Fire!
Everyone hitch your
horses a bit further on.
Switch to ODM gear.
I have to break
away for a little while.
Eld's in charge
'til I get back.
[LEVI] Tuck Eren
somewhere out of sight,
[LEVI] away from
the Female Titan.
[LEVI] And see to my horse.
Wait, what?
[EREN] They're going to
take her alive? Seriously?
So what do you
think of us now, Eren?
We managed to
outsmart the damn thing!
Let this be a lesson
to you, greenhorn!
Don't ever
underestimate the Scouts!
[ORUO] Never again! Agreed?
Agreed!
She's not putting
up much of a fight.
That's no reason
to let our guard down.
[ERWIN] Good work
leading her here.
I'm more than
a little impressed.
We couldn't have
without the rear contingent
whose lives bought us
time. This belongs to them.
I don't intend
to ever forget that.
That so?
[LEVI] Yes.
Because of their sacrifices,
[LEVI] we can expose
whoever this really is.
Ten to one they're in there
pissing themselves
right about now.
[NARRATOR] Erwin
Smith's top-secret plan to
[NARRATOR] capture the
Female Titan has succeeded.
[NARRATOR] But as the
Scout Regiment attempts to
[NARRATOR] reveal
her true identity,
[NARRATOR] they find a
nasty shock waiting for them.