[MAN] That's good, Annie.
I expect the
best from my daughter.
[heavy breathing]
[ANNIE'S DAD] Move! Who
told you it was time to rest?
[MAN] Hold on. You
mean you haven't heard?
[MAN] The Titan kid and
those big shot handlers of his
[MAN] have been
summoned to the capital.
Which means they'll be
passing through here today.
Is that so? Well then
maybe this time they'll just
dissect him and
get it over with.
[MAN] I just hope he
doesn't stir up any trouble.
[MAN] I say
let him pass through
[MAN] and seal the
gate shut behind him!
Infidel! To even
suggest sealing the gate!
The hands of
heretics must never
taint the sanctity
of our Walls!
[MAN] Maria! Rose! Sina!
To even think of defiling
the three goddesses.
We tempt the
specter of damnation!
These lunatics
all worship the Walls
as if they're
some kind of gods.
It creeps me out.
Damn cult. Can't believe
they're still around.
Let's go.
Look who's finally awake!
[HITCH] You look so
terrifying when you're asleep
[HITCH] I didn't
dare disturb you.
Prob'ly should've. Sorry.
You've been pretty lax
in your duties, recently.
[HITCH] Look, Marlo.
You've upset her.
[MARLO] She's
antisocial, not upset.
Knock it off, you guys. She
fought in the Battle of Trost
before coming here. Which
makes her the only one of us
who's ever seen
any real action.
[BORIS] She's just
been through hell.
[BORIS] Probably
takes time to readjust.
[HITCH] Ah! So. You have a
crush on the new girl, huh?
[Hitch chuckling]
[HITCH] What could you
possibly see in her?
[MARLO] I dunno, Hitch. Maybe
it's that she got into the MP's
[MARLO] based on skill,
unlike some I could mention.
[HITCH] Oh. I don't know
what you're implying.
[HITCH] Why don't you clarify?
[BORIS] That's enough, you two.
[DENNIS] Great. Thanks,
guys. I called you all here
[DENNIS] 'cause I've got
actual work for you today.
Not just the same ol' crap.
It's got somethin'
to do with the Scouts
being summoned to the capital.
Sometime today, they'll
be passing through town
along the main street.
[DENNIS] HQ has already provided
a security detail, so we're
[DENNIS] only being asked to
assist until the convoy's clear.
[DENNIS] ODM use in city
limits has been authorized.
[DENNIS] You'll follow
beside the convoy,
[DENNIS] as additional security.
[DENNIS] There's a
barge waiting to take you
[DENNIS] to the starting
point. Dismissed.
Sir! A question, if I may.
[DENNIS] Hmm? Go ahead.
What exactly are
we supposed to be
protecting this
convoy from, sir?
Hmm?
It's just that I've
never heard of anyone
defying the government.
They're just glad to be safe.
There are
petty criminals, sure.
But I find it hard to imagine
any actual organization
existing within the wall
that would attempt a strike.
I mean, what possible
motive would they have?
Man! Aren't you serious?
You can be in charge of this.
[DENNIS] Everything you need
to know is right in here.
Uh... Huh?
We officers are
busy enough as it is.
Prove that you can
handle this one yourselves.
[DENNIS] Oh, and you better
not screw it up, got it?
[DENNIS] Hey, sorry 'bout
that. Back to business.
[DENNIS] Who's turn was it?
[MARLO] Damn. This stinks!
Got that right. The amount
of slacking that goes on
in this outfit is
even more than I imagined.
I mean, that is why I
chose to join, but still.
I might've thought twice
if I'd known that meant
the rookies got stuck doing
all the work all the time.
Seriously. Wish someone
would've warned me.
Bastards. They're
all irresponsible,
self absorbed
imbeciles! All of them!
Hmm. So what's
that make you, Marlo?
You chose to join
the Military Police.
You're a slacker just
like the rest of us.
You're wrong, Boris.
I'm nothing like the
rest of you degenerates!
[MARLO] I joined up
because the Military Police
[MARLO] is in
dire need of repair!
[Hitch clapping]
Wow. That was great, Marlo!
I never pegged you
for the crusader type!
Just how do
you plan to fix it?
By working my way
to the top, of course.
And then once I'm in charge.
I can install a new system
to make sure all
those who are dishonest
pay for their transgressions.
It's as simple as that.
The MPs just need a little
discipline, and nothing more.
[MARLO] I'll shape
them back into the people
[MARLO] they're supposed to be.
[Hitch laughing]
[HITCH] Wow. That is something!
[HITCH] And I thought you
were a total buzzkill before!
Well, that's a
rather lofty ideal.
So, y'know, good
luck with all that.
[ANNIE] What's the point?
I think if a do-gooder like you
was actually put in
charge of this regiment,
you'd quickly find
yourself working alone.
Really? That's the first thing
you open your mouth to say?
[ANNIE] Don't get me wrong,
I don't doubt your sincerity.
[ANNIE] I know conviction
when I see it.
[ANNIE] You're not
the first person I've met
[ANNIE] who thought they
could take on the world
[ANNIE] and change
things for the better.
[ANNIE] It takes a lot of
courage to go against the flow.
[ANNIE] I respect that.
[ANNIE] Of course, it
could be that you're all
[ANNIE] just a bunch of fools.
They might be, but don't
go lumping me in with them!
[MARLO] Is that understood?
[MARLO] Bah! Enough
chit-chat. Let's go!
[MARLO] The escort wagons
are scheduled to pass through
[MARLO] the outer gate
in forty five minutes.
[MARLO] Once we arrive, everyone
take up your positions. Got it?
[HITCH] Yeah, yeah.
Hey! Watch it, bud!
[HITCH] What's goin'
on? That's our gear.
Shipping it to the Interior?
Isn't it a bit strange,
having the Merchant's Guild
conduct the transport?
[MARLO] What're they up to?
Are those bastards illegally
selling government property?
Hey, this isn't
our assignment!
Look at him! Crusader-man's
the genuine article!
Well, I suppose we
have the time to spare.
I bet this'll be entertaining.
I'd say we've earned
ourselves a drink!
Hmm?
What do you think you're
lookin' at? Huh, rookie?
You-- You can't sell
government equipment.
It's against the law!
Is that so?
Those supplies are the property
of the hard-working citizens
who pay for
them with their taxes.
[MARLO] And that means--
[MP laughing]
Can you believe this business?
A rookie blackmailing
his superior officers!
[MP] I'm thinkin' you got a
bright future ahead of you, kid.
Go spend it on a girl, alright?
She'll help you unwind.
Wait. Hey!
What you did
was against the law!
[Marlo coughing]
[grunts and gasps]
Hey wait!
[chuckling]
You're under arrest
for a treasonable offense
against an officer.
[MARLO] Blatant disregard
for the rule of law--
[MP] Is standard
procedure! So is this!
[ANNIE] He's had enough.
Don't you think, sir?
[HITCH] So sorry
about that fellas!
I hope our idiot hasn't
caused you too much trouble.
[HITCH] We'll be sure
to drive the lesson home,
[HITCH] don't you worry!
Unless, of course...
you'd rather have...
[HITCH] a much bigger
problem on your hands.
[clears throat]
Just this once.
[ALL] Sir!
[MP 1] So, about that drink.
[MP 2] Yeah. I worked
up quite the thirst!
[ANNIE] Go ahead.
[ANNIE] Aren't you going
to "make the dishonest
[ANNIE] pay for
their transgressions"?
[ANNIE] I'm not entirely opposed
to helping you out with that.
[MP] Is it me, or do
those serving gals
[MP] get prettier
with every sip?
[MARLO] Damn it!
[MP] Hey, little lady! You
workin' hard? Or hardly working?
[WOMAN] You boys are
all the same! [giggles]
[MARLO] Those people you know.
[MARLO] The other
"fools" you mentioned.
[MARLO] Would
they have done it?
They might've.
[MARLO] I wanted to be brave.
To go against the flow.
[MARLO] But when it comes
down to it, I'm just another
[MARLO] piece of scum being
swept away by the current.
[ANNIE] Not sure
what to say about that.
Maybe... that's just a part of
what it means to be ordinary.
[ANNIE] Simply
going with the flow.
Is that so bad? To some
people it makes you weak,
[ANNIE] but an ordinary
person is all I want to be.
[horses trotting]
[MAN] Annie!
Hello.
[ARMIN] So, you're
a full-fledged MP now.
[ANNIE] Armin.
[ANNIE] So, uh.
What's with the outfit?
Why I'm in the
rain gear, you mean?
It's a makeshift disguise.
Needed to conceal
my ODM rig. See?
What's this about?
Annie. We have a
plan for Eren to escape,
and we're hoping
that you'll help us.
[ANNIE] Wait, escape to where?
Stuck behind these walls,
[ANNIE] where can you possibly
hide that they won't find you?
[ARMIN] We'll only need to
hide him for a short while.
[ARMIN] This isn't a mutiny.
[ARMIN] We have every
intention of returning.
View this as a few
loyal Scouts staging
a small act of protest.
It's a stall tactic.
We need time to gather
enough evidence to overrun
the council's ruling about
Eren. That's all we want.
You're serious about this?
How can you be so
sure the evidence exists?
And what is it?
I can't say. I'm sorry.
[sigh]
[ANNIE] Sorry, Armin.
I'm gonna have to decline.
[ANNIE] My lips are sealed,
though. Best of luck.
Hold on! Annie, please!
They're going to kill Eren!
[ARMIN] They'll kill him for
no better reason than that
[ARMIN] they fear what
they don't understand.
They don't see
that their fear is
pushing humanity to
the brink of extinction!
Maybe it's too late
to change their minds.
[ANNIE] But what if we can?
We have no choice but
[ANNIE] to bet
everything on that chance!
I'm sorry. The last thing
we want is to cause you grief.
But, well. The only
way to sneak him through
the Wall Sina checkpoints
is with the help of
someone in the Military Police!
[ARMIN] It's our only hope.
But why me? Do
I really look like
that good of a person to you?
A good person? I dunno.
Actually, I've never placed much
value in those sorts of labels.
[ARMIN] The way I see it,
"good" is merely a word
[ARMIN] applied to people who
are convenient to our needs
in some way. It's
purely subjective.
Any way you try to look at it,
labeling people
dehumanizes them.
Regardless, if you still choose
to say "no" to this request,
then at least in my eyes
that makes you a bad person.
[ANNIE] Alright.
[ANNIE] Let's go.
We made it. Can't
believe it was so easy.
Hush!
The Military Police,
hard at work.
I'm almost surprised they
bothered to show up at all.
Let's just keep moving.
[EREN] Hopefully they haven't
noticed my stand-in yet, either.
[EREN] It's not gonna hold
up under close scrutiny.
After all, Jean and
I look nothing alike.
It's close enough. You both
have that same angry scowl,
and the same boulder-sized
chip on your shoulder.
Well, yeah! But I don't
have his horse face!
Hey. So if I had refused
to help you guys out,
then what was your Plan B
for getting over the wall?
We would've used our ODM gear
to barge right
through the checkpoint.
That's stupid. Why
didn't you just avoid
all this trouble
in the first place?
You could've escaped before
reaching Stohess, right?
[ANNIE] I mean,
why wait 'til now?
[ARMIN] I felt that this town's
complex layout would allow us
[ARMIN] to squeeze a
bit more time out of
[ARMIN] our body-double ploy.
Of course. A head-on
assault is ill-advised.
So as long as the convoy acts
like it's following orders.
Then everyone keeps
their defenses down.
I see. It's a very good plan.
[ARMIN] Ah! There it is!
[ANNIE] Here?
[ARMIN] Yeah. We'll
pass through here.
[ARMIN] It's what remains of
an underground city they were
[ARMIN] planning to
build way back when.
[ARMIN] And if I'm right,
it should lead us
to the vicinity
of the outer gate.
Nice work,
Armin. That's amazing
[EREN] Annie?
[EREN] What's the matter?
You're not afraid of dark,
cramped spaces
or anything, are you?
So what? So what if I am?
I wouldn't expect a suicidal
maniac like you to understand.
You don't know what it is
to be an ordinary
girl, crippled with fear.
A girl who can flip a
full-grown man upside down
has nothing to
fear from the dark.
Cut the crap and let's move!
[ANNIE] No. I refuse.
I'm too afraid.
Above ground, I'll help.
Otherwise the deal's off.
Quit being stubborn, dammit!
Just get the hell down here!
Move! We're running
out of time, alright?
Stop shouting.
Someone will hear you.
[ANNIE] I'm sure
it's fine, Mikasa.
It seems that,
for whatever reason,
this place has
been completely deserted.
That hurts me. It really does.
[ANNIE] The way you're
looking at me now.
[ANNIE] If I didn't know better,
I'd say you didn't trust me.
[ANNIE] Eh, Armin?
Annie. Tell me.
[ARMIN] What were you doing
with Marco's ODM gear?
[ARMIN] It had all the
same dents and scrapes.
[ARMIN] See, I helped
him with maintenance,
[ARMIN] so, I know you used it.
[ANNIE] Yes. I found it.
Found it and took it.
[worried breath]
[ARMIN] Then the two
Titans we had in custody.
It was you that killed them.
No one knows.
But if you suspected
all of this a month ago,
why did you wait this
long to say anything?
Because even
now it's difficult.
I just didn't want--
I didn't want to believe
that I was right.
So I stayed quiet.
But then, out in the field.
[ARMIN] The fact that you
didn't kill me then and there.
[ARMIN] That's the moment
that set us on the path
[ARMIN] to our
current situation.
Yes. We're here
'cause I let you live.
Of course, I never
would've dreamed you'd
end up cornering
in on me like this.
[ANNIE] Why? Why didn't
I do anything then?
Annie, please! You've
taken this joke far enough.
Just tell us this is some
kinda horrible prank.
It's not too late!
Come on! We'll understand!
Come down, lets talk.
You can prove to
us that we're mistaken
by walking down these stairs!
Prove we're
wrong to accuse you!
[ANNIE] We both know I
can't. Like I told you,
I don't have the
constitution for it.
Annie, stop!
We're talking about a
matter of life and death!
Work with us, Annie!
We can reason this
out like human beings.
[MIKASA] Enough.
[MIKASA] I'm not listening
to another word of this.
No point.
[MIKASA] I'm going
to carve you up again!
Do you understand me, Titan?
[chuckling]
[Annie laughing]
[ANNIE] You know, Armin.
It's nice that I could be
[ANNIE]
a "good person" for you.
[ANNIE] For now, at least, it
looks like you won your bet.
[ANNIE] But--
I'm going to gamble, too.
And here's my wager!
[MIKASA] Eren!
[Mikasa gasp]
What're you--?
It's too late.
[screaming]
[NARRATOR] The identity
of the Female Titan
[NARRATOR] has been discovered.
[NARRATOR] All along,
it was Annie Leonhart.
[NARRATOR] However, even when
faced with irrefutable truth,
[NARRATOR] Eren can neither
bring himself to transform,
[NARRATOR] nor fight
his former comrade in arms.