[NARRATOR] In the year 845,
two terrifying new breeds
[NARRATOR] of Titan appeared:
the Colossal and the Armored,
[NARRATOR] barreling
through the outer walls as if
[NARRATOR] wholesale
destruction was child's play.
[NARRATOR] The territory
couched within the circle
[NARRATOR] of Wall
Maria was abandoned.
[NARRATOR] Twenty percent
of the human race perished.
[NARRATOR] As the
Titan onslaught advanced,
[NARRATOR] our only choice was
to withdrawal behind Wall Rose.
[NARRATOR] Five years
later, in the year 850...
[EREN] Mankind didn't
start this fight,
[EREN] but we're
gonna finish it!
[EREN] Mounted
Cannon Squad Four,
take out the Colossal Titan!
This is our chance!
Don't let it slip away!
You.
It's been a while.
[EREN] Son of a bitch.
[EREN] He took out the cannons!
[EREN] The gate
was no accident then.
[EREN] He-- He planned it.
He has intelligence!
[EREN] All the more reason
not to waste this moment!
[EREN] Without him, the
other Titans have nothing!
[EREN] I've gotta take him down!
Damn it!
Take this!
Ahhhhhhhh!
[EREN] How did I miss?
[EREN] What the--?
[EREN] Did he just
vanish into thin air?
Eren! Where'd he go? Did he
get away or'd you take him out?
He's gone! Exactly
like five years ago.
He's here one moment and
gone the next; just like that.
[EREN] I'm sorry, I--
Don't apologize. Look at us.
We were too scared to move.
Hey! Wallow on your own time!
In case you hadn't noticed,
there's a breach.
We have to act now!
If they start
pouring in, that's it!
[ELITE] Look alive!
Operation Colossal Titan
Response is in effect.
I expect you to
take part! Report to HQ!
[ELITE] If you got close to the
damn thing, we need details!
Sir!
Sir! We pray the Advance
Team will be victorious!
[chaos]
Pare down! Take only
what you need to survive!
[ELITE] File through
as calmly as possible!
[ELITE] You understand
what we're facing.
[ELITE] If they get through,
[ELITE] we'll have a
repeat of five years ago.
[ELITE] Consider this
the last line of defense!
[ELITE] The Titans get
held off here or nowhere!
[ELITE] Prepare to intercept!
[ELITE] Fire!
Soldiers, charge!
[ELITE] Out of the frying
pan and into the fire, cadets!
[ELITE] Time to put
your training to work!
I have faith each of you will
be a credit to your regiment!
I promise we'll
get through this.
You're safe as
long as I'm beside you.
[HANNA] Franz.
[EREN] Armin? What's wrong?
I-- Don't worry, I'm fine.
Just give me a second
for my nerves to settle.
[ARMIN] This is bad, isn't it?
There's a hole in the wall
[ARMIN] eight meters wide and
we don't even remotely have the
[ARMIN] engineering-
know-how to plug it.
[ARMIN] That huge boulder near
the front gate was our best bet,
[ARMIN] but we couldn't figure
out how to hoist it in place.
[ARMIN] Unless
we seal the breach,
the entire city's
as good as dead!
[ARMIN] How long do you think
before they take Wall Rose?
[ARMIN] Seriously,
how long? Think about it.
[ARMIN] Any time
the mood strikes them,
[ARMIN] they can wipe out
the human race in an afternoon!
[EREN] Armin!
Listen to me. You're focused
on the past. Look ahead.
[EREN] We're not gonna
be the victims anymore!
[ARMIN] Sorry, I-- I'm okay.
[MAN] Come now.
Take this seriously.
[MAN] Very well. Yet
another victory is mine.
[MAN] Dear oh dear. One would
think our monthly rows would see
[MAN] at least some
modest improvement
[MAN] in your approach
to the game, Pyxis.
One would think so, yes.
Clearly my brain is
inferior to yours, Lord Wald.
[laughing]
[WALD] Such obsequiousness from
the single highest-ranking
officer in the
southern territory.
Tell me. Seriously.
[WALD] How can you hope
to thwart the Titan--
[ELITE] Commander Pyxis,
sir! I bring news!
[WALD] I beg your
pardon, young man.
The Colossal Titan has laid
siege to the city of Trost!
[ELITE] Reports say the
gate has been destroyed!
Ah. This vintage is
worthy of your good taste.
One man of action to another.
I obsequiously
accept it as a gift.
[WALD] Where are
you going? Pyxis, wait!
[WALD] You can't just march
off! I command you to stay!
Preparations must be made!
[WALD] Assemble your troops
and establish a garrison
[WALD] around my
estate this instant!
Damn it all, it's your
sworn duty to defend us!
Lord Wald, Sir. Untold numbers
of our brave comrades-in-arms
are laying down their lives in
defense of Trost as we speak.
Commander, I'll go
ready the horses, Sir.
When the dust has
settled, there may well be
more graves than
people to dig them.
An astronomical number of lives
snuffed out in a twinkling.
Yes, well, no help for it,
is there? If it's their time.
Besides, what earthly good
can the presence of a man who
persistently loses to me
at chess do for them now?
Why not remain
where I can assist you?
Your lordship, if I may speak
freely. Should the commander
actually face a Titan in battle,
he won't feel compelled
to play down his skill
as he does with you.
That's enough,
soldier. Good day, Sir.
[PYXIS] I wish you another
opulently appointed day
[PYXIS] of sloth
and tranquility.
Please don't go.
Don't do this to me!
[WALD] Pyxis, please!
I'm beggin you!
[WALD] Pyxis!
[ELITE] I want everyone
split into four squadrons,
[ELITE] as practiced.
[ELITE] All squadrons are
responsible for supply-running,
ELITE] message relay,
and enemy combat
[MAN] under the command
of the Garrision Regiment!
The Intercept Squadron
will be taking the vanguard.
[ELITE] Cadets will be
taking the middle guard,
[ELITE] led by
the support squad.
[ELITE] Rear guard
will go to the elites.
[ELITE] I expect you
all to man your posts
[ELITE knowing the Advance
Team has been wiped out.
[ELITE] That's right;
the outer gate is history.
[ELITE] The Titans are in.
This means the "Armored
Titan" is likely to reappear.
[ELITE] If and when he does, the
inner gate will also be history.
Is this real?
Please be a dream.
God, what if the bastards manage
to bust through Wall Rose?
[ELITE] Quiet!
Right! Those in
the vanguard, be ready!
The whole area is
well-nigh saturated.
Your mission is
a very simple one:
Defend the wall 'til
the evacuation's done!
Now. Be aware, all of you,
that desertion is
punishable by execution!
[ELITE] If it comes to it, lay
down your lives! Dismissed!
[ALL] Sir!
[chatter]
[JEAN] Why'd this
have to happen now?
Just one more day
and I'd have been
heading for the Interior!
You gonna be alright?
[GIRL CADET] Please, no.
Please, no. Please, no.
Move it!
What the hell, man?
What's wrong with you?
What kinda question is that?
We're all about
to be Titan chow.
You expect me to sing
you a happy little song?
[JEAN] You're loving this,
aren't you, you little psycho?
[JEAN] 'Course you are!
[JEAN] You're whole life's
aspiration is to be eaten!
I was one day shy of
shipping off to the MP!
Jean! Get ahold--
No! Not all of us are suicidal!
Damn it! Shut up for second!
We're trained for this!
What do you think the
last three years were about?
We survived. We stared death
in the face and we lived.
Not everyone can
say that, can they?
Some people couldn't take it
and either ran
or were thrown out.
Hell, some people
actually died, but not us!
[EREN] Am I right? We powered
through for three years!
[EREN] What's one more day?
You can do this, Jean. Alright?
The MP will still be
waiting for you tomorrow.
Shit.
[JEAN] On your feet,
Daz. Stop bawling.
[DAZ] Um, okay.
Eren. If things take
a turn for the worse,
I want you to
come find me, alright?
What? We're in completely
different squads!
Look. This is gonna
get ugly and when it does
the plan goes out the window.
Come and find me
so I can protect you.
Who the hell do
you think you are?
[IAN] Ackermann, you're with me.
You've been assigned to the
rear guard on special orders.
Let's get moving.
[MIKASA] But, sir! I'm a
cadet! I'll slow everyone down!
What?
You're not being asked
for a self-evaluation here.
The mass exodus
is falling apart.
We need as many elite soldiers
as possible to get
things back on track.
Sir. With all due re--!
Hey!
You've been given a direct
order! Pull it together. Now!
This is bigger than the
two of us and you know it!
We're on the verge
of extinction here.
Have some damn perspective!
You're right; I'm sorry.
This whole situation
just has me out of my head.
Just promise--
Promise me one thing.
Whatever happens.
Don't get yourself killed.
[EREN] I hadn't
planned on it. Thanks.
No. I won't allow
myself to get killed.
[EREN] Not until I
taste what life is like
[EREN] outside of
these godforsaken walls.
[MAN] What surviving historical
documents we have access to
[MAN] tell us nothing
of the Titans' origin.
Almost everything
about them is obscure.
Now, that isn't to suggest
we're completely ignorant.
[Teacher] Thanks to the efforts
of the Scout Regiment,
[TEACHER] we do know
something of their ecology.
[TEACHER] Whether Titans
possess human-like intelligence
[TEACHER] is up
for debate, of course.
[TEACHER] And to date
there've been no reports
[TEACHER] of high-level
communication between them.
[TEACHER] We do know
that Titan physiology is
[TEACHER] fundamentally
different than most
[TEACHER] organic life. As
they lack reproductive organs,
[TEACHER] it's unclear
how they reproduce.
[TEACHER] Apart from this,
to all appearances,
[TEACHER] their
physique resembles
[TEACHER] the average
human male. We also know
[TEACHER] their body
temperatures run quite high.
[TEACHER] And, baffling though
it is, their appetite seems
[TEACHER] geared exclusively
towards human beings.
[TEACHER] In fact, a
Titan's driving principle
[TEACHER] seems
to be this appetite.
[TEACHER] Given that
they've subsisted for
[TEACHER] over a
century without access to
[TEACHER] their only source
of nourishment, however,
[TEACHER] we surmise that
these creatures do not in fact,
[TEACHER] consume us to live.
[TEACHER] Let that sink in.
[TEACHER] Titans aren't
motivated by hunger as such.
[TEACHER] They're
simply in it for the kill.
The terrifying vitality
of these creatures
is beyond scientific dispute.
We have only to consider events
of the recent past to see this.
[TEACHER] Mankind has long
possessed cannon technology,
[TEACHER] as you're aware.
[TEACHER] But that alone proved
tragically insufficient.
[TEACHER] Even with
their heads blown to bits,
[TEACHER] the Titans persist.
[TEACHER] Though there is
some variability on this score,
[TEACHER] a Titan's head usually
regenerates within two minutes.
Is that true?
As if their size
wasn't frightening enough.
Excuse me, sir.
Are you basically saying
that the Titans are immortal?
[TEACHER] No, I'm not.
There is, in fact,
one way to ensure death.
Strike here.
[TEACHER] If the back of their
neck takes adequate damage,
[TEACHER] a Titan
will not regenerate.
[TEACHER] This is the chink
in the proverbial armor.
[TEACHER] That, as
you may have surmised,
[TEACHER] is where
the flesh-paring blades
[TEACHER] you see here
come in. A good, deep strike
[TEACHER] with one of these
to a Titan's weak spot,
[TEACHER] and the monster
is left no time to regenerate.
[TEACHER] They
die and stay dead.
[EREN] Look at
it this way, Armin.
[EREN] It's a
golden opportunity.
I mean if we prove our
worth as soldiers right here,
we'll rise up right
through the ranks.
Before long we could even
be leading our own regiment.
We can bypass rookie
status altogether!
Sounds good. I'm
with you all the way.
Now, now boys. You're not
the only ones in your class.
Save some of the glory
for the rest of us!
Good luck beatin' us to the
punch a second time, Eren.
No head-starts
for you this round!
[EREN] Is that a challenge?
Listen up. Whoever
kills the most Titans
gets bragging rights.
[EREN] Better not
fudge your scores.
Squadron 34, move out!
The vanguard needs support!
Right! Give 'em hell!
[ALL] Yeah!
[MINA] There's so many of them!
The vanguard's been
completely overwhelmed!
I don't believe this.
Those guys always talk so big!
I thought things would
be hairy, but this...
this is insane!
[EREN] We've got
an Abnormal! Hold up!
Oh my god. Please. Help me.
♪
You bastard!
[ARMIN] Eren!
[MILIEUS] Wait!
Stay with the group!
Get back here! You're gonna
pay for killing my friend!
[EREN] You're not getting away!
You're not getting away!
Eren!
Oh god, no!
♪
[Milieus screaming]
[MILIEUS] Don't! Please
stop! I don't want to die!
♪
Why? Why?
[ARMIN] My friends
are being devoured
[ARMIN] and all
I can do is watch.
[ARMIN] What's wrong
with me? Why can't I move?
[Armin screaming]
No. Armin.
[ARMIN] Eren! Eren!
[ARMIN] Eren!
Why are you shouting?
Sorry. I found a book my
grandpa keeps hidden away!
[ARMIN] Believe it or not,
it's about life on the outside!
I really hope this
is your idea of a joke.
Stuff about the
outside world is illegal.
Seriously. You could
go to jail for that.
Trust me, you'd change
your mind if you knew
what was actually out there!
For example,
according to this book,
most of the world is covered
with salty water so deep
you can't reach the bottom!
There's a name for it, too!
They call it "The Sea!"
Like, salty for real?
C'mon, you're making it up.
If something valuable
like salt was just
floating around under water,
merchants would've
scooped it out ages ago!
That's the thing! The Sea
never runs out! It's that big!
Yeah, whatever.
Just bear with me;
there's a lot more than salt.
[ARMIN] Water that glows
like fire; fields of ice;
[ARMIN] giant rocks
that take days to climb.
[ARMIN] Imagine how huge
the outside world must be!
It does sound really neat.
Okay, you've got to promise on
your life not to tell anyone.
But my parents are, uh--
Well, they're going to
sneak outside the walls
to see for themselves.
They'll know what
it's like firsthand.
[ARMIN] Look at me.
We should do it ourselves one
day. We can have adventures
like the guy
who wrote this book.
♪
Eren!
I refuse to die
like this, understand?
Armin, listen. We're still
going to the outside world.
[EREN] The things
you told me about...
I have to see them. I have to!
Eren! No!
[Armin screaming]
♪
[NARRATOR] All of a
sudden, it's raining.
[NARRATOR] The sound
is so faint. So gentle.
[NARRATOR]
The scent so like flowers.
[NARRATOR] Odd how it can remind
you of something so horrible.