Attention!
[PYXIS] The blueprint of the
[PYXIS] Trost Recovery
Operation is this.
That's where this
fellow comes in.
Allow me to introduce
Cadet Eren Jager.
[PYXIS] Don't let
appearances deceive you.
[PYXIS] This
young man is in fact
[PYXIS] the successful product
of cutting-edge science.
[PYXIS] Recall
the massive boulder
[PYXIS] roughly a
league from the gate.
[PYXIS] Having assumed
Titan form, Cadet Jaeger will
[PYXIS] hoist said
boulder on his back,
[PYXIS] schlep it to
the hole, and voila!
[PYXIS] And this is
where you all come in.
[PYXIS] Your job will
be to defend him. Yes.
[PYXIS] Defend a Titan
against his own kind.
Should we succeed,
we'll make history!
[PYXIS] Today is the day!
[PYXIS] Lands taken
by our greatest enemy
[PYXIS] will be reclaimed!
[PYXIS] Now, it may seem an
insignificant plot of land
[PYXIS] compared
to the vast tracts of
[PYXIS] former glory
long abandoned.
[PYXIS] But as a
symbol. As an idea.
[PYXIS] Trost regained shall
stand as a reclamation of
[PYXIS] pride and
hope beyond measure!
[PYXIS] A leap greater
than we have ever taken!
[MIKASA] Eren! I know
you're in there!
Snap out it!
Come on! We need you!
Get out of there!
[MITABI] What the hell?
[MITABI] You tellin' me the kid
was a regular Titan all along?
[IAN] Our job now is to
keep the others off him
until he can be recovered.
Whether we like it or not
he's still our last best chance.
[IAN] We're not
about to abandon him.
[IAN] We're
expendable. He isn't.
[EREN] Wait.
[EREN] That's right, of course.
[CONNY] Jean!
[CONNY] And why the hell
isn't he using his gear?
Hang on!
[CONNY] Don't tell
me it's not working!
I am not going to die today!
[ARMIN] Mikasa!
Why'd the plan go belly-up?
[MIKASA] We've
had to shift tac.
[MIKASA] Right now all
we can do is protect him.
[MIKASA] He's defenseless.
[MIKASA] And there's--
There's just so many.
[MIKASA] I don't know how much
longer we can keep this up!
[ARMIN] From the back of the
head to the nape of the neck.
[ARMIN] One meter high
and ten centimeters across!
Tell me, honestly.
[ARMIN] Even though your first
step beyond the wall meant
[ARMIN] the difference between
a warm hearth and hell on earth.
[ARMIN] Why? Why throw
caution to the wind
[ARMIN] and venture outside?
What kind of question is that?
[EREN] Because the world beyond
the wall is my birthright!
[roar]
Eren!
Way to go. Draggin'
everybody down. Great job.
[JEAN] Maybe I won't die today.
What are we
going to do, Captain?
[FEMALE SQUAD]
We're all that's left!
We fall back to the boulder!
[IAN] Status report!
[MALE SQUAD] Five Titans
approaching from the gate, sir!
If I wait for the all-clear
I'll never make it out alive!
I've got to do something!
Jean!
[CONNY] His gear is busted!
What's happening?
[JEAN] Damn it!
Ugh. Come on!
Work with me here!
[CONNY] Jean! Look out!
[JEAN] Marco! What the
hell are you doing?
Crap. Why you
gotta go be the hero?
What? You've got
to be kidding me.
Why is the trigger so stiff?
[CONNY] Jean!
[CONNY] Ow!
Are you insane?
What are you waiting
for? Get out of there!
♪
You idiots got a death wish?
Don't even start, man.
Yeah! You scared
the hell outta me!
I'll be damned.
[Titan footsteps]
♪
Eren.
[ARMIN] Mikasa!
[MIKASA] Armin!
He came out of it
somehow! We're set!
He's determined to see the
mission through to the end!
[ARMIN] As long as
we've got his back
[ARMIN] while he
heads for the wall,
victory will be ours!
[IAN] Defend him!
[IAN] To the last man if
that's what it comes to!
[IAN] Eren must reach the gate!
[IAN] I don't want a single
Titan anywhere near him!
It looks like we're back on!
Focus on keeping Eren safe!
The both of you, go! I want
you with Eren immediately!
Hop to, soldiers!
That's an order!
[BOTH] Sir, yes sir!
[IAN] Team Mitabi!
What are you doing?
The ugly sons-a-bitches
have lost all interest in us!
We need to get close enough
to grab their attention!
Hey big guy, over here!
You walkin' away?
Maybe you want us to
shove our blades right
up your smelly asses?
[SQUAD 1] It worked!
[SQUAD 2] We've got two of 'em!
Alright! Make a
B-line for the buildings!
[ARMIN] They're insane!
[ARMIN] Setting foot
down there is suicide!
If they get cornered somewhere
there'll be nothing they can do!
[IAN] Yeah. I know.
Let's move out.
Everyone, follow Team Mitabi!
Come on. We need to go.
[IAN] Over here! Come get me!
[EREN TITAN] I feel
like-- Like I'm about to
[EREN TITAN] buckle
under the weight.
[EREN TITAN] Mikasa. Armin.
[EREN TITAN] What are you doing?
[EREN TITAN] Get to the
rooftops! You'll be killed!
Hey! What's the
matter? Can't catch me?
[MALE SQUAD] You never
will with that attitude--
[screaming]
No! Damn it!
[MALE SQUAD] Mitabi!
Why? Why throw caution to
the wind and venture outside?
[EREN TITAN] We're
born free. All of us.
[screaming]
[EREN TITAN] Free.
[EREN TITAN]
Some don't believe it.
[EREN TITAN] Some
try to take it away.
[EREN TITAN]
To hell with them!
[EREN TITAN] Water like fire.
[EREN TITAN] Mountains
of ice. The whole bit.
[EREN TITAN]
Lay your eyes on that,
[EREN TITAN] and you'll
know what freedom is.
[EREN TITAN] That
it's worth fighting for!
[EREN TITAN] Fight to live!
Risk it all for even
[EREN TITAN] a glimmer
of real freedom!
[screaming]
[EREN TITAN] It doesn't matter
what's waiting outside the gate,
[EREN TITAN] or what comes in.
[EREN TITAN] It doesn't matter
how cruel the world can be!
[EREN TITAN] Or how unjust!
[EREN TITAN]
Fight! Fight! Fight!
[EREN TITAN] Fight!
[ARMIN] There's
still one ahead of us!
[MIKASA] I'll take care of it!
Out of the way!
[small roar]
[battle cry]
Go!
[EREN TITAN] Fight!
♪
Comrades. Your
sacrifices weren't in vain.
[gun fire]
We have made history.
This day belongs to humanity!
[ANKA] Definitely
yellow smoke, sir.
Oh my god. The
mission was a success!
Deploy all reinforcements.
[PYXIS] Bring
the Elite Squad home.
[RICO] Mind the stragglers!
Ackerman! Pull back!
With all due respect,
I'm not withdrawing
until I recover Eren!
[MIKASA] Armin! How is he?
[ARMIN] Unconscious and
scorching to the touch!
There we go.
[ARMIN] We have to
get him up the wall!
Uh oh, damn it.
He's fused to the carcass!
I can't work him free!
[RICO] Then we cut.
Wait! We don't know
what that might do!
Eren! Armin!
♪
Mikasa!
Who's that?
[EREN] The wings... of freedom.
Pay attention, kiddos.
[LEVI] This is the part
where you explain to me
[LEVI] exactly what
it is I'm looking at.
[NARRATOR] Afterward, thanks
to the coordinated efforts of
[NARRATOR]
the Scout Regiment and
[NARRATOR] the Garrison
Regiment's Corps of Engineers,
[NARRATOR] Wall Rose
once against stood as
[NARRATOR] a bulwark
against the Titan hordes.
[NARRATOR] It was a full day's
work dispatching the Titans
[NARRATOR] who
remained corralled within
[NARRATOR] Trost's
perimeter, during which
[NARRATOR] the wall-mounted
cannons fired ceaselessly.
[NARRATOR] Most of the
Titans nearest the wall
[NARRATOR] were wiped
out by explosive shells.
[NARRATOR] The few that remained
once the smoked cleared were
[NARRATOR] summarily cut
down by the Scout Regiment.
[NARRATOR] During the so-called
cleanup operation, two Titans,
[NARRATOR] a 4-meter and
a 7-meter, were captured
[NARRATOR] alive and
successfully restrained.
[NARRATOR] However...
[NARRATOR] All told, 207 people
were either dead or missing.
[NARRATOR] 897 were
counted among the injured.
[NARRATOR] So while
the reclamation of Trost
[NARRATOR] represented the
first true victory for humanity
[NARRATOR] in its
fight against the Titans,
[NARRATOR] too many
soldiers had fallen
[NARRATOR] for
celebration to be in order.
[JEAN] I-Is--
[JEAN] Is that... Marco?
[DOCTOR] If you have
a name for this one,
[DOCTOR] it'd be
helpful to pass it along.
[JEAN] I wondered where he was.
But he's-- He's not the
sort of guy... who, you know--
Marco. What happened?
[JEAN] No. Somebody
saw it. Had to've.
[JEAN] Somebody
knows how he went out.
[DOCTOR] I need his name.
We don't have time for this.
Please, son. You understand?
It's been two
days since we bored up
the hole in Wall
Rose. That's too long.
We're nowhere near
accounting for all the dead.
Unless these poor
souls are dealt with soon,
an epidemic is
likely to break out.
[DOCTOR] We're the
first line of defense
[DOCTOR] against
secondary disaster.
[DOCTOR] We'll lament the fallen
after we've done our jobs.
Is that understood?
[JEAN] He was a member
of the 104th Cadet Corps,
[JEAN] captain of
Squad 19. Marco Bodt.
Bodt. Duly noted, then.
Thank you, cadet.
I appreciate the help.
Continue.
[SASHA] Wha--
What is this thing?
Leftover Titan vomit.
[ELITE A] Apparently they
don't have a digestive tract,
[ELITE A] so once they've
had their fill of people,
[ELITE A] they upchuck
them like hairballs.
That's sick.
Ugh. So gross. Can't
even make out a face.
[ANNIE] I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I...
Contrition does them no good.
What they need
is a proper burial.
[MAN] Any questions?
[EREN] That's Commander Erwin,
[EREN] head of the Scout
Regiment's Task Force.
[EREN] What's he doing
here? And Captain Levi?
Uh... I, uh--
[EREN] Where...
[EREN] Where am I?
[ERWIN] I think it's obvious.
Let's just call it a dungeon.
[ERWIN] You're currently in the
custody of the Military Police.
[ERWIN] We were
granted permission to
[ERWIN] see you only just now.
[chains rattling]
Where'd you get that?
[ERWIN] Off of you. Don't
worry, you'll get it back.
Let's talk home.
Specifically the good doctor's
cellar back in Shiganshina.
Pretty big secret
in there, right?
[ERWIN] About the Titans?
Yeah. I think so.
That's what Dad said anyway.
Must suck having your
dad and your memory
MIA at the same time.
Unless, of course,
that's just a cover story.
Enough. We've been
over this already.
We know he has
no reason to lie.
And that's all we know.
How 'bout you shed a little
light on things for me
by telling us your intentions.
M-- My what?
What do you mean?
[ERWIN] Here's the lay
of the land, my friend.
[ERWIN] If we want to pay
your dad's cellar a visit,
[ERWIN] we have to venture
back into Shiganshina.
[ERWIN] Sealing the breach there
as we did in Trost would be
[ERWIN] the smart way to
go about it, don't you think?
[ERWIN] Naturally, we'll
need your special powers.
[ERWIN] Any way you slice it,
a Titan's deciding our fate.
[ERWIN] It's been
conjectured that the Colossal
[ERWN] and the Armored Titan
[ERWIN] are more or
less the same as you.
It's why I ask your intentions.
They could be the key to
turning the tide forever.
[ERWIN] You could save us.
I don't know what I am.
[EREN TITAN] No. This is over.
[EREN TITAN] I'm going
to put a stop to this!
[EREN] I'll kill them
with my bare hands!
[LEVI] C'mon. It's an easy
question. So answer it.
What the hell
is it you wanna do?
I want to become a
member of the Scouts
and slaughter every
Titan that crosses my path!
Huh. Well played.
[LEVI] Alright, then. I'll
take responsibility for him.
[LEVI] Let the higher-ups
know what's going on.
Not that I implicitly
trust him, of course.
It's more a matter
of me trusting myself
to deal with him.
Kill him, if I have to.
The big wigs aren't
likely to raise a stink.
My record more than speaks
for itself, I'm pretty sure.
[LEVI] Good news, Jaeger.
[LEVI] You're now officially
a member of the Scouts.
[NARRATOR]
A special court marshal.
[NARRATOR] Eren is released
from his underground cell
[NARRATOR] only to be
dragged before a tribunal of
[NARRATOR] the military's
highest ranking officials.
[NARRATOR] The
issue being decided?
[NARRATOR] Whether
he lives or dies.