What choice do we have?
[MIKASA] The world
is a cruel place.
[Eren gasp]
[struggling]
[EREN] I swore...
to kill them all!
[EREN] Every last one!
[power yell]
[NARRATOR]
And just like that...
[NARRATOR] everything changed.
[NARRATOR]
At that terrible moment,
[NARRATOR] in our
hearts, we knew.
[NARRATOR] Home was a
pen. Humanity... cattle.
[foot steps]
[Eren Titan roar]
Eren!
Eren...
[growl]
[NICK] Brothers and sisters.
[NICK] Let us pray
for the continued strength
[NICK] of saints
Maria, Rose, and Sina.
[NICK] May they stand firm.
Their grace
is a manifestation
of our good faith...
We give thanks to the light
of the Divine Architect.
[NICK] He whose
wisdom is the mortar;
[NICK] whose sublime
love for His creation
[NICK] is the steadfast stone.
[NICK] He, and he
alone, protects us from
[NICK] the Titan scourge,
in proportion to our worship.
Verily... Innocence and
obedience are all He asks--
[screaming]
[growl]
[gasp]
[NICK] No! Impossible!
[NICK] Dear God!
Please! Not the wall!
Stay away!
[gasp]
[villagers screaming]
[villagers panic]
[Eren Titan growl]
Well I daresay it
looks like our boy's
in control of
himself this time.
Yeah. Still, though...
there's no guarantee
this will turn
out any differently
than their last meeting.
[JEAN] Come on, he
wouldn't have transformed...
[JEAN] unless he knew he
could take her this time...
[JEAN] he's got this, okay?
[ARMIN] I don't doubt that.
[ARMIN] But determination alone
isn't enough to win a fight.
[ARMIN] You of all
people should know that.
[heavy exhale]
It'll take more
than that to beat Annie.
[ARMIN] A lot more.
[SOLDIER] Damn it!
She's making a
break for level ground!
So much for
our gear! What now?
Split into two
teams and go around!
[SOLDIER] Understood!
[worried screams]
[Eren Titan roaring]
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
Son of a-- Where'd
they come from?
[all gasp]
[worried screams]
[Eren Titan growling]
[soldiers screaming]
♪
[EREN] Annie...
Always so cynical...
[EREN] Like every little
thing around you was pointless.
[EREN] Nothing
worth a second look.
[EREN] Every now
and then, though,
[EREN] I could see
through the act...
[EREN] Especially when
you were showing off
[EREN] your fighting skills.
[EREN] Maybe hand-to-hand
combat didn't count for squat
[EREN] against our final
grade back at the academy...
[EREN] But to you? It was a
different story altogether.
[EREN] Yeah... about
that much at least.
[EREN] It was
obvious you were a liar.
[EREN] Fighting's
your whole world,
[EREN] but what exactly
are you fighting for?
[EREN] What could
possibly have been worth
[EREN] all this
death and destruction?!
[roar]
[Eren Titan roaring]
[roaring]
[SOLDIER] Oh, god...
[MOBLIT] Section Commander,
I hate to say it,
[MOBLIT] but the city'll be
[MOBLIT] debris and
corpses before long...
even if we manage to catch her.
Well, then
that's how it's gonna be!
We're sticking to Commander
Erwin's plan, got it?
[HANGE] So stop babbling
and ready the nets.
[MOBLIT] Right.
[MIKASA] Eren...
[HITCH] We didn't
sign up for this.
They-- They didn't
say there'd be
Titans fighting in the streets.
No kidding. This is crazy.
[NILE] We've got two of 'em
hashing it out in the streets?
[SOLDIER] Yes, sir.
[SOLDIER] The city's collapsing
like a house of cards.
It's just...
It's horrifying...
We can only guess
how many casualties...
Erwin! Your arrogance has
brought Hell right to our door!
I know.
[screaming]
[ERWIN] I acted entirely
on my own authority.
And I offer no excuses.
[grunting]
[NILE] You knew what this would
do to us, you son of a bitch!
You knew and
our lives be damned!
[NILE] Why? Damn you, why?
[ERWIN] For humanity.
[ERWIN] For victory.
Don't give me that!
You're nothing but a traitor!
I ought to kill
you right here and now!
[NILE] None of the higher
ups would fault me!
[ERWIN] Do as your
conscience dictates.
[ERWIN] My post is yours.
The Female Titan
must not escape.
Deployment is through Peer
and Beirer is in
command of Provisions.
[ERWIN] Work with them closely.
[ERWIN] Do whatever is required
to ensure she doesn't--
Shut up!
Do... Do you really believe...
[NILE] ...this is
for the good of us all?
[ERWIN] I have faith
it's a step forward.
[grunting]
[sigh]
Everyone, lower your rifles.
Place this man under arrest.
Sir!
Deploy all troops immediately.
[NILE] As of now...
focus on evacuation.
[SOLDIERS] Yes, Sir!
Erwin... I hereby
wash my hands of you
and leave you
to the high court.
I'll accept their
judgment. Thank you, Nile.
Levi. For now, stay here.
A pointless death
wouldn't suit you.
No, I doubt it would...
Any more than it
suits anyone else.
[ARMIN] To rise above monsters,
[ARMIN] we have to
abandon our humanity.
[ARMIN] What we
fight, we become...
[roar]
[ARMIN] ...fire with fire.
[Eren Titan roaring]
[ARMIN] Look at her.
Annie can do it.
[Eren Titan roar]
[Eren Titan growl]
[ANNIE'S FATHER] Annie...
[ANNIE'S FATHER] Annie!
[roar]
[Eren Titan growling]
[Annie Titan grunting]
[Eren Titan roaring]
[roar]
[ANNIE'S FATHER] Annie...
[Annie Titan grunt]
[ANNIE'S FATHER]
I believe in you.
I'm always on your side.
[roar]
[EREN TITAN] I...
will... kill them...
[EREN] Every last one!
[EREN TITAN] Every last one!
♪
[roar]
[roaring]
Eren!
What is he--?
Help him!
No! With the state he's in,
it's probably best that
we keep our distance.
[worried gasp]
[Eren Titan roaring]
[roar]
[Annie Titan roar]
[Eren Titan growl]
[Annie Titan screaming]
[soldiers gasping]
God.
[Annie Titan roar]
[Annie Titan screaming]
[Eren Titan growling]
[Annie Titan roar]
[growl]
[Annie Titan growl]
She's headed up the wall!
[HANGE] She's trying to escape!
[heavy breathing]
[Eren Titan growling]
[ARMIN] No, no, no!
We can't let her get away!
I won't let her!
[growl]
[Mikasa grunt]
[Annie Titan growl]
[warcry]
[MIKASA] It's over, Annie.
Now fall.
♪
[ANNIE'S FATHER] Annie...
[ANNIE'S FATHER] I'm so sorry.
[ANNIE'S FATHER] I don't
expect you to forgive me.
[ANNIE'S FATHER]
But... please...
please just...
[Eren Titan growling]
[ANNIE'S FATHER] Stand your
ground. Stand your ground
[ANNIE'S FATHER] even if the
whole world stands against you.
[EREN TITAN] Die...
All of you... Everything...
[ANNIE'S FATHER]
They'll despise you...
They won't understand.
[ANNIE'S FATHER] But I
will. Your dad always will.
[gasp] Oh, no! He's
gonna devour her whole!
Eren! Back off!
Don't do it!
[EREN TITAN]
This... is freedom!
[ANNIE'S FATHER] Promise
me you'll return...
[ANNIE'S FATHER]
That's all I ask.
[growl]
♪
[HANGE] Wha... What's he doing?
[growl]
[NILE] Son of a...?
[Armin gasp]
[ARMIN] They're merging?
[Eren Titan growling]
Stop it, Eren!
[gasp]
[Levi grunt]
It's not a good idea
to eat our key evidence...
you idiot.
♪
[wincing]
Eren.
Mikasa... Is Annie...?
[metal clinging]
[Jean grunting]
[JEAN] Damn it! All
the shit we've been through
[JEAN] and this is what we get?
[JEAN] Annie! Wake up!
C'mon, face the
music! You owe us!
[JEAN] Don't be a coward!
I know you can hear me!
[grunt]
[LEVI] That's enough.
[LEVI] It's over.
[HANGE] Someone
get me a wire net!
This thing belongs
deep underground!
[SOLDIERS] Understood!
[sigh]
[HANGE] What have we done?
[HANGE] If we can't get
any answers out of her,
[HANGE] then what was
the point of all this?
[HANGE] We're left with nothing
but countless casualties,
[HANGE] ruined lives,
and unanswered questions.
[HANGE] All for what?
Well, it was a valiant effort.
Can't win 'em
all though, right?
Right.
At the very least the Scout
Regiment's been exonerated.
Sure, by the skin
of its teeth, but still.
Let's hope the brass agrees.
[DISTRICT HEAD] As you might
imagine, we have many questions.
If the target's identity
was beyond all doubt,
why would you
neglect to request aid
from the Military Police?
Discretion. We had
reason to believe she was
operating in conjunction
with other insiders.
I felt it was
necessary to involve
only those well
above suspicion, sir.
[LEADER 1] Yes. And the
price of your "discretion"
[LEADER 1] was the near
obliteration of Stohess.
[LEADER 1] Well done.
[ERWIN] I didn't foresee
the damage's scale, sir.
[ERWIN]
Blame my incompetence.
[LEADER 2] Blame isn't
going to rebuild my roof!
[ERWIN] If the Female Titan
were left to roam free...
[ERWIN] the wall was
subject to breach...
[ERWIN] and the
damage to Stohess
[ERWIN] would've been
beyond devastating.
[DISTRICT HEAD] Perhaps.
Erwin...
You have me grasping at
straws to exonerate you...
What I need is
proof that your tactics
yielded some
manner of benefit.
[DISTRICT HEAD] Granted, Annie
Leonhart is rendered innocuous,
[DISTRICT HEAD] but
also essentially useless.
[ERWIN] Yes, sir. That she is.
[all gasp]
Are you saying...
it was all for nothing...?
[MIKASA] Hey.
[MIKASA] You feel okay?
[EREN] Yeah...
[EREN] In fact it's
weird how "okay" I feel.
So, is... Annie still
stuck in that thing?
[MIKASA] Uh-huh.
Yeah... You'd think
after all we sacrificed
to get her back, fate
would cut us a little slack.
[ARMIN] It's humbling,
knowing how far she'll go
[ARMIN] to keep her secrets.
Humbling?
More like infuriating.
[ARMIN] Why'd
you let her go, Eren?
You did... didn't you?
[ARMIN] You gave her an out.
I know. I didn't mean to, I...
I just couldn't help it.
[EREN] When I saw
her face, I just froze...
[MP] Armin Arlelt.
And Jean Kirschtein...
You two are up first.
[ARMIN] Yes, sir.
Debriefing time.
See you later, I guess.
[EREN] Sure.
Honestly...
It felt kinda... good.
[EREN] Just letting go...
[EREN] my body,
my mind, everything...
For a minute it was almost...
like I wanted to die...
Eren, stop it!
[EREN] Don't worry,
I'm better now.
[gasp]
[MIKASA] I'm glad...
[MIKASA] I'm
glad you're back...
[JEAN] I can't get my
head wrapped around it.
This whole fighting fire with
fire business or whatever.
Is that really the
only option we've got?
Not necessarily. Just the only
one that's presented itself.
And now we know Eren can do it.
Yeah, well... if it's
that easy for the fight to
turn us all into monsters...
[JEAN] ...then maybe
we don't deserve to win.
[gasp]
[MIKASA] Go on.
[ARMIN] No one ever promised us
we'd come out of this unscathed.
[ERWIN] For nothing? I
believe this latest tragedy
[ERWIN] has moved us forward
by leaps and bounds, sir.
[ERWIN] Not long ago,
we hadn't even imagined
[ERWIN] the
possibility of humans
[ERWIN] transforming
into Titans.
[ERWIN] Now, we're
not only aware of
[ERWIN] the
enemy in our midst...
[ERWIN] we've managed
to capture one of them.
[ERWIN] Make no mistake,
there are more out there.
[ERWIN] And we will
hunt down every last one.
[ERWIN] The initiative is ours.
Starting now...
[ERWIN] we launch an attack on
the Titans within our walls!
[NARRATOR] The Scout Regiment's
recall to the capital
[NARRATOR] and Eren's
incarceration were rescinded.
[NARRATOR] Instead,
they were charged with
[NARRATOR] guarding Annie
Leonhart in her holding cell
[NARRATOR] deep underground,
where they kept strict vigil
[NARRATOR] day and night.
[NARRATOR] Sadly, however...
[NARRATOR] it would
take a far longer time...
[NARRATOR] and cost a
great many more lives...
[NARRATOR] for humanity to
discover the true nature...
[NARRATOR] of
what it held captive.
♪