[NARRATOR] They first appeared
over a hundred years ago.
[NARRATOR] Giant,
humanoid creatures
[NARRATOR] with a
taste for our blood.
[NARRATOR] The brute strength
of these aberrations trumped
[NARRATOR] an average
person's many times over.
[NARRATOR] We were
shoved to the brink
[NARRATOR] of extinction
almost overnight.
[NARRATOR] The survivors erected
Walls Maria, Rose, and Sina;
[NARRATOR] withdrawing behind
them in frightened huddles
[NARRATOR] for what was to
be a century of uneasy peace.
[NARRATOR] In the year 845,
two terrifying new breeds
[NARRATOR] of Titan appeared:
the Colossal and the Armored,
[NARRATOR] barreling
through the outer walls as if
[NARRATOR] wholesale
destruction was child's play.
[NARRATOR] The territory
couched within the circle
[NARRATOR] of Wall
Maria was abandoned.
[NARRATOR] Twenty percent
of the human race perished.
[NARRATOR] As the
Titan onslaught advanced,
[NARRATOR] our only choice was
to withdrawal behind Wall Rose.
[NARRATOR] In the year 850, the
Colossal appeared once again,
[NARRATOR] breaching
the wall bordering Trost
[NARRATOR] before disappearing.
[NARRATOR] The Titans flooded
in through the broken gate.
Eren! No!
[Armin screaming]
[NARRATOR] Two hours
later, the evacuation of
[NARRATOR] the entire
populace was complete.
[NARRATOR] As a result,
[NARRATOR] no civilians
were lost to the Titans.
[NARRATOR] The same cannot be
said for the countless soldiers
[NARRATOR] who perished,
buying the people time.
[MIKASA] Eren. As long
as you're part of my life,
[MIKASA] I can fight
to the bitter end.
[MALE SOLDIER]
Captain, please wait!
[MALE SOLDIER] There's only
a handful of us left, sir.
[MALE SOLDIER] If the Titans
were to attack here in force,
[MALE SOLDIER] we wouldn't
have a chance in hell
[MALE SOLDIER]
of holding them off!
[FEMALE SOLDIER] Please,
sir. We need you here!
Out of my way, soldier.
We have to get going.
My expertise is needed to
help direct the reinforcements.
Behind the safety of
the inner gate. Am I right?
Just what the hell
are you implying?
They need my
help reorganizing.
Or would you rather
us be overwhelmed
due to a logistical nightmare!
But-- But sir! If
we lose those supplies--
That's enough!
Question my orders again,
or delay me in my duties,
and I'll run your treasonous
hide straight through!
Why isn't anyone
going over the wall?
They must have heard
the withdrawal signal.
It's over.
All over. We're doomed.
[weeping]
[Titan growling]
[whimpering]
There!
[FEMALE SOLDIER] C'mon
now. That musket's
[FEMALE SOLDIER]
not enough to stop them.
[FEMALE SOLDIER] Huh?
[gun shot]
[screaming]
[CONNY] Hey, Jean.
What're we gonna do?
We can't do anything.
They finally gave us
the order to withdraw.
And we were all
out of gas, of course.
I can't believe this
is how it's going to end.
Because of those
damned cowards!
Y'mean the supply depot? What
is going on? Where are they?
They all lost
their will to fight.
And I can understand why.
[JEAN] But they abandoned
their duty to supply us,
[JEAN] barricading
themselves inside HQ.
[JEAN] And of course,
Titans have swarmed the place,
[JEAN] which means we
can't get the gas ourselves.
Then why're we
waitin'? We gotta go.
Start thinning their
numbers so we have a chance!
[CONNY] Sitting here on this
roof is totally pointless!
[CONNY] Eventually the
Titans are gonna come for us.
We don't have much gas left.
We'll just waste
what little we've got
if we try to run.
And without our mobility,
[CONNY] we're
completely screwed!
You're using your head
for once, Conny. Nice going.
But I'm just not sure if
we've got the numbers needed
to pull this thing
off. The veterans in
the Vanguard force
have all been killed.
[JEAN] How, exactly, do
a bunch of rookies pull off
[JEAN] a suicide
mission like this?
[JEAN] I mean, let's
assume half of our force
[JEAN] even survives
the initial assault.
[JEAN] Then what? The supply
room is probably crawling with
[JEAN] Titans in the
three or four meter range.
[JEAN] I don't see us
accomplishing much in there.
It's hopeless.
God, what a dull life
this turned out to be.
I never even got to
tell her just how I feel.
[SASHA] C'mon guys,
we can do it!
Right? Let's go.
If we all work together,
we can make this happen,
[SASHA] I know we can! All
right? I'll take the lead.
Armin! It's time to go.
[ANNIE] Reiner. Do we move out?
Not yet. We have to
let them gather up first.
[MARCO] It's no use.
There's too many of them.
I don't think any of us
are going to survive this.
I've come to accept
my pending demise.
[MARCO] I just... wanted
my death to mean something.
[CADET] Mikasa! Weren't
you with the rearguard?
[MIKASA] Annie!
I know how bad things
have gotten. It's selfish.
Putting personal
matters in the forefront,
but have you
seen Eren's squad?
Some squads made it back.
But I don't know about Eren's.
We found Armin,
he's over there.
[MIKASA] Armin!
Mikasa! I can't. How do I
tell her what happened to Eren?
I survived, and
it means nothing.
I'm so useless!
[ARMIN] I wish I had
died with him instead!
Armin. Are you okay?
You're not hurt, are you?
Where is Eren?
[MIKASA] Armin?
[Armin crying]
[ARMIN] They were-- The cadets
of Squad 34. Thomas Wagner.
[ARMIN] Nack Tierce. Milieus
Zeremski. Mina Carolina.
[ARMIN] Eren Jaeger!
[ARMIN] These brave
five upheld their duties.
[ARMIN] They died valiantly
on the field of battle!
[Armin weeping]
Please, no.
[CADET 1] His whole
squad was wiped out?
[CADET 2] The same
will happen to us
[CADET 2] if we try
to take on those Titans.
[weeping]
I'm so sorry, Mikasa!
It should have been
me that died, not Eren!
I-- I couldn't do a
thing! I'm worthless.
[MIKASA] Armin.
Calm yourself.
We haven't got time
for you to get
emotional right now.
Huh?
[MIKASA] On your feet.
[MIKASA] Marco. If we eliminate
or bypass the Titans at HQ,
we can there refuel
our gear, allowing us to
get back over the wall.
Is that assessment correct?
Well-- Uh yeah I guess so,
sure. But there's just too many
of them out there.
Even with you on point.
I can do it.
What?
I'm strong. Real strong.
[MIKASA] None of you
come close. You hear me?
[MIKASA] I am a warrior.
Know this. I
have the power to slay
all of the Titans
that block our path!
Even if I
have to do it alone.
[MIKASA] As far as I'm
concerned, I am surrounded by
[MIKASA] a bunch of
unskilled, cowardly worms.
[MIKASA] You dissappoint
me. You can just sit here
[MIKASA] and twiddle your
thumbs, and watch how it's done!
Wait, Mikasa. Are you out
of your mind? That's crazy!
You can't be serious! Trying
to take them out by yourself?
There's no way you
can hope to beat them!
If I can't beat them, then
I die. But, if I win, I live.
And the only way
to win is to fight!
[MARCO] Hey!
You know, I was expecting
something more motivational.
Your way with words
was kind of a let down.
I blame everything
about this on you, Eren!
Hey! Don't just stand
there! We weren't taught to
[JEAN] let our
comrades fight alone!
[JEAN] 'Less you are
a coward, in which case
[JEAN] stay out of my way!
Never expected that from him.
♪
Hey! Seriously? C'mon,
you bunch of chickens!
[CADET] They're nuts!
Damn it. All right, let's go!
[rally cry]
[JEAN] Hurry up! Follow Mikasa!
Avoid fighting, if you can.
[JEAN] And get to HQ
before you run out of gas!
Whoa, Mikasa is a badass!
[CONNY] How is
she going so fast?
No! Mikasa's
using too much gas!
[ARMIN] She could
run out at any second!
[ARMIN] It doesn't
matter how skilled she is.
[ARMIN] Once we lose mobility,
we're as good as dead!
♪
[ARMIN] I see through
the veil of her composure.
She's letting adrenaline
distract her from grief!
[ARMIN] At any
time, she could...
Mikasa!
Damn!
Jean! You lead the rest
to HQ! I'm going after Armin!
[JEAN] I'll go with you!
[CONNY] Don't be stupid! There
are still Titans everywhere!
You've gotta help the others!
It happened. Why this again?
[MIKASA] I've lost my family.
[MIKASA] Why? Wasn't
the first time enough?
It's all over.
Nothing left for
them to take from me.
[Titan footsteps]
[JEAN] It's no use.
We're not getting
[JEAN] anywhere
near Headquarters.
[JEAN] Unless, of course,
we don't mind dying.
[Cadet wimpering]
Shit! He's out of gas!
Stay back!
[MOBB] Tom! I'll save you!
No, wait!
[CADET] I'm comin'!
[crying]
Stop it!
[screaming]
Why couldn't I stop them?
Why didn't I stop them?
If I'd kept us all together,
this never would
have happened!
[screaming]
[JEAN] I wasn't meant
to lead. I'm the last person
that should've
been given the reigns!
[FEMALE CADET] No! [screaming]
[MALE CADET] I hope you
choke on me, you bastard!
[Female Cadet screaming]
[FEMALE CADET] No! No!
♪
[MIKASA] This world is cruel.
But it's also--
It's also beautiful.
[Titan footsteps]
It was a good life.
♪
Why?
[MIKASA] I'd already given up.
[MIKASA] So why--
Why am I struggling?
[MIKASA] Why do
I keep getting up?
[MIKASA] Why am
I still fighting?
[MIKASA] I mean, I've
lost any reason to live.
[MIKASA] What keeps pushing me?
[EREN] Fight!
Fight! Fight!
Eren.
[EREN] Kill or be killed!
[EREN] The only way
to live is to fight!
I'm so sorry, Eren.
I'm through giving up.
I'll never give up again.
[MIKASA] Because if I die, these
memories of you die with me.
[MIKASA] That's why I'll
do whatever it takes to win!
[MIKASA] Whatever
it takes to live!
[war cry]
What was that?
[growling]
[howling]
[MIKASA] That Titan.
He's... killing--
[MIKASA] He's
killing the other one.
♪
Please be all right.
I'm coming for you!
[ARMIN] There she is!
Mikasa! Are you okay?
Are you guys all right?
Yeah.
Then we better
get outta here!
[CONNY] Crap. Two
fifteen-meter Titans!
No. That one's different.
How?
[roar]
Huh?
[growl]
[ARMIN] It-- It just
finished it off.
[ARMIN] He knew exactly
where the weak spot was!
[CONNY] C'mon guys,
time to split!
[CONNY] Last thing we
need is him coming our way!
No. He has no reaction to us.
Any other Titan would've
been on top of us by now!
It seemed to understand the
skill of hand-to-hand combat.
What is that thing?
Just chalk it up
as another Abnormal!
Hell, they're always an
unpleasant surprise, right?
Forget about it. Let's
just get outta here!
[ARMIN] Wait a minute, hold
on. Mikasa's tanks are empty!
[CONNY] Huh? What
are we gonna do?
[CONNY] We can't clear
HQ without your help!
There's only one thing to do.
I know there isn't
very much left in them,
[ARMIN] but it's better
than your empty ones.
Armin!
This is our only choice!
[ARMIN] It'll be a complete
waste if I keep them. But--
Use this gas more sparingly.
Everyone's lives
are riding on you.
What have I done?
I led the attack
[MIKASA] without any
regard for their lives at all.
[MIKASA] I was even
reckless with my own life.
[MIKASA] I lost track
of what you taught me.
[MIKASA] Oh, Eren.
I'm so ashamed.
[MIKASA] Eren.
[ARMIN] There! Got it!
The ODM gear's functional.
[ARMIN] And I
restocked your blades.
[ARMIN] Just-- Just
leave me this one, okay?
[ARMIN] It's just that, I
would rather this be my end,
[ARMIN] not being eaten alive.
Why'd you--?
[MIKASA] Armin.
I will not leave you behind.
[MIKASA] What was he?
[MIKASA] Are there
any more like him?
[MIKASA] I've never heard of
a Titan killing another Titan.
[MIKASA] No one has.
[MIKASA] But it
struck a chord in me.
[MIKASA] Something
so familiar. So primal.
[roar]
[MIKASA] I bore witness to
[MIKASA] the manifestation
of humanity's rage.
[growl]
[NARRATOR] A Titan
killing a Titan.
[NARRATOR] The very sight
of it in action leaves
[NARRATOR] the 104th Cadet Corps
Class completely speechless.
[NARRATOR] However,
the cadets have
[NARRATOR] much
more in store for them.