[ERWIN] It's officially begun.
The 57th Recon Mission!
[ERWIN] Scouts, move out!
[NARRATOR] After
setting forth to establish
[NARRATOR]
a route to Shiganshina,
[NARRATOR] the Scout Regiment
encountered a Female Titan
[NARRATOR] seemingly
possessed of sharp,
[NARRATOR]
cold-hearted intelligence.
[ARMIN] We're not
dealing with an Abnormal,
[ARMIN] this thing's
showing intelligence!
[ARMIN] It's a human being
wrapped in a Titan body!
[NARRATOR] As soldier upon
soldier fell to this new foe,
[NARRATOR] the
regiment retreated into
[NARRATOR] a forest
of massive trees.
[NARRATOR] Though
to what purpose,
[NARRATOR] no one
appeared to know.
[EREN] If the Levi Squad can't
stop this thing, then who can?
[EREN] Those men need us!
[LEVI] The choice is yours.
[LEVI] You can trust yourself,
[LEVI] or you can trust
the people willing to
[LEVI] put their
lives on the line for you.
I'm with you!
Fire!
[LEVI] Oh, that's right.
[LEVI] While we're on
that subject, let me ask.
You're okay with me cuttin' your
limbs off at the joints, right?
[LEVI] I'm mean,
they'll grow back?
[LEVI] I'm talking
about your actual body.
[LEVI] Don't want
you dead just yet.
[LEVI] Timing wouldn't work.
[Female Titan roaring]
[ERWIN] Think about it.
The enemy was prepared
[ERWIN] to make
sacrifices. Enormous ones.
[ERWIN] So committed to
maintaining her secret,
[ERWIN] she would
rather let herself be
[ERWIN] cannibalized
than exposed.
[ERWIN] All hands, withdraw!
[ERWIN] Redeploy the formation!
[ERWIN] Return to
Calaneth District!
[HANGE] Erwin. Why bother
having him replenish?
[HANGE] There's no time.
[ERWIN] We saw the
Female Titan get eaten.
[ERWIN] Did we actually
see the person inside
[ERWIN] suffer the
same fate? I didn't.
[gasp] You mean?
[ERWIN] Yes. Your hypothesis
is correct. This isn't over.
We're dealing
with someone like Eren.
[ERWIN] Someone who regenerates
in and out of Titan form.
[ERWIN] Suppose that
person equipped themselves
[ERWIN] with
ODM gear in advance.
[ERWIN] Suppose further
that they're also disguised
[ERWIN] in one
of our uniforms?
[ERWIN] What would
their next move be?
[GUNTHER] Captain Levi?
Wait, that--
That's not-- Oh shit!
[EREN] Gunther!
[gasp]
[ERWIN] How do you
ferret out the enemy...
[ERWIN] when they're
one of your own?
[ERWIN] When the Colossal
Titan breached the wall
[ERWIN] and disappeared,
theoretically,
whoever was inside
had with ODM gear.
They would have used it in
escape before the steam cleared.
It's possible the
same thing happened here.
I don't see how, sir.
Based on Eren's condition when
he emerged from Titan form,
I think it's safe to assume
that something like that
is highly unlikely.
[HANGE] His equipment
was broken.
[HANGE] Parts of his
uniform were missing.
[HANGE] More importantly, Eren
was so spent he couldn't even
[HANGE] stand on his own
two feet without assistance.
The Female Titan's ability
to summon reinforcements
was unlike anything
we've encountered before.
Our failure to anticipate that
factor cost us the operation.
[ERWIN] Evidently, there are
different levels of mastery
[ERWIN] to the Titan ability.
[ERWIN] We were naive to
think that a mere novice
[ERWIN] like Eren
would set the standard.
If we're to stop
this enemy, it's clear now
that we'll need to
broaden our way of thinking.
[JEAN] So if we're
goin' home, that means
the operation's
a success, right?
Hopefully so.
If that is the case, then that
might mean they've already
discovered the
Female Titan's identity.
[JEAN] I wouldn't mind
knowin' that myself.
[JEAN] Still, I'm
impressed with the commander.
[JEAN] How'd he know
she'd come after us
[JEAN] once we took
Eren beyond the Wall?
[ARMIN] Think about it.
During the Trost invasion,
[ARMIN] did it strike you
as odd the way the Titans
[ARMIN] suddenly halted
their advance midway through?
[JEAN] Huh?
They must have
intended some purpose
when they destroyed
the front gate,
[ARMIN] but they never made
a move on the inner gate.
[ARMIN] Nor did they
interfere with Eren
[ARMIN] when he
sealed the breach.
[ARMIN] Perhaps, something
happened which made them
[ARMIN] re-evaluate
their plan entirely.
And what would that be?
Something drew their focus away
from the Wall's destruction.
Something that forced
them to call off the attack.
You mean Eren's
transformation?
[ARMIN] That's the
most logical conclusion.
Wait, but then
that would mean--
It means they were there.
[ARMIN] Whoever called off
the attack saw Eren transform.
[ARMIN] It means the
enemy is one of us!
Gunther!
[ORUO] Go kid! C'mon!
Keep moving!
[EREN] We-- We're
just leaving him?
Who is that?
[ELD] Keep 'em away from Eren!
Damn it! Hey, Eld.
What're we doin', huh?
There isn't time
to get the horses.
Make for HQ at full speed!
Is that the Female Titan?
Or did she have an accomplice?
Damn! Whoever it is,
they're gonna pay!
Even if it's
the last thing I do!
[EREN] The Female Titan?
No. That can't be right!
[EREN] I thought we caught her!
[ERWIN] We have to consider
that if the enemy was
still able-bodied
when they escaped,
then it's entirely
possible they can
make the Titan
reappear as well.
[ORUO] I hate being right!
No time to lose! Move it!
[ELD] She's coming for us!
[EREN] Damn you! Not again!
I'll kill you! I swear I will!
No! Don't!
We've got this! The
three of us can handle her!
You get back
to base! Go! Now!
[ERWIN] This enemy
forces us to rethink
[ERWIN] everything
we've learned.
What seems the
most logical strategy
might prove to be the
worst course of action.
Mark my words.
The time will come
when risking everything is
the only choice left to us.
[EREN] I can fight her, too!
[ELD] Just go! This is
our best course of action!
We can not afford
to put you at risk!
Have you learned nothing?
After all this, you
still doubt our skills?
Is that true, Eren?
I thought you had faith
in us. That you trusted us!
And unless we can take that
risk, humanity can never win.
[EREN] I have faith
in the Levi Squad!
[EREN] Good luck!
[warcry]
[gasp]
[ELD] We've blinded her!
That should give us at least
[ELD] a minute before
she can regenerate!
[PETRA] We'll finish
her well before then!
[ORUO] To hell
with capturing you!
[ELD] We're gonna kill you!
[PETRA] We're
gonna carve you up!
[ORUO] We'll make
you pay, bitch!
[ELD] Covering your
neck isn't gonna save you!
[ELD] We'll just keep
slicing those shoulders
[ELD] 'til your
arms are worthless.
T[ELD] rust me, we know
what we're doing. No mercy!
[PETRA] We'll
cut you to ribbons!
[ORUO] Lop off your arms!
[ELD] Send you to hell!
[ORUO] They're down!
Now go for the neck!
[ORUO] Take out the
muscles supporting her head!
Let's chop our
way to the nape!
[EREN] They-- They've got
her totally overwhelmed!
[EREN] They're so
good. They pulled off
[EREN] a coordinated attack
without even saying a word!
[EREN] It must be
the trust they have
[EREN] in each
other as teammates.
[EREN] That's how
they've survived this long.
[EREN] It's how they're
able to stay strong
[EREN] even
after losing Gunther.
[EREN] Gotta keep going!
[EREN] I have to have
faith that the right choice
[EREN] is to keep
moving without looking back!
[EREN] I've got to trust in
them. I understand that, now!
[LEVI] Truth is, I don't
know which is better.
I never have. Should
I go out on my own?
Or should I put myself
in the hands of my comrades?
Either way,
there's no guarantee.
[gasp]
[ELD] Say goodbye
to your nape--!
[PETRA] Eld!
How? She can see again?
That's impossible!
[PETRA] It hasn't even
been thirty seconds.
Only one eye? She channeled
her energy into one eye
[PETRA] to grow it back
quicker? How can she do that?
[ORUO] Petra! Pull
yourself together!
[ORUO] Petra!
[Petra screaming]
[screaming]
Now...
die!
What the hell? My
blades weren't able to--
♪
[EREN] I'm gonna...
I'm gonna...
kill you!
[roaring]
That's Eren!
Hang on a second! Mikasa!
[LEVI] That roaring.
This isn't good.
[Eren Titan roar]
[Eren Titan roaring]
[Eren Titan panting]
[Erenn Titan growling]
[distant Titan fighting]
♪
[Eren Titan growl]
[roar]
[EREN TITAN] I made the wrong
decision when you came after us.
[EREN TITAN] I made the
choice to trust my teammates.
[EREN TITAN] And it
got them all killed!
[howling]
[EREN TITAN] I should
never have left it to them.
[EREN TITAN] I should have
fought her from the very start!
[EREN TITAN]
I-It's all my fault.
[EREN TITAN] I should
have killed her!
[roaring]
[EREN TITAN] I should've--
[EREN TITAN] I should've
changed into a Titan then.
[EREN TITAN] No.
Even earlier than that.
[EREN TITAN]
I should've fought back!
[EREN TITAN] And
with Captain Levi there.
[EREN TITAN] We
would've beaten her.
[EREN TITAN] We could've
captured this monster!
[LEVI] I wouldn't blame you.
[LEVI] Do as your
conscience dictates.
[EREN TITAN] It was--
It was my choice.
[EREN TITAN] And
because of that choice,
[EREN TITAN] my
squad-mates are dead.
[EREN TITAN] All of them,
gone. And I'm to blame.
[EREN TITAN] No. More than
anything, this is your fault!
[growling]
[EREN TITAN] I'm going
to rip you to shreds.
[EREN TITAN]
Once my hands heal.
[EREN TITAN] I'll tear
you apart. Piece by piece.
[EREN TITAN]
Then I'll devour you!
[roar]
[Eren Titan heavy breathing]
[Female Titan sigh]
[worried breaths]
[EREN] A--
♪
Eren, no!
[MIKASA] N-No. Wait, I--
Eren. [gasp]
Please, you can't leave me.
Give him back.
[MIKASA] Do you hear
me? Give him back!
[Mikasa warcry]
Give him back!
[Mikasa power yell]
[MIKASA] My blades
didn't even break the skin.
He's still alive.
And I'm coming for him.
Just hang on, Eren!
[MIKASA] I know
you're in there.
And after I kill her,
I'll carve out her insides,
and pull you out
again. I swear I will.
Just hang on a little longer.
Don't give up, Eren.
Never give up!
Get back here!
[MIKASA] What?
We'll stay back for now.
Maintain current distance.
[LEVI] She's
slowed down a bit.
[LEVI] That fight
wore her out, too.
It looked like she may have
bitten the entire nape off.
It's unlikely Eren survived.
[NARRATOR] "He's still
alive. Give him back."
[NARRATOR] After
watching helplessly
[NARRATOR] as Eren
was taken away,
[NARRATOR] Mikasa
fights alongside Levi,
[NARRATOR] humanity's
greatest soldier,
[NARRATOR] in a battle
against the Female Titan.