Go!
[roaring]
[NARRATOR] In the year 850,
humankind reclaimed lands
[NARRATOR] from the
Titans for the first time
[NARRATOR]
since their appearance
[NARRATOR] some
hundred-odd years before.
[NARRATOR] The cost,
however, was great.
[ERWIN] You who stayed,
you are now one of us.
Allow me to welcome
you to the Scout Regiment.
This is a genuine
salute, soldiers!
Together, we give our hearts!
Sir!
[ERWIN] Those of
you standing here have
[ERWIN] worked
through your fear.
You've proven
yourselves courageous.
[ERWIN] Each one
of you has my respect.
[NARRATOR] One short month
later, led by Erwin Smith,
[NARRATOR] the
Scout Regiment set out.
[NARRATOR] Leaving the
relative comfort and safety
[NARRATOR] of Calaneth District,
[NARRATOR] they sought to
carve a route to Shiganshina,
[NARRATOR] the place believed
to hold the Titans' secrets.
[ERWIN] It's officially
begun. The 57th Recon Mission!
Scouts, move out!
♪
We've got a ten-meter
closing in from the left! Gah!
[HANGE] I want to know
what's rolling around
[HANGE] in that glorious belly!
[HANGE] Never mind. Let the
support squad do their job.
[ELITE] Damn! Too shallow!
Just focus on
defending the ranks!
[COMMANDER] Eyes front!
Their job's to handle it.
Yours is to keep moving!
[COMMANDER] Forward!
Ride for all you're worth!
[GUNTHER] They'll only
have our backs 'til we're
[GUNTHER] clear
of the city ruins.
Everything beyond that will be
uninterrupted Titan territory.
We'll be more
or less on our own.
The only thing to fall
back on out there is
Commander Erwin's
long-range scouting formation.
[GUNTHER] The special ops
squad'll be positioned here.
Loaded question.
Be straight with me.
[EREN] You think my friends have
a shot at taking down a Titan?
Really? I should
certainly hope so,
otherwise what the hell
have they been training for?
Now listen, and listen
well. Prepared or not,
you're all Scouts, which
means the time is nigh
to choke back
those fears and--!
Long-range
formation. Let's go!
See you 'round. Good luck.
Do us a favor if you
run into one of 'em
and don't piss yourself.
Yeah. Same goes for you.
[ERWIN] The long-range
scouting formation
[ERWIN] is a
forward-facing semicircle.
[ERWIN] We'll be positioned
relative to one another at equal
[ERWIN] intervals within view
of signal fire on all sides.
[ERWIN] The idea is
to extend our spotting
[ERWIN] and signal
range as far as possible.
♪
[heavy breathing]
[ARMIN] Stay calm.
You're alright.
[NESS] You can bet the lucky
bastards riding in the front-row
[NESS] spotting squads
will see a lot of Titans.
[NESS] The second one comes
into view, lock and load.
[NESS] Alert your
nearest comrades with
[NESS] a red smoke signal.
[NESS] They in turn will
alert their nearest comrades
[NESS] by doing
the same, and so on.
[NESS] Once the
commander feels he has
[NESS] a decent read
on the Titan's position,
[NESS] he'll be firing
off a green smoke signal.
[NESS] At the sight of one,
[NESS] the platoon is
to reroute accordingly.
[NESS] The fewer Titans
confronted head-on en route
[NESS] to our goal, the better;
[NESS] we'll need all the
able bodies we can spare.
[NESS] The name of the
game then is evasion.
[NESS] Now keep in mind, this
isn't a foolproof strategy.
[NESS] The terrain is
wild; plenty of places
[NESS] for the enemy
to lie in ambush.
Red smoke. Have to fire--
[COMMANDER] Braus! Over here!
Damn! The Spotters
missed a live one!
I say we lure it
in our direction!
[COMMANDER] Braus!
Cross back over to us!
♪
Break away!
I'll take care of it!
Sir!
♪
[worried breathing]
Sorry!
[COMMANDER] It's alright, he's
out. Return to your position.
[ARMIN] Something feels off.
[ARMIN] It's been too long
since the last red signal,
[ARMIN] and the formation's
still all over the map.
[ARMIN] Wait.
[NESS] Keep in mind too,
this whole approach assumes
[NESS] we'll be dealing
largely with Normals;
[NESS] Titans whose
behavior is predictable.
[ARMIN] Black smoke? There's
a Titan ignoring the outliers
[ARMIN] and making a
b-line for the center!
[ARMIN] That can only mean...
[ARMIN] ...an Abnormal!
[NESS] If one or
more of those show up,
[NESS] I'm afraid we'll
have no choice but to engage.
Son of a-- Well there's no
help for it I guess. Heads up!
The nape's all yours,
okay? I'll go for the legs!
[CIS] You got it!
[NESS] ODM gear's worth
squat on level ground.
[NESS] I'm not exactly
thrilled about our odds here.
[NESS] But hell, we can't
let it break up the formation!
[NESS] Arlelt's up ahead
at my ten o'clock, isn't he?
[NESS] I'm not letting a
rookie face this bastard alone!
[NESS] It's now or never!
All yours, Cis!
[warcry]
Way to go!
Nicely done, Ness!
Not so bad.
[NESS] Hey, hey!
Nothing scares you, huh?
[NESS] That's my
li'l darlin' Charrette!
Not again. What in the hell
are the right wing
spotters doing back there?
Looks like we've got
another Abnormal on our hands.
It's not their fault.
[NESS] Ahhhh.
I hate these things.
Fine. One more
for the road, then.
[CIS] Right!
Damn it. Someone mind
tellin' me what we did
to deserve two in a row?
Bad enough it's an Abnormal,
but it's gotta be 14 meters.
This is gonna be
a pain in the ass.
♪
It's moving so fast. Too fast!
We have to keep it
clear of Arlelt! Cis!
[CIS] On it!
[Cis battle cry]
♪
Did that really just happen?
We're not dealing
with an Abnormal.
This thing's
showing intelligence!
Like the Colossal. Like Eren!
It's a human being
wrapped in a Titan body!
[ARMIN] But who? Why?
What am I gonna do?
I'm dead! I'm so dead!
[ARMIN] Go!
Make a break for it!
♪
[ARMIN] Why is it--
[ARMIN] No. Why are they...
[ARMIN] ...doing this?
[ELITE] Somebody
tell the others.
[ELITE] The right-wing
spotters are all but wiped out.
Tell Commander Erwin...
that the Female Titan
brought a hoard with her.
[ELITE] Is anyone left?
There has to be someone.
[shaky breathing]
Huh?
This doesn't make any sense.
Why didn't it--
Why didn't it kill me?
It pulled back my
hood. Looked at my--
Why would it need
to check my face?
[REINER] Armin!
Reiner!
Hey. Can you ride?
What the hell are you doing?
This is full-blown
Titan country,
[REINER] you can't be
without a horse! Climb on!
[REINER] I came
as fast as I could
[REINER] when I
saw the black smoke.
[REINER] Nice ass for an
Abnormal, you gotta admit.
[ARMIN] It's not an Abnormal.
[ARMIN] It's a person
controlling a Titan body.
Wait. What?
I'll explain in a second.
We need to fire off
a signal to
warn the others!
[ARMIN] Come on! Work
you piece of garbage!
It's an emergency!
Hey. It's alright. Looks
like Jean's got you covered.
[REINER] Oh man, that's not
good. The right-wing spotters
[REINER] have suffered too
many causalities to carry on!
Yeah, apparently
most of them were
wiped out by a Titan ambush.
I don't know how it
happened, but it was bad.
Sons-a-bitches
were lighting-fast.
[JEAN] The spotters
didn't have time to react.
[JEAN] Whoever's left is
trying to hold them off,
[JEAN] but that means now
there's no one on lookout duty.
[JEAN] Talk about
a setback, right?
[JEAN] If we don't
watch ourselves,
[JEAN] we're all
gonna get wiped out.
Wait. She came
from that direction.
Does that mean--
Could she have led the
Titans here like a commander?
Who, her?
[JEAN] Why the hell's she
running from us, by the way?
Is she an Abnormal?
No, she's isn't. I still
don't know how it's possible,
but she's another human
who's taken Titan form.
Someone who has
the same power as Eren.
Please say you're not serious.
Really? Why
do you think that?
Titans eat people,
but they're not murderers.
Sure, they kill
us in the process,
but that's not their intent;
they just feed on
instinct like any creature.
This one was different. When
the others went for her nape,
[ARMIN] she struck
them down in cold blood.
[ARMIN]
Swatted them like flies.
[ARMIN] She didn't eat them;
she killed them and moved on.
[ARMIN] That's out of character,
even for an Abnormal.
The Titans that
took out the right-wing?
I think she
brought them here.
Just like the Colossal and
the Armored when they struck.
I just know it.
She's not simply
satisfying bloodlust.
She has it in for us.
Or perhaps
more specifically,
I think she's actually
after someone in particular.
At which point the question
becomes who and why?
Hey, wait a second,
could it be Eren?
[REINER] Eren?
He's with Levi Squad.
[REINER] They're spearheading
the right-wing. Or, they were.
Wait. Levi's team?
I'm pretty sure you're
wrong there, big guy.
My copy of the plan
had them in the left wing.
That's odd, because my
copy of the plan had them
at the front of
the right-wing, too,
which now that I think
about it doesn't make sense.
Putting them at
the vanguard like that
wouldn't be
smart strategically.
Then where exactly
are they supposed to be?
Come on, where else? The safest
position in the formation.
Which, I assume, at least, would
be rear of the center rank.
[LEVI] Armin!
Now's not the time to be
chasin' our own
tails about this!
We've got to get word out
how dangerous this one is;
smoke signals
aren't gonna cut it!
[JEAN] At this rate, she'll
cut down the command squad!
[JEAN] We let that happen,
the formation goes to hell
[JEAN] and we all die!
[REINER] You have a plan?
More of a wing and a prayer.
Look, we've got to try
and distract her so the
platoon has a chance to retreat.
If we're careful,
from this distance
we should be able to manage it.
And make it out alive.
Well, maybe anyway.
She's smarter than the
ones we usually deal with.
You can take my word for
it. From her perspective
we're little
more than insects.
One swipe of that arm
and we're all flattened.
Is that a fact?
What a terrifying thought.
Seriously. What have you
done with the real Jean?
No offense, man, but the
one I knew could only be
counted on to
look out for himself.
Your people skills need work.
Believe me, friends. I'm
still all about number one.
[JEAN] I just don't wanna
end up a pile of bones
[JEAN] no one knows were mine.
Thing is, I get it now.
I get what needs to be done
if we're going to
survive this fight!
And last I checked,
nobody forced us
to take on this position.
Now are you with me or not?
Pull your hood all the
way over so it covers you.
She won't try to kill you
if she can't see your face!
[ARMIN] If she's looking
for someone specific,
[ARMIN] she won't mow
us down unless she knows
[ARMIN] for
sure we're not them.
[REINER] Good idea. As far
as she knows, any one of us
could be Eren
underneath this getup.
That's actually kind
of an encouraging thought.
Hey, you never know,
maybe we'll get lucky
and she'll be
near-sighted to boot.
Not gonna lie. The way you
clung to Eren like a security
blanket all the time
used to really creep me out.
But I always knew
you were brilliant.
Uh. Okay, thank you.
Not exactly sure how I ought
to take that, but thanks.
♪
[ARMIN] She's slowed a bit
since she first came at us.
[ARMIN] Tired maybe?
Let's hope.
[ARMIN] If she
speeds up, we lose her.
[ARMIN] We have to do this now,
before she gets her wind back!
♪
[JEAN] Okay, guys.
Like we discussed.
[JEAN] Lure her away from
the others so they have
[JEAN] a chance
to get out of here.
[JEAN] Keep her on our
trail for as long as possible.
[JEAN] Give the rest of
the platoon plenty of time.
[JEAN] Slicing
her Achilles' tendon
[JEAN] should do
the trick, I think.
[JEAN] Nothing crazy.
If she's what Armin says,
[JEAN] we need her alive.
[ARMIN] She's aware of her
soft spot, so she'll defend it.
[ARMIN] No run of-the-mill
nightmare, this one.
[ARMIN] Killing her
is out of the question.
[ARMIN] Well, it would be
for normal people anyway,
[ARMIN] So let's just focus
on keeping her distracted.
♪
[ARMIN] When the time comes,
maybe they could take her down.
♪
[Armin yelp]
[frigtened breathing]
[JEAN] Armin!
[JEAN] The moves on this one,
she's like a damn athlete!
[JEAN] We are so screwed!
Didn't think this through!
[JEAN] What? She's
protecting her weak spot?
Jean!
[JEAN] Damn it!
There's nothing I can do.
[JEAN] I'm a dead man! She's
gonna yank my wire and--!
Jean! Don't let that
suicidal maniac die in vain!
[JEAN] What the--?
[JEAN] Why did she stop?
She did it! She's
the one who killed him!
I told him the
right wing was suicide
but he went along anyway!
And how he's dead,
thanks to her!
♪
[JEAN] What the
hell's going on?
[JEAN] Of all the times
for Armin to get the sense
[JEAN] knocked out of him!
What's he talkin' about?
[JEAN] Reiner.
She crushed my best friend,
I saw it with my own eyes!
[ARMIN] His entrails were
stuck to the bottom of her foot!
[JEAN] He's going straight
for the nape? Of course!
[JEAN] Now's his chance,
while she's focused on Armin!
♪
Oh no. No.
[Reiner struggling]
[Jean shocked]
[JEAN] No! Reiner. Oh, god.
[Reiner warcry]
[JEAN] That beautiful bastard!
[JEAN] Mikasa's been hogging
so much of the limelight
[JEAN] these days,
I'd let myself forget
[JEAN] how much
of a badass he is.
Odds are that bought the
platoon more than enough time.
I say we follow suit
and get outta here!
[REINER] If she
doesn't have an appetite
[REINER] for
people like you say,
[REINER] I'm guessin'
she's not gonna follow us.
Alright! Looks
like she's in retreat!
Poor thing's running home
with her tail between her legs!
[ARMIN] What? Wait. No.
[ARMIN] She's headed
for the center rank.
[ARMIN] She's--
She's going for Eren!
[NARRATOR] The monster advances.
[NARRATOR] Even
the Scout Regiment,
[NARRATOR] for all
its training and skill,
[NARRATOR] cannot bring
its newest foe to heel.
[NARRATOR] Until at last,
in a forest of giant trees,
[NARRATOR] she catches
sight of her goal.