[NARRATOR] After
setting forth to establish
[NARRATOR] a route
to Shiganshina,
[NARRATOR] the Scout Regiment
encountered a Female Titan
[NARRATOR] seemingly
possessed of sharp,
[NARRATOR]
cold-hearted intelligence.
♪
[NARRATOR] As soldier upon
soldier fell to this new foe,
[NARRATOR] the
regiment retreated into
[NARRATOR] a forest
of massive trees.
[NARRATOR] Though
to what purpose,
[NARRATOR] no one
appeared to know.
[EREN] If the Levi Squad can't
stop this thing, then who can?
[EREN] Those men need us!
[EREN] Another one!
[EREN] Damn it,
he didn't have to die!
[LEVI] The choice is yours.
You can trust yourself,
[LEVI] or you can trust
the people willing to
[LEVI] put their lives
on the line for you.
I'm with you!
Fire!
[EREN] Wait, what?
[EREN] They're going to
take her alive? Seriously?
So what do you
think of us now, Eren?
We managed to
outsmart the damn thing!
Let this be a lesson
to you, greenhorn.
Don't ever
underestimate the Scouts!
[ORUO] Never again! Agreed?
Agreed!
She's not putting
up much of a fight.
That's no reason
to let our guard down.
[ERWIN] Good work,
leading her here.
[ERWIN] I'm more than
a little impressed.
We couldn't have
without the rear contingent
whose lives bought us
time. This belongs to them.
I don't intend
to ever forget that.
That so?
[LEVI] Yes.
Because of their sacrifices,
[LEVI] we can expose
whoever this really is.
Ten to one they're in there
pissing themselves
right about now.
[EREN] An Abnormal?
No, she's more like--
more like the Colossal Titan!
Wait, so does that mean
Commander Erwin was--?
Hey! Snap out of it, runt!
[PETRA] You can
puzzle it all out later.
Right now we need you
focused on pushing ahead.
Right!
Not quite yet, Levi.
A little more insurance.
[ERWIN] Second and third waves!
Fire!
[ERWIN] All reserves!
[distant weapon fire]
[grunting]
They, uh-- They've
figured out how to climb.
I can see that. Well,
if they make it up this far
we can always go up a
little further, I suppose.
[NANABA] Anyway. I doubt
we'll be here much longer.
[NANABA] I suspect
the order to withdraw
will be coming any minute.
[CHRISTA] What
makes you say that?
[CHRISTA] Those
explosions just now?
[CHRISTA] I hope
everything's alright in there.
Me, too.
[SASHA] Mikasa. You think
that's cannon fire or what?
I mean, nothing else makes
that kind of racket, right?
[REINER] If that's the case,
why didn't we see them
[REINER] bring any cannons in?
What the hell's with
all the noise? Seriously.
Gimme a hand here, Bertholdt.
[YMIR] You happen see what
tree Christa scuttled up?
Sorry. I don't have a clue.
[CONNY] Nothing
makes sense anymore.
[CONNY] What are
we even doing here?
[CONNY] I just wanna go home.
Whaddya say we
get outta the way?
[JEAN] Ugly bastard is
really gettin' the hang of it.
At this rate, he's
gonna try his hand
at buildin' a damn tree house.
The alarming thing is that
this shows that they can learn.
Not a pleasant thought.
Of course, they probably
[ARMIN] all develop
at different rates.
[JEAN] Hey, Armin. They
want us keeping these Titans
[JEAN] outta the forest right?
[JEAN] I think I
just figured out why.
[JEAN] We're here to lure
that Female Titan into a trap.
[JEAN] C'mon.
What else could it be?
[JEAN] It's like you said.
[JEAN] There's a person
inside it steerin' the thing.
[JEAN] Commander Erwin
wants to find out who.
[EREN] So that was
the plan from the start?
[EREN] We weren't flying
by the seat of our pants?
Look, I'm not complaining.
I get keeping it from me.
But, come on! Keeping
you guys in the dark?
You'd think you'd
earned a little more
trust than that, right?
Damn, you're annoying.
I hope you're not suggesting the
captain kept the plan from us
because he thinks
we're a liability!
[EREN] I'm sorry, but I am!
[EREN] There's just no
other way it makes sense!
[ORUO] Enough of this!
[ORUO] Petra! Knock the
teeth out of his skull!
Look, I hate to say it,
but he's got a point.
[ORUO] Huh?
For being as
supposedly instrumental
to the plan as we were,
[ELD] the captain didn't
give us much to go on.
So, what?
[ELD] That means he doesn't
trust us. Kind of a big deal.
C'mon, you guys.
Think about it.
Maybe Eren isn't the
only one who can change.
[ELD] Maybe someone in
the regiment's a Titan spy.
It's the only way all
the pieces fit. You with me?
Yeah. Best explanation.
[GUNTHER] A spy?
Are you sure about that?
[ELD] Well, no. But I'm sure
the commander believes it.
He'd have to. And
I'll wager you anything
the only people
in the know on this
were the survivors
from five years ago.
[GUNTHER] Of course.
That's got to be it.
I concur whole-heartedly.
Hear that, Snivel-drop?
There was a good reason.
Right. Yes. A
perfectly good reason.
It adds up. After
all, in their position,
it's the best way of
narrowing down the list
of suspects to a
manageable number.
[PETRA] Shiganshina's
probably when the spy got in.
So, you think this
person's responsible
for killing Sawney and Beane?
Possibly. In fact,
after it happened,
the commander asked
me this odd question.
What is it you think you see?
Who do you think
the real enemy is here?
So that's what
he meant. Of course.
[ELD] If we'd known the
answer to that question,
he probably would've let us
in on what was happening today.
Though, there again, I really
don't think any of us could've.
[ORUO] Speak for yourself,
my friend. I knew.
I just decided to
keep my own counsel.
Doubtless you appreciate
the reason for my silence.
[PETRA] Which would be?
[ORUO] Oh, come now. Surely
you all know? Dear oh dear.
[ORUO] Perhaps I've
said too much already.
[ORUO] Well,
one day, when you've
[ORUO] reached my
level of expertise...
Look, we all get that you like
to pretend you're Captain Levi.
[PETRA] But that's
not how he sounds.
[EREN] If we pull this off,
[EREN] we might learn
what the Titans are all about.
[EREN] But, even for that...
[EREN] was it worth
letting so many people die?
You think the
commander was wrong
to leave us out of the loop?
Well he certainly
wasn't in the right.
Why put so many
of our lives at risk
just because one
of us can't be trusted?
Hell, we could've
smoked out the spy.
Maybe saved some good people.
No. He did what was necessary.
Are you seriously
trying to defend him?
Do you know
how many of us died
so the commander
could play intrigue?
[ARMIN] Of course
I do. All I'm saying
[ARMIN] is it's easy
to judge in hindsight.
[ARMIN] At the time, though,
there was no way to know
how things would turn out.
He's a commander,
not a soothsayer.
He had to act on
what he had. Period.
[ARMIN] He had to choose: a
handful of us, or all of us?
[ARMIN] What
would you have done?
He made a decision. He
sacrificed a hundred lives
for the good of mankind.
Eren, I can understand why
you still have your doubts,
but in time you'll come to
realize, just like we all did,
why Erwin Smith was
entrusted to lead the Scouts
and carry humanity's hope.
Or why even someone as cagey
as Captain Levi can trust him.
Indeed. Live long enough
and you'll understand
the weight of it.
[ARMIN] I may be naive but,
there's one thing I
know beyond all doubt.
Genuine harbingers of
change must be able to
do what others won't dare.
Sacrifice their heart.
Accept the burden of
doing the unspeakable.
[ARMIN] Whether we like to admit
it or not, the fact is this:
[ARMIN] To rise above monsters,
we have to abandon our humanity.
[ARMIN] That's
the irony, really.
If you can't let it go,
it's not worth holding on to.
Fire!
[HANGE] Poor thing.
[HANGE] Can't so much
as bat an eyelash, can we?
[HANGE] Must be
terribly frustrating.
[HANGE] Get
used to it, my dear.
Heh. Biology can
often times be a curse.
Case in point, the
more your wounds heal,
the stiffer
your joints become.
[Hange chuckling]
[HANGE] Now what in the world
is the hold-up on the extraction
of our esteemed guest?
It won't get any easier.
[HANGE] Strike while
the iron is hot, I say!
[ERWIN] An impressive ability.
So she can harden her skin
[ERWIN] to protect
portions of her body.
[ERWIN] Similar to the
one who rushed Wall Maria.
[ERWIN] The Armored Titan,
I believe they called him.
[ERWIN] The question is,
how many blade strikes
[ERWIN] would it take to
finally chip our way through?
[ERWIN] Too many, in
any event. Time is short.
Yes, sir?
Prepare an artillery round.
I want her hands blown off.
With all due
respect, Commander,
there's a risk if we
use the cannons.
The hands will get blown off,
but whatever's beneath
them will too, sir.
[ERWIN] A fine point,
soldier. Which is why
[ERWIN] you'll aim carefully
and sever them at the wrists.
On my signal I want
an all-out salvo.
[SOLDIER] Yes, sir!
[LEVI] Knock knock.
We know you're in there.
[LEVI] Why don't you make
this easy and come on out.
[LEVI] Stop wasting our time.
[LEVI] Seriously, what can
you hope to gain by stalling?
[LEVI] If you're thinking
we'll let you go, we won't.
about trying to escape, don't.
All you should
be thinking about
are the good men
you killed today.
[LEVI] Not that you would.
[LEVI] That's not your
style, is it? Remorse.
[LEVI] You enjoy killing.
Which means we have
something in common.
'Course, I enjoy
killing Titans.
But it's a start.
I'm sure we can still
find some middle ground.
[LEVI] Oh, that's right.
[LEVI] While we're on
that subject, let me ask.
You're okay with me cuttin' your
limbs off at the joints, right?
[LEVI] I mean,
they'll grow back.
[LEVI] I'm talking
about your actual body.
[LEVI] Don't want
you dead just yet.
[LEVI] Timing wouldn't work.
[Female Titan roaring]
Nicely done. I almost
lost my composure.
Were those like, death
throes or something?
[MICHE] They're coming.
I can smell them.
From what direction?
From every direction.
Fast. Dozens.
What the hell is this?
They-- They're all going in!
[JEAN] Why're they ignoring
us all've a sudden?
Oh no.
You-- You tellin' me
they're all Abnormals?
Who cares? Concentrate
on pushing 'em back!
[ELITE] Engage!
[MIKASA] What's
going on over there?
[SASHA] Wait! Please!
I know that sound.
It used to haunt my sleep.
I'd hear it from the
forest in the dead of night.
Believe me, nothing in
the world screams like that
except a dying animal.
It's the sound of a creature
who knows it's got
absolutely nothing to lose.
It's alright, I
know to be careful.
That is not the
right attitude to have!
You can't just be careful,
you have to be terrified!
Have you ever seen me
terrified of anything?
No! And I'm tellin' ya this'd
be a good time to try it out!
Right.
[MIKASA] I have
to give her credit.
[MIKASA] The girl's instincts
are usually dead-on.
[MIKASA] Especially right
before all hell breaks lose.
[MIKASA] Eren's in
the center rank, I think.
[MIKASA] That's what Armin said.
Faster on the
artillery, gentlemen!
Here they are. First
wave's closing from the east,
and coming in fast!
Wagon defense squad!
Intercept, now!
[gasps]
What's going on? Damn
things passed right by us!
[SOLDIER 1] Three Titans
have broken through!
[SAOLDIER 2] Captain Levi!
[LEVI] Hey! What did you do?
[LEVI] You called up
some friends, didn't you?
[ERWIN] It ignored us
and went straight for her?
[SOLDIER] The enemy is bearing
down from all directions!
All hands, commence combat!
[ERWIN] Defend the
Female Titan at all costs!
♪
[HANGE] No!
[ERWIN] All hands, withdraw!
[ERWIN] Redeploy the formation!
Return to Calaneth District!
[panting]
[ERWIN] We've been bested.
Oh, don't give me that crap.
Not now. Not yet.
[ERWIN] Think about it.
The enemy was prepared
to make sacrifices.
Enormous ones.
[ERWIN] So committed
to maintaining her secret,
[ERWIN] she would
rather let herself
[ERWIN] be cannibalized
than exposed.
[LEVI] That whole song
and dance in the courtroom,
[LEVI] and this is what
we've got to show for it.
[LEVI] We scurry back now with
our tail between our legs,
[LEVI] Eren's right
back in chains, or worse.
[ERWIN] We'll jump off that
bridge when we come to it.
[ERWIN] Right now our only
concern is getting back without
[ERWIN] sustaining further
casualties. However we can.
[ERWIN] This steam
isn't helping matters.
[ERWIN] Smoke signals aren't
likely to cut through the murk.
[LEVI] I'll
gather up my squad.
[ERWIN] Not yet, Levi.
First replenish your
blades and your fuel.
I can deal
with what I've got.
We're running against
the clock as it is. Why?
Because I said.
That's an order.
Whatever you say, sir.
I trust you implicitly.
[NANABA] Withdraw? I
guess we're done here.
We return to HQ on horseback.
Understood.
Hold on. You tellin'
me it's over?
Ah! Thank god!
[MIKASA] I don't
like this. Eren...
[GUNTHER] That's our cue.
Alright, let's saddle
up! We're going home!
Chop-chop, runt. One would
think you'd be beside yourself
to get an eyeful of who's
driving that gargantuan harpy.
[EREN] You really think
they found out who it is?
Of course, all thanks to you!
[EREN] I didn't do anything.
You learned to trust the
fellow members of your squad.
That's big. The sort of
thing that turns out well
for everyone
involved, actually.
A lesser man in your dilemma
probably would've buckled.
[PETRA] Then where would we be?
[ORUO] Oh, please.
[ORUO] Why don't you stroke
his forehead while you're at it.
[ORUO] We'd be
exactly where we are now,
without of course having had
to endure his incessant whining.
Don't wait for me
to decorate your path
in pink and white rose petals.
Survive the journey home
and I might be
persuaded to respect you.
The mission isn't over.
Not 'til we're
though the gates.
[ORUO] Do you understand?
Yes, sir. I
completely understand.
Oruo! Petra! I gotta
hand it to ya both.
For someone who wet
themselves first time out,
[ELD] you've come a long way.
[screaming]
I thought we agreed
never to speak of it again!
[EREN] Whoa. Seriously?
Relax. Incidentally, I've never
once pissed myself in battle.
[ORUO] How dare you! I have
the highest kill-count
of anyone on the
damn squad! Argh! Imbecile!
[ELD] You wanna hide that
stain behind your kill-counts,
be my guest.
Shut your hole!
[EREN] So did it, like,
rain down on everyone
[EREN] midair, or what?
[GUNTHER] Enough! No one
cares who pissed who's pants!
Focus on the job at hand!
For the record, my
shorts've always been dry.
Huh?
[GUNTHER] Must be a signal
from the captain himself.
Stow the chatter
'til we're home.
We'll rendezvous
with Levi shortly.
[HANGE] Erwin. Why bother
having him replenish?
There's no time.
We saw the Female
Titan get eaten.
Did we actually see the person
inside suffer the same fate?
[ERWIN] I didn't.
[gasp] You mean...?
[ERWIN] Yes. Your hypothesis
is correct. This isn't over.
We're dealing
with someone like Eren.
[ERWIN] Someone who regenerates
in and out of Titan form.
Suppose that person
equipped themselves
[ERWIN] with
ODM gear in advance.
[ERWIN] Suppose further
that they're also disguised
[ERWIN] in one
of our uniforms?
[ERWIN] What would
their next move be?
[GUNTHER] Captain Levi?
Wait, that--
That's not-- Oh shit!
[all gasp]
[EREN] Gunther! You
okay? What happened?
[EREN] Talk to me!
[gasp]
[ERWIN] How do you
ferret out the enemy...
[ERWIN] when they're
one of your own?
[NARRATOR] Erwin's
plan has backfired.
[NARRATOR] The dreaded Female
Titan comes for Eren yet again.
[NARRATOR] But between
her and her quarry
[NARRATOR] stands a team
of expert Titan slayers.
[NARRATOR] The
Special Operations Squad.