Wake up! Armin! Hey!
[CONNY] Can you hear me? C'mon!
Snap out of it! I need you
to talk to me! Say something!
[CONNY] There you
are. You with me now?
[CONNY] What's going
on? Where's your squad?
[ARMIN] Squad?
Alright, let's
get you on your feet.
You shouldn't
be out here alone.
And what the hell you got all
over you that's so damn slimy?
[CONNY] What happened?
[Armin screaming]
You're worthless!
Why can't you just die?
Hey, you need to
pull yourself together!
Damn you!
[CONNY] Where is everyone?
[YMIR] Let it go, Conny.
He's it. There
rest of 'em are dead.
Damn it, don't talk like that!
We can't assume
he's the only one!
Take a look around
you; isn't it obvious?
We can't waste any
more time here with him.
We've gotta move on.
You're not making any sense.
Why would the Titans ignore him?
I dunno. Maybe they thought he
was already dead or something.
When you get right down to it,
that's the real tragedy here.
[YMIR] Eren and the
others bust their asses,
[YMIR] and the one
left standing is him.
Alright. That does it, bitch.
I'm gonna shut your
mouth up permanently!
Both of you stop it right now!
Look, we're all at the
end of our tether, okay?
We're seeing our friends
being killed like animals.
It's normal to be upset.
Look at my Christa
keepin' the peace!
You're so gonna
have to marry me
when all this crap
is over! [laughing]
[CONNY] Yeah, well...
She'd best get a
hold of that mouth.
Alright. Come on.
We gotta get out of here.
Are you able to stand?
Sorry to be a nuisance.
Don't worry about me.
I'll rendezvous
with the rear guard.
But-- Armin!
[MALE CADET] Conny, hop to!
[MALE CADET] We've been
given orders to advance!
[ARMIN] I was wrong. This
world hasn't become hell.
It's been hell. I just
couldn't see it before now.
We're condemned. All of us.
Have been from the beginning.
[ARMIN] Strength
preys on weakness.
[ARMIN] It's a very
straightforward
[ARMIN] arrangement, actually.
[ARMIN] And my
friends... They--
[ARMIN] They tried. They
knew how the world worked.
[ARMIN] They wanted
to be strong. For me.
[ARMIN] Someone who
only brought them down.
[ARMIN] In their
eyes, I was a victim.
[ARMIN] I needed protection.
[ARMIN] But all I
wanted was to stand
[ARMIN] shoulder-
to-shoulder with them;
[ARMIN] to be strong,
like they were.
[ARMIN] To be worth something.
[ARMIN] And this
is how it all ends up.
[ARMIN] Eren tried
to protect me and--
Hanna. What are
you trying to do?
Oh god, Armin! Help me, please!
Franz quit breathing
and I can't wake him up!
[HANNA] He won't respond
to CPR! Come on, baby!
[HANNA] You got
this! Stay with me!
Somebody help us!
Hanna, please. It's
not safe on the ground,
we need to get
you on a rooftop--
[HANNA] No! I'm not
leaving him like this!
You really don't
understand, do you?
Hanna, I'm sorry. Franz is-
Please stop.
Please stop doing that.
[ARMIN] I can't.
[ARMIN] I-- I can't take it.
[ARMIN] This is hell.
[frantic shouting]
What in the hell is wrong with
you people? I don't think you
fully appreciate how
bad the situation is!
Oh, I appreciate it just fine,
believe me! You wanna make it
out of here alive,
stop whining and help!
[crowd shouting]
You're a soldier! Do something!
Make him move that damn wagon!
I'm not exactly sure--
Take your best
shot, little man.
I'm the president of
this town's merchant guild.
Uh-- Well, I--
Who do you think pays all
the bills for the food you
and your buddies crap out?
Or maybe you've got some
finances tucked away to fund
the racket you call a job?
Now shut up and push!
This cargo's worth more than
you people make
in your whole lives!
[MERCHANT] Nobody's
getting out of here unless
[MERCHANT] the
wagon's in front of 'em!
[MERCHANT] There's a
reward in it if you help!
[WOMAN] Don't worry, sweetheart.
[WOMAN] Daddy's
going to use those big,
[WOMAN] loud cannons he showed
us to scare the Titans off.
Mommie, look. There.
[screaming]
Push it through, dammit!
If you don't, that
thing's gonna kill us all!
[WOMAN] Stop! You'll
trample the children!
Someone wanna tell me why the
son of a bitch is ignoring us?
It's an Abnormal; stop
trying to figure him out!
He's too fast! There's
no way we'll overtake him
before he reaches the gate!
Just stay on him!
[MIKASA] Excuse me.
What is all this?
Couldn't have asked
for better timing!
Force these useless
morons to push my wagon!
I'll pay you handsomely!
Seriously? Soldiers
are dying back there.
Laying down
their lives for you.
All because this
is taking too long.
Yeah, that's their job.
You expect me to shed a tear
'cause they gotta fulfill
the duties they signed on for?
They're supposed to be willing
to lay down their lives!
Don't get all high-handed
on me just 'cause you finally
gotta earn your damn
keep after all these years!
[quiet chatter]
Yeah. No arguing with that.
You're absolutely right, sir.
Guess it's what you call
the greater good. Still.
Sometimes it's not
the life or the death
of a soldier that makes
the biggest difference.
Don't you even dare! Your
commander and I are old friends!
One word from me and
you'll be court marshaled!
[MERCHANT] Believe it!
That word gonna come
from beyond the grave?
No! Wait!
Sir, maybe we should uh--
Pull the damn wagon out.
[chatter]
[GIRL] You're amazing!
You've saved our lives, miss.
All of us are in your debt.
[IAN] Good work,
Ackerman. I'm impressed.
[MIKASA] I did what I could
here, sir. But, thank you.
I need to be a bit more
careful in the future.
I inadvertently dulled
both of the blades.
I'll do better next time.
What on earth have
you had to live through
to be so non-chalant.
I'm sorry. That
was uncalled for.
Why do I have to
suddenly think of you now?
[MIKASA] I'm finished, Momma!
What do you think?
Did I do good?
Oh, darling. It's absolutely
fantastic! Excellent work!
Aww, thank you!
We've kept this style of
embroidery a special family
secret for heaven knows
how many generations.
One day, when you have
children of your own,
you'll be able to
pass the secret on to them.
Huh? I don't understand;
how can I have children?
[MIKASA'S MOM] Uh. Honey,
why don't you explain?
Yeah! Please, Daddy?
Well I'm not sure I'm really
an expert on the subject.
But you know what? That nice
Dr. Jaeger's scheduled to
pay us a visit today.
Maybe you could talk to him.
[knock-knock]
[MIKASA'S DAD] Ah!
Speak of the devil!
[knock-knock]
[MIKASA'S DAD] Just a moment.
[EREN] Her name's Mikasa?
Yes, and she's
just about your age,
so try to get along, okay?
There aren't really that
many children around here
and I'd rather you not
grow up to be an outcast.
If she's nice to me, then
we won't have a problem.
Eren. Look for
the bad in people
expecting to find
it and you will.
That's odd. Are they home?
[knocking] Mr. Ackermann!
It's Dr. Jaeger!
Is anyone there?
Well are they or aren't they?
[EREN] Dad? What's wrong?
[GRISHA] Damn it.
Look around. Can you
see the daughter anywhere?
Perhaps she's outside.
[EREN] I don't think so.
This is bad. I need to alert
the Military Police of this
while the trail's warm. Wait for
me at the foot of the mountain.
[GRISHA] Understood? Say that
back to me. Word for word.
[GRISHA] Eren!
[MAN 1] Uh-huh. All I'm
sayin' is she better go
[MAN 1] for a decent price.
[MAN 1] I didn't get blood
on my hands for nothing.
Look at her face and
tell me what's she's worth.
[MAN 1] Sure, she's cute
and all. Just young.
[MAN 1] Wouldn't
go for her myself.
Then I guess we're lucky you're
not the one we're sellin' to.
Plenty of folks'd
pay a premium.
She's exotic; what they
used to call an "Oriental."
You know about all that, right?
Back when there used to be
different breeds of
people. A bunch of 'em from
the Far East came
scramblin' here for safety.
[MAN 2] The old
perverts in the capital
[MAN 2] really go for
that sort of thing.
[MAN 2] This li'l beauty's
gonna fetch a mint at auction.
[MAN 2] It's great business;
she's the last of her kind.
[MAN 2] All the rest
of her people died out.
Tell me another one.
It's not like she's
a pureblood or anything.
Her old man wasn't "Oriental."
Good point there.
The mother would've been
a nice addition, right?
Too bad she's in pieces!
Gimme a break! What
was I supposed to do?
She was puttin' up a fight!
[MAN 2] So you couldn't have
just knocked her unconscious?
[knock-knock]
We were just talking
about you, Doctor--
Sorry. Hope we're
not interrupting.
[MAN 1] Let's take this nice and
easy. I don't imagine anybody
[MAN 1] wants their skulls
split open by this little guy--
[struggling scream]
This bitch is out of her mind!
Run, Mikasa! Run
as fast as you can!
Stop it; you're scaring me.
I want you to be scared!
Move it! Get away from here!
[struggling screams]
[MIKASA] Dad?
Screw it. You
ain't worth this crap!
You stupid bastard! The plan
was to only kill the father!
She was nuts!
I'm supposed to let her
[MAN 1] gouge my eyes
out with those shears?
[MAN 2] I don't want to
hear it! Just bag the kid!
[MAN 1] Fine!
[MAN 1] Hey. Let's not give
me any attitude, alright?
If you're feelin' feisty,
this is what you get.
So cold.
[EREN] Oh, I'm sorry.
[MAN 1] Don't move from
that spot, you little vermin.
How did you even
you find this place?
Uh. Well, I was in
the woods and got lost.
[EREN] I saw your cabin and--
Lost in the woods, huh? A kid
your age shouldn't be out there
on his own to begin with.
Big bad wolves are liable to
[MAN 1] pounce on
you from outta nowhere.
It's alright now, though;
you'll be safe here.
My buddy and I'll
be happy to take y--
[EREN] I appreciate that,
sir. But I'm not stupid.
And I'm the last
thing you'll ever see.
What the hell do
you think you're doing?
Hey, you little
bastard! Get back here!
[Eren screaming]
[EREN] You're an animal! You
hear me? No! You're a disease!
This is what you get,
you son of a bitch!
This is what you get
for being what you are!
Die! Die!
The hard part's
over. You're safe now.
Anyway, Mikasa, right?
My name's Eren.
I'm Dr. Jaeger's son.
I met your folks once or
twice while I was with him.
[EREN] We were stopping by
your house today for a checkup.
[EREN] We saw...
What happened
to the third one?
This is all
your doing, isn't it?
[MAN] Answer me, you little
bastard! You did this!
I'm gonna kill you!
You're gonna die!
Take-- Take him out.
[EREN] Fight!
Kill or be killed.
Fight for your life!
[EREN] It's--
It's the only way.
Who the hell do you think
you are, you little brat?
[EREN] The only way
to live is to fight!
I can't. I don't
think I can do this.
[MIKASA} And all of
a sudden, I remembered.
[MIKASA] I'd seen it all before.
[MIKASA] Many, many times.
Since the day I was born.
[MIKASA] It'd been all
around me. Forever.
[MIKASA] But...
[MIKASA] I always
looked the other way.
[MIKASA] Yeah. The
world is a cruel place.
[MIKASA] And it's home.
[MIKASA] All of a sudden,
my body wasn't shaking.
[MIKASA] I was in total
control. Focused. Ready.
[MIKASA] All of a sudden,
I could do anything.
[MIKASA] "Fight."
[MIKASA] "Fight!"
[MIKASA] Fight!
[Mikasa screaming]
[ELITE] Stabbed through
the heart from behind.
Surely a couple of kids
couldn't've done this.
Damn it, son. I made it
clear I wanted you to wait
at the foot of the mountain.
Do you even understand
the magnitude of what
you've done here today?
Sorry, Dad. I'm not gonna
feel bad for what happened.
They were animals
disguised as humans
who needed to be put down.
Listen to yourself!
[EREN] By the time the
Military Police got here,
[EREN] they'd have been
long gone and you know it!
[EREN] We couldn't
afford to wait!
That's not what
I'm arguing about!
You threw caution to the wind
and survived by pure luck!
[GRISHA] You're strong, yes,
[GRISHA] but you are
too damn young to be
[GRISHA] so casual about
gambling with your life!
But, I-- I didn't know how
else I was supposed to save her.
Mikasa. Remember me?
We met a few times before
when you were just
a tiny little thing.
Yes, Dr. Jaeger. So, um--
Sorry, can you just
tell me how to get home?
[MIKASA] It's cold. I'm tired.
There's really nowhere
else for me to go.
[EREN] Don't worry.
You can keep it.
That ought to keep
you warm, right?
I think so.
Mikasa, how would you feel
about coming to live with us?
[MIKASA] What?
I can't even imagine
what you've been through.
[GRISHA] But I do know
you need your share of rest.
[EREN] What's the problem?
[EREN] Don't think
about it. Just come on.
We gotta get home.
Yeah. Okay.
[MIKASA] The world's
a cruel place.
[MIKASA] If you want to
live, you have to fight.
[IAN] That's it. We're done.
Now scale the wall.
I should help the
vanguard withdraw, sir.
Ackerman! Wait!
[MIKASA] It's a cruel world,
but I have a place in it.
[MIKASA] Eren. As long
as you're part of my life,
[MIKASA] I can fight
to the bitter end.
[NARRATOR] "It's a cruel world,
but I have a place in it."
[NARRATOR] Mikasa races
through hell to be beside
[NARRATOR] the one person who
makes the struggle worthwhile
[NARRATOR] only to learn
just how deep hell goes.