[NARRATOR] In the year 850, the
Colossal Titan again appeared
[NARRATOR] and decimated
yet another barrier
[NARRATOR] between us and them.
[NARRATOR] Once more,
mankind retreated in panic
[NARRATOR] before the
advance of its greatest foe.
[NARRATOR] Brave soul
after brave soul perished.
[NARRATOR] Eaten alive.
Eren! No!
[Armin screaming]
[NARRATOR] Eren, himself,
fell prey to their hunger.
[CONNY] Whoa,
Mikasa is a badass!
[CONNY] How is
she going so fast?
[ARMIN] No! Mikasa's
using too much gas!
[MIKASA] I'll do
whatever it takes to win!
[MIKASA] Whatever
it takes to live!
[battle cry]
[NARRATOR] Just when things
seemed their darkest for Mikasa,
[NARRATOR] out of nowhere
came the unlikeliest of allies.
[roar]
[ARMIN] There. Got it!
The ODM gear's functional.
[ARMIN] And I restocked
your blades.
[ARMIN] Just-- Just
leave me this one, okay?
[ARMIN] It's just that...
I would rather this be my end,
[ARMIN] not being eaten alive.
Why'd you--?
[MIKASA] Armin.
I will not leave you behind.
[ARMIN] But-- I mean--
Titans are everywhere!
You can't jump and
carry me on your back at--
[CONNY] Come on. Let's move.
[ARMIN] Please. Don't do
this. It's not going to work.
[ARMIN[ Enough people
have died on my account.
[roar]
[gasp]
[ARMIN] No!
[ARMIN] Hold on!
I've got an idea!
What is it then?
[ARMIN] Only you two are
capable of pulling this off,
[ARMIN] so it's
really your choice.
This may sound crazy, but
I think he might be useful.
Whoa, you mean the Titan?
[ARMIN] He only
attacks his own kind.
He seems to have
no interest in us.
What if we can
somehow steer him to HQ
and let him loose
on the other Titans?
Look, we know he's taken
at least one out already.
We can use him as a weapon!
You have got to be kidding!
How the hell you think
we're supposed
to steer that thing!
Well, something tells me
he's fighting on instinct.
I'm almost sure if you
take down the pair he's
tangling with now,
he'll go look for others.
That'd lead him straight to HQ.
[ARMIN] We're not steering
him so much as luring him.
[ARMIN] I think
it'll work. I really do.
Think? You're asking us to
risk our necks on
a stupid gut feeling?
If I'm right about this,
we can put down the siege
[ARMIN[ on headquarters
in one fell swoop!
[MIKASA] It's worth a shot.
Huh? Seriously?
Better to take a gamble
on Armin's gut feeling
than wait around
to be slaughtered.
If there's a decent
shot, why not take it?
[CONNY] So, basically we're
going to recruit a Titan?
[MIKASA] Yes. Exactly.
We'll look like morons
if we screw this up.
Yeah. But if we don't, look how
many lives we stand to save.
Where there's a
will there's a way.
It's still nuts,
but what the hell.
Why couldn't I stop them?
[JEAN] I'm the last person that
should've been given the reigns!
No! No. This is our chance.
[JEAN] We can get
the drop on them
[JEAN] while they're
preoccupied. It's perfect!
[JEAN] Let's go!
Make for a break for HQ
while they're distracted!
We can do this! Hey, we run
out of gas, we're dead anyway.
Give it everything you've got!
[roar]
[struggling]
♪
Jean!
You really came through for us
there, man; we owe you big time.
Huh?
Don't shrug it off, I'm serious.
We're alive because of you!
Like I said, you
make a great leader!
Easy with that crap.
We're not outta this yet!
[Male Cadet screaming]
Damn it!
[war cry]
[glass breaking]
[JEAN] How many--
How many of us made it?
How many bodies
did I crawl over?
How many of our
comrades died on my orders?
[crying]
Hold on a sec. You guys
with the supply team?
[MALE SOLDIER] Yeah.
[MARCO] Jean! Stop!
You cowards! You left
us out there on our own!
People are dead
'cause you didn't
have the guts to do your job!
The Titans were coming
at us from every angle!
They overran the
supply room, okay?
It's your job to deal with
it and back us up anyway!
[REINER] Hit the deck!
Son of a--
[JEAN] There's too many
people! They can smell us!
[SOLDIER 1] Run!
[SOLDIER 2] Get further in!
[SOLDIER 3] We can't
all go at once!
[CADET 1] Where's Mikasa?
Have you seen her?
[CADET 2] She ran out of gas.
Forget about her. She's dead!
This is it. This is reality.
[JEAN] Of course it is.
How deluded was I?
[distant chaos]
[JEAN] No. No, on some
level, I knew it all along.
I mean, when you stop and
think for second, it's obvious.
There's no winning.
Not against them.
[gasp]
[heart beats]
[JEAN] What?
[roar]
Wha-- What the--? My god.
[glass breaking]
Mikasa, you're--!
Wow. Close one.
I was running on fumes.
We made it here, though!
Crazy, but we did!
You-- I-- Am I
dreaming this, or what?
You're a certified genius!
From now on, far as I'm
concerned, your word is law!
Check it out! We found
an Abnormal that's got
a bone to pick
with its own kind.
And the best part? He
couldn't care less about us!
[CONNY] That's right, you
heard me. This big beautiful
[CONNY] S.O.B.'s our
ticket out of here!
You mean like
fighting fire with fire?
Listen to yourself. A
Titan's not gonna help us!
You're out of your mind
if you think this can work--
[MIKASA] It is working.
For whatever reason
he's rampaging against them.
Stand back and let him
do it. Trust me. You'll see.
[roar]
[MIKASA] Either way.
What choice do we have?
[MIKASA] Right now that thing
is our best chance at survival.
[growling]
[roar]
[CONNY] Look at him go!
This guy makes the others
[CONNY] look like
total weaklings.
[CONNY] They're not
gonna take this building.
[CONNY] Not with him
on a rampage out there.
That's all well and good.
But what's to keep him
from turning on
us once he's done?
Guess we'll worry
about that when we're safe.
Yeah, you're right. At least
he's buying us a little time.
[JEAN] Good news!
Courtesy of the Military Police.
And covered
with a layer of dust.
Are you absolutely sure
buckshot is the way to go?
Seems like we might
as well throw spit wads.
[JEAN] I mean, c'mon guys.
Are guns even effective?
I dunno, but they're bound
to be better than nothing.
We're looking at seven
Titans in the supply room of
the four-meters-tall variety.
If we time this perfectly,
this much ammo oughta
be enough to do the trick.
[ARMIN] Step one, we lower
a group into the area via lift
[ARMIN] to get
the Titans' attention.
[ARMIN] Step two, when
the Titans come within range,
[ARMIN] the group
fires in all four directions
[ARMIN] simultaneously,
blinding them.
Then the hard part.
[ARMIN] The moment
of truth, as it were.
[ARMIN] Before the
Titans have time to recover,
[ARMIN] seven of us
swoop down from the ceiling
[ARMIN] and strike
their vital regions.
[ARMIN] That's it.
That's the plan.
It puts all our
lives on the line--
We screw up, we're dead.
That's a hell of a risk
[ARMIN] for one attack,
but it's our only chance.
[ARMIN] Seven people
have to slay seven Titans
[ARMIN] in one blow,
at the same time.
We're gonna need the best of
you. The seven soldiers most
physically gifted and adept
with their paring blades.
You'll be the difference
between life and death
for the rest of us.
I'm sorry. That's how it is.
Seems like a sound plan.
When you get
right down to it,
the risk is the
same for everyone.
Doesn't really matter who goes.
Look, I-- I'm willing
to be talked out of this.
One half-baked strategy can't
be our only option, right?
Hey, don't be so
hard on yourself.
C'mon, with what
we're looking at?
'Cause for our only option,
it's pretty well thought-out.
If we give it our all,
we might just pull this off!
It'll be fine. You just
have to be confident.
You're a better strategist than
you give yourself credit for.
[MIKASA] I'm serious.
That mind's saved Eren
and me more than once.
When did I ever
save you? That's not--
Alright, the lift's ready to go.
Guns are loaded to the stocks.
Let's go kill some Titans!
You didn't realize
it at the time.
We can talk about it later.
[CONNY] Okay. I'm gonna
ask the obvious question.
[CONNY] Can we do
this without ODM gear?
[REINER] No problem. These
guys are only four-meters tall.
[REINER] Their weak spots are
not too far above eye level.
[JEAN] He's right. Size won't be
an issue; the spot's still only
[JEAN] one meter high
and ten centimeters across.
[SASHA] Back 'o the head
to the nape o' the neck!
Worse comes to worst, you can
always just shove one of these
[REINER] up their ass.
That's the other weak spot.
Are you serious?
That's news to me!
Did I miss a day of
training or something?
[JEAN] Come on.
Knock it off, Reiner.
You want your final
words to be an ass joke?
[MARCO] Good.
We're still at seven.
Okay now, nice and easy.
[Titan footsteps]
Don't lose your cool!
Fire only when
they're all within range!
[MARCO] Steady.
[REINER] That's right;
wait for it.
[JEAN] Our lives
are riding on this.
[CONNY] Gotta make
this attack count.
[MARCO] Steady...
[Titan footsteps]
[Cadet terrified]
Almost...
Fire!
Got it!
How're you guys?
Uh-- I, uh--
I'm sorry. I didn't.
[CONNY] Oh crap.
[SASHA] I didn't mean
to sneak up on you.
Sasha and Conny missed!
Lead 'em the hell back!
[SASHA] I-- Oh, god.
I said I was sorry!
[SASHA] Mikasa!
You saved my life!
Are you okay?
Because of you I am!
Then get up.
I owe you one.
No worries.
[REINER] Wow.
By the skin of your teeth.
You're damn lucky you
didn't end up worse off.
[JEAN] They're all dead!
Start loading up supplies!
It worked!
[CADET 1] We're gonna
make it! We're gonna live!
[CADET 2] No more
of 'em coming in!
[CADET 1] Thank you,
crazy-berserker Titan!
I caved. In front
of the whole gang.
I'm never gonna be able
to face any of 'em again!
Damn it, feel sorry
for yourself later!
Focus on escape!
Listen, man. What you said
about me bein' a leader and all.
Don't talk to me like
that again, alright?
Promise me you're not going
to take this the wrong way.
But I don't think you're a good
leader 'cause you're strong.
I think you're a good leader
'cause you know
what it is to be weak.
[MARCO] You're one of us.
[MARCO] You're scared out of
your mind just like we all are.
[MARCO] It makes
you alert; sympathetic.
You made a damn
good call out there.
Got me runnin' for my life.
You're why I can say this.
[CADET] Ready,
people? Let's do this!
[shouting]
[ARMIN] Mikasa?
What're you doing?
We have to leave now!
Look. Down there.
[ARMIN] Cannibalism?
Can he not regenerate
like the others?
This may sound stupid, but I was
hoping he'd be the key for us.
That he'd help
mankind break the cycle.
Turn the tide just long enough
to give us a little ray of hope.
[REINER] She's right.
He's too valuable to just
let die. There's too much
we can learn from him.
I think it's perfectly clear
our priority should be to
ward the scavengers off him.
He's no good
to us picked apart.
[JEAN] Are you
out of your mind?
We've got a path out of this
nightmare and you wanna stay?
Think about it. Having an
Abnormal as an ally would be
an incredible advantage,
right? A cannon's got nothing
on a Titan who likes
to rip apart his own kind.
You-- Do you hear yourself?
He's not like a new friend!
[ARMIN] Oh, no.
It's the one that ate Thomas!
[roaring]
[growling]
Holy--
[roar]
[JEAN] What was
that you were saying?
[JEAN] 'Cause I think
it's a moot point now.
Alright, enough of this!
Let's leave while we can!
We're lucky the ugly
bastard didn't get bored.
We'd have been
next on the menu.
Look, a Titan's a Titan--
[gasp]
[ARMIN] Mikasa!
[heavy breathing]
[gasp]
[heart beats]
[Mikasa crying]
[ARMIN] It's him.
[ARMIN] But... his arm.
His leg. I don't understand.
I watched him get
eaten. I watched him die.
[ARMIN] I saw--
[Armin crying]
How is this possible?
Okay. So, uh...
[JEAN] Eren did all this?
[NARRATOR] The overwhelming
desire for revenge;
[NARRATOR] an emotion
powerful enough to alter
[NARRATOR] even
our physical bodies.
[NARRATOR] When
hate transforms you into
[NARRATOR] the very
thing you despise, however;
[NARRATOR] you might
just find the swords
[NARRATOR] of your
allies turned on you.