[NARRATOR] In the year 845,
two terrifying new breeds
[NARRATOR] of Titan appeared:
the Colossal and the Armored,
[NARRATOR] barreling
through the outer walls as if
[NARRATOR] wholesale
destruction was child's play.
[NARRATOR] In blood and
thunder, our way of life ended;
[NARRATOR] the Titans
fed their hunger
[NARRATOR] for human
flesh unchecked.
Stop it! No!
[NARRATOR] The territory
couched within the circle
[NARRATOR] of Wall
Maria was abandoned.
[NARRATOR] Twenty percent
of the human race perished.
[NARRATOR] As the
Titan onslaught advanced,
[NARRATOR] our only choice was
to withdraw behind Wall Rose.
[KEITH] Pick up the pace,
you lead-heeled laggards!
Your boots
water-logged, Arlelt?
[KEITH] Let's see some hustle!
Gear too heavy for
you, son? Hell, drop it!
[KEITH] Leave it in the mud!
The Titans'll have
easier work digesting you
without all the excess baggage.
Dammit.
[REINER] Seriously?
Here. Focus on staying upright.
We are being graded
on this, you know?
Thanks, but uh. Won't they
demerit you for helping?
Yeah, if they find out.
Just make the cut
and we're even, alright?
[KEITH] Reiner Braun.
[KEITH] The mind and
constitution of a grass-fed ox.
[KEITH] Respected
by his comrades.
I'm no one's burden,
you hear me?
[KEITH] Armin Arlelt.
[KEITH] Built like a daffodil,
but academically brilliant.
Annie Leonhart.
Gifted with a sword,
but does not exactly
play well with others.
Bertholdt Hoover.
Heaps of native talent,
but too mild-mannered.
Jean Kirschtein.
Head of the class on ODM;
also an insufferable smartass
with a hair-trigger temper.
Think those showoffs
can slice and dice?
Best hope you see
a Titan before I do!
Military Police.
Save a place for Jean!
Way to lead the charge!
You don't care if I
steal your thunder, right?
Yeah-ah! Woo hoo!
[KEITH] Sasha Braus.
Unusually fine instincts.
[KEITH] Rarely shares them
with her teammates.
[KEITH] Conny Springer.
Agile on the switchbacks.
[KEITH] Few sandwiches
shy of a picnic.
Get ready.
Damn it! Still not deep enough!
[KEITH] Mikasa Ackermann. Model
cadet. Excels in everything.
[KEITH] In fact,
it's no overstatement
[KEITH] to call
the girl a genius.
[KEITH] Eren Jaeger.
Lackluster in the classroom,
[KEITH] marginally
better in the field.
[KEITH] But. Driven
by a sense of purpose
[KEITH] that's
almost terrifying.
Ahhhhh!
Ah!
[EREN] Sorry, man. I've really
gotta learn to hold back.
Eh, it's alright. Let's
see how you do as the Rogue.
[REINER]
What're you waitin' on?
[EREN] This training
doesn't make sense.
We're not exactly picking fights
with someone our own size.
A guy'd have to be stupid
to use this. I mean, a knife?
[REINER] What if
there's not an option?
The fight doesn't give us a
say. If it wants to get ugly,
it gets ugly. It's our
job to be prepared.
[REINER] The enemy
comes in many forms.
[REINER] Artillery's not
always gonna be the answer.
Soldiers, the ones
worth their salt anyway,
are ready for anything.
Don't believe me? Look.
[EREN] Yeah? What about her?
Only thing she's ready for
is any chance to slack off.
You think so? Maybe somebody
ought to give her a talkin' to.
Give her a li'l hard-knocks
lesson in preparedness.
Commandant not
beaten you down enough?
Keep it up, you'll be as flat
as the dirt you're walking on.
I suggest you think back to why
you enlisted in the first place.
[EREN] Uh. What are you doing?
Whoa, she's pissed. Wow, I
thought she looked scary before.
You couldn't pay me
enough to be on her bad side.
Okay! Now, go get 'er!
Huh? What the hell? Wait.
Right. I hope you don't expect
me to hold back. Heads up!
Ugh. Son of a--!
That was a dirty move!
Are we done here?
Not just yet. You know the
drill: take up the dagger.
No, wait! This
isn't how-- Oh crap.
There.
So you ready to take me
on yourself yet or what?
Uh. Not exactly.
[EREN] Don't you dare.
She's got a lesson coming,
right? You go get her.
Yeah. A soldier can't really
afford to back down either.
Get ready, here I c--
[EREN] That's some
technique you've got.
[EREN] Who taught you
how to fight like that?
My father did.
[EREN] He, like,
pioneer it or--?
Does it really matter?
[ANNIE] It's pointless,
just like all this.
Wait, you mean the
training in general?
Hand-to-hand
combat doesn't really
count against our final grade.
[ANNIE] The smart
ones blow it off.
It's a crapshoot anyway.
Only the top ten cadets get to
serve in the Interior.
The rest of us? Forget it.
[ANNIE] Point is,
only the idiots like you
[ANNIE] take this part
of boot camp seriously.
[ANNIE] Idiots.
And whatever they are.
Oh-- Hello, sir.
First rule of this life, kid.
The better you are at
dropping the bad guys,
the more distance the
powers-that-be put between you.
That's what this whole
stupid farce is about.
Sure. Whatever you say!
Face it. You don't fight
the nature of things and win.
Look around you, Eren.
All the sons of bitches
really expect us to do is play
the game. Don't be a pawn.
[REINER] Yeah, well I still
stand by what I said earlier.
I've been so fixated on building
myself up, I couldn't see it.
She's absolutely right.
They're not honing
their skills to fight.
They're honing
their skill to run.
[ARMIN] I know, okay.
And look, I'm not
saying it's right,
it's just the way things are.
Before Wall Maria
was compromised,
ODM experts were rare.
[ARMIN] Only Scouts ever
risked proximity to the Titans,
[ARMIN] and their regiment
wasn't large to begin with.
[JEAN] That's how
you conserve fuel.
Let your momentum
do the work for you.
[DAZ] Still, that's
pretty advanced.
Duh. It's called
having a sixth sense
for the finer
points of your gear.
You gotta do the strut
if you wanna make the cut.
[JEAN] The MP only
recruit the best.
Ah. Man, that'd be amazing.
Workin' within a stone's throw
of the king. No
greater honor than that.
[JEAN] Shut up, Marco.
[JEAN] We're not children. You
can drop the misty-eyed B.S.
Honor doesn't have
any damn part of it.
You just want a nice,
cushy job in the Interior
playing glorified sentry.
That's not true!
That's not me at all!
[EREN] Listen to you guys.
Interior? Five years ago,
this was part of it.
You got a point to make,
friend? I'm right here.
Poor Jean. So
misguided. And besides,
I don't think your head'll
fit in the Interior anyway.
[snickering]
Very funny.
Seems a little backwards to me.
Fine-tuning your
Titan-killing skills so
the brass'll station you
somewhere you'll never see one.
You'd rather I was
good at gettin' killed?
Thank you, but I'll pass.
Better to play the system
than get gnawed on.
You son of bitch!
Bring it on,
you little bastard!
Eren, please stop it!
Gentlemen, please.
You think you can judge me?
Huh? You rip my
shirt, you're dead!
[JEAN] I don't give a damn about
your shirt! You piss me off!
[EREN] What? Are you crazy?
Oh, wait. I get it.
[EREN] He has something
to prove. Sounds familiar.
[EREN] Sorry to do this.
[EREN] It's only to end this
before things get out of hand.
Dammit! What the
hell was that move?
Little something I picked up
this afternoon while you were
busy with your
thumb up your ass.
You honestly believe
the Military Police
are your ticket
to the good life?
[EREN] You're not a
soldier. You're a joke.
Would someone care to explain
the little ruckus
I heard just now?
I do hope
everything's all right.
Sasha passed
some gas, Commandant.
Why am I not surprised?
For the love of god,
learn some self-control.
[NARRATOR] Of the
original recruits,
[NARRATOR] two-hundred and
eighteen cadets graduated.
[NARRATOR] Some with honors.
[COMMANDER] Do you have heart?
Sir!
[COMMANDER] As of this moment,
you have three options
[COMMANDER] open
to you. Choose wisely.
[COMMANDER]
The Garrison Regiment,
[COMMANDER] whose job
is to reinforce the Walls.
[COMMANDER] The Scout Regiment,
[COMMANDER] who rides
out into Titan country
[COMMANDER] to take
back what was once ours.
[COMMANDER] And the MP Regiment,
[COMMANDER] maintaining
law and order
[COMMANDER] under orders
from His Royal Majesty.
Those cadets eligible for
the MP have already been named.
The rest of you, take a look.
These are the top of your class.
[EREN] This is it.
We've made it.
[EREN] Our time is now.
Titans, be ready!
[cheering]
Alright! MP, here I come!
Three square meals
a day for life!
How in god's name did
I get ranked under Eren?
You're really gonna turn your
back on the MP for the Scouts?
Why in the world would you
do that? You're in the top ten.
The Scouts have
always been my goal.
I don't want the easy life. Not
with all the work I've put in.
[EREN] I trained
to fight Titans.
Are you insane?
How many people have died?
We're talkin' a fifth
of the population!
[THOMAS] If that doesn't
paint a picture for you,
[THOMAS] I don't know what will.
[THOMAS] This is our life
now. We can't beat them.
[EREN] Yeah? So what?
We buckle? Take
it all lying down?
[EREN] Things have changed.
Maybe not a helluva
lot, but enough.
They aren't the mystery
they were five years ago.
[EREN] There's still a long way
to go, but we've made progress.
[EREN] Every battle we
lost taught us a lesson,
[EREN] gave us
the tiniest inroad
[EREN] toward
something like hope.
[EREN] You tellin' me it's
better to cut our losses?
[EREN] Let all the death and
destruction be meaningless?
[EREN] Just to ball up and
accept it? Not on your life!
[EREN] Humanity's future
lies outside the walls,
and I'm gonna clear the way!
I'm gonna take
back what was ours!
I'll drive them out.
And as long as at least
one of us can say
that, we're not done.
[ARMIN] Eren, wait!
Yeah, good luck
out there, hotshot.
I'll root for you from
His Majesty's barracks.
[ARMIN] That was, uh, quite
a speech you gave us there.
Yeah. Most of it was yours.
All that stuff you used
to say back in the day.
Yeah, well I'm joining
the Scout Regiment, too!
Now you're just
being stupid. Come on!
You're not a fighter!
Your life is with books!
I'm through with letting
other people fight for me.
[MIKASA] Guess it's the
Scouts for me, too, then.
Oh, come on! You were
top of the class!
You'd be wasting your shot!
[MIKASA] Understand this,
Eren. Where you go, I go.
I made a promise to
your mom before she died.
I'm not letting you die.
I've got your back
whether you like it or not.
So just deal with it.
Yeah. Well, Mom's not here.
A lot of the people I used to
care about aren't here either.
♪
[COMMONER] Heads up!
[COMMONER] The main unit
of the Scout Regiment is back!
[COMMONER] That's right,
Commander Erwin!
[COMMONER] Did ya give those
ugly bastards a thrashing?
Look! It's Captain Levi!
[COMMONER] They say he's like
an entire brigade unto himself!
Spare me, please.
Feel how excited everybody is?
It's like the crowd just
has a different energy now.
Well, we are going on
five years without incident.
Seems like a good omen.
And you should check
out all the cannon upgrades.
The sight alone oughta
be enough to scare 'em off.
That's the truth.
You in denial 'cause you're
a couple? What's that about?
Whoa whoa whoa! This isn't
what it looks like! Okay?
Knock it off, man!
It's embarrassing!
[laughing]
Hey hey, lookie here!
Mr. Hannes!
Word on the street's they
let you graduate yesterday.
Either you've grown up
or standards have plummeted.
Oh yeah, like
you're one to talk!
The Corps of Engineers keep
their new chief in the drink?
Watch it.
I'm sorry if this is out of the
blue. But I want you to know
you're Mom's death
still haunts me.
Me too, but it
wasn't your fault.
We were shooting
in the dark then.
But nothing like
that's gonna happen again.
We know what we're
dealing with now.
Fired up and capable make
a good combination, kid.
Don't screw it up by dyin'.
What? The hell you mean
you're joining the Scouts?
What happened to the MP?
That was your whole thing!
Don't worry about it!
A guy's allowed to
change his mind, okay?
[MINA] I think your speech
yesterday lit a fire under him.
[CONNY] Ain't nobody
talkin' to you!
His temper tantrum
had nothing to do with it.
[THOMAS] Take it easy.
It's not like
you're the only one.
What? Are you serious?
[SASHA] Can you
guys keep a secret?
'Cause I totally
just helped myself
to the Officer's Pantry.
Sasha! They can throw your
butt in the clink for that!
Seriously, what
is wrong with you?
What isn't wrong with her?
It'll be fine.
I'm willing to share.
Oh, can you
imagine the sandwiches?
[CONNY] Put it back!
[MINA] Yeah! Do you have
any idea how rare meat's been
since the Titans
took Wall Maria?
[SASHA] Um, li'l bit. Yeah.
Just look at it
this way. Pretty soon,
[SASHA] we'll take back all
the room we need for livestock.
I would really
like a slice, please!
Hey if he gets one,
so do I! Just so you know.
Me, too! I'm in on it, too!
But.
[SAMUEL] Come on!
Don't just stand there.
If they see us slacking
off, we're in for it.
See you guys at lunchtime.
[EREN] Has it really
been five years?
[EREN] Look at us.
Ready to stand tall again.
We can do it.
Mankind didn't start this fight,
but we're gonna finish it!
It's hot!
[CONNY] Samuel!
[MINA] Sasha!
Try not to move! Understand?
That was too damn close.
[gasp]
Oh god, no. Not again!
[CONNY] They're gonna
get in. They're gonna get in.
[CONNY] They're gonna get in!
[EREN] No. This is over.
I'm gonna put a stop to this!
I will. This ends now.
[EREN] This is it,
people! Do or die!
Mounted Cannon Squad Four,
take out the Colossal Titan!
This is our chance!
Don't let it slip away!
You. It's been a while.
[NARRATOR] The jaws of Hell
reopen. Before you can even
[NARRATOR] catch your breath,
you're between its teeth.
[NARRATOR] Sometimes, saving
the people dearest to you
[NARRATOR] means making
the ultimate sacrifice.