-You're siblings?
-However, if I were truly
born her older brother,
then I would have
been much happier.
-What do you mean?
-Yuki is without a doubt
a pureblood daughter
of the Kuran family.
Even a pathetic vampire like you
should be able to sense that.
But then, you're also
something that hunts us.
What will you do?
[theme music]
-Why isn't big brother back yet?
-Don't worry.
He should be coming
home any minute now.
-Yuki, you really love
your brother, don't you?
-Yeah!
[door opening]
-Big brother's back!
Welcome home, Kaname!
-Good to be home, Yuki.
I went to see a rare rose
that blooms only once every 10
years.
But I couldn't bring
it back with me.
It withers as soon
as you pick it.
The next time it blooms, I'll
have it encased in resin.
-Was it really pretty, Kaname?
KANAME: How long does Yuki have
to stay here in this basement
room without any windows?
-Kaname--
-It seems nowadays
the Senate isn't
trying to control the
power of our blood.
They want to control our
very existence as well.
-Yuki's still young.
I don't want her to have
anything to do with them.
I know we're being selfish,
but we want to protect Yuki.
YUKI: I'm fine, I promise.
So you don't have to look
so scared, Kaname, OK?
-I will always be
with you, Yuki.
-I'm surprised you were
able to make it here
under the watch of the
Senate, big brother.
-I came to get your
daughter you've
been so carefully hiding.
-You bastard.
You're targeting my child again!
-It's all right.
I will stay with you.
-I can smell lots of blood.
-It really hurts me to
see you scared like this.
Maybe I have just been
reveling in these happy times
and avoiding it.
But I have made up my mind now.
I will create a
place for you where
you won't have to live
in fear ever again.
[door opening]
-Kaname, Yuki--
-Mother!
Mother, where's father?
-I see.
I'm so sorry.
I should have taken care
of things with Rido myself.
-Thank you.
Please keep taking
care of Yuki for us.
All right, Yuki.
Come with me.
-What about Kaname?
Kaname!
Kana-- Kaname!
-Yuki, I'm going to seal
all your vampire genes
and turn you into a human.
-Mother, Kaname
is-- mother, there's
something scary outside too.
-Listen to me very
closely, Yuki.
Once I use this spell, I'm
afraid I cannot be with you
anymore.
But I'm so happy I'm
able to do this for you.
I don't want you to hate me for
making this decision for you.
But--
-Mother?
-When you wake up, Yuki,
you won't remember anything.
-Yuki--
-That girl.
It can't be.
-That's enough.
Stop, or you'll kill her.
-You showing
compassion for a human?
So then, is that part
of Kaname's idealism?
-Yes, it is.
The smell of that blood.
-So she is finally awakened.
Kaname has restored that girl
to a vampire without pain.
But I have a feeling she
would have been happier
if she had instead drunk the
blood of Kuran as a human
and then gone insane
upon her awakening.
-So it turns out that Yuki
Cross is a pureblood vampire.
-She's your sister, then?
-Hanabusa, no daughters were
ever born to the Kuran family.
-Actually, Yuki is the true
daughter of Haruka and Juri.
And she is the child who
was born to become my wife.
But that depends on Yuki.
If she still wishes it so.
Why are you surprised?
It is not uncommon in a
pureblood lineage for siblings
to marry.
-No, it's not.
-So the source of this
threatening atmosphere
throughout the Academy
is coming from the person
who's after your sister.
-You're not going
to ask who it is?
-We don't obey you simply
because you're a pureblood.
We'll keep watch no
matter who the enemy is.
-I'm taking
advantage of you two.
RUKA (VOICEOVER): That
girl is Lord Kaname's--
KANAME (VOICEOVER):
Yuki is without a doubt
a pureblood daughter
of the Kuran family.
-Zero Kiryu, Ichiru's
twin brother.
-Yuki is a pureblood.
-Ichijo, you know the curse on
twins born to vampire hunters.
-I do know how the hunters
came into existence.
-Well, if those two
keep going at each other
like they have been, it may
not even matter in the end.
You look unhappy, Ichijo.
You don't want me to
sacrifice that girl in order
to resurrect myself?
Or perhaps it's because
you have betrayed Kaname.
Or is that look a
response to the fact
that I've taken
Senri's body hostage.
-Please, stop.
-(CHUCKLING) There's no reason
to keep hiding up there.
Just come on down, Rima.
-So just who are you?
I won't stand by and let
you get away with it.
-My body is burning up.
My throat is parched-- so dry.
-Yuki.
You don't have to hold back.
-Kaname-- Kaname, I--
-It's all right.
I know what you want to do.
-I want--
-Yuki, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I've brought you
back into this hateful smell
of blood.
-I only want--
-Yes, deeply.
Yuki.
Don't cry.
Perhaps I honestly did
yearn for this day to come.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): This man's
blood is permeating my body.
I can't tell where
our boundaries are.
What is that?
A fragment of memories.
-You see it?
-Yes.
It was a frightening creature.
But I'm-- but I'm not
a human either, am I?
I remember now, that night.
Mother sacrificed her life and
then cast a spell to seal me.
Father said he'd protect
me from the bad people,
and then he left.
They were both strong people.
But now they're gone.
But why?
Why'd they do it?
What exactly were they
trying to protect me from?
-Relax, Yuki.
Calm down.
-I did that?
-Yuki, don't deny
your existence.
And most of all, don't ever
question their love for you.
For 10 years I've
watched over you
in place of those two, the Yuki
who'd forgotten everything.
-Kaname-- Kaname, I'm afraid
that something is wrong with
me.
-Why is that?
-Because this whole time I've
been in love with my brother.
-What's wrong with that?
-Yes, but I've been living
as a human for so long now.
-And so what?
It doesn't change the fact
that you're still my fiance.
-You and I, we're going to
be like our father and mother
when we grow up.
-Do you really mean it, Kaname?
YUKI: Father and mother
were siblings as well.
But Kaname, you realize
that's something only--
-Something only beasts would do?
Exactly.
We're not human, Yuki.
Or will you leave
me alone again?
-Alone-- that smell, what is it?
Blood?
But whose?
-Yuki, yes.
Enjoy the smell of blood.
And by doing so,
you will eventually
come to understand where
it is you truly belong.
Stay here, Yuki.
I'll be back soon.
-Whose?
I sense something unpleasant
and the smell of blood.
It's not Zero.
-Rima!
-Whoever you are, I won't
let you get away with this.
[chuckling]
-Injuring a model's
face is pretty low.
-I'm relieved.
It wasn't Zero's blood.
But I no longer have any
right to worry about him.
-At times like this,
I'm glad I'm a vampire.
I heal quickly.
-Rima, please be careful.
-Takumo, what are you--
-Please stop.
You shouldn't be
using Senri for this.
You've already made your point.
-In time, I will destroy
anyone who defies the Senate.
Exactly as Ichijo
wishes me to do.
-Lord Rido--
-So annoying.
Just because you're
in Senri's body
doesn't mean you can
act superior, OK?
Whoever you are,
I'll drive you out.
Now get ready.
-Hmph.
You won't find that easy to do.
-Rima!
-I missed.
Don't interfere, Ichijo.
-Lord Rido!
-Senri-- idiot.
Letting someone
take over your body.
What are you doing?
You really need to love
yourself more, Senri.
-Do not defy me, Senri.
-Just a little longer.
Come on, hurry, Yuki Cross.
-I am a pureblood vampire.
FEMALE SPEAKER
(VOICEOVER): Yes, you
are the very thing
that Zero despises.
You're a monster.
-It's over.
I can't be near him anymore.
I've been deceiving
Zero this whole time.
And on top of that, I
let him drink my blood
while telling myself
that I was saving him.
What was I thinking?
FEMALE SPEAKER (VOICEOVER):
Such a hypocrite.
-And still-- I can't help it.
I still want to see Zero.
FEMALE SPEAKER
(VOICEOVER): And then what?
-I need to talk to him.
FEMALE SPEAKER (VOICEOVER):
What could you possibly
say to him now?
-I want to see Zero.
-Hey, Hanabusa.
She seems to be escaping.
-Hold on, Yuki Cross.
I mean, Lady Yuki Kuran.
Lord Kaname has given us orders
to stay here and protect you
no matter what happens.
-Please step aside now,
Hanabusa, Akatsuki.
-We can't do that.
-Please just go back
to your room, Yuki--
-Out of my way.
You two--
-Huh?
-If you want to avoid being
reprimanded by Kaname,
then I suggest you
come along with me.
-Seiren, dawn is coming.
Gather those who can
move during the day
and have them
guard the Sun dorm.
And don't let the day
class students outside.
-Understood, my lord.
I'll take care of it.
-Lord Kaname.
-Ruka.
-By the smell of blood in
the air and by her presence,
I know what has happened.
-So if you understand
what has happened,
then why do you
look so apologetic?
-I have behaved
like a fool who was
incapable of dealing with the
burden of her own emotions
until now, when the truth
was thrust before me.
I will go to the Sun
dormitory and be useful.
-And Ruka, I am sorry.
-No, I was merely
dancing by myself.
Please don't
apologize, Lord Kaname.
-All right.
Instead, Ruka, I
will say this to you.
I'll say something very cruel.
I trust you fully, Ruka.
-Thank you for saying that.
-Akatsuki, I'm glad you're here.
Dawn is going to break soon,
but you should both continue
to guard the Sun dormitory
for the time being.
Day classes are canceled.
Make sure you don't
let anyone outside.
-Hey, Ruka, are you all right?
-I want to be able
to show him that I
am a cool, dependable woman.
Besides, from now
on, I'm not the one
who will suffer the most.
-The time has come, if I
still have the strength.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): I made
up my mind to come here.
But--
-It sounds as if
you're desperately
saying that you
really do need me.
[theme music]