ZERO (VOICEOVER): If at any
time I lose the human part of me
and go out of control, use this.
-Zero.
[theme music]
--[laughing] Fighting amongst
themselves for control
and power.
That is the true
nature of vampires.
ZERO (VOICEOVER): But as long as
Rido exists, he will not stop.
He will keep coming
to devour her.
You want to pretend like
you haven't noticed,
what you have so willingly
taken inside yourself,
has begun to pulsate.
-Ichiru.
-The time has come, Zero.
-Rima.
I heard you.
When you called out to me
back there, I heard it.
-Idiot, letting someone
take over your body.
What are you doing?
You really need to
love yourself, Senri.
-Thank you, Rima.
-You're such a pain in the neck.
Perfect.
I've got a bad feeling.
-Something strange has
entered the Academy.
-Is the man who possessed
your body behind it?
-Probably.
-Where's Takuma?
-He has gone to do
what has to be done?
-Ruka, are you all right?
-Yes.
-Ah!
-I only get attacked by men,
that's not nearly as much fun.
-Hanabusa.
-I believe your job is
to protect Princess Yuki.
-Uh, yeah, she seems
to have disappeared.
-How did you let that happen?
You realize that she's
the one they're after?
-The dorm president is going
to kill you for sure this time.
-Listen, don't worry.
It's all gonna work out.
-And just what
makes you so sure?
-Because the enemy
is a pureblood.
If he's really serious, he
won't just keep attacking us.
What I'm trying to say is he's
either totally underestimated
our strength, or--
-You think that he's got
something bigger in store.
-Today, we're celebrating
my resurrection.
Ensure yourselves.
Don't hold anything back.
-I don't believe it.
The crowd keeps coming.
That aura.
It's him.
-What's going on?
-Why can't we go--
-Silence!
No on is leaving this hall until
the headmaster says we can.
I am just as in the
dark on this as you are.
-May I help you,
Association President?
-That's a very dangerous
weapon you have there.
I believe you once vowed never
to carry that thing again.
-I'll do whatever is necessary
to protect my students.
-All I want is for you to
hand Zero Kiryu over to us.
-Sorry, I won't do that.
-I see.
Fine then.
That was very foolish.
You just wasted
your last chance.
Now, say hello to hell.
-Sorry, but I'll
decide my own fate.
-We come together, and
then we take what we want.
That is what vampires do.
So many are coming,
all to congratulate me.
Those people and
those people too.
Won't you be coming as well?
I so want to be entertained
by you, Zero and Ichiru Kiryu.
-The time has come.
You must play the part
you are meant to play.
This is why I let you live.
It's all been for Yuki.
-Ichiru, you're not--
-Zero.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): I know
the smell of this blood.
That's Zero.
-You're becoming a problem.
I'm guessing you want to
go and see Zero, correct?
-Kaname, I just--
-Zero is in the process
of resurrecting himself.
I did it to protect you, Yuki.
-What are you talking about?
Rido Kuran.
-In order to protect
you from that man,
I'm afraid that I
had to use Zero.
There's more.
I also killed Shizuka Hio.
Please, forgive me, Yuki.
In trying to protect you, all
I've done is hurt you the most.
Sorry.
-Why were we born
as separate beings?
I wanted to be born
as one with you, Zero.
If I knew I'd be born
incomplete like this.
I just-- I'm sorry.
-Ow, you made me hit my head.
-I'm sorry, Ichiru.
I'm so sorry.
-It was only a little bump.
There's no need to
apologize, Zero.
It isn't that bad.
ICHIRU (VOICEOVER): I
know, yet I say this to him
because I know how
Zero will react.
I felt I could be Zero's
other half only in moments
when I hurt him.
You already realize it, Zero.
ZERO (VOICEOVER): I don't
know what to do, Ichiru.
Even if I understand
how Ichiru feels,
I don't know what
I can do for him.
Or what I should do for him.
Ichiru has been
sickly since birth,
and it's probably-- I stole
something from my other half
while we were in
our mother's womb.
I stole it and made it mine.
-Zero?
Hey, what are you
thinking about?
Shall I guess what it is?
You get too worked up.
You're never going to become
a cool strong hunter acting
like this.
Zero, there are things
we can't tell each other
because you and I are so close.
-That's why, little by little,
little by little, the wheel
starts to turn.
-Ichiru, you haven't
taken your medicine yet.
It's all right.
For some reason, I seem
to feel much better
when you're with me, Zero.
-I made up my mind to do
whatever Ichiru wanted.
-I'm home.
Sorry for being late.
Sleep well, Ichiru.
Sleep well, Zero.
ZERO (VOICEOVER):
Stop it, Mother.
The love that mother gives
us equally belongs to Ichiru.
Let Ichiru have her love,
because I stole his ability
to become a hunter.
And I--
-Zero, don't let
your mind wander.
Look at me.
You've meekly allowed
yourself to be imprisoned.
You were always
demeaning yourself
back when we were kids.
Is this how you
atone for your sins?
You couldn't
possibly have thought
your acts were of
comfort to me, could you?
The only thing your
actions have done
is force me to realize that
you would have been free
if I had never existed at all.
However, this is no consolation
for having Shizuka taken away
from me.
-Don't worry.
My naive pursuit of
atonement is long gone now.
I let it go when I saw
you smiling that night.
How could you smile at the
murder of mother and father?
-So then, are you about
to lose control now?
Just so you know, I didn't
wish for them to die.
Our parents were
the ones who hunted
and killed Shizuka's lover.
Her lover also happened
to be a former human.
He had yet to fall to a
level E, but still his name
was on the hunters'
execution list.
Our parents were not at fault.
They were just following
orders, but when Shizuka told me
what happened, I was disgusted.
On the day they executed
Shizuka's lover,
they held us with the same
arms they killed with.
ICHIRU'S FATHER: We have to
report it to the Society,
that Ichiru is unfit to
become a vampire hunter.
ICHIRU'S MOTHER: You're right.
Ultimately, Ichiru won't
be able to stay with Zero.
-And I found it painful that
they looked at me from time
to time with the eyes of the
Association's watch dogs.
-Ichiru, one last question.
Why are you hurt so badly?
-All I wanted was to
fulfill Shizuka's wish.
He was my only target.
The one who imprisoned
Shizuka and interfered
with the execution
list, Rido Kuran.
-Shall I ask you just
why you're doing this?
-I'm here to
retaliate for Shizuka,
whose life was ruined
because of you.
I wanted to deliver
the final blow.
That's why I've been here this
whole time eagerly awaiting
your resurrection.
-Flee.
I have no use for the weak.
-Even though I did all I
could, I knew that in the end
I couldn't do much.
I'm so useless.
Was there anything else
that I wanted to say?
-Ichiru.
-I-- I feel so sick.
This place reeks of our blood.
It must be tempting
for you, Zero.
I'm surprised you're still sane.
You've become a different being
now, but for whatever reason,
I still feel
comfortable next to you.
It's proof-- proof that
we were once one embryo.
Zero, I want you to devour
what remains of my life.
-What are you saying?
-You already know.
If you devour me, you
can regain the powers
you were meant to have at birth.
Then you'll be able
to control yourself.
You can control those urges.
-I won't.
I can't do something like that.
-Yes, you will.
it was meant to be.
Why do you think I shot
you with a bloody rose?
You have to, Zero.
-I won't do it.
Please, don't die.
I don't want to
lose anybody else.
-Hearing that,
makes me so happy.
I thought I was
already dead to you.
-Maria wanted to
see you, as well.
-She did, huh?
-Father and mother, they
watched over you too,
and they did love you.
I promise.
-I know, Zero.
You don't have to
forgive Shizuka,
but don't hold a
grudge against her.
Shizuka, she truly cherished me.
I know she did.
That's why I don't regret
what's happened to me.
And soon--
-Ichiru.
I can't do this.
It's wrong.
-Is it really?
If that's what you truly
believe, then live.
Live, Zero, and
do what I cannot.
Live, Zero, do it for me!
-If I gave the rest of my life
so that Yuki could have hers,
I'd have no regrets.
-Soon I will become
one with Zero again.
-Ahhh!
-What's wrong, Zero?
I Come on out.
I want to play.
If you don't hurry
that Kuran princess--
-I can't do this.
This is wrong.
-If that's what you
truly believe, then live.
Live Zero.
-The time has come.
I must go and do what I must do.
And you, Yuki, must
do what you must do.
-Lord Kaname.
-Believe what you
will, your turn
will come next, Zero Kiryu.
[theme music]