[music playing]
[knock]
CROSS: Come in.
Sorry for having
you stop by so late,
but this person
here is nocturnal.
-I guess we should
introduce ourselves,
shouldn't we, Ichiru Kiryu?
-So tell me, what does the
president of the Moon Dormitory
want with me?
Is it your intention to make me
yet another pawn in your game?
-Well, actually, you already
are a piece on the chess board.
So who's your target?
-Even if I told you, you
couldn't do anything about it.
If you find me offensive, then
go ahead and get rid of me
quickly.
[door slams]
[music - on/off, "rinne rondo"]
-It takes a certain
amount of courage
to invite a child in
who might cause trouble.
-What is it?
Are you beginning to
regret admitting him here?
-No, it's just--
-The whole purpose
of this school
is to allow the
pursuit of pacifism.
I have no intention of
destroying your ideals.
CROSS: I trust you.
I just need to do
everything in my power
so that I can make
her wishes come true.
I made a promise to you when
we established the Night Class.
You have the power to
make all decisions related
to vampires, Kaname.
But concerning Yuki, I
was surprised to hear
your intentions toward her.
I mean, your lover?
Kaname.
(GRUFFLY) If you hurt Yuki,
I will never forgive you.
Kaname?
You seem unhappy
about something.
-Not at all.
As a matter of fact,
I'm quite happy.
Finally.
KANAME (VOICEOVER): Be my lover.
BOY (VOICEOVER): They
say when we grow up,
we'll be like Mother and Father.
SHADOWY FIGURE (VOICEOVER):
You will be mine.
[gasp]
[screams]
-Yuki!
-My-- my head hurts.
-Yuki.
Are you really all right?
You hardly ate
anything for breakfast.
-Yeah.
-You know, if you
don't feel well,
then you should get some rest.
-I'll be all right.
I have a lot of my mind
now, that-- that's all.
I started thinking about it,
and I guess I got really tense.
-What's going on?
What's making you so tense?
-Mm.
Zero.
Good morning.
-Oh, hey.
-Good morning.
-Morning.
-Hey, what's going on
between the two of you?
-Nothing.
-All right, let's go, Yuki.
-Mm.
-Uh?
-We're following the
orders of President Kuran.
We shall stay by your side--
-No way.
-This isn't fair.
-And watch over you.
[whispers all around]
-Lady Yuki.
-Huh?
What's this about?
-Did you see something to
make them bully you, Yuki?
-Uh--
ZERO: Let's go.
-Oh, they're all following me.
-Maybe it's their
way of bullying you.
-What is this?
What's going on?
-It's that
disciplinary committee.
-Not fair.
-It's always only Yuki.
-Mm!
(SHOUTING) Listen, I'm sorry!
I don't know what
Kaname told you,
but please try to
be considerate!
This isn't the time
or place for this!
-Shut up, Yuki Cross.
-It's Lady.
-For whatever reason, our
Lord Pureblood, Lord Kaname,
has deemed you special.
-Uh?
HANABUSA: So we must treat
you in the proper manner.
You're just a human girl.
You wouldn't understand.
See this, involves our
pride as Aristocrats.
TEACHER: All right, everybody,
please solve this problem.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): I wonder
why Kaname is doing this.
KANAME (VOICEOVER): Be my lover.
-His lover?
Kaname's lover?
SHADOWY FIGURE (VOICEOVER):
You will be mine!
[gasp]
[thud]
-Yuki!
TEACHER: What's wrong, Yuki?
-Are you all right?
-I'm fine.
I just haven't been able
to get enough sleep lately.
I've had too much on my mind.
I'm so sorry.
It seems that I always make
you worry about me somehow.
-This isn't about me.
-Yeah, but--
ZERO: This is what it
means to be with him.
Just bear with it.
You made up your mind
to face him for real.
You can't back down.
All right, then.
[door closes]
[footsteps approaching]
VO: That's Zero's--
wasn't he with the Senate?
-Hold on.
There's a girl
recovering in there.
-Are you saying
I need permission
to enter the infirmary?
I just need some medicine.
[slams door]
[footsteps approach]
[tiny bell rings]
WOMAN (VOICEOVER): I won't
turn you into a vampire.
[gasp]
-Even I-- someone like me--
has a person that I don't
want to see turned
into a vampire.
[door bursts open]
HANABUSA: What are you doing?
-Mm.
Zero?
[tiny bell rings]
-I will take whatever it
is you have in your hand.
-Ichiru?
Uh, why are you--
-You are so coddled.
You have no idea
what's going on.
I will make sure to report
this to Lord Kaname.
-Do as you wish.
-Huh?
-Hmph.
-So Ichiru Kiryu
had this on him?
-Yes.
-You did well to stop him.
-I'm honored to
be of assistance.
Um, whose blood is that?
Forgive me.
It's really none of my business.
-No, no, it's fine.
Just don't mention
this to anyone.
In regards to Ichiru, I have
no intention of punishing him.
He has his own role
to play in this.
-Yes, but what if he tries
to do something to Yuki--
I mean Lady Yuki?
-That's why I have asked
you to guard her well.
-If that is what
Lord Kaname wishes.
And--
[knock]
HANABUSA (VOICEOVER):
About Ruka--
KANAME (VOICEOVER): I see.
She still hasn't left her room?
HANABUSA (VOICEOVER): Yes.
She hasn't left
since-- since she
heard that Lady
Yuki is your lover.
-Don't worry about it.
Just let her be alone
for now, all right?
-Very well.
-Hanabusa.
-Uh?
-Regarding Yuki, I
really am grateful.
-Uh-- any time.
-I won't let you use
this wretched blood
to fulfill your
wicked ambitions.
[poof]
[bell ringing]
CROSS: I wanted to talk to you.
-So have you decided
on a punishment for me?
CROSS: Punishment?
-That's not what this is about?
Then what is it?
-There's something
I need to tell you.
Ichiru, please come
to dinner tonight.
Zero and Yuki will
both be there as well.
I know a lot has happened, but
that doesn't change the fact
that you and Zero
are still twins.
Listen, I think if
both of you tried,
you two could have a
different relationship.
[tiny bell rings]
-But that choice is yours.
[slams door]
[sigh]
HANABUSA: Lord Kaname doesn't
intend to punish you this time.
But you should remember this.
I won't let you lay a
hand on Yuki Cross again.
-Fine with me.
-Uh?
[knock]
ZERO: Yuki, can I come in?
-Y-yeah.
-Classes are over now.
Do you think you
can eat something?
-Presidential Kuran
has asked for you.
Come with me.
-Huh?
-Zero, you too.
[whispers all around]
HANABUSA: So, Yuki, you've
lost your memories of the past,
have you?
-Yes, that's right.
I have.
Why do you ask?
-I took it upon myself
to look into the matter.
-Huh?
Aido, you really
looked into my past?
I didn't ask you to do that!
That was awfully--
-You're so wrong!
I wouldn't look into your
past if someone begged me to.
What I was talking about
is Lord Kaname's past.
-Uh?
-I assume you know by now that
Lord Kaname's parents have
since passed away, so I
did some investigating
surrounding their deaths.
I looked and when I
reached any sort of clue,
it'd been deleted or burned.
It was a deliberate
cover-up, just
like what happened
with your memories.
And now Lord Kaname has
taken it upon himself
to treat a human girl
like you as his lover.
Do you know why?
Because your new status
means the rest of us
are now forced to protect you.
It would seem to me
that Lord Kaname knows
that something is
going to happen to you.
I'm going to take my leave now.
I don't want to hear that
either of you were rude to him.
-Yuki.
Finally, we have time together.
Come here.
There's nothing to
hold us back now.
Come.
-Kaname.
No.
-Why are you
standing so far away?
I guess you still don't
understand, do you?
-You know, you
really didn't have
to come outside during the day.
-I'm quite all right.
-I mustn't be swept away.
-Ah, I see.
You're taking things
too seriously.
-Uh?
-Don't worry, Yuki.
I won't ask for too
many things at once.
-Now look here!
Kaname, I don't--
-What is it?
You don't like the
snacks that I brought?
-You promised me.
You said that you would
tell me about my past.
-This isn't the best time.
You look so scary right now
that I don't want to tell you.
-I knew you were going to do
this, dodge the subject again.
Listen, if you won't
tell me, well, then I'm
just going to make
up my own story.
[excited whispers]
-Seems you have
nothing to do, Zero.
Please shoo away the
Day Class students
before they raise a fuss.
[girls scream]
-Thank you, Zero.
That's much better.
-Uh-- uh?
-I hear that you weren't
feeling very well today, Yuki.
Are you all right?
-Uh, yeah, I am.
I'm fine.
I just-- I have a
lot of my mind lately
and I haven't been sleeping.
-Was it me you were
thinking about?
I hope that you were.
It'll make me very happy to
know I was on your mind, Yuki.
I've decided I'm going to give
the Night Class a few days off.
-Huh?
-That'll give you
a small reprieve
from the night patrols.
Try to get some rest.
-You can't just stop--
KANAME: If I don't,
I'm afraid I'll
lose sleep worrying about you.
HANABUSA (VOICEOVER):
It seems to me
that Lord Kaname knows something
is going to happen to you.
CROSS (VOICEOVER): I
think if both of you
tried, you two could have
a different relationship.
-Well, hello, Ichiru.
How are you doing today?
Look, I've just picked some
vegetables from the garden.
They're really fresh.
Come on, let's go inside.
KANAME: I've waited
a long time for this.
I'm glad this day has come.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): It's
like somehow, we're
playing the part of
the happy couple.
-The sun is setting now.
I hate the thought
of saying goodbye,
but I do need to
send you on your way.
After all, you really do
need to get some rest.
YUKI (VOICEOVER):
It's like he's trying
to enjoy every minute until
the final curtain falls.
Why am I feeling this way?
I've wanted nothing more
than for him to look at me.
Deep down, I have
always loved him.
But--
KANAME: What's wrong?
-I don't know why
you're doing this.
I don't know why you insist
on behaving this way.
I don't get it.
-I wish you would understand.
CROSS: All right now.
Can you mix this for me?
And be careful.
Don't burn the sauce.
[sigh] Zero eats
anything I cook for him,
and yet I still don't know
what his favorite meal is.
Do you know, Ichiru?
YOUNG ICHIRU (VOICEOVER):
Here have it.
You really like it, right?
YOUNG ZERO (VOICEOVER): But
you like it too, Ichiru.
I want you to have it.
I'm saying thank you because
you're always so nice to me.
-Don't worry if you don't know.
It's all right.
-It's vegetable soup.
-Ah?
Oh, right!
I almost forgot about the soup!
Maybe I'll make
vegetable soup tonight.
Let's see, what
kind of vegetables?
Hm.
I know, tomatoes!
Tomato soup is always
good, don't you think?
ZERO: Are you all right?
-Hm?
Yes, although I still feel like
he avoided the subject again.
Sorry that you had to
come along as well.
ZERO: It's OK.
Just remember what
I told you before.
I will never let you
become a vampire.
Never.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): Do you think
my heart will grow stronger
if I become a vampire?
ZERO (VOICEOVER): I will
never let that happen to you.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): Zero's trying
to keep that menacing look
of his under control,
but it stabs me all over.
It hurts.
I can't let Zero suffer
like this anymore.
-Come on in!
We have a very special
menu for you tonight.
-Ichiru?
CROSS: I invited him.
-Come on, Zero,
what's the matter?
I mean, you two
are twins, right?
Wow, you two are identical.
It's amazing how similar
the both of you are!
When I woke up in the
infirmary earlier,
I was still a bit fuzzy and
I mistook Ichiru for Zero.
[gasp]
-Why were you there?
What were you planning
to do to Yuki?
-It's all right, Zero.
Nothing happened.
-Ta-dah!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
ICHIRU: I'm leaving.
-But dinner is finally--
-(QUIETLY) It's useless.
It's too late to choose
a different path now.
-Huh?
You-- what?
But what about the
special menu that I made?
-There's nothing to worry about.
We'll eat it.
I promise.
Won't we, Zero?
We'll eat it before
it gets too cold.
[gasp]
-Is there something wrong?
-Nothing.
-Sorry.
-It's fine.
-It's because of what I said
tonight that made Ichiru leave,
wasn't it?
-No, it wasn't your fault.
-Yeah, but it isn't
only about that.
Listen, you and Ichiru
too, both of you
have had some really bad
experiences in your life.
I mean, horrible.
So the last thing I want
is for the two of you
to keep hurting each other.
The headmaster said
the same thing.
[gasp]
-Are you all right?
Is your head hurting again?
-No.
No, it's nothing.
I'm totally fine, honest.
Don't worry about me.
-Forget about my problems.
Just get some rest.
[tiny bell rings distantly]
-I'm sorry.
Good night.
ICHIRU: Hey, Zero, don't
fall in love with that girl.
It appears your taste in women's
gotten a whole lot worse.
-Why don't you tell me what
your real motives are here?
-I don't owe you an explanation.
TAKUMA: We'll be
arriving soon, Senri.
-Hm.
I wonder what the
false heir will do now
that the true head of the
family is finally back.
[whimpering in sleep]
-[sigh] I'm so tired.
They made me do weird work.
[door opens]
Senri?
Where have you been?
[gasp]
Who are you?
[MUSIC - KANON WAKESHIMA, "SUNA
NO OSHIRO"]
[music playing]