YUKI (VOICEOVER): The first
time I looked at sunlight
with my vampire eyes.
-I can't believe
it's morning already.
Let's get back before
Lord Kaname returns.
-All right.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): It
wasn't gentle anymore.
I thought I smelled
Kaname's blood.
-You'll be sensitive
to many new things now,
but Lord Kaname will be
worried if you aren't there.
-But I-- I sense a
horrible presence.
It seems like others
are stirring too,
as if by command
of that presence.
-My master--
[gasp]
-This Academy is no longer the
safe haven I had hoped for.
Let the students know.
They must go home.
[theme music]
-You all to return home
until further notice
from the headmaster.
Once you're packed, please
proceed to building 12
and follow Mr.
Yagari's instructions.
And just where are you going?
-To get Mister Bear.
-And what is that?
-He's my teddy bear?
-That's what you want?
You will leave that behind.
OK, fine.
You can get it.
But make it snappy!
-Sayori, what are you doing?
The class rep says we
have to leave here now.
-Yes, but--
-Come on, let's go.
-I wanted to take our time
and gradually show the world
that at this Academy, there
are vampires with whom
we can co-exist.
-It's too bad that dream
never became true for you.
-No, I won't give
up on that dream.
Not yet.
-I'm taking Senri.
He doesn't need him anymore.
-Do as you wish.
[door closing]
-Shizuka, it's all most time.
Just a little longer.
-Come on, this way.
And be quick!
-I didn't know there
was a hallway here.
-It's an emergency exit.
-Hey Shindo, have you
seen Yuki anywhere?
-Huh?
I figured you knew
where she was, Sayori.
SAYORI (VOICEOVER):
I know there's
something you can't tell me.
I understand you're
keeping it a secret
because you don't
want to make me worry,
but it feels like you
don't trust me, Yuki.
-Hey, I know I said to hurry,
but come on, wear your shoes.
YUKI (VOICEOVER):
This ominous feeling
I have, I've felt it before.
-Is it all right now to
let the students outside?
-Kaname's orders were clear.
We are to make sure the
day class students stay out
of harm's way.
-That's if we can even
get them out of here.
-What's that?
-Is that an elevator?
-If everyone's here, let's go.
-Wait!
Wait, wait, wait!
There's more.
We're missing some
female students!
It's all my fault.
I told them repeatedly to hurry.
-Why didn't they
get here in time?
-Gather all the students
in the auditorium.
I'll handle the rest.
-Got it.
Change of plans.
Proceed to the
auditorium immediately.
-Hurry up, people!
KAIEN (VOICEOVER):
Forgive me, Juri.
In order to fulfill
your wish, I'm
afraid that I must now
break my promise to you.
-Say, maybe this
wasn't a good idea.
But who knows when we'll see
the night class students next?
I'm already going
through withdrawals.
-Good morning, ladies.
-Huh?
-Young girls are so full of
energy, even in the morning.
I used to be that way too.
My, my-- you will be
gifts for my master.
[screaming]
You bastard.
Akatsuki, why are you
going so easy on her?
These vampires
are former humans.
So then, I wonder whose
servants they are.
We will not stand
by and allow enemies
into Lord Kaname's territory.
[grunting]
[screaming]
-Kaien Cross.
-He's a legend among
vampire hunters--
the strongest in history.
-Thank you for
protecting the students.
-Of course.
-I'm sure the real attack
will come after sundown.
We can't led our guard down.
KAIEN (VOICEOVER):
Fighting vampires
with vampires-- I can't
believe the irony.
AIDO: Hey, what are you doing?
-I feel it.
Something's about to happen,
and I have to stop it.
-Look, you-- if you
get hurt, Lord Kaname
will hold me responsible.
-I may have become a vampire,
but I'm still a guardian.
-Yes, but-- huh?
[screaming]
-Well, hello there, miss.
We haven't seen our master
in a very long time,
and we so desperately
want to bring him a gift.
-Who are--
-That's not important, K?
-Yuri!
Yuri, are you all right?
-Yuki, what have you be--
-Stand back.
-She's the pureblood princess.
-So this is his princess.
-Anyone who tries to hurt
Yuri must first answer to me.
Why did--
-For our master!
-You're no match for me.
-Yuki, what is going on?
-I'm sorry, Yuri.
The man who just turned to
dust, I'm the same being.
I didn't mean to scare you.
I'm sorry.
-(SOBBING) No.
Don't apologize and
give me that sad face.
I'll feel even
lonelier if you do.
I've been waiting for
you to come back safely.
I would have been
more scared if I
didn't know why my best
friend never returned.
-Yuri.
KANAME: Yuki.
-Kaname.
-Yuki, what are
you doing out here?
-Something is about to happen
at the Academy, isn't it?
That's why I--
-You mustn't be so careless.
Your condition is
still unstable.
Take Yuki to a quiet
place so she can rest.
-Yes.
-Kaname, listen to me.
There are people here that
I want to protect as well.
-But you can't even
handle Artemis.
-All right, let's
get going, Yuki.
-Yuki.
No matter what, we will
always be best friends.
-Oh, Yuri.
-Yes.
-That was impressive.
What's with the long face?
You made Zero hunt
vampires under the guise
that you were protecting him.
But now that you're
back hunting yourself,
you suddenly have a problem
with the morality of it?
You, the legendary hunter?
-That may sound like
a good title to you,
but I wanted no part
of being a legend.
I feel that if I
condone vampire hunting,
I'll be rejecting
Yuki and Zero, as well
as all the night class students.
I've killed far
too many vampires
to say that I understand them.
However, at least I haven't
lost sight of my duty.
I'm going to see the
Hunter Society's president,
and I intend to
put an end to this.
-But you have lost sight.
I believe you have work
to do here, headmaster.
I'm tired of babysitting kids.
It's not my scene.
I am still a vampire hunter.
Now, let me show
you what I can do.
Besides, that tough talk
doesn't suit you, old man.
-Yagari, smoking on school
grounds is strictly prohibited.
-First, I thought you were
early risers for vampires.
Now I see you're human guests.
-You've been ignoring
the association.
The president is not
happy about that.
Just hand over Zero Kiryu,
and we'll all go away.
-I won't do it.
[gasp]
-We're not going
back to headquarters
without him, Yagari.
-Well, if that's
what you really want,
then you'll have
to come through me.
Not bad.
The sword's a good choice.
It works on humans
as well as vampires.
-That's enough.
Even if we all take
you on at once,
we won't be able to defeat you.
Yagari, why are you defying
the president's orders?
-Just because the
president gave the order
doesn't make it right.
Tell the president that if he
has a problem, he can come here
and discuss it personally.
ZERO (VOICEOVER):
Something is happening.
And whatever it is, it's
making the cursed blood
within my body begin to boil.
-Zero--
-Just go away.
-Zero!
-Go away!
ZERO (VOICEOVER): I want you
to be the one to kill me.
I didn't know anything.
-I'm really glad
nothing happened to you.
ZERO (VOICEOVER): I tried
to protect her, but--
-How could I ever hate you?
ZERO (VOICEOVER): --the only
thing I feel right now is hate.
-I think I was able to live
on because you were beside me.
ZERO (VOICEOVER): But Yuki has--
YUKI (VOICEOVER):
Because the vampire Yuki
completely devoured her.
ZERO (VOICEOVER): Already.
AIDO: You'll be
able to rest here.
It's quiet.
-This room--
-I personally guarantee
that it's safe.
-A bell?
-Is something wrong?
-No.
-Now rest.
I mean, please rest.
-There's no way
that I can rest now.
I must help Yuri.
And everybody else
at the Academy.
-I understand.
But please rest.
You've become a vampire now.
This is the time you
must get your sleep.
-The truth is that Kaname is
the progenitor of the Kurans.
But to me, you're
something quite different.
You were my dear
old friend, Kaname.
Those are my only
memories of you.
That's why-- Shiki, I'm sorry.
I know I should have done this
much sooner, but I didn't.
And you ended up in this
state because of it.
I want to stay by
your side, but now I
must go and do
what I have to do.
I must end this curse.
ZERO (VOICEOVER): What's the
point in us meeting again?
That arrogant pureblood,
toying with people's emotions.
[ringing]
-Shizuka.
-You didn't know,
but your existence
had quite an effect
on everything.
I began to forget about revenge.
I even went so far as
to consider running away
with you to the very
ends of the earth.
This idea is pointless.
Even if humans and
vampires could co-exist,
their futures would be
the same as his-- hell.
I won't share my
feelings with you.
Instead, when my life is finally
over, the gift I will give you
is my own flesh and blood.
It's a fitting way for two
vampires to share their love.
Shall I remain with you?
-Sorry.
I didn't mean to wake you.
-Kaname, I just--
-What's wrong?
-It felt like Shizuka
was just there.
KANAME: Ah, well, this
was Shizuka's room.
You may have sensed something.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): That woman's
emotions, so full of hate,
came rushing.
Unable to escape her
fate as a pureblood,
she faded away,
feeling sad and alone.
-What is it, Yuki?
You all right?
Listen, there's
someplace I must go soon.
I want you to come with me.
-I can't.
I can't leave the Academy.
Can you do that, Kaname?
-Your Artemis should have
made it clear to you.
You can no longer
live as a human, Yuki.
Not like before.
-I don't care.
I will still protect
what is precious to me.
-Listen, Yuki.
I have allowed us
to be parted once.
I suffered that pain
for 10 long years.
Would you put me
through that again?
SHIKURA (VOICEOVER):
Shall I remain with you?
-When the time is right,
I will come for you.
Until then, get some rest.
-I'm so sorry.
I don't mean to
hurt you, Kaname.
I promise.
-It's all right.
I know that.
All too well.
-You don't know when to stop.
You shouldn't defy
Lord Kaname like that.
-I know.
I really didn't mean to.
I'm just so worried
about everyone.
-Like Zero?
ZERO (VOICEOVER): I sense
an arrogant pureblood
who does nothing
but toy with people.
-No, Zero is already--
-I was eagerly waiting for
your inevitable resurrection,
Lord Rido.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): That
distant, ominous feeling
has suddenly become
quite present.
Those sinister eyes.
-I have to go.
-Have you already forgotten
what Kaname just told you?
-I won't just sit in this
room and let the entire school
be put in danger because of me.
I'm still a guardian
at this Academy.
-You're wrong.
You are the pureblood princess.
-I know.
But I've-- I've lived
as a human for so long.
Everyone here has helped
me, and I've protected them.
If I just turn my
back on that now,
I won't have any idea
how to properly live
my life in the future.
-Perhaps, but you can't
even hold Artemis.
-I have a gun.
-Uh-- well, you must be hungry.
-I'm not hungry.
-Yes, you are.
You're hungry.
I have to get you food
because you're so hungry.
-Aido, you're--
-Enough.
Do not leave this room.
I may not be locking the door,
but do not leave this room.
-Aido, what are you--
-There's another
pureblood vampire.
How ominous.
No.
Yuki's different.
What am I saying?
-I'm surprised.
I thought for a moment
that you were crying.
-I don't want to see you.
Just leave.
-Ah yes, you must be strong.
Otherwise I'll be in trouble.
-Why would you be in trouble?
-It's been a little
over four years,
and the pawn I've
carefully nurtured
is now almost able
to devour the king.
You're the pawn.
You're going to destroy Rido.
The monster just
rose from his coffin.
-Are you crazy?
You can do it yourself.
-You want to pretend
like you haven't noticed?
What you have so willingly
taken inside yourself
has begun to pulsate.
First, you unconsciously
stole the powers of your twin,
and as a consequence, you
were born into your family
with the power of 1 and
1/2 vampire hunters.
If you had devoured
your twin entirely,
things would have been
a bit easier for you.
-Stop it.
-Then Shizuka made
you into a vampire.
Many, many times, you
devoured the blood of Yuki
who was watching
over you tenderly.
-Shut up!
-And because she has
awakened, Yuki's blood
is now permeating
throughout your body
with the true powers
of Kuran, which
I'm sure is coursing
inside you right now.
And then I too
gave you my blood,
which contains Shizuka's
blood and powers.
Everything was
done for this day.
Soon, you'll become
the strongest vampire
hunter of all.
Only you will be able to
free me from Rido's spell.
-Do you really think I'd lift
a finger to save you, Kaname?
-I know that you
will not betray Yuki.
I'll take Yuki and
leave this Academy.
But as long as Rido
exists, he will not stop.
He will keep coming
to devour her.
Goodbye.
[theme music]