[gun cocking]
-Coming here to talk?
You don't really think that'll
make a difference, do you?
Discussing things
like turning humans
into vampires-- but of course
you transformed from a vampire
into a human.
On the other side
of this door, I
sense an arrogant pureblood
who does nothing but toy
with people.
-Yes, Zero.
I'm glad you understand.
The Yuki you once knew is
gone because the vampire Yuki
completely devoured her.
[theme music]
[door creaking]
-Your shoes.
I had Ruka fetch them for you.
Hey!
Wait!
-There you go, Hanabusa.
Follow her.
-Wait up, Yuki Cross.
Uh, I mean, Lady Yuki.
Don't run around barefoot.
Don't tell me you hurt yourself.
-I thought that I
might have gone and cut
the soles of my feet.
-Lord Kaname's going
to kill me for this.
Never mind that.
Just get these on, will you?
I mean, would you please put
on your shoes, Lady Yuki?
-I didn't think there'd be
a day when you would ever
call me "Lady," Hanabusa.
It's kind of creepy.
Just call me Yuki Cross or
hey you like you usually do.
Either is fine.
-Please forgive me for
my former rudeness.
Just get them on.
I mean, please wear them.
Lord Kaname will
be worried if you
don't hurry up and
return to your room soon.
Hm?
I've never heard of a pureblood
crying in public before.
-If I'm only allowed to
cry within the confines
of my own heart,
then to me that seems
like a punishment of some kind.
-This room used to be
Ichijo and Senri's.
Now it serves as Lord
Rido's temporary residence.
So what did you come here for?
-Ichiru Kiryu, I want you
to open that coffin lid.
Will you do that for me?
You are free to disobey
me, if you wish.
-No.
KANAME: You're
like your brother.
I can reason with you.
Did I offend you just now?
You see, this is
the first time I've
seen a pair of hunter
twins who are both alive.
And because it's so rare,
well, in the hunter lineage,
when a mother is
pregnant with twins,
the two embryos will
usually combine,
or else there will
be a stillbirth.
Driven only by
instinct, the two beings
will attempt to devour
each other while still
in their mother's womb.
-Shizuka told me that
the hunters deserved that
as a punishment for when
our ancestors devoured
a founder of the vampire race
to gain powers to hunt them.
-Occasionally a twin fetus
will devour the entire life
and powers of the
other twin in the womb
and be born as one of the
strongest and most depraved
of hunters.
Your other half didn't
entirely devour you.
Your brother was soft-hearted
before he was even born.
-There.
The coffin is open.
I cannot stop you.
Do as you wish.
You want to destroy
Lord Rido, don't you?
Yes, of course that's
what you want to do.
You demolished Lord Rido,
reduced him to pieces of flesh,
unable to retain
his original form.
You are both purebloods.
If you're that much
stronger, then surely
you could have easily
destroyed him completely.
And yet for some reason
you chose not to.
Or perhaps you were
just unable to.
-If I had chosen to destroy
this beast once and for all,
then Shizuka's fate might
have been different.
All right, Rido.
The time you have awaited
eagerly is finally here.
-Vampires are selfish.
-Yuki is without a doubt
a pureblood daughter
of the Kuran family.
-It's too late.
-The Yuki that you once knew,
Zero, is now gone for good.
Because--
-Just shut up.
--the vampire Yuki
completely devoured her.
-Go away!
-It's good to see
you again, Yagari.
Depending on why
you're here, I may
ask you to leave immediately.
-I've been gone for
quite some time.
The air around here reeks
of something unpleasant.
I received an order from
the Hunter Association
to kill Zero Kiryu.
I'm guessing you're aware of
this order too, aren't you?
-So tell me, have
you come back here
to be the front
line in this attack?
-If so, what will you do?
-I will show no mercy,
not even to you.
-If you let Zero stay
here, this Academy
will become a battleground.
Is that what you want?
-I will protect my
son at all costs.
-That's the first time I've ever
seen that look in your eyes.
All right, all right, you win.
I value my life far
too much to go up
against the legendary hunter.
I have to say, your
complacency used
to really irritate me at times.
I'm glad I saw that look.
Now I know that you--
-Zero?
-So then, you've
come to kill me.
Of course you have.
After all, I am a vampire.
Come on.
Do it!
-Zero, stop it.
[screaming]
-Kaname, what are you doing?
Kaname--
-Why do you seem so
panicked, Ichijo?
Everything is going to be fine.
I can tear this man to 1,000
pieces, but unfortunately,
I cannot deal him
the final blow.
So as a result, I've decided
to resurrect him as he wishes.
Take it, Rido.
You defiled everything in
your relentless pursuit
of this-- the purest
blood of Kuran.
-Juri, you and I have
lived a very long time.
It has been far
more than enough.
It's been almost 3,000
years since you were born.
We were always together.
I was happy.
After careful
consideration, we were
blessed with a lovely child.
And that child is the
fruit of our love.
Don't you think that this
may be the time, Juri?
What you want to do
for Yuki, I can now
agree to do it-- using
our powers to give her
a different future.
-Yes, Haruka.
Then I will go now.
Kaname may get angry about this.
-Do you think so?
He's a bit like me.
He hides his feelings.
You've been rather
quiet this whole time.
After all, you've come this far
what's holding you back now,
henchman of the Senate?
I've already turned the
first attackers to dust.
-I'm afraid, Lord Haruka,
that you misunderstand us.
You see, we have no connection
at all to the Senate.
We are merely servants of
Lord Rido-- nothing more.
-Let's stop this
ridiculous farce
and be frank with each other.
You cannot control us, and as
a result, we are in your way.
Now you and Rido share
a mutual interest.
RIDO: You are correct.
You and I are so different.
You always tried to keep your
distance from the Senate.
But I, on the other hand,
have been friends with them
for a long time.
It's impossible that
you didn't know.
Now I think it's
time you confess
as to why you had me
imprisoned and kept
under the Senate's watch.
-You want to know why?
I was trying to keep you as
far away from Juri and me
as I could.
It seemed like the
best thing to do,
since you stole our first child.
-Oh, that boy.
Well, you see, I needed
that child in order for me
to create my ultimate servant.
But in the end,
he wasn't enough.
You've always been naive.
This is when you should
let hate overtake you.
Go on-- wield your powers.
If you crush my
head or my heart,
even an immortal
pureblood will be still.
If that happens, I can't
be resurrected so easily--
unless I'm giving more
rarefied pureblood blood.
-Fine.
Instead of your stomach, I'll
go for your head and heart next.
I will not allow you to
resurrect, big brother.
-My servants, go
get the little girl.
-Now it's time for you
to devour your master.
-You see, everything has
been for this moment.
That sword is-- father, no.
That weapon, it's a
vampire hunter sword.
Father, stay back.
-Kaname--
-I will take care of this.
It's my duty to
destroy him, not yours.
And besides, I don't want
you dirtying your hands
with the blood of
vermin, like him.
He's a vampire, and yet he's
wielding a hunter's weapon
when he's fighting
you one on one.
-Kaname, you stay back.
Don't destroy my pride as
a parent by protecting me.
-No, father, I--
Haruka-- I only--
-It's all right.
I know you know this,
but I'm saying it anyway.
-Haruka, that sword pierced
your heart, didn't it?
-Listen to me,
regardless of the past,
I want you to know, you've
always been our dear child,
Kaname.
-Rido, Haruka has already done
serious damage to your head.
And if I were to use
this hunter's sword,
it would take away
your ability to heel.
That head wound you have
now would become fatal.
I would prefer it if you didn't
suffer a quick and easy death
by my hand.
But for Yuki's sake, I will put
an end to your life right now.
I will use this
sword to kill you.
-Your arms cannot move.
Has happiness addled your brain?
Don't you know
you can't kill me?
You see, even if you regain
your powers and hurt me,
you will still be unable
to deliver the final blow.
I shall rest a while.
And when the time comes
to fully resurrect myself,
I'll return for the
rich blood of Kuran.
And even then, you still
won't be able to kill me.
It's such a wonderful feeling.
It was I who chained
the strongest monster.
-That someone like
yourself could ever be born
was a miscalculation on my part.
Until that time comes,
I shall secure a way
to destroy you once and for all.
But in the meantime, I
think that it's best for you
to just lie low.
Everything is for this moment.
-Kaname, what do you
mean you can't kill him?
No, that sounded wrong.
Listen, I don't care
what you do to him.
His life is meaningless to me.
But first, I want you
to tell me why, Kaname.
Why do you and the
other purebloods
always take such
extreme measures?
Fine, I know you won't
even try to explain to me.
But it makes me sad, though.
-I put my blood into his
body, so the next night he
will no longer need to
use Senri as a host.
You see, even in this state,
we can still be resurrected.
We purebloods are
repulsive, aren't we?
Don't worry, unlike us,
you will still turn to dust
if your head or heart is crushed
or if you're somehow beheaded.
-Kaname, what are you--
-Your desire to destroy
Rido still hasn't changed.
However, according to
what you just said,
you are unable to
kill him yourself.
But why is that?
-Because I am the
progenitor of the Kurans,
meaning that Rido is
my master, for he's
the one who awakened
me from my coffin.
ICHIJO: It is only
a matter of time
before Lord Rido obtains
the blood of Kuran
and is fully resurrected.
After that, I plan
to have him replace
Lord Kaname as the head
of the Kuran family.
Once that happens, the Senate
will become even more powerful.
But still, there are
currently hunters
who are roaming
free at the Academy.
And I have to admit
that does worry me.
-I don't understand why.
What is there to worry about?
You're well aware that Lord
Rido is no ordinary vampire.
-I know he has lived many
times longer than I have,
but in spite of that,
he's still a child.
And it is because of
this insolent behavior
that I find it hard to
understand what he's thinking.
As it is, I still
have no idea why
he's keeping one of the
Kiryu twins as his pet.
-Well, it could be
for a silly reason,
like he has too much
time on his hands.
Oh, excuse me.
I understand you
have your concerns,
but you need not worry about
the other twin, Ichijo.
You see, that boy Zero,
he was born a twin
in the distinguished
Kiryu family.
But he was transformed
into a vampire
and drank the blood of the
Kuran lady many, many times.
I thought perhaps
I could use him,
but unfortunately
he seems to have
no intention of obeying me.
So the hunters have detained
him as a very dangerous vampire
under my orders.
-It's been a long night.
-What are you getting
so worked up for?
Who do you think I am anyway?
If I wanted to
hunt you down, I'd
have done it a long time ago.
The Hunter Association President
and the Senate are all in bed
together on this.
The Hunter Association,
this Academy-- [scoff].
This whole world is rotten.
Don't get me wrong.
I still intend to
keep killing vampires.
Just not you.
If you're going to sit around
feeling sorry for yourself,
then stay in here until
you clear your head.
Maybe then you'll
find a solution.
I'll just say one more
thing-- you are not a vampire.
You are a vampire hunter.
YUKI (VOICEOVER):
The Yuki you once
knew is gone,
because the vampire
Yuki completely devoured her.
-Zero!
ZERO: Shut up.
ZERO (VOICEOVER): Two pulses
that are both similar.
I feel the presence of those
two throughout my body.
They're resonating.
I can't think calmly.
[theme music]