KANAME (VOICEOVER): Every
era must come to a close.
Burdened by the weighted
of its own ugliness,
that world is reduced
to ash, washed away
in a sea of fiery red.
YOUNG YUKI: Isn't
it pretty, Kaname?
Can we touch a sunset?
Or maybe it would
be too hot to touch.
Is that what it is, Kaname?
-Yes, it's too hot.
-Well, maybe I could just try
and touch it a little bit,
then.
I mean, why wouldn't
you want to touch it?
It's so pretty.
-Yuki, I desperately
want to tell you
that what is beautiful
is not this world
but rather the way in
which your eyes see it.
That is what's truly beautiful.
[theme music]
And you, Yuki, must
do what you must do.
YUKI (VOICEOVER):
What I must do.
-I want you to be
the one to kill me.
[screaming]
-Hey, what are you doing?
Why didn't you try to use
your Artemis Rod on them?
-I can't use that right now.
-Huh?
-Well, then it's
best you stay hidden.
After all, you've
only just awakened.
Trying to fight right
now is reckless and rash.
-That may be true, but
still I want to fight.
-Fine, then let me put
it to you another way.
Princess Yuki, I
implore you, please
stop behaving with
such petulance.
It is not helping.
-Ruka, I didn't mean to.
-Our master has given us orders.
We are to protect you from
Rido Kuran at all costs.
-Yuki, I do not want to
see any ugliness reflected
in your eyes.
Rido Kuran's awakening has
set in motion the most violent
of atrocities.
-You taste like trash.
I really should
have expected this.
Cheap blood doesn't
do it for me.
There is only one thing I
will find truly satisfying.
And Juri, that is the
taste of your blood.
-Just let me go, please.
KANAME (VOICEOVER): If a vampire
tries to attack a pureblood,
their powers will become sealed.
That's why in order
to protect Yuki,
it was necessary for me to
create a pawn to oppose it,
someone who would
never betray her.
My plan progressed perfectly.
Everything was on track.
But then, for the
first time, my heart
was overwhelmed with
an intolerable pain.
-You are the focus of Rido
Kuran's objective, princess.
Please, do as we ask
and leave here at once.
-I understand.
But that's exactly why I--
-Will you please stop this?
Look at the state
you're in right now.
You aren't even--
-This is going to be a
long, difficult battle.
-Hanabusa.
-You do know what you're
getting into, right?
[gunfire]
-It's from the main gate.
-This is a losing
proposition-- trying
to keep Yuki Cross
from getting hurt.
-I disagree.
If someone Lord Kaname
cares about gets hurt,
then he's going
to suffer as well.
And the last thing I want is
to see Lord Kaname suffer.
-Well, if that's the
case, then perhaps
the person I should
be protecting
is Dorm President Kuran.
-Akatsuki?
[gunfire]
-Damn, out of ammo.
I should have brought
my sword instead.
-Mr. Yagari.
-Well, well, you know when your
teacher's getting beaten up,
the least you can do
is get here sooner.
-Are you all right?
Did you get hurt?
-Just who are they?
-They're ours.
It's one of the Hunters'
Associations dirty secrets.
They breed their own Level E's.
They're here now.
-Headmaster?
-Sorry that I'm a little late.
So tell me, are
they back yet, Yuki?
The memories that you have
of Juri, your real mother.
Very well.
Everyone, protect Yuki.
Or rather, Cross Academy.
This is as far as
I'll allow you to go.
Leave these ones to me.
-No, that's crazy.
-He can't take on that
many of them alone.
-Headmaster.
-It's not Headmaster.
It's father.
-You're right, father.
Father, no!
-Your father sure is
one crazy old man.
-Everything he's done is
to protect this Academy.
Let's go.
Let's find Rido Kuran.
-Are you sure?
-This is not a matter
of what I want.
This is a matter of what
I have to do in order
to protect this Academy.
-You may not be blood related,
but you are his daughter.
You're just as stubborn
and reckless as he is.
Don't worry.
I won't let the old
man fight alone.
-You guys are way late.
-Have you found Rido?
-We didn't even need to look.
He has really bad taste.
-He is just way too obvious.
ASSOCIATION PRESIDENT:
Sir Ichijo-- blood, I
have come to get blood.
-Oh?
And just what do you have
to offer me in return?
-Well, Kaien Cross is
a very obstinate man,
but I'm doing my best
to force him to comply.
I've ordered every Level
E the Association has
to descend upon that Academy.
It's just a matter of time
before it's completely
destroyed.
-Very well then.
-Sir Ichijo, my reward.
-There's no need to rush.
-But I need the
vampire blood now.
It's the only way a
human can rejuvenate.
Sir Ichijo, please.
This was the agreement.
This is what you promised,
my chance at eternal beauty.
-You sold out your friends
for your own personal gain.
A person like you has nothing
in common with beauty,
nor do you have any right
to ask for blood when
you are just a human.
-Blood, blood-- hurry.
-You disgust me.
[cracking]
-Wow, bummer.
-That smell has--
-I've been waiting
for you, Juri.
You've grown to be
so beautiful, Yuki.
-What are you--
KANAME (VOICEOVER):
You've become so strong
and refined that it's blinding.
MALE SPEAKER: Lord Kaname--
-I'm sorry, Kaname.
KANAME (VOICEOVER):
You've made me happy.
nothing has given me more
joy than seeing you grown up.
Thank you.
-We need to report
this to Lord Ichijo.
KANAME (VOICEOVER):
Fly high, Yuki.
And no matter how
far you fly away,
you will always be
the most precious girl
in the world to me.
-I'm so glad you came, Juri.
Are you ready to
become one with me?
-You'll have to come
through us first.
-And we'll reduce you to ash.
-Such fools.
-Why can't I use--
-You are all vampires.
You cannot lay a
hand on a pureblood.
This is a special
night, and I don't
want to ruin it by behaving
like a selfish cad.
So why don't you guys
have a bit of fun now?
-No!
That's enough.
Rido, stop.
Let go of me!
-You know, you smell
exactly like Juri did.
-No!
YUKI (VOICEOVER): At this rate,
what I-- what I must do is--
-Let her be!
-Artemis, it worked!
-But how is a pureblood
princess able to wield
a vampire hunter's weapon?
-You see, I am a guardian.
And no matter what, I will
protect this Academy, and not
just the day class students.
I am here to protect the
night class students as well.
-That's the Juri I know.
No wait, that's Juri's daughter.
-And as for the rest of you,
step away from those students
right now.
-You seem to have a lot
more pluck than Juri did.
Juri was a lot more
docile than you are.
Indeed, the very first time
I had a taste of her blood--
-Let go of her!
This has gone far enough.
I won't--
-Hanabusa!
-Come on, cry out for help.
It's all right.
Juri cried for help too.
She begged for
someone to save her
when I first drank her blood.
Muffled by her tears, she
pleaded for Haruka to save her.
It was absolutely brilliant.
-What are you--
-Give it a try.
Call out the name
of the one you love.
YUKI (VOICEOVER):
The one I love?
[gunfire]
-Zero.
-Get your filthy hands
off of her right now.
-Where are you going?
-I was thinking I
would try and escape
while I still had the chance.
-I see.
A wise move.
-It would be a little
premature to turn me
into ash at this juncture.
-If you're going
to find your god,
I think it's safe to
say that he's already
been torn to shreds by the beast
that I have so carefully been
nurturing.
-God, is it?
-What's the matter?
Did you not find me
suitable for your purposes?
-That wasn't the case at all.
The only reason we didn't choose
you was because you're a person
we cannot control.
Rido Kuran is nothing
more than a fool.
As long as you manage to satisfy
his appetite, controlling him
is rather easy.
But still--
-Let's end this
conversation here.
-Please, allow me
to handle this one.
-Takuma.
-As a vampire, I
have betrayed you.
However, as your
friend, you have my word
that I will never do it again.
Now please, allow me
to prove that to you.
Thank you, Kaname.
-Takuma?
Come, now.
Do you honestly intend to
point that blade at me?
This is not an attempt
to beg for my life,
but I had always hoped that you
would follow in my footsteps,
and one day you would take
over my place in the Senate.
-Let's put an end to this.
Let's draw the curtains on
the Ichijo family together.
KANAME (VOICEOVER): In any plan,
there is always the unexpected.
Pawns, positioned to
protect to hold dear.
That is all I had expected
of them-- nothing more.
Yet these pieces performed in
ways that I could not predict.
They gave far more
than I asked of them.
They shined far brighter than
I ever dreamed they would.
My battle is over.
Now, have you fulfilled
your duty, Zero Kiryu?
-Zero!
Zero, what did you do to Ichiru?
-So dangerous.
-You monster.
-Zero!
-What's wrong?
-I don't think he has any
idea how to control his power.
-Zero!
-This is bad,
[screaming]
-Zero!
-This is what happens when a
former human devours his twin.
-Rido.
-There is now far more
power in your human vessel
than it is able to contain.
You can't master all
that strength so quickly.
-Zero!
-Yuki--
-What are you--
-Use your Artemis and cut me.
-Zero.
-Are you out of your mind?
-There isn't any other
option right now.
His power is out of control.
It's the only way to stop it.
-But Zero, if I use the
Artemis Rod on you, then--
-Don't worry, Yuki.
That isn't a weapon
that can kill me.
Remember our promise.
ZERO (VOICEOVER):
One day, if I'm
about to lose control, I
want you to be the one.
-Zero!
ZERO (VOICEOVER):
This pain is proof.
-Live, Zero, and
do what I cannot.
Proof that Ichiru still
lives on inside me.
-Zero!
-He has the Bloody Rose.
-Finally, Ichiru,
you and I are one.
-(CHUCKLING) Interesting.
All right, fine.
If you want to play, I'm game.
Kill me as often as you want.
And I will resurrect every time.
-I choose to keep on living.
-Zero, what have you done?
-That light is not in harmony
with a vampire knight.
[theme music]