[music playing]
YUKI (VOICEOVER): A rose that
blooms only once every 10
years.
That night, 10 years
ago, was my beginning.
Kaname is my-- but why?
Why was he there that night?
Who took away my memories?
And if I uncover the
truth, what will happen?
LITTLE GIRL
(VOICEOVER): I'm scared.
It doesn't matter.
I have to find out.
[gasp]
What was that?
[music - on/off, "rinne rondo"]
YUKI: Thanks for
everything today.
So have a good night.
See you.
LITTLE GIRL (VOICEOVER):
He's going to eat me!
-Uh?
-I'll see you later, Yuki.
-Uh, sounds good.
[gasp]
LITTLE GIRL (VOICEOVER): The
scary vampire is going to--
[gasp]
[teacup smashes]
CROSS: Oh, dear,
look what I've done!
The rose tea was a present.
I'll make some more, Zero.
Would you like some?
It's from Kaname.
-No, thank you.
I just came to report every
Night Class student except two
have returned to the dorm.
Now that I've given
you my report, goodbye.
-Owie!
I cut my finger.
Want a lick so it doesn't
go to waste, Zero?
--[sigh] Please don't
act the same as Yuki.
-What?
What are you trying
to say, Zero?
When did you lick Yuki's finger?
-You do know.
-Huh?
-That I'm still
drinking Yuki's blood.
-Hm.
Of course.
I've watched over the two of
you for quite some time now.
But even despite
the obvious pain,
you both chose that path anyway.
So I won't do anything for now,
even if it is a forbidden act.
Is that wrong?
While you still
have your sanity,
I plan to turn a blind eye.
W-wait!
Don't go!
There's something important
I want to tell you.
A new student wants to
enter the Day Class.
I can't accept him
into the Academy
unless I have your permission.
-[gasp]
YUKI (VOICEOVER): This
blood is only an illusion.
Yes.
It's not real.
WOMAN (VOICEOVER): Or is it?
[gasp]
WOMAN (VOICEOVER):
You're always--
YUKI (VOICEOVER): No!
WOMAN (VOICEOVER): Like this.
-Stop it!
WOMAN (VOICEOVER): Hurting
those who are important to you.
-Yuki.
-Kaname, I--
-What scared you?
[breathing shortly]
KANAME: Calm down, Yuki.
[rod clatters on floor]
-I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, Kaname.
-It's all right, Yuki.
It's all right.
-I'm so sorry!
YUKI (VOICEOVER):
What did I just do?
I-- I used the Artemis
Rod against him.
KANAME: Yuki, what did you
want to talk to me about?
-There's something
I want to ask you.
Kaname, what were you
doing on that snowy day?
Are you the one who
took my memories away?
-Please, don't worry.
No matter what you
ask, Yuki, my feelings
for you will never
change, no matter what.
I've never actually
said it aloud to you,
but you do know, Yuki-- I
love you, more than anyone.
If it were at all possible,
I would take them away,
all your fears and anxieties.
ZERO: Are you all right, Yuki?
-It's something I had to do.
I had to face
Kaname and ask him.
But then I-- I couldn't
find the words to do it
when I had the chance.
-Yuki.
You don't have to rush things.
You can always ask him
those questions eventually.
So just take your time.
-Mm.
SEIREN: Why have you come
at this time of night?
Please leave.
KANAME: What is it, Seiren?
-Lord Kaname.
-I thought that I sensed
something horribly unpleasant.
It was you.
Come in.
Take a seat.
[door closes]
-I want the truth.
Did you erase Yuki's
memories or not?
Answer me.
Did you have something to do
with Yuki's past or didn't you?
Have you no desire to
alleviate her fears?
-So, shall I destroy one
of Yuki's fears right now?
One less problem?
-[grunts]
-Do it.
I can probably get a shot
off at the same time.
-Look at you.
You're quite the anomaly.
Vampires should fear and
respect Purebloods by instinct,
but still you bare your
fangs without reserve.
I really do hate you.
[crash]
-[grunting]
-You have no intention
of killing me.
-And if I kill you needlessly,
it will only cause Yuki grief.
And I want no part of that.
-Your body is honest.
Your eyes lust for
the blood it sees.
I can smell Yuki on you.
You ungrateful Level E.
-[gasp]
-Now that you've
lost all that blood,
I'm sure you're desperately
thirsting for more.
[breathing jaggedly]
KANAME: Listen, Zero,
take my blood again.
-You must be joking.
Do you really think I want
any more of your blood?
-I can't have you die now.
I've allowed you
to live this long
so that you can serve Yuki.
Because I know that
you won't betray her.
-You're assuming
things, as usual.
-Oh, but I know.
Because it's my belief
that our feelings for Yuki
are probably the same.
-I just-- all I want
is for Yuki to be
happy-- I mean truly happy.
-Me too.
-I don't want for her
to sacrifice herself.
I want her to be safe.
-Exactly.
[breathing jaggedly]
-And Zero, I don't
want you to ever forget
for whom this blood was offered.
HANABUSA: Stop!
[gasp] You!
KANAME (VOICEOVER): It would be
wise not to delve any further.
-But you might be able to
delve further into the place
where Lord Kaname
hides his darkness.
-Hanabusa!
-Get out of here!
The entire Night Class has
caught on to the scent.
They know it's Lord
Kaname's blood.
ZERO (VOICEOVER): Where Kaname
Kuran hides his darkness.
That's where Yuki's--
[car door opens and closes]
-Be sure you do your duties
well if you want my lord
to assist with your revenge.
[bell rings]
-Yes, sir.
YORI: Are you OK, Yuki?
I'm going to ask the campus
physician to come by later.
[door opens and closes]
YUKI (VOICEOVER):
I couldn't think.
I couldn't answer.
KANAME (VOICEOVER): I love you.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): The
innocent times are over.
Before, I tried not to
think about Kaname and me.
I felt that I shouldn't
think about it.
KANAME (VOICEOVER): I've never
actually said it aloud to you,
but you do know.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): I'm afraid
of what the answer will mean.
[students chattering]
TEACHER: Quiet, everyone.
Please introduce yourself.
ICHIRU: Hello.
I'll be your new classmate.
-Uh?
Zero's not here.
-Yuki!
Is your headache better?
-I'm fine.
Thanks, Yori.
Hey, what's going on?
-That is.
-Uh?
-You see, due to
various circumstances,
we've been living separately.
I'm Zero's twin, Ichiru Kiryu.
Nice to meet you.
-Ah?
TEACHER: Yuki!
-Oh!
YUKI: If you're going to
take a seat, do it now.
-Uh.
Class rep, please look after
Ichiru for the time being.
-[protests]
YUKI (VOICEOVER): He came
back to avenge Shizuka.
He thinks Zero killed her.
Why?
Why would the headmaster--
[tiny bell rings]
ICHIRU: Zero used
to have good taste.
-Mm?
-I can't believe he
actually cares for you.
-Huh?
-So then you know him?
-Uh, well, sort of.
he Seems even more warped
than Kiryu Number One does.
-Exactly.
-And I guess Number One holds
you a bit dear, doesn't he?
CROSS: You're really leaving?
-I am.
Thanks for everything.
-Please don't go!
I'll be lonely if you leave.
-Why did you allow
Ichiru to transfer here?
-Listen, I still don't know
what the Hunters Association is
up to, and it seems
whether inside or outside
of school grounds,
Zero and Ichiru
are going to cross paths.
We won't be able to avoid that.
So if we can't stop
them from meeting,
we can at least
give them a chance
to understand each other.
-Very well.
I see your point now.
-Then stay!
We can be together forever!
-Get off!
I'll have my own look at
the Hunters Association
and see what they're up to.
But no, I'm not abandoning you.
-Huh?
Yagari.
-See ya.
[thud]
-Uh!
Um, hello.
CROSS: Yuki.
-Uh, I was just--
-See you later, young lady.
-Oh.
CROSS: Did you hear us?
-Uh, well, a little bit.
-Zero allowed Ichiru's transfer.
He had final say.
-He did?
CROSS: Mm.
I know Zero has a quick temper
and can seem rather scary,
but he's becoming
quite an adult.
GIRL: You're identical
twins, right?
But you don't exactly match.
You don't have the
same hairstyle.
-No, but if everyone
prefers it that way,
then maybe I will cut it.
[tiny bell rings]
GIRL: Really?
You wouldn't mind?
Ichiru, you're friendly.
You're not like
your brother at all.
-You're the hope
of the Day Class.
The other boys are
completely hopeless.
I mean it, Ichiru.
-Oh, really?
-Aah!
ICHIRU: Oh, class rep.
-Yes, that's me.
-Well, I don't know
anything about this place,
so can I depend on you?
-Mm!
Sure.
And if you have any
questions whatsoever,
please do not
hesitate to ask me.
You are far more likable
than your brother is.
[door creaks]
[students gasp]
[frantic whispers]
-Ah!
What I meant to say was--
-Please excuse me.
What is it?
And stop looking so menacing.
You're frightening everyone.
-If you came for revenge,
why don't you take it now?
-What's this?
I thought you let
me transfer here
so you could try and comfort
your poor little brother.
But perhaps I was wrong.
-You talked before
about the Cursed Twins.
What does that mean?
-Don't know.
I just know that when twins
are born to a Vampire Hunter
family, that's what
they're called.
Kind of perfect, huh?
A name like the Cursed
Twins, it-- it fits us.
I'm eager to see what it's
like to be a normal high school
student.
No reason to let you
have all the fun.
ZERO: I finished reporting in.
-OK.
Zero, you were talking
to Ichiru earlier.
-You saw us?
-I did.
I was impressed by it, really.
It seems like you're trying your
best to meet Ichiru halfway.
You're facing your past.
Zero, you're amazing.
-I told you, you shouldn't
try to rush things too much.
KANAME (VOICEOVER):
And Zero, I don't
want you to ever forget for
whom this blood was offered.
ZERO: OK?
-Mm.
I've decided that I'm going
to confront Kaname tonight.
For 10 years now, Kaname
has been a consistent part
of my life in one
form or another,
and I've always
felt that I wouldn't
mind if one day he betrayed me.
But I was also afraid
to ask him about it,
and it took a long time
to gather my courage.
I know I've taken
the moral high ground
and lectured you a lot, Zero.
But I really like Kaname.
I've liked him for 10 years now.
-What brought all this on?
-I already know.
I know that Kaname is
hiding something from me.
But still, I don't care.
I need to go.
-Forget it.
You should just go.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): When
I first opened my eyes,
both the world and my
memories were pure white.
But your mere existence
instantly colored my world.
KANAME: Yuki.
I've been waiting.
-Please, tell me the truth.
I don't want to remain
like a child who's
forgiven for not
knowing anything.
-What is it?
-I want you to
tell me the truth,
and don't evade me this time.
-Evade you?
Ah, like you did when
I said I love you?
-Uh!
-Hm?
-Um, yes.
-That's how I truly feel.
You find my love repulsive?
-[gasp] Of course not!
I've never felt
that way about you.
I've always loved you.
I love you now!
YUKI (VOICEOVER): The times
you came to see me each year.
-Yuki!
-Kaname!
[giggles]
YUKI (VOICEOVER):
The arms I could
jump into and feel safe in.
That beautiful man who
looked at me tenderly.
Those things saved me.
-After everything
you've done for me,
I have absolutely no reason
to try and avoid you,
even if you were
the same vampire
who tried to devour
me back then.
Because you were there, Kaname.
I-- [gasp]
-Yuki--
-Why does it have to be me?
I see the situation clearly now.
No matter how hard I try, even
if I reach beyond my station,
I'm just not suitable for you.
Kaname, you have something
to do with my forgotten past,
don't you?
-Mm.
-[gasp] So it is true!
Then why won't you
tell me what happened?
Please!
I have to know what
really happened!
I can't stay in the
dark like this anymore!
Mean
I don't want you to use
this bond between us
to avoid the issue.
I want to know everything
and grow strong.
Please!
-Don't be silly.
Let things remain
just as they are.
Be happy in this
academy a while longer.
OK?
Because the truth you seek
might be covered with blood.
Even then, would you
still want to know?
-Yes, Kaname.
-To be honest, I've
been afraid, wondering
if the only person
who gives me warmth
will change, afraid
that when she finally
learns the truth about
everything, she will hate me.
-I wouldn't do that.
I will never hate you.
-All right.
Then prove it to me, Yuki.
Be my lover.
[gasp]
ZERO (VOICEOVER):
Her arm was so thin
that I thought it would break.
Don't go, Yuki.
You don't need to know.
If you know, then you--
YUKI: No!
Let me go!
You think I'll back
down if you say that?
Let me go!
Stop dodging the issue!
-Yuki, if you prove
it to me, then I
promise I will tell
you everything.
That's all that I
am asking of you.
-You're lying.
-I'm not.
If you want to know the
truth, hear what I'm saying.
YUKI: Why?
-That's a good girl.
-Why?
Kaname.
-You needn't look at us with
such worried eyes, Zero.
From now on, this is my domain.
I will watch over and protect
Yuki as my lover, all right?
[MUSIC - KANON WAKESHIMA, "SUNA
NO OSHIRO"]
[music playing]