-Zero!
[theme music]
-That was quite a show.
-Where's Rido Kuran?
-That's him.
He's still here.
Zero!
-What are you thinking?
-No.
I'm not done yet.
Not till I devour Juri.
-I hate to interrupt
your meal, but in case
you haven't noticed,
dawn is upon us.
It's time for our
curtain to finally fall
on our vampire knight.
-You think only you can
actually draw that curtain?
Wow, that does hurt.
But you know, those
little attacks of yours
won't finish me.
-You're right.
I cannot do that.
But I am not the one who
will drop the curtain.
You're late.
Go on.
Finish that thing off.
-(LAUGHING) Have you forgotten
you're nothing more than
a servant with a lapdog
who can't defy me?
-Goodbye.
-It's gone.
Rido's presence.
-Yes, I think it's over.
-Well done.
-You realize you're
next, Kaname Kuran.
You didn't think that
everything would go exactly
as you planned it, did you?
-I did wonder.
I knew all too well, once you
gained this unrivaled power
and finished Rido off
for good that chances
were you would most
likely come after my life.
However, I also knew that you
wouldn't pull that trigger.
-What?
-Zero.
Kaname, what are you--
-Yuki, listen, it will
be time to leave soon.
Yes, I knew it all
along-- every bit of it.
-We did it.
We protected her.
-Hanabusa, you tried hard
to be chivalrous back there.
It was quite amusing.
-I did no such thing.
That's more apt for Seiren.
You said Dorm
President Kuran ordered
us to protect Yuki Cross.
Who knew even someone
like you could lie?
-I've decided to put
an end to all of this.
From here forward, you
can do as you wish.
-Huh?
-Lord Kaname, what are you--
-You were all pawns that I had
gathered here to protect Yuki.
I'm sure you can sense
it, this presence.
There is someone else
now who can protect Yuki.
You are dismissed.
I have no further use of you.
-But Lord Kaname--
[chuckling]
-Hanabusa.
[laughing]
-Are you all right?
Keep it together.
-I'm fine.
Ecstatic, actually.
If he really did
think of us as pawns,
then he would have sacrificed
us and we'd be dead.
-But in the end, that
isn't what Lord Kaname did.
HANABUSA: No, he saw
us as individuals.
And that was his way of
acknowledging each of us.
Nothing's changed.
I still like Lord Kaname.
-Hanabusa, he sounded
pretty passionate, huh?
-To the point that it
was kind of creepy.
-Hey!
I can still hear you, you know.
-All right, then.
What are we going to do now?
-Huh?
-The battle is finally over.
Dorm President Kuran has
released us to do what we want.
-Following my master
is the only path I see.
-All right, guess
which hand it's in.
-Huh?
-Guess which hand it's in.
If you get it
right, then-- then I
will follow Dorm
President Kuran.
Choose already.
-We already know what
you're going to do.
-Will you hurry up?
-Such a philistine.
-Why couldn't you just say
that's what you wanted?
HANABUSA: Shut up!
-What are your plans?
-Well, I'll go with him.
I want to end this
curse with my own hands.
So are you in as well?
-Yo, good work.
-Yagari, you're still alive.
-Hey, that's my line.
That trusted sword
of yours finally
gets to see the light
of day, and you treat it
like an old man's cane.
-It's time for it
to sleep once again.
Forever this time.
-So bright.
-Yes, it was bright.
I used to watch
you from up here.
-Zero.
-I'd watch you as you
watched Kaname Kuran.
Whether you were with
him or anybody else,
you always had a
smile on your face.
Even when I did something
that was unforgivable,
that smile was still there.
I was perfectly willing
to sacrifice my whole life
for you.
That's what I was prepared to
do-- to give up everything.
So you're going to
leave now, aren't you?
KANAME (VOICEOVER):
I wonder why.
-Yes.
-I thought so.
-You once asked me
to kill you if you
become a vampire, remember?
-I do.
-But what if I become a vampire?
-Well, I'm still not
sure if I believe
that you really are a vampire.
There's no proof.
-But Zero, come on.
That's just--
-All right, if you really are
a vampire, then drink my blood.
If you truly are a vampire
that I should hate, go on.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): I'm sorry.
Kaname, I'm-- so, so sorry.
-I know that you are.
-I can taste Zero.
It's like what he once said.
-Your blood had that taste.
-I understand now.
-Yuki, Yuki, Yuki, Yuki.
-Zero's feelings
are flowing into me.
-You're right.
You are a vampire.
This means we can no longer
live in the same world.
But someday in
the future, I will
come after you to kill you.
-I'll be waiting.
-No matter what, we will
always be best friends.
-Thank you.
[door opening]
KANAME (VOICEOVER): In
trying to protect you,
all I've done is
hurt you the most.
Why is that?
For some reason,
my feelings for you
always have the opposite effect.
I wonder why that is.
YUKI: I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I am the one who hurt
this man the most.
For 10 years I made
him wait alone.
And I never even knew.
I mean it, Kaname.
I'm so sorry.
Now listen, you must do
what you must do, Yuki.
-We'd better get going
before the sun gets too high.
-Yuki.
-I'm sorry that I'm
running a little late.
My bags are kind of heavy.
-Tell me, why did you come?
-Huh?
Because you said that
it's almost time to leave,
didn't you?
-Yes, but you're free now.
-Well, that may be true,
but the only reason I'm free
is because of everything
you did to save me.
-I see.
So it's gratitude.
-Huh?
-You needn't force
yourself to come.
You said there were people
you wanted to protect.
You're free to do that.
-Yes, there are people
I want to protect.
And you, Kaname, you will
always be one of them.
-That makes me happy.
But if you're going
to protect me,
Yuki, you will have
to be very strong.
-My feelings always have
the opposite effect.
I want to protect you,
but I hurt you instead.
I want to cry and
somehow I laugh.
-You haven't changed a bit.
-Lord Kaname?
-Do you remember?
Before you lost your memories.
-Don't cry.
-Yuki.
Don't worry.
I'm not crying.
-It's OK.
Good boy.
I am here for you.
KANAME (VOICEOVER):
Even then, you
were able to see into my heart.
From the very beginning, you've
been there protecting me.
Only you.
You have always been
the most precious thing
in the world for me.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): I
want to protect him.
KANAME (VOICEOVER):
Don't you need
to say goodbye to the
headmaster before we go?
-No.
I'm afraid that he might
start crying if I do.
KAIEN: Of course I will cry!
Come on!
Let me have a good cry!
Yuki!
Oh, I won't be able to
experience this feeling again
for a long time.
-Headmaster?
-Don't say that!
You were calling
me father earlier!
-I can't breathe!
-Yuki, you are going of
your own free will, right?
-I am.
-All right.
Kaname, if you ever hurt Yuki,
I will never forgive you.
-Thank you.
I'm going now, father.
-Let's be clear.
We are not pawns for
you to play with.
So even if you disapprove, we
are still going to follow you.
That understood?
-You may do as you please.
-Watch it.
-Hey, are you trying
to cut in front of me?
-Come on, that wasn't
my intention at all.
Listen, just because
I have longer legs--
-What did you say?
-Grow up.
Will you get out of my way?
-Here we go.
-Yuki is my child.
And all that I want
is for her to grow up
like a normal human girl.
I want her to be free from the
fate of a pureblood vampire.
I want her to smile.
-Juri, in the end, Yuki chose
not to run away from her fate.
But I want you to
know that she still
smiles like a normal human girl.
Goodbye, everyone.
-Yo, you do have other
students here, headmaster.
Did you forget about them?
-Oh!
-It's not my fault
if you get sunburned.
-Uh-huh.
-I wonder how they're all doing.
-This belongs to Takuma.
-Do you think he really is gone?
-So not you.
-Yeah.
But it doesn't
really need to be.
This is Takuma's after all.
-Where are you going?
-Well, to give this
back to Takuma.
-Give it back?
-There must be some
kind of reward for it.
-Oh.
I'll come too.
-Hm?
-Someone has to feed to you.
Here.
-I'm sorry, everyone.
The danger has passed.
You're all safe.
-Yuki.
-Bastard.
He created this mess.
He's the one who should
clean it up, not me.
Glad you're here.
[cheering]
-All right, everyone get back.
-Wild!
Aido, please come out.
-Ruka!
Ruka, look over here.
Please look this way.
-Day class students must
return to their dorms.
Huh?
Zero, are you trying
to skip out on work?
Come on, hurry.
Get over here.
-Yuki, one day.
YUKI (VOICEOVER):
I'll be waiting, Zero.
Until then.
[theme music]