-Sorry to keep you waiting.
-That's quite all right.
-Well, shall we go?
RIMA: It feels sort of
strange that we're all
going to the Aido Villa but
Hanabusa isn't coming with us.
-As long as I'm with Lord
Kaname, I really don't care.
-Senri, you're not coming too?
-My mother keeps
harassing me to go home,
so this time I'll go see her.
-Here.
Good luck with that.
MALE SPEAKER: Someone has
committed the greatest taboo.
They have dared to
kill a pureblood.
-Why?
AKATSUKI: We have no
idea what Dorm President
Kuran is planning right now.
So until we do, there's nothing.
[theme music]
KANAME (VOICEOVER): I hope
you do realize, Yuki, I
know what you told
me was the truth.
Will you become a vampire?
YUKI (VOICEOVER):
I can do anything
if it's for Lord Kaname.
That's what I thought.
I'm scared.
Scared?
Scared of what?
I'm scared.
What is it?
What is this feeling?
I'm scared.
FEMALE SPEAKER: The
truth cannot be changed.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): What is truth?
I'm scared.
FEMALE SPEAKER: You
can avert your eyes--
YUKI (VOICEOVER): I'm scared.
FEMALE SPEAKER:
--but it won't work.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): I'm scared.
-Where are you going, Yuki?
-Dorm president--
-I'll remind you, even though
we're on break, we have rules.
And it's almost curfew.
Please remember, even if you're
on the disciplinary committee,
you shouldn't visit the
boys' dorm so casually.
-Listen, I--
-Look, either way, I just know
that this can't be proper.
[gasp]
-Huh?
Hanabusa?
-You can try to sneak
in during the break,
but there's hardly anyone here.
Besides, this is the boys' dorm.
What do you want?
-I don't care what you
say or how this may look,
I'm not here to see Zero--
[gasping]
-Hanabusa, what
are you doing here?
-Dorm President--
-The Sun and Moon
dorms are set up so
that students can't
go between them.
-I'm sorry.
I ran away from my dorm.
-You what?
-Just pretend that
you didn't see me.
-Oh, all right, then.
But if I were on the
disciplinary committee,
I would punish you.
-Thank you.
-Hanabusa, in case
you've forgotten,
the knight class is
not supposed to enter
the grounds of the
Sun dormitories.
-He's right, Hanabusa.
Please go back to your dorm.
-Yes, but I don't
want to be there.
So I am not going to go back.
-Yuki, go get a rope.
We'll drag him back.
-You'll have to catch me first.
-Don't waste my time
with your stupid games.
-You realize this could have
all been avoided if you had just
helped me out from the start.
-All right, then.
I hope the headmaster's private
quarters will be OK with you.
Or maybe you'd prefer
Zero's room in the Sun dorm.
BOTH: Never.
-Hanabusa, did something happen
to make you want to run away?
-You know, I'm hungry.
Oh come now, what
are you afraid of?
Just cook me something.
Anything will be fine.
Oh, I'm going to need a soft
bed to sleep in during the day.
And the linens must have
a nice lavender scent.
And as for a toothbrush--
-Now, now.
--I prefer a small, soft head.
YAGARI: I don't like this.
I'm sure Zero and Ichiru
didn't meet at that soiree
by coincidence.
Zero being a suspect
in Shizuka Hio's murder
wasn't questioned by the Senate
to protect Kaname Kuran's
dignity.
Ichiru deeply despises
Zero and attacks him
in order to gain revenge for
the death of Shizuka Hio.
And since that stems from a
personal grudge from the past,
they don't let Kaname
file a complaint.
That about sum it up?
KAIEN (VOICEOVER):
If this is all true,
does that mean the Senate
approached the Hunter
Association with a deal?
Or maybe--
YUKI (VOICEOVER): He
ate our portion too.
-I was able to eat it.
It was all right, but
there wasn't enough.
-You sure are pretty
picky for a runaway.
-Is there a problem?
-Yes, but don't worry about it.
I'll just make sure to
tell Kaname on you later.
YUKI (VOICEOVER):
I've got him now.
-What?
I cooked enough for
three and he wants more?
-Yeah.
He looks a little depressed.
-Is he stressed out?
He doesn't seem like
the sensitive type.
Here, give him blood
tablets for now.
I'll cook up more food.
It's fine.
I don't hate cooking.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): An
unnatural silent moment.
-If you want something
particular, just tell me.
-I guess some salt ramen.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): I can only
assume that his uncertainty
and loneliness
has to be growing.
So Zero, what is it that
you're thinking about?
-Where's my food?
-There's more coming.
Zero said to give you these
blood tablets for now.
-These are Zero's, right?
-No, you're wrong.
-Oh, don't panic.
I mean, after all,
I am a genius,
so of course I
would figure it out.
-Um yeah, of course
you are, but--
-And besides, Zero knows
that I know as well.
Although he doesn't mention
it, Lord Kaname knows too.
Unfortunately I have
no idea exactly what
Lord Kaname is thinking.
-Hanabusa--
-I have never understood why he
gives an ordinary girl like you
special treatment and dares
sour relations with the senate.
It makes no sense.
-He doesn't give me
special treatment.
-If you had really meant what
you just said, I'd kill you.
-In what I can remember
from my earliest memory,
there are two vampires--
the frightening vampire who
tried to devour me and a
frightening but kind vampire
who killed the other to save me.
I adore the kind
vampire, Lord Kaname.
I owe my life to him.
But I think our relationship
is a simple one, not
a special one.
-Simple, huh?
Do you trust him no
matter what happens?
-It's true.
Sometimes I do have my
doubts, but in the end,
I really do trust him.
Even if he betrays me,
I-- I'd be OK with it.
-I like rose tea.
-Yes, the fragrance is lovely.
-If I mix in the rose jam, will
the flavor become more intense?
-Personally, I like jam on my
biscuits and not on my tea.
-I brought you biscuits, miss.
I hope you enjoy them.
-There's only use for them now.
-Yes, I see.
-I don't understand.
Why didn't Hanabusa
come along with us too?
-I don't know.
And for some reason, Akatsuki
has shut himself in his room.
I don't know what's
going on with them.
AKATSUKI: I need
to ask you a favor.
The villa you're going to
houses record of the soirees
and family trees
of certain clans.
So while you're there, I
want you to go through them
and see who might hold a grudge
against the Kuran family.
-What you're asking
sounds intrusive.
-I have a very bad feeling.
And that's why I
need to figure out
what Lord Kaname's secret is.
-So why don't you
just go yourself?
-Please, for me.
AKATSUKI (VOICEOVER): Is
dorm president Kuran's secret
somehow connected to
Shizuka Hio's death?
-I'm home now.
-Senri-- Senri, Senri.
-I'm home, mother.
Please brush your hair.
The fans you had when
you were an actress
would cry seeing you like this.
-You look more like that
savage brute every day.
-Really?
I have no idea what my
father actually looked like.
-Yesterday, my uncle
told me to make
sure to send you
over for a visit.
You can't refuse his request.
After all, he's from the Senate.
But hurry back, and feed
your poor, hungry mother
some of your blood.
I will be waiting.
-You're still greedy,
but all right.
-Kaname, why?
-Wow, look at that, Hana.
You're so smart.
That's a hard book
you're reading.
-Hum.
-Ladies, I'm afraid
the break is over now.
ALL: All right.
-Well, you're preparing
for your lesson.
I heard the master say
he's very pleased he's
been blessed with
such a wonderful son.
-Um, I sensed a child
here, so I couldn't
resist coming up to see you.
Are you a child of this family.
I just--
-Who are you?
You've got no manners
barging in here.
-Lord Kaname, if you'd waited,
I'd have given you a tour.
-I'm sorry I barged in.
-No, no.
It's quite all right.
Don't worry.
I hope our Hanabusa
wasn't rude to you.
-Huh?
Father, he's the rude one.
-He's right.
It's my fault.
I haven't been around
children my age that much.
My name is Kaname Kuran.
HANABUSA (VOICEOVER):
He's a Kuran,
one of the pureblood lines.
-Will you be my friend?
-No.
-How can you be so reckless?
Master Hanabusa!
-So what if he is a pureblood?
-Hanabusa, I believe
today's lesson
will be on how our race
came into existence.
In ancient times, human
civilization almost perished.
The progenitor of the vampires
appeared around that time.
The pureblood lineage hasn't
mixed with the human race
at all since then.
So as the vampire
race increased,
the need for some sort
of sovereign entity
became apparent.
And the Kurans became
the royal family.
-So then he really
is of noble blood.
He didn't act that way at all.
He didn't.
-Two generations back, the
king of the Kuran family
abolished the monarchy to
avoid authoritarianism,
allowing the Senate
to govern us.
-I see.
Yes, that means purebloods
aren't a big deal after all.
-It would be very easy for
them to take control and create
an army.
Do you understand?
That is within their powers.
-So Hanabusa, did
you really refuse
to become friends
with Lord Kaname?
-Huh?
-Akatsuki told me
you met Lord Kaname.
What was he like?
I've heard he's really handsome,
smart, kind, and admirable.
-Not really.
-Good evening.
-Hanabusa, may I
have a word with you?
-I'm doing an experiment to test
the strength of sand materials
right now.
I don't want you interfering.
-It just appears to me I've done
something to make you angry.
All I wanted was to apologize,
so I asked to come back here.
I'm truly sorry.
HANABUSA (VOICEOVER):
Is he stupid?
He didn't do anything wrong.
-Huh?
Oh him, no need to
worry about him.
HANABUSA (VOICEOVER):
A bodyguard.
No, a watchdog.
-You don't need to apologize.
I just hate you, that's all.
HANABUSA (VOICEOVER): Even
though he terrifies everyone,
they still expect
a lot from him.
But he cares for others.
--much more than I do.
MALE SPEAKER: Oh, Lord Kaname.
FEMALE SPEAKER: How terrible.
He lost both his
parents at once.
MALE SPEAKER: A double suicide.
-I-- I just--
-So you're old enough to
attend the soirees now.
-My deepest condolences.
-Thank you.
Yes, you had met my parents.
-I did.
I'm so sorry.
They seemed quite affectionate.
-Yes, they were.
If that's all, Hanabusa--
-Huh?
--goodbye.
-Wait.
I was just wondering, did
something else happen?
-And just why do you ask?
-Nothing.
It was no real reason.
-I expect an answer.
HANABUSA (VOICEOVER): Did he
used to be so frightening?
-You seem different now.
-Oh, that was all.
If you had actually
known something,
I might have had to kill you.
It was a joke.
But a bad joke, huh?
ICHIJO: Lord Kaname,
if you don't mind,
there are people
here who would like
to offer you their sympathies.
-Of course.
I will be right there, Ichijo.
-Sympathy?
Lord Kaname, if you don't
want to do something,
you can say so.
Just tell them--
-Tell me, why do you care?
-Because-- because I'm
your friend, that's why.
-Really?
Because I thought you
told me you hated me.
-I lied.
I hated myself for not
being able to admit
that I-- that I really like you.
Lord Kaname-- please, I--
I love you, Lord Kaname.
HANABUSA (VOICEOVER):
And then my heart
decided I would become someone
who could really protect him.
But Lord Kaname changed
after his parents' deaths.
The aristocrats avoided
talking about it,
as if they were
afraid of something.
Lord Kaname's parents loved
him and cherished him so much.
So why?
Why did they have
to commit suicide?
[crashing]
-What's wrong with you?
-Sorry.
-Don't touch the pieces.
I'll--
-Hold on.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): I'm
not afraid of Zero.
I-- I have to be--
-Here, lick it.
YUKI (VOICEOVER): I'm scared.
I can feel Zero's fangs.
-No, don't resist it.
I understand.
I know how much you
hunger for this.
It's OK.
-Yuki--
YUKI (VOICEOVER): This is
Zero's way of telling me
he's still here, even if he
doesn't know for sure just
what he is right now.
A dull pain.
Blood.
-Just what am I to you, Yuki?
YUKI (VOICEOVER):
What am I to Zero?
His eyes have a
blood-colored luster.
They're the eyes of a vampire.
I'm scared, but I
can't look away.
Why?
-What the hell?
I didn't need to see that.
Zero was possessed by blood.
What is wrong with me?
Why am I worrying about him?
HANABUSA (VOICEOVER): I'm
worried about Lord Kaname.
-Even if he betrays me,
I'd-- I'd be OK with it.
HANABUSA (VOICEOVER):
I feel the same way.
It's true.
Lord Kaname is
planning something.
What I felt back then was--
-That's strange.
What happened to Hanabusa?
He's not here either.
-Maybe he finally
changed his mind
and headed back
to the Moon dorm.
-What?
After making such a big fuss?
He told us he was running away,
but all he really wanted to do
was eat all our food.
-Tell me, what
happened with you?
-Huh?
What do you mean?
Nothing happened at all.
-Quit pretending.
I can tell.
Look, you're uneasy right now.
Stop forcing it.
You don't have to
smile around me.
-I've got so much.
I've got the headmaster,
Kaname, you and Yori.
I've been so lucky.
Yet I still wonder, do you think
my heart will grow stronger
if I become a vampire?
Kaname asked me if I
wanted to become a vampire.
And I--
-You thought that somehow
becoming a vampire
was a good idea.
-Yeah, but Kaname
was just joking.
He wasn't serious about it.
-I will never let
that happen to you.
I don't care if it means
making Kaname my enemy of even
if you hate me for it.
[theme music]