Tanjiro: Naho! Kiyo! Sumi!
Girls: Huh?
Tanjiro: Would you mind
helping me train later?
While I'm sleeping,
if I stop breathing right,
can you hit me
with these carpet beaters?
( Girls murmur )
Tanjiro: I'd appreciate it!
( Girls gasp )
We'll do it!
Tanjiro: Oh, thank you!
( Insects chirping )
( Tanjiro breathing deeply )
Naho: Nothing wrong here.
Kiyo: He's doing a great job.
Sumi: He is.
( Tanjiro snorts )
- ( Girls yelling )
- ( Tanjiro yelps )
( Gurgles )
¶
( singing in Japanese )
Tanjiro: I'm a fool.
Please let me try again!
Girls: Sure!
Tanjiro: Thank you.
Girls: Try your best!
Tanjiro: This is it.
( Deep inhale )
( Snores )
- ( Girls yelling )
- ( Tanjiro yelps )
One more! This time, for sure!
Aoi: It's just you
again today, huh?
Tanjiro: I'm sorry.
I did ask them to come, but...
Aoi: Well,
it doesn't matter to me.
Tanjiro: I'll go
talk to them about it later.
( Grunting )
I'm starting
to get used to training
while doing
total concentration breathing.
I still can't keep it up
for the whole day
unless I really
get myself pumped up.
( Groans )
- Girls: 437...
- Tanjiro: Even so,
the longer I continue doing it,
the greater my stamina becomes.
( Grunting )
¶
Girls: You can do it!
( Tanjiro yells )
( Kanao gasps )
Tanjiro: Look at that.
I'm not far behind her.
I can do this!
( Yells )
( Groans )
( Wails )
( Gasping )
( Bird squawks )
Thank you for your training!
( Bird squawking )
( Aoi grunts )
- Hmph!
- Tanjiro: Eh?
( Bird squawks )
( Both groan )
Tanjiro: Zenitsu! Inosuke!
Aoi: I'm not
helping you with them.
¶
( Tanjiro inhales deeply )
( Blows and grunts )
Girls: Keep at it!
Keep at it! Keep at it!
( Blowing and grunting )
( Girls laugh )
Tanjiro: I did it!
( Girls squeal, laugh )
Naho: Now all you have to do
is break is this huge gourd!
- Tanjiro: Mm-hmm.
- Kiyo: You're doing great!
Tanjiro: What a relief!
Thanks, everyone!
- It's because of you all!
- ( Girls laughing )
Zenitsu: Not good.
( Breathing softly )
( Groans )
( Inosuke snoring )
( Zenitsu groans )
Looks like Tanjiro's
already gone off to train.
And at this hour
of the morning?
Working hard isn't my thing.
Slaving away day in and day out
is exhausting.
( Chuntaro chirps )
Zenitsu: Eh? Chuntaro.
Maybe I'm panicking
because I was left behind,
but I can't seem to get the hang
of anything Tanjiro shows me.
- ( Chuntaro chirps )
- Zenitsu: It must be
because I'm a lost cause,
isn't it?
( Chuntaro chirps )
Zenitsu: Did you
just agree with me?
How can you be so cruel?
Would it kill you
to say something like,
"you're doing your best,"
even just this once?
( Chuntaro chirps )
Zenitsu: "Work harder," you say?
( Sighs ) If you say so.
( Groans )
( Winces )
- ( Chuntaro chirps )
- Zenitsu: Awful.
- ( Sheets rustle )
- ( Chuntaro chirps )
Zenitsu: Huh?
( Singers vocalizing )
Inosuke: Let's go, monitsu.
Shinobu: What Tanjiro
is trying to master
is a skill called
total concentration, constant.
By doing total concentration
breathing all day and all night,
your stamina level
will skyrocket.
( Both murmur )
( Shinobu giggles )
Shall we try our hand at it?
( Zenitsu and Inosuke gasping )
Zenitsu: Impossible!
This is utterly impossible!
Tanjiro: I still can't do total
concentration breathing all day
unless I really
put my mind to it,
but I bet you two can.
Go like this,
and your lungs will expand.
Your blood shakes,
your sinew feels
like "boom! Boom!"
And that's when
you gotta stop.
( Both groan )
Tanjiro: It just takes
lots of practice!
( Both groan )
( Babbling )
( Tanjiro groans )
Shinobu: Come now.
We're talking about a skill
I'd call very elementary,
so what's the problem here?
Though I will say
it does require ample effort.
( Inosuke grunting )
Shinobu: Tell me,
are you not able to do it?
( Inosuke grunts )
Shinobu: I was sure it'd be
child's play for you, Inosuke.
Was I wrong about that?
I guess it was just too much!
Oh, well, then. Don't you worry.
You can't do it,
and that's that!
( Crack )
Inosuke: 'Scuse me?!
Why do you think that?!
I can do it!
Talk to me like that again,
and I'll mess you up big time!
( Zenitsu yelps )
Shinobu: Please give it
your all, Zenitsu.
I'm your number one supporter.
- Zenitsu: Okay!
- ( Shinobu laughs )
( Zenitsu yelling )
( Inosuke grunting )
Shinobu: You're in their class,
so why not join them?
- ( Wind blowing )
- ( Birds chirping )
( Water drips )
- ( Zenitsu grunting )
- Tanjiro: There you go!
Keep going! Feel your blood
beating like a drum! Go!
Inosuke: Stick with it,
you damn weakling!
- Tanjiro: Go!
- ( Zenitsu wailing )
Tanjiro: You got this, Zenitsu!
¶
( flies buzzing )
( Singers vocalizing )
( Young Kanao shuddering )
( Yelps )
( Door shuts )
Kanao: I hurt.
I was hungry.
I was sad.
I felt hopeless.
I was in agony.
I was lonely.
Such was my life.
But then, one day...
I heard a snapping sound...
( Silence )
And I never knew pain again.
Kano: I never knew pain again.
Living in poverty,
even having
my parents sell me off,
it didn't make me feel sad.
( Villagers chattering )
Woman: Excuse me.
Do you have a minute?
Man: Huh?
Slayer: I'm curious.
Why is that child
is all tied up?
Is she a criminal, perhaps?
Man: Isn't it obvious?
She's dirty and flea-ridden.
Besides,
she might try to escape.
Slayer: Hello there.
How are you?
My name is kanae Kocho.
What is your name?
( Gasps )
Man: She doesn't have a name,
all right?
She never got one.
Happy now? Now go away!
( Gasps )
Shinobu: Please
don't touch my sister.
Man: What's the deal
with you two?
If you're so interested in her,
then buy her!
( Shinobu sighs )
Very well, then. We will.
Is this enough?
( Coins clink )
¶
( man gasps )
Hey! Get back here!
Shinobu: You should hurry
and pick all that up!
There's a strong wind
and a hungry crowd.
Kanae: Uh,
are you sure about this?
- Shinobu: Yes.
- Kanae: We must be going now!
Man: Hands off!
This is my money!
Kanae: What a commotion.
Shinobu: Sister, what do we do?!
This little girl
is completely helpless!
Kanae: Hmm?
Shinobu: She can't do
anything on her own.
She has to be told.
She won't even eat
unless I say to,
no matter how hungry she is!
Kanae: Oh, she'll be fine.
Shinobu: What are we
going to do with her?
Kanae: Now, now.
Don't you worry so.
I hate to see
that smile I love disappear.
( Shinobu groans )
I'm serious!
Taking a kid under our wing
who can't even think
for herself is reckless!
Kanae: Well,
you do have a point.
Shinobu: She can't
make decisions,
even simple ones!
Kanae: Next time
you're on your own,
flip this coin
to help you make a choice.
That sound good?
Shinobu: Oh, come on!
Kanae: How can you be
so cross with Kanao here?
Look how adorable she is!
Shinobu: What kind
of reason is that?
Kanae: As long as one
is given a chance,
a person's soul will open up.
When you fall in love someday,
you'll change, too, Kanao.
( Birds chirping )
Tanjiro: You're doing great!
Keep it up!
- ( Inosuke growling )
- Tanjiro: Keep going!
Even more! That's it!
- You got this, Zenitsu!
- ( Zenitsu groaning )
Tanjiro: Don't give up!
You're doing great!
- ( Inosuke yelling )
- ( Zenitsu wailing )
( Kasugai caws )
Tanjiro: Ah.
Inosuke! Inosuke!
Hey, they're bringing our
reforged nichirin swords now!
- Inosuke: For real?
- Tanjiro: Yeah!
I just heard it from the crow!
( Sniffs )
That's Haganezuka's scent!
Inosuke: Yee-hoo!
- ( Laughs ) Whoo!
- Tanjiro: Let's go! Let's go!
- ( Laughs )
- Inosuke: Whoo-hoo!
Tanjiro: Oh, he's right there!
Hey! Haganezuka!
( Bells jingling )
Over here!
Long time, no see!
( Flesh creaks )
Tanjiro:
How have you been since we--
( stammers )
( Haganezuka shrieks )
( Tanjiro gasps )
H-Haganezuka?
Haganezuka: How dare you
snap my precious sword in two?!
You've got a lot of nerve, boy!
Tanjiro: I-I'm sorry!
But, you know,
I-I did almost die.
My opponent was really strong!
Haganezuka: Excuses,
excuses, excuses.
The only person you have
to blame is yourself! Got it?!
If you hadn't been
so pathetically weak,
it wouldn't have broke!
There's no way
it would have just snapped
like that otherwise!
Tanjiro: But I...
Haganezuka:
I'm going to kill you!
( Both screaming )
Haganezuka: Slice you!
( Muttering )
You get back here!
Shinobu: Is this
a new training regimen?
Aoi: I don't think so.
( Bells jingle )
Man: What can I say?
Haganezuka is very passionate.
Tanjiro: He is.
Man: He loves his swords
more than any person.
Even among other sword makers,
he is one of a kind.
Tanjiro: I can believe it.
( Haganezuka grumbles )
Man: Oh, you may
address me as kanamori.
I was the one who forged
Master Inosuke's swords.
I hope they
will be useful in battle.
¶
( Haganezuka grunting )
Kanamori: Ah, beautiful,
aren't they?
The dull sheen of that
indigo-gray hue is wonderful,
a fine color for a sword.
Tanjiro: Inosuke, I'm so happy
you're getting
a great replacement.
Inosuke: Huh?
Kanamori: How do you like
the hilts on them?
This is actually the first time
I've ever forged blades
for a dual-wielder.
( Cheek stretching )
Kanamori: Master Inosuke?
( Tanjiro gasps )
Kanamori: Hmm?
( Inosuke grunting )
- ( Tanjiro wails )
- ( Rock pounding )
Inosuke: Good.
Kanamori:
I'm gonna skin you alive!
You bastard! Are you
trying to provoke me?!
Tanjiro: I'm sorry, sir!
Please forgive him!
( Inosuke grunts )
( Grunting )
- Kanamori: You dirty swine!
- Tanjiro: We're sorry!
Kanamori: That's it!
You're a dead man!
Tanjiro: We're sorry!
Kanamori: Unbelievable!
Just unbelievable!
- Tanjiro: We're sorry...
- Kanamori: I can't believe
he smashed a stone
against my babies!
Tanjiro: We're sorry.
( Breathing deeply )
Naho: No problems here.
Sumi: Tanjiro's
doing a great job!
Kiyo: Let's make him
more rice balls! Yeah!
( Tanjiro breathing deeply )
( Singers vocalizing )
My body's stronger now.
I can't wait to swing
my nichirin sword...
With these hands!
I did it!
( Grunts )
Sumi: Nice move there!
You can win!
( Tanjiro grunts )
Don't let up for a second.
You can do this!
( Yells )
I grabbed it!
Let's go!
This water smells bad.
I shouldn't splash it on her.
( Gasps )
( Grunts )
- Sumi: He got the water!
- Kiyo: It still counts, right?
Naho: Yeah, I think
he still wins either way!
- Tanjiro: Yeah!
- Girls: Yay!
Tanjiro: I did it! I did it!
Both: Well, then...
( Zenitsu yelling )
( Inosuke grunting )
I'm not gonna lose!
Shinobu: All right, say, "ahh"!
Tanjiro: Ahh.
Shinobu: Good!
Looks like your jaw
is as good as new.
You can close your mouth now.
That ends the exam.
Since you're
in physically good health,
you're fit to carry out
your missions now.
Tanjiro: So I'm done training?
Shinobu: Yes.
Next is in-field combat.
Tanjiro: Great!
Oh, before I forget,
there's something
I wanted to ask you.
Shinobu: What is it?
Tanjiro: Have you ever heard
of the hinokami kagura?
Shinobu: I have not.
Tanjiro: Huh?!
I, uh--well, then,
what about fire breathing?
Shinobu: Never heard of it.
( Tanjiro whimpers )
Well, these are techniques
that I learned in my family
growing up.
Shinobu: Mm. Mm-hmm.
I see.
So you're saying your father
seemed to be using
fire breathing.
All I can tell you is that
flame breathing does exist,
but that's not fire breathing.
Tanjiro: Huh?
They're not the same thing?
Shinobu: I don't quite know
the details myself.
I'm sorry. But I do know
that they're very strict
about the exact phrasing.
Flame breathing
must never be referred to
as "fire breathing."
The flame hashira, Rengoku,
might know something
about this technique,
but unfortunately
he's out on a mission.
Tanjiro: I understand.
And thank you for everything
that you've taught me.
I'll ask Mr. Rengoku
when I see him again.
- Shinobu: Good.
- Tanjiro: For now, I'll be off.
- Shinobu: Tanjiro.
- Tanjiro: Yes?
Shinobu: You'll do great things.
( Tanjiro sighs )
Thanks!
( Insects chirping )
( Door slides )
She still hasn't gotten up.
I know that they said you could
sleep as much as you wanted
to recover all your strength.
Even so, when you
don't open your eyes,
I worry a bit.
( Nezuko breathing softly )
( Tanjiro sighs )
Guess what? In not too long,
I'll be leaving this place.
My body's healed,
and I'm stronger.
I'm still practicing
the new techniques, too.
And those two
should be with me as well.
Having them close
gives me courage.
( Sighs )
Yeah.
I'm sure you'd agree...
They're both good people.
To turn you back into a human,
I have to defeat strong demons
and then send their blood
to miss Tamayo.
Am I capable of doing that?
Nezuko: I know you can do it,
big brother.
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Nezuko breathing softly )
¶
Tanjiro: Thanks, Nezuko,
for spurring me on.
I vow to stay strong.
( Train whistle blows )
( Woman screams )
( Chorus vocalizing )
¶
( singing in Japanese )