( Tanjiro gasps )
( Man gasping )
Woman: Oh?
What's going on?
Are you all right, sweetheart?
( Man gurgling )
Woman: You look pale.
( Demon roars )
Tanjiro: No! Stop!
( Demon growling )
( Woman screaming )
¶
( singing in Japanese )
( woman screams )
- ( Crowd murmuring )
- Man 2: What is it?
- Man 3: What's wrong?
- Woman 2: Is that blood?
( Demon growling )
Tanjiro: Stop! No!
¶
( demon growling )
Woman 1: No! Sweetheart!
Tanjiro: Listen!
You need to worry
about yourself, ma'am!
Cover that wound, and apply
as much pressure as you can!
( Demon growling )
Tanjiro: It's all right.
It'll all turn out fine.
The woman's wound
doesn't look fatal.
Press down harder!
It needs more pressure!
Tie it down with a rope!
It's gonna be okay.
This man
hasn't killed anyone yet.
( Demon growling )
Tanjiro: A few seconds ago,
this guy was
minding his own business,
walking down the street!
( Girl crying )
Kibutsuji: Are you all right?
Don't look, okay?
Rei, I think we should go.
It's not safe.
Tanjiro: Where is he?
( Demon grunting )
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Singers vocalizing )
Tanjiro: Damn.
Damn it all!
I can't leave
this man alone here.
Muzan kibutsuji!
No matter where you go,
I promise you won't escape me!
Rei: What's the matter
with that boy, tsukihiko?
Tsukihiko?
Tanjiro: You can run
as far as you want!
I'll follow you
to the ends of hell,
and my blade will be
the last thing you see!
I'll never forgive you
for what you've done!
Officer: What the hell's
going on over here?
Officer 2: Another drunk.
Officer 3: Step away
from that man right now, kid!
Tanjiro: I can't!
Bring restraints
to hold him down! Quickly!
Officer 2:
Get away from him. Get up!
Tanjiro: Please don't do that!
I'm the only one
who can hold him back!
- Officer 3: Get off!
- Tanjiro: I'm begging you, no!
( Officer 2 gasps )
Get a load of this guy's face.
Looks like he's lost his mind!
Officer 1: Help me
get the kid off him!
Tanjiro: Let me go! I don't want
to let this person kill anybody!
Just stay out of the way!
Someone could get hurt!
Officer 1: Damn it.
Listen to me!
If you keep resisting,
I'll have to use force.
¶
( tanjiro gasps )
Woman 3:
Scent of illusory blood.
Visual dream.
Tanjiro: That smell, what is it?
Officer 1: Huh?
What's with the flowers?
( Crowd gasping )
Officer 2: The hell is this?!
I can't see anything!
Tanjiro: Some kind of spell?
That could mean trouble.
The smell's getting stronger.
Woman 3: I beg your pardon,
but you said, "person,"
even though
this particular person
is now a demon,
and now you're
trying to save him.
So, if you don't mind,
I'd like to lend you a hand.
Tanjiro: Why in the world
would you--
your scent. I know what you are.
Woman 3: You do. I'm a demon.
But I am also a doctor.
I want to help,
and I want
to destroy kibutsuji as well.
( Overlapping chatter )
Girl: You're not
coming with us, daddy?
Kibutsuji: No,
daddy has work to do.
I have to go to a boring
old business meeting,
and I'm worried
about what just happened.
Rei: Oh, darling.
Kibutsuji: Not to worry.
I'm just going down
to check in with the police.
Now hop in.
( Door closes )
Girl: Promise you'll
come home soon, okay, daddy?
Kibutsuji: I will.
Be a good girl for mommy.
Take them back to the house.
Quickly, please.
Man: Come on! Let's hit
one more bar! ( Laughs )
Woman: Are you
feeling all right there?
Man: Yeah, I'm fine! ( Laughs )
I'm not even
a little bit drunk yet--huh?
Hey, what the hell
are you doing, mister?
Kibutsuji: Apologies.
Man: Where you goin'?
Kibutsuji: I'm terribly sorry,
but I'm in a bit of a hurry.
Man: What the hell'd
you say to me?
Look at you, all decked out
in your fancy-pants clothes.
You're pissin' me off,
you and your stupid pale face.
You look like you're
about to fall over dead.
¶
aren't you gonna say anything,
or did you just croak?
Hmm?
( Woman shrieks ) No!
Man 2: What'd you do
to my kid brother?
Woman: No! He's dead!
This monster killed him!
( Man 2 gasps )
( Growls ) You bast--
( woman gasps )
¶
( man 2 gags )
( Woman gasping )
Kibutsuji: So does my complexion
look at all unhealthy to you?
Does my face
seem unusually pale?
Do I look a bit sickly?
Does it appear
I'm not long for this world?
Do you fear for my life?
You couldn't
possibly be more wrong.
I'm very much alive
and not far from perfection.
( Woman gags )
Kibutsuji: What do you
think would happen
if I gave you
a constant stream of my blood?
( Woman babbling )
Kibutsuji: The human body
is unable to withstand
such a rapid transformation.
( Woman gags )
( Groaning )
Kibutsuji: And its cells
are destroyed.
( Woman gags )
¶
Kibutsuji:
There's a demon slayer
who wears hanafuda earrings.
I want you to bring me his head.
Got that?
Demon: Yes.
Demon 2: As you wish.
¶
Kibutsuji: Hanafuda earrings.
( Singers vocalizing )
To me, all right?!
It has nothing
to do with money!
That's not the problem here!
I just can't forgive the fact
that you would walk away
from a perfectly good
bowl of udon!
Tanjiro: I'm so sorry!
Can I please have another one?
- Shopkeeper: To eat?
- Tanjiro: Yes!
Shopkeeper: You promise?
Tanjiro: I promise!
Shopkeeper: All right.
What about you?
If you're eating udon,
you better take off
that bamboo thingie!
What the heck is it, anyway?
Now take these chopsticks,
all right?!
Tanjiro: I'd like
a bowl of udon!
In fact, give me two of 'em!
Shopkeeper: Uh, okay.
¶
( gasps )
( Tanjiro sighs )
( Slurping )
Thanks for the great meal!
It was delicious!
Shopkeeper:
I'm glad you liked it!
Come back again!
Anytime!
Tanjiro: I'm so sorry, nezuko.
I left you behind.
- ( Nezuko grunts )
- Tanjiro: Eh?
- What is it? What's wrong?
- ( Nezuko growls )
( Tanjiro gasps )
Are you out here
waiting for us?
Boy: I'm here on her orders.
I'm supposed
to bring you back with me.
Tanjiro: You know, I could
have just tracked your scent.
Boy: Our hiding place
is protected
by a concealment spell.
You'd never have found it.
Tanjiro: Concealment?
Boy: Before we go,
did you know that girl
is a demon?
And not much to look at.
Tanjiro: What was that?
Did he just--
doesn't that mean ugly?
But who--
¶
nezuko?!
You've gotta be
out of your mind!
Who would look at nezuko
and think she's ugly?!
She was the most beautiful girl
in our whole town!
You know that?!
- Boy: Let's go.
- Tanjiro: I know!
We're already coming!
But take back
what you said about her!
You just need
to get a good look at her
somewhere with better lighting!
Come on! Over there! Let's go!
I know what it is!
It's this stupid muzzle!
That's the only explanation.
You just need
to behold nezuko's beauty
when she's not wearing
this ugly thing!
Huh?
Boy: Hurry it up,
while nobody's looking.
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Gasps )
I could have sworn
that street was a dead end.
Boy: Pay attention!
Now, make sure you don't
offend the lady in any way,
because I couldn't care less
what happens to you.
I only brought you here
because she insisted. Got it?
Tanjiro: Uh, okay, sure.
( Knock on door )
Doctor: Come in.
Boy: I've returned, my lady.
Doctor: I'm glad you made it.
Tanjiro: I'm sorry
that I left everything
for you to take care of.
So how's she doing?
Doctor: She'll make
a full recovery.
But her husband
has to be locked up.
He's restrained
in the basement.
Tanjiro: Isn't it difficult
treating humans?
All of that blood...
( Groans )
Boy: Is that what you think,
she chokes back her own drool
when she treats a human?
'Cause demons
can't control themselves?
Tanjiro: Sorry.
Doctor: Don't do that.
Why would you
resort to violence?
( Boy sighs )
Doctor: Did I ever
introduce myself?
Apologies. My name is tamayo,
and this is yushiro.
I hope you two can be friends.
( Both gasps )
( Yushiro muttering )
Tanjiro: That seems unlikely.
Tamayo: It's not
all that difficult,
at least, not for me,
but it's different
for other demons.
My body's physiology has gone
through considerable changes,
and I've removed
kibutsuji's curse.
Tanjiro: What curse?
And what kind of changes?
Tamayo: Come with me.
( Nezuko sighs )
Tanjiro: Hey, nezuko,
that's bad manners.
( Tamayo chuckles )
It's quite all right.
Make yourselves at home.
Tanjiro: Sorry about that.
Tamayo: As I was saying,
I made several adjustments
to our bodies so that we
could continue to live
without harming
any human beings.
We can survive on just
a small amount of human blood.
Tanjiro: Wait. Blood?
So you're saying...
Tamayo: I understand
if you find it distasteful,
but I buy it
from those in poverty.
I tell them
I'll use it for transfusions.
But, of course, I never take
enough blood to impair anyone.
Tanjiro: No wonder.
That would explain
why neither one of them
has the same scent
as a normal demon.
Except, they still
need human blood.
If that's the case,
what about nezuko?
Tamayo: And yushiro needs
even less blood than I do,
since I'm the one
who turned him into a demon.
- Tanjiro: Huh? You turned him?
- ( Nezuko grunts )
Tanjiro: But how?
Tamayo: How did I do it?
As far as anyone knows,
kibutsuji is the only one
who can create demons,
and that's
more or less accurate.
It took me over 200 years,
and, after all that,
I could only transform yushiro.
- Tanjiro: Two...
- ( Nezuko grunts )
Tanjiro: 200 years?
It took you 200 years
before you could figure out
how to transform
just one person?!
How old are you,
miss tamayo?! ( Groans )
Yushiro: You should know better
than to ask a lady her age!
Tanjiro: Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Tamayo: Yushiro,
if you hit that boy again,
I'll make you regret it.
Yushiro: Yes, ma'am!
She's beautiful,
even when she's angry.
( Tanjiro coughs )
Tamayo: I'm sorry.
I'd like
to clarify that further.
Creating more demons
is not one of my goals.
And I only do so
when necessary,
the terminally ill or injured,
only when they won't survive.
And, even in those cases,
I always ask in advance
if they truly prefer
to live on as a demon.
( Tanjiro sniffs )
Her scent is pure.
No sign of deception.
I think I can trust her.
( Fists creak )
Miss tamayo...
Once someone becomes a demon,
is there a way
to turn them back again?
( Singers vocalizing )
( Ball bouncing, ringing )
( Demon 1 sighs )
Hmm?
Demon 2: You see anything?
Demon 1: Yes.
I can see their footprints.
No question, this is it.
They make a sharp turn
right over there...
Three of them, headed that way.
One's carrying
some kind of oversized box.
( Ball rings )
Demon 2: I wonder how
we should kill them. ( Laughs )
I can feel the power.
I can feel the blood he gave me
coursing through my veins.
Demon 1: And of course
we're going to be ruthless
when we kill them.
Tamayo: A way to make
a demon turn human again?
There is.
( Tanjiro gasps )
Please tell me how--
yushiro: You keep your distance
from lady tamayo!
Tamayo: Yushiro.
( Yushiro gasps ) I'm sorry.
I only threw him.
I didn't hit him.
- Tamayo: Neither is acceptable.
- Yushiro: Right!
Tanjiro: Ah, man,
that really smarts.
Can you please tell me how?
Tamayo: There's always
some kind of medicine or aid,
no matter the wound or ailment.
I don't know how to turn
a demon back into a human yet,
but there must be a way.
( Tanjiro sighs )
Tamayo: And I promise
we are going to find it.
We are dedicated to establishing
such a treatment.
Toward that end, I'd like to
ask you to do something for me.
In order to discover a cure,
the first step
is studying the blood
of several different demons,
which means
I have two favors to ask you.
First, I'd like permission
to study your sister's blood.
Second, I need more samples.
I'd like you
to retrieve them from demons
as closely related
to kibutsuji as possible.
Nezuko's condition
is extremely rare,
perhaps entirely unique.
I understand she was asleep
for two straight years.
I believe her body changed
during that time.
In most cases,
that long without food,
neither human flesh
nor even the blood
of some kind of animal,
any demon would
undoubtedly grow violent.
Yushiro: Lady tamayo
is as beautiful as ever.
She'll be
even more beautiful tomorrow.
Tamayo: However,
against all odds,
nezuko is showing
none of those signs.
That miracle could be
the key to finding a solution.
Tanjiro: Nezuko.
( Nezuko grunts )
( Chuckles )
Tamayo: But my second request
is not a simple one.
When I say, "demons closely
related to kibutsuji,"
I mean demons with powers
such like those
of kibutsuji himself.
Extracting blood from that kind
of demon won't be easy.
What do you think?
Are these requests acceptable,
if not pleasant?
Tanjiro: If it's really
the only way, then I'll do it.
Besides, if you research
all that blood
and you can create
this medicine,
then it won't
just be nezuko, will it?
A whole lot of other people
will be saved, too.
Tamayo: Ah.
Yes, they will.
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Yushiro growling )
( Gasps ) Get down!
¶
- ( Balls ring )
- ( Demon 2 laughs )
( Demon 1 chuckles )
Did you decide
how we'll kill them?
Demon 2: Ruthlessly!
Hah! Hah!
( Laughs )
( Demon 1 growls )
( Yushiro gasps )
¶
( singing in Japanese )