( Ball ringing )
Susamaru: I wonder how
we should kill them. ( Laughs )
I can feel the power.
I can feel the blood he gave me
coursing through my veins.
Yahaba: And of course
we're going to be ruthless
when we kill them.
( Yushiro gasps ) Get down!
¶
- ( Balls ring )
- ( Susamaru laughs )
( Yahaba chuckles )
Did you decide
how we'll kill them?
Susamaru: Ruthlessly!
Hah! Hah!
( Laughs )
( Yahaba growls )
( Yushiro gasps )
¶
( singing in japanese )
( house rumbling )
( Ball rings )
( Susamaru laughs )
Turns out
you were right, yahaba.
This building just materialized
out of nowhere.
Yahaba: Huh.
The handiwork of someone
using a blood demon art
that can hide objects.
What is this?
We're tracking down
a demon slayer.
Is he with demons?
( Susamaru laughs )
Isn't this fun?
( Balls ring )
Yahaba: I have to say, susamaru,
your way of doing things
is just so immature,
utterly careless.
You splattered me.
My kimono is covered with dust.
Susamaru: Oh, stop whining.
Who cares about dust?
My temari just uncovered
their hiding place.
And now the real fun begins!
( Temari ring )
( Yahaba growls )
Stop splattering me!
Susamaru: Stop being so uptight.
Your kimono
looks just fine to me.
And look.
( Laughs )
Come out, come out,
wherever you are.
Tanjiro: A temari?
Throwing a temari
caused all this damage?
Yushiro: That woman,
did kibutsuji send her?
( Susamaru laughs )
Hah!
( Singers vocalizing )
Yushiro: Lady tamayo! ( Gasps )
Tanjiro: Yushiro!
Damn it!
Nezuko, the lady
sleeping in the back room,
take her outside,
and get her to safety!
( Nezuko grunts )
Tamayo: It's too dangerous!
We have a basement!
Take her there!
Tanjiro: Good idea.
- Nezuko.
- ( Nezuko grunts )
( Susamaru laughs )
One down. Three to go.
Tanjiro: Her scent is different
than any other demon
I've ever met.
It's stronger or thicker.
It feels heavy inside my lungs.
( Temari ringing )
Susamaru: Hmm.
There's a demon slayer
who wears hanafuda earrings.
That would be you, right?
( Tanjiro gasps )
They're targeting me?
Miss tamayo, I want you
to go find a place to hide!
These demons are after me.
Tamayo: No, tanjiro.
You need to focus on the fight.
Don't worry about us.
We'll be just fine
without your protection.
We're demons, too.
Susamaru: All righty.
It's all over for you!
Tanjiro: It'll only swerve
if I dodge it.
The fastest thrusting technique
of all ten forms.
Total concentration.
Water breathing!
Seventh form! Drop ripple...
Thrust-curve!
( Splashing )
Susamaru: Oh?
You think you can soften
the temari's blow
by stabbing it like that?
How cute.
( Rattling )
( Tanjiro groans )
How does it
move around like that?
It did the same kind
of weird swerve
when it hit yushiro, too.
She doesn't seem to be
putting any spin on it, though,
so how?
Tamayo: Yushiro.
Yushiro!
( Squelching )
( Yushiro grunting )
( Tanjiro gasps )
Yushiro: Lady tamayo!
I tried to tell you, didn't I?
I said not to get involved
with a demon slayer,
and I was right!
My concealment spell
is still a work in progress.
You should have known that
just as well as I do.
I may be able
to conceal buildings
and people and their scent,
but it's not like I can hide
the fact that they exist!
( Tamayo grunts )
Yushiro:
The greater our numbers,
the more traces we leave,
and the greater the odds
that kibutsuji will find us!
Tanjiro: Those demons
got so close to us,
but there was no scent
until they attacked.
Was that yushiro's
blood demon art?
Yushiro: I hate
anyone who gets in the way
of the time I spend alone
with you. I despise them!
I loathe them with passion!
It's unforgivable!
( Susamaru laughs )
That one's babbling now.
Who's having fun?
I know I sure am.
You're about to be killed
by one of the twelve kizuki.
Doesn't that
make you feel special?
Tanjiro: Twelve kizuki?
Tamayo: They're directly
under kibutsuji.
( Susamaru laughs )
Tanjiro: That's a lot of arms.
( Temari ringing )
Susamaru: Now, then,
let the games continue
until morning comes,
until you're all dead!
( Yushiro winces )
Tamayo: If I were to cast
my spell right now,
it would affect tanjiro as well,
and yushiro needs time in order
to switch to attack mode,
but if this goes on...
Tanjiro: It happened again.
They change directions,
even without hitting anything.
( Groans )
If I cut them in half,
it blunts the blow,
but they still hit me anyway.
¶
two different scents of blood.
There are two demons,
and the scent
tells me where they are,
but I can't...
Miss tamayo! Yushiro, no!
It's no use.
I don't have time
to protect them!
Tamayo: We'll heal ourselves
soon enough!
Don't worry about us!
Yushiro: Hey,
idiot demon slayer,
the arrows will tell you
which direction they're going,
so dodge the arrows!
Tanjiro: What arrows?
Yushiro: Seriously?
You're telling me
you can't see them?
I'm lending you
my sense of sight!
That should at least
give you the chance
to kill the temari woman!
( Tanjiro gasps )
I see them now.
She was using these arrows
to control the temari.
That explains it!
Thanks a lot, yushiro!
I can see the arrows!
That helps!
Yushiro: Then, hurry up,
and get rid of her!
Tanjiro: Nezuko,
let's go outside!
Take care of the one
in the tree!
( Nezuko grunts )
( Temari ring )
Tanjiro: I'm the one
you came here for.
Susamaru: You are
the demon slayer
who wears hanafuda earrings.
I knew it.
I'm going to take off that head
of yours and bring it to him.
( Laughs )
This is so much fun!
¶
tanjiro: Nezuko, hurry up.
( Nezuko gasps )
( Yahaba gasps )
Tanjiro: They're gone!
Water breathing.
Hyah!
Third form! Flowing dance!
Miss tamayo, are these two
closely related to kibutsuji?
Tamayo: Possibly.
Tanjiro: That's what I thought.
Looks like we found
your first blood samples!
Bles )
Tamayo: Which means
I have two favors to ask you.
First, I'd like permission
to study your sister's blood.
Second, I need more samples.
I'd like you
to retrieve them from demons
as closely related
to kibutsuji as possible.
When I say, "demons closely
related to kibutsuji,"
I mean demons with powers
such like those
of kibutsuji himself.
Extracting blood from that kind
of demon won't be easy.
Tanjiro: Third form!
Flowing dance!
Miss tamayo,
are these two closely related
to kibutsuji?
Tamayo: Possibly.
( Flesh crackling )
( Susamaru laughs )
You think you'll be
able to take blood from us?
I'm not really sure what kind
of schemes you're up to,
but there's no way
I'm going to let you
do anything that will
displease him whatsoever.
( Tanjiro gasps )
Susamaru: If you want blood
from the twelve kizuki,
then give it a shot.
Let's see if you can!
Yushiro: Watch your back!
Don't let your guard down!
If they really are
some of the twelve kizuki,
don't underestimate them.
They're more powerful
than any other demon
you've faced before!
Tanjiro: Right! I understand!
Keep my guard up.
I'll watch my back,
be careful, and breathe.
'Kay! Here I go!
Yushiro: Lady tamayo...
Let's escape
while they're all distracted.
( Tamayo gasps )
Yushiro: I'm just kidding!
( Yahaba gasps )
( Groans )
Stop stirring up so much dust.
You're filthy!
( Nezuko gasps )
( Susamaru laughs )
( Singers vocalizing )
Tanjiro: That didn't take long.
She can regenerate so fast.
The demons
during final selection
were a lot slower than this.
Susamaru: He'll be so happy
having your head as a trophy.
( Tanjiro gasps )
Nezuko!
( Yahaba grunts )
Susamaru: Good!
You can both die together!
( Yells )
Tanjiro: You all right, nezuko?
Yushiro: Hey, demon slayer!
We're gonna need you to deal
with the arrow guy first!
Let the rest of us
take care of the temari woman!
Tanjiro: Understood!
Nezuko,
don't push yourself too hard.
( Nezuko grunts )
( Wood clattering )
( Nezuko sighs )
( Growls )
¶
tanjiro: Go get her.
All right.
Time to get those blood samples!
I'll fight any demon I have to
if it means
the medicine'll be finished
even one minute sooner,
and I'll beat them all!
( Thread rings )
Got it! The opening thread!
( Yahaba scoffs )
What a grimy little urchin
you are.
Don't come anywhere near me!
Tanjiro: What the--
it snapped!
¶
( tanjiro yelps )
( Groans )
That hurts!
I mean, that really hurts!
Whaah!
I need a move.
I've gotta do something
to blunt the attack!
Eighth form! Waterfall basin!
¶
( Susamaru laughs )
Where is he?
( Yushiro yells )
( Susamaru groans )
Yushiro: Lady tamayo
is in pain because of you.
I can't forgive that!
Yahaba: Tamayo?
Susamaru,
can you believe our luck?
We found tamayo, the fugitive.
She'll make quite a souvenir.
Susamaru: Yes, she will.
- Yushiro: Don't!
- Tamayo: You can't kick them!
( Susamaru laughs )
- ( Temari ringing )
- Honestly,
this is really too much fun.
Are we playing kickball?
Yahaba, you think four heads
will be enough
for us to take home?
Yahaba: Too many.
We only need two,
demon slayer and the fugitive.
We have no use for the others.
( Tanjiro gasps )
Tamayo: Oh, no.
The bleeding isn't stopping.
She recovers slowly.
Take this medicine.
It'll help your leg heal faster.
( Nezuko sighs )
¶
tanjiro: What do I do?
I can't lose this fight.
But even if I can see
the opening thread,
hitting him won't be easy.
Any move is pointless
unless I can hit his opening.
I'm gonna need
pinpoint precision!
If I'm the slightest bit off,
the move's not going
to be powerful enough.
But the problem is
his arrows can change
the sword's direction.
And what's with
the eyeballs on his hands?
They're really creeping me out!
So weird!
Yahaba: Hah. ( Laughs )
Tanjiro: These things
are so fast.
It doesn't look like they'll
go away until they hit me,
and my sword
won't do anything to them.
As soon as the blade touches it,
the arrow carries me away again!
( Yelps )
( Groans )
What can I do?
( Yahaba chuckles )
It's all going
just how I planned!
I'll be taking that arm!
( Creaking )
( Tanjiro groans )
Yahaba: Clever of you to spin
the same direction
as the kouketsu arrow.
Damn monkey.
Tanjiro: I can't take a whole
lot more of these attacks.
I gotta get to him!
Somehow I need to change
the direction of the arrows
without touching them!
( Yahaba growls )
Time for you to die!
Tanjiro: I'll adapt my moves.
First, the sixth form
to envelop the arrow!
Then I'll use the footwork
of the third form...
And close in on him!
¶
( yells )
Twist! Envelop!
Twisting whirlpool!
Flowing water!
( Yahaba groans )
( Tanjiro groaning )
My sword is so heavy.
But I've got this!
Second form improved!
Lateral water wheel!
( Yahaba gags )
¶
( singing in japanese )