( Tanjiro gasps )
( Groaning )
¶
No way. My sword!
( Singing in Japanese )
¶
( chorus vocalizing )
( Inosuke panting )
Incredible.
He's on a whole other level.
The force of his strike alone
is in a class of its own.
He cut through
that tough-as-nails monster
like it was tofu!
Amazing.
That was absolutely amazing!
Who even is this guy?
I still have goose bumps!
( Women vocalizing )
- ( Pop )
- ( Music stops )
Inosuke: Hold on a second!
Fight me, Mr. Mismatched outfit!
You beat that member
of the twelve kizuki,
and now, right here,
I'm gonna beat you!
If I can manage that...
That'll make me
the most powerful of all!
Tomioka: I have a better idea.
Go train more.
¶
Inosuke: What'd you say to me?!
Tomioka: That wasn't
one of the twelve kizuki.
Could you not even tell that?
Inosuke: Of course I could tell!
For your information,
it was Tanjiro who was
saying it was one of 'em!
I was just repeating
what he said to me earlier.
I knew that amateur couldn't
have been one of those guys!
( Stammers ) What the hell?
When did he tie me up?
I see it's not just a sword
he's quick with.
Hey, you, get back here!
Tomioka: If you are not aware
of what state your body is in,
you shouldn't be fighting.
Inosuke: Huh?! I can't hear you!
Your voice is too soft,
and you're walking too fast!
I said hold your horses!
Untie these ropes right now!
Get me down!
( Zenitsu inhales )
( Exhales )
( Inhales )
Shinobu: I said hello there!
You can hear me, can't you?
Zenitsu: Thanks, gramps.
Shinobu: Are you
calling me gramps?
Zenitsu: Just now,
gramps showed up
and told me
not to give up ever.
Shinobu: Ah! Your life
flashed before your eyes.
You know,
according to one theory,
the reason you see images
like that just before death
is because you're searching
for a way to avoid death
by going through all your
past experiences and memories.
Truthfully,
I can't speak from experience,
as it's never happened to me.
Good. I can tell
you slowed the poison
by adjusting your breathing.
If you weren't able to do that,
you would have already
turned into a spider.
I'll inject you
with the antidote now.
( Zenitsu winces )
Woman: Hurry!
This way! Over here!
- Man: Can we get them down?
- Woman: Be careful with them.
Man: Good.
They're all still alive!
¶
( Tanjiro panting )
My sword's been broken.
I can't believe it!
Are those threads
he's controlling even tougher
than that demon whose body
I couldn't cut through?
Urokodaki...
Haganezuka, forgive me.
Thanks to my inexperience,
my sword is now shattered.
Now's not the time
to feel sorry for yourself.
Now's the time to think!
If I can't cut those threads,
then I'll just
have to meet him head-on!
It's like those threads
have a life of their own
and are refusing
to let me get close.
Even though he's holding back
so as not to kill me,
he's overpowering me
all the same!
Rui: What now?
Do you still refuse to take back
what you said earlier?
You refuse? Fine.
I'll put an end to you now.
Tanjiro: I can't dodge this!
¶
( Rui gasps )
( Tanjiro gasps )
Nezuko!
( Nezuko gasping )
Tanjiro: Nezuko, hang in there.
You protected me. Thank you.
Sister: The girl
emerged from that box
and defended him.
But I'm sure she's one of us.
( Gasps )
¶
Rui: That girl...
Is she--
( shudders ) Is--
is she your sibling?
Tanjiro: And so what if she is?
The cut is so deep,
her left wrist
is about to fall off.
( Nezuko groaning )
Tanjiro: Come on!
Heal up already!
It has to heal!
Rui: Siblings. Siblings.
His sister's
been turned into a demon,
- yet she stays by his side.
- Sister: Rui.
Rui: She risked her own life
to protect him.
That is a genuine bond,
and it'll be mine!
Sister: Rui! Hold on a second!
Please reconsider!
I'm your elder sister!
You can't abandon me!
- Rui: Shut up!
- ( Sister yelps )
( Tanjiro gasps )
Rui: None of you
were ever able to fulfill
the roles you were assigned,
not once in your entire life.
Sister: Wait. Brother,
wasn't I the elder sister
that you wanted?
Give me another chance.
Rui: Very well, then.
Go kill the humans wandering
all over this mountain.
If you do that, I'll forgive you
for what just happened.
Sister: A-all right.
Yes, I'll do that.
( Gasps )
- Rui: Boy...
- ( Tanjiro gasps )
Rui: Let's talk,
just the two of us.
Come on out.
( Nezuko grunting )
Tanjiro: Why is he
being so friendly?
Rui: The truth is,
what your sister did,
I found it
genuinely moving to behold.
I doubt any words exist that
describe exactly how I felt.
However,
your fate now is death,
a disagreeable conclusion
for you, no doubt.
So listen close.
I'll impart to you
how you can escape your fate.
It involves your sister.
I want you to give her to me.
If you do so,
then I will spare your life.
( Tanjiro gasps )
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Rui: As of today, instead
of being your little sister,
she's mine.
Tanjiro:
You don't actually think
I'd ever agree to that, do you?
First off, Nezuko's not a thing!
She has her own will
and feelings!
There's no way
she'll ever be your sister!
Rui: It's all right.
You don't need to worry.
I'm stronger than you.
I will create a bond with her,
one made of terror.
She'll know what happens
when I'm defied.
Tanjiro: I've had enough of you
spouting this nonsense!
Using fear to keep someone
shackled to you
isn't the bond of a family,
and until you are able
to figure that out,
you'll never get
what it is you desire!
Rui: So irritating.
Would you mind not shouting?
It's clear we don't agree.
¶
Tanjiro: I'll never
hand Nezuko over to you!
Rui: Very well, then.
I'll just kill you.
Tanjiro: Not if I manage
to cut your head off first!
Rui: Now, that's the spirit.
I would love to see you try it.
Let's see if you can
take down a being like me,
one of the twelve kizuki.
I: In a family,
the father has
his designated role to fulfill,
and the mother has hers in turn.
The parents protect
their eldest children,
and the eldest
protect the younger ones.
This is carried out,
no matter what,
even at the risk
of their own lives.
The way I see it,
if you don't understand
your own role in this life,
there's no reason
in living it to begin with.
As for you,
I'll tell you your role.
It is to relinquish
your younger sister to me
and disappear.
If you refuse,
your only other path is death,
for you cannot defeat me.
Tanjiro: His eye
says "lower five."
As I thought.
This power--
he really is one of the twelve.
It won't be easy
to cut those threads,
but what do I do
if his neck is even tougher?
Not to mention my broken sword.
Rui: That steely look
in your eyes,
I don't like it.
What are you plotting?
Don't tell me...
That you think
you'll be able to defeat me!
( Tanjiro gasps )
¶
Nezuko!
Rui: It's settled.
I'll be taking her.
You understand your role now,
don't you?
Tanjiro: Let her go!
Rui: Did I not I tell you
that I'd spare your life
in return for your obedience?
( Nezuko growls )
( Tanjiro yells )
( Gasps )
( Chorus vocalizing )
Tanjiro: Where'd she go?
( Gasps )
¶
n-Nezuko!
( Nezuko whimpers )
Rui: Quiet down.
This won't be enough
to kill her.
She's a demon.
But it does appear
I'll have to teach her a lesson.
I'm going to let her bleed
for a while.
If she won't learn
to be obedient,
I'll just leave her like that
until daybreak
and then let her burn.
Tanjiro: I won't allow it!
Let her go!
( Grunting )
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Gagging )
( Coughs )
( Panting )
Rui: Now, I may be
mistaken here...
But you think,
if you get close enough to me,
you can chop my head off,
don't you?
Well, then, here.
Give it a shot.
( Clang )
( Tanjiro gasps )
The blade, it won't go through!
( Grunting )
Rui: Didn't I tell you?
You have no chance against me.
My body is more durable
than any of the threads
I can manipulate.
If you can't even cut
those threads,
then you'll never
be able to cut my neck.
( Nezuko grunting )
( Tanjiro coughs )
( Thinking )
He's incredibly strong.
His strength is beyond any other
demon I've fought so far.
So this is the might
of the twelve kizuki,
the power of a demon
closely related to Kibutsuji.
( Nezuko grunting )
Rui: You're noisy.
If you don't quiet down...
( Nezuko gasps )
( Shrieks )
Tanjiro: No! Stop that!
Rui: As of today,
I'm her elder brother,
and I command
she cease that noise.
( Tanjiro groans )
¶
calm down. Don't get emotional.
If you do, you'll play
right into his hands.
( Nezuko sighs )
Rui: Huh? What happened to her?
Did she pass out?
This demon has a unique aura.
I haven't seen
anything quite like it.
Fascinating.
Tanjiro: Concentrate.
Control your breathing.
Unleash the most precise
final form!
Total concentration!
( Rui scoffs )
Don't you see this is futile?
( Gasps )
Tanjiro: Water breathing!
Tenth form...
Constant flux!
( Dragon roars )
Tanjiro: I did it!
I cut the threads!
Rui: Gathering force
with each rotation.
This could be worrisome.
Tanjiro: If I can keep closing
the distance between us,
I can defeat him!
( Dragon roars )
Rui: Boy, you don't
think these threads
are at maximum strength, do you?
Blood demon art.
Cutting thread cage.
I have no more use for you.
Farewell.
( Dragon shrieks )
Tanjiro: Not good.
I can't get enough rotations in
to cut away these threads.
They're giving off
a totally different scent
than the other ones.
This can't be
how it ends, can it?
Am I really gonna die here?
Am I?
¶
( Children laughing )
( Bells jingling )
( Drum pounding )
¶
Tanjiro: Father.
Tanjuro: Tanjiro...
Your breathing.
Master your command over it,
and then become
more like hinokami.
( Heart beats )
( Woman singing in Japanese )
¶
Kie: Look, Tanjiro.
That is
your father's kagura dance.
Our family works with fire,
so to ward off
injuries and disasters,
we offer this dance to hinokami
along with our prayers
at the start of each year.
( Bells rattling )
Tanjiro: Um, mommy?
Kie: Hmm?
Tanjiro: Father's always
been pretty sick, right?
So how can he be
out in the snow
and still
keep dancing and dancing?
If that were me,
I bet my lungs would freeze.
Tanjuro: There exists
a breathing technique,
one that will prevent you
from ever exhausting yourself.
Tanjiro: Really?
Tanjuro: Yes.
If you can master
the correct way to breathe,
you'll be able
to dance forever, too.
Even the cold won't bother you.
Tanjiro...
This ceremonial dance
and pair of earrings,
I wish for them
to be passed down to you.
This is my gift.
¶
( woman singing in Japanese )
( Tanjiro inhales )
Hinokami kagura...
Dance!
Rui: My threads. ( Gasps )
Tanjiro: Don't stop.
Keep running!
If you hesitate
and switch between
different breathing techniques,
there'll be repercussions!
If that happens, I'll be
rendered immobile for a time!
That's why
I need to keep pressing on!
Run!
You have to protect Nezuko!
( Yelling )
Rui: How?
( Thread rings )
Tanjiro: I see it,
the opening thread!
You have to take him down now,
even if it means
getting slashed in the process!
Kie: Nezuko. Nezuko.
Wake up, Nezuko.
You need to save your brother.
You're capable of doing so.
I know you are.
Nezuko, help him.
Your brother will be killed
if you don't!
( Nezuko growls )
( Woman singing in Japanese )
Nezuko: Blood demon art.
Exploding blood!
( Rui gasps )
Impossible!
The threads were burned away?
Tanjiro: The bond
between Nezuko and I
cannot be severed,
not by anyone!
¶
( Woman singing in Japanese )