( Both gasping )
( Tanjiro grunting )
Zenitsu: Incredible.
Inosuke: Look at 'em go.
( Tanjiro groans )
( Kanao gasps )
Aoi: That's it!
( Tanjiro gasps )
You really are fast, Kanao.
ｶ
aoi: Your score is now
ten wins and ten loses.
Tanjiro: I'm still up for more.
Let's go for a run.
Wanna join me?
Zenitsu: Doing
total concentration, constant?
Tanjiro: Yeah.
( Grunts )
Zenitsu: I gotta keep this up?
Inosuke: Do me next!
Zenitsu: How's this?
Inosuke: That's nothin'!
Zenitsu: More brawn than brain.
Tanjiro: Let's go!
ｶ
( lower six panting )
( Gasps )
Where the hell is this place?
( Structure creaking )
Is this her blood demon art?
It looks like the whole space
is distorted around that woman.
ｶ
( Structure creaking )
Only the lower ranks
of the twelve kizuki
have been summoned.
That's never happened before.
Lower five isn't here yet.
- ( Gasps )
- ( All gasping )
Lower six: It moved!
Is this her doing?
ｶ
what is it with this woman?
Who is she?
Kibutsuji: Lower your heads,
and kneel down.
( Lower six gasps )
Kibutsuji: Prostrate yourselves.
Lower six:
That's Master Muzan's voice.
- I didn't recognize him at all!
- ( Sweat pattering )
Even his aura
is completely different.
His disguise is astounding.
( Lower four gasps )
Please forgive us, Master!
Since you've assumed
a different form, we--
Kibutsuji: Who gave you
permission to speak?
Don't presume your thoughts
are of any worth to me.
All you are allowed to do
is answer my questions.
( Singers vocalizing )
The lower five was killed.
His name was Rui.
This is my single question
for all of you.
Why is it you demons
in the lower ranks
are so utterly weak?
You shouldn't be satisfied
merely being
among the twelve kizuki.
That is only the start.
You must devour more humans,
gain more power.
That is the path
to becoming useful to me.
For over a century,
the upper members
of the twelve kizuki
have remained unchanged,
and it has always
been those members
who have disposed
of the hashira.
Meanwhile, how many times
have you been replaced?
Lower six:
You make it sound so easy,
but the fact is--
Kibutsuji:
"You make it sound so easy,
but the fact is..."
What? Say it.
Lower six: He can read my mind?
This is bad.
Kibutsuji: What is bad?
Finish your thought.
( Lower six shuddering )
Forgive me, Master Kibutsuji!
Please! Please show me mercy!
I'm sorry!
I'm so very, very sorry!
( Shrieks )
( Mouth burps )
Lower three:
Why is this happening?
Am I next?
After all I went through
to become a twelve kizuki,
why? Why this?
I thought I was
going to do so much more!
Kibutsuji: Are you more afraid
of the demon slayers than of me?
Lower four: No!
Kibutsuji: I'm sure every time
you run into
a hashira-level Demon Slayer,
your only thoughts
are of escaping.
Lower four:
No, I'd never do that!
I would put
my own life on the line
in order to fight for you!
Kibutsuji:
You're not contradicting
what I just said, are you?
( Lower four sobs )
( Mouths growl )
( Singers vocalizing )
( Gurgling )
Lower three: It's all hopeless.
Whether we agree
or disagree with him,
he's going to kill us.
We can't beat him
in a fight, either.
In that case...
( Lower two gasps )
Lower three: I'll run!
ｶ
lower one: What a fool.
Lower three: I just need
to make it out of here somehow.
Now that I'm far away...
Kibutsuji: The twelve kizuki
are better off
consisting of just
the upper ranks.
I will be dismantling
the others.
Lower three: He got me?
How?
Was it
that fute player's technique?
No, I didn't hear it
make any sounds.
( Groans )
I can't regenerate my body. Why?
( Blood dripping )
ｶ
( blood splashes )
Kibutsuji: Do either of you
have any last words to share?
( Lower two gasps )
I can still be of use to you!
If you could just give me
a little bit of time,
I swear you won't regret it!
Kibutsuji: Exactly how long
are you asking for?
How do you intend
to be useful to me,
and what precisely
can you accomplish
with your meager skills?
Lower two: Your blood!
If you could give me
a portion of your blood,
I will surely rise
to meet your expectations!
I will fight for you
stronger than before!
Kibutsuji: Do you actually
believe you're in any position
to order me
to give you my blood?
Shameless is an understatement.
You will remember your place.
( Lower two gasping )
You misunderstand me!
I only said...
Kibutsuji: Silence.
I misunderstood nothing.
I am never mistaken.
I am the one
who calls the shots.
My word is absolute.
What I say
is correct by default.
It is not for you to refute.
And yet you try
to give me instructions?
You deserve to die for that.
Do you have any last words?
Lower three:
He'll be next to go.
Everything hinges
on the Master's mood.
I'll be dead soon myself.
Well, let me see.
( Sighs )
This is all
like a wonderful dream for me.
For me to be able to perish
by your very hand in the flesh.
And I so enjoyed hearing
the other demons's
dying breaths.
How truly fortunate am I.
I do so love to see others
in the throes
of despair and agony.
It's like a dream
come true for me.
You have my profound gratitude
for saving me for the end.
( Gagging )
Kibutsuji: That's more like it.
I'll give you
a generous amount of my blood,
although you may not be able
to handle its magnitude and die.
If you do manage to acclimate,
you are certain
to become stronger.
Then you are
to make yourself useful...
By killing hashira
of the demon slayers.
If you are able to kill
the Demon Slayer
wearing hanafuda earrings,
I will give you
even more of my blood.
( Lower one coughs )
( Sighs )
( Chords playing )
- ( Chords stop )
- ( Wind blowing )
( Gasps )
What's this?
I see something.
It's pouring into me
along with Master Muzan's blood.
ｶ
( gasping )
If I kill a hashira
and this kid,
I can get even more blood.
It's like a dream.
Kasugai: It is now morning!
Wake up, everyone!
Inosuke: The hell?
Zenitsu: Uh, what's going on?
Kasugai: The casualties
of the mugen train--
more than 40 are missing
as it currently stands.
You are to join
Kyojuro Rengoku on-site.
Head west at once!
( Wind blowing )
Sion,
I've decided to send
Tanjiro and the others.
Might I ask what caused you
to recommend him
in the first place, Shinobu?
Shinobu: Tanjiro has a pure soul
and will work diligently
toward all his goals,
and the potential he showed
exceeded my expectations.
And perhaps
most importantly of all,
he has a clear path in mind
in regards
to defeating Kibutsuji.
Ubuyashiki: I am
in complete agreement with you
on those counts.
Shinobu: On another matter,
Tanjiro told me that his father
had used fire breathing.
Ubuyashiki: Ah.
Shinobu: As of now,
there's no denying
that he still
has quite a way to go,
but I think that Rengoku,
our flame hashira,
could give him assistance.
Ubuyashiki: Fair enough.
Considering that his sister
is not a danger to humans,
as well as the fact
he came face to face with Muzan,
these signs
may very well point
towards this being
Tanjiro's destiny.
Tanjiro: All right,
it's time to go!
Hmm? Someone's coming.
( Grunts )
He was really intent
on bumping into me.
Wait. This guy...
Was he at final selection?
ｶ
he bulked up a lot
in such a short time...
But there's something else...
His scent.
It's been awhile!
Glad to see you're doing well!
( Groans )
Aoi: Oh, really?
You're heading out now?
It was only for a short time,
but I'm glad
we got to spend it together.
Good luck out there.
You take care now.
Tanjiro: Thanks for everything.
You looked after us,
even though
you were busy yourself,
and now we can
get back into battle.
Aoi: No need to thank me.
It was by chance
I got through final selection,
and after that,
I was too cowardly
to even step foot into battle.
- Tanjiro: None of that matters.
- ( Aoi sighs )
Tanjiro: Because you
kindly helped me out, aoi,
you're a part of me now.
All your emotions, I'll carry
them into the battlefield.
( Aoi gasps )
Tanjiro: If I get hurt, I hope
you'll look after me again!
ｶ
There you are!
( Running footsteps )
Hey, Kanao!
We're heading out now.
Thanks for everything.
Uh...
Hmm? What's that?
Kanao: All I did was follow
the teacher's orders,
and so there's no need
for you to thank me.
Farewell.
Tanjiro:
She actually talked to me!
What was that you just flipped?
Kanao: Bye for now.
Tanjiro: Money?
It says "heads"
and "tails," huh?
Why did you flip it?
Kanao: Goodbye.
Tanjiro: You sure
made that thing spin.
Kanao: I flip this
to help me decide
things that weren't ordered.
Just now, I decided
whether to speak to you or not.
Don't speak was heads,
and do speak was tails,
and tails is what it landed on.
Farewell.
Tanjiro: Why don't you
choose for yourself?
Which do you wanna do?
Kanao: It doesn't matter.
Nothing matters to me,
so I can't decide for myself.
Tanjiro: I don't think
there's anything in this world
that doesn't matter.
I guess...
The voice in your heart
is just really tiny.
( Groans )
Following orders is important
to an extent, but...
( Grunts )
Hey, can I borrow that?
Kanao: Uh, sure.
Tanjiro: Thank you.
Okay, we're gonna
use this to decide!
Kanao: Decide?
Tanjiro: Whether you'll listen
to your own heart
from this point on!
Whoa!
I flipped it way too high!
Heads! Let's make it heads!
If it comes up as heads,
you're going
to follow your heart!
- ( Wind blows )
- ( Kanao winces )
Tanjiro: Huh? Hey!
Where did it go?
( Stammers )
Oh, is that it?
You see that, Kanao? I got it!
( Kanao gasps )
Tanjiro: Are you ready?
Kanao: Which will it be?
His back was blocking it,
so I couldn't see
which way it fell.
Tanjiro: It came up as heads!
Here you go!
ｶ
- remember...
- ( Kanao gasps )
Tanjiro: It's the heart
that drives people,
so it can grow
as strong as you need it to.
( Kanao whimpers )
Tanjiro: All right.
See you later!
Kanao: How--how did it
come up heads?!
I saw his hand
when he flipped it.
I'm sure he didn't cheat,
but still...
Tanjiro: Just by chance.
Although, if it were tails,
I was gonna keep tossing it
until it finally
came up as heads.
( Laughs )
( Kanao gasps )
Tanjiro: Take care of yourself!
( Footsteps receding )
( All blowing and grunting )
Girls: You can do it!
You can do it! You can do it!
Great job, everyone!
Kiyo: Here!
- Inosuke: Ahh.
- Tanjiro: Thanks, girls.
Zenitsu: Don't eat it now.
Girls: We hope you all
defeat a lot of demons.
Tanjiro: We'll do our best.
Zenitsu: Hey, I told you
not to eat it now!
Inosuke: Shut up!
Zenitsu: Someone should
teach you some manners!
Tanjiro: Tomioka!
Tomioka:
Heading into battle now?
Tanjiro: Yes, sir.
Tomioka: I hear
that you've mastered
total concentration, constant.
Tanjiro: I have.
Tomioka: You should keep at it.
Tanjiro: Yes, sir.
Tomioka...
About Nezuko...
Thank you very much.
The fact that you put
your life on the line,
I had no idea.
I don't know
how to ever repay you.
Tomioka: You can thank me
by doing your best work.
Our mission is to kill demons.
That is all. Got it?
Tanjiro: Got it!
( Girls moan )
Kiyo: Be safe, you guys.
Zenitsu: Oh, no! Saying goodbye
has broken your little hearts.
I can stay behind if you like.
Kiyo: Zenitsu,
while you're on your journey,
please learn to be considerate
and respectful of girls, okay?
Zenitsu: Yes.
Inosuke: I'm feeling happy.
Zenitsu: You do
feel a little sad
that I'm leaving, though, right?
Girls: We're not sad!
Tanjiro: All right, everyone!
( Footstep echoes )
We're heading out now!
( Singers vocalizing )
Inosuke: Hey,
wait a damn minute!
( Whistle blowing )
Wh-what the...
What the hell is this creature?!
Wait. Could it be?
I've heard of such a being,
the Master and ruler
of this land!
At such an intimidating size,
there's no mistaking it!
It looks like it's asleep,
but don't let that fool you!
Zenitsu: It's a train.
You've never seen one?
Inosuke: Pipe down,
or you'll wake it!
I'll lead the charge
to take it down!
- Tanjiro: Inosuke, stop!
- Inosuke: Huh?
Tanjiro: This might be the
guardian spirit of this land,
so we shouldn't
be attacking it carelessly.
Zenitsu: Uh,
I said it's a train.
You've never seen one, either?
A vehicle for transportation?
Man, you're sheltered.
Tanjiro: Huh? A train?
That's what the crow
was talking about?
- Eh?
- Zenitsu: Huh?
What is he doing?
( Inosuke shrieks )
Ready or not,
I'm comin' through!
Zenitsu: Stop embarrassing us!
( Conductor blows whistle )
Hey! What do you
think you're doing?
- ( Zenitsu shrieks )
- Conductor: Look!
These three have swords!
The police! Call the police!
Zenitsu: Not good!
Not good! Not good!
Run for it!
We went through hell
'cause of you, Inosuke!
Say you're sorry!
Inosuke: Oh, yeah?!
Explain to me
why we had to run from
those guys in the first place?!
Zenitsu: 'Cause demon slayers
aren't officially recognized
by the government,
so we can't just have our swords
out in public like that.
If we told them
about the demons,
it's not like they would
believe us, anyway, you know?
Tanjiro: But we're
trying hard to help everyone.
Zenitsu: It's the way things go.
For now,
let's hide our swords away.
( Inosuke laughs )
( Chuckling )
Zenitsu: We can see them.
Put something on.
( Whistle blowing )
Oh, no! The train's leaving!
Are the police still around?
Tanjiro: We have to go,
either way!
Inosuke: Hah hah!
Here I come, Master of the land!
Zenitsu: What are you doing?!
Tanjiro: We should go, too!
Conductor: Hey! You three!
Zenitsu: Tanjiro! Inosuke!
Tanjiro: Zenitsu!
( All grunt )
( Singers vocalizing )
( Inosuke whoops )
This thing's fast!
- Zenitsu: Hey, Tanjiro...
- Tanjiro: Eh?
Zenitsu: You sure
about bringing Nezuko along?
Wouldn't
the safest place for her
be back at headquarters?
( Tanjiro grunts )
This is fine.
Wherever we go,
we will always be together.
We're never
going to be apart again.
ｶ
( singing in Japanese )
( Zenitsu chuckles )
Tanjiro: No matter
what it takes,
your big brother will save you!
Muzan Kibutsuji,
no matter where you go,
I promise you won't escape me!
Nezuko's staying with me.
Nothing's gonna break us apart.
The bond
between Nezuko and I...
Cannot be severed...
Not by anyone!
Nezuko...
I swear to you...
( Singing in Japanese )