Crow: South-southeast!
The next place you need to go
is south-southeast!
- Tanjiro: I heard you!
- ( Crow caws )
Tanjiro: You don't have to keep
squawking it at me, okay?
- Crow: South-southeast!
- Tanjiro: I'm begging you!
I got the message, so be quiet!
- Zenitsu: Please!
- ( Crow squawks )
( Stammers )
Zenitsu: Please! Please! Please!
Please marry me!
You know I could die
any day now!
Marry me so I don't die alone!
Marry me!
I'm begging you, please!
- Tanjiro: Wh-what is he doing?
- ( Zenitsu sobbing )
Tanjiro: What on earth?
( Sparrow chirping )
Tanjiro: Uh, yes?
Tanjiro: Huh?
¶
( singing in Japanese )
( sparrow chirping )
Zenitsu: Come on!
I'm begging you!
There's no one else!
You're the only hope
that I have left!
Tanjiro: Mm. Mm-hmm.
So that's it, then.
Okay, I'll try to help.
( Sparrow trills )
Zenitsu: Please!
I'm asking you again!
Marry me! I beg you!
Tanjiro: Why are you
making such a scene
in the middle of the road?
She's clearly
not interested in you!
Also, you're stressing
your sparrow out!
Zenitsu: Wait. That uniform.
Aren't you that guy
from final selection?
Tanjiro: Don't go pretending
like we know each other,
cause we don't, 'kay?!
Zenitsu: Huh?! But we have met!
Don't you remember?!
Don't get angry at me
when you're the one
with the terrible memory!
( No audible dialogue )
Tanjiro: All right.
You're all set
to head home again.
Do you need help
with anything else?
Girl: No. Thank you very much.
Zenitsu: Hang on!
Don't you interfere!
That girl
is madly in love with me!
The two of us
are gonna get marrie--
( groans )
Aah! Hey! Ouch! That hurts!
Aah! Aah! Stop! Ow! Ow!
Tanjiro: Hey, calm down!
( Zenitsu wails )
Girl: When did I say anything
even resembling
that I loved you?!
All I did was come talk to you
while you were crumpled up
all disheveled
on the side of the road!
Zenitsu: Huh?! No!
So are you telling me
the reason you did that
wasn't because you were
falling in love with me?
Girl: Considering that I
already have a fiancﾉ,
that's exactly what
I've been trying to tell you!
Well, you seem to be
perfectly fine now, so goodbye!
- ( Huffs )
- Zenitsu: W-wait!
Come back! Please--
tanjiro: Would you
give it a rest already?
Zenitsu: Wh-why did you
have to get in my way?
This had nothing to do with you.
Why are you
looking at me like that?
Stop it! You're staring at me
like I'm some sort of
pitiful creature or something!
Now listen here, you!
The reason I missed out
on getting married
is all your fault!
( Tanjiro gasps )
Zenitsu: Say something,
would you?!
Look, during my next job,
I'll likely die.
The reason is
I'm just a weakling.
Do you understand?
You have to help protect me
until I manage
to get married, mister.
Tanjiro: My name's tanjiro.
And you are?
Zenitsu: Tanjiro?
That's good to know.
I'm zenitsu agatsuma.
Please, you've gotta do
what you can to save me.
Tanjiro: Aren't you
being a bit dramatic?
Why did you
even become a swordsman?
You're acting
utterly pathetic right now.
Zenitsu:
That's a harsh way to put it!
I got conned by a woman
and racked up a lot of debt!
The old geezer
who took it over for me
happened to be
this tough-as-nails instructor!
He made me train
to the bone every day!
It was so hellish,
I just wanted to die!
I was hoping that'd happen
during final selection!
But, since I survived,
this nightmare
continues to haunt me!
Agh! I'm so scared,
terrified, frightened!
I just know I'm gonna
get eaten by a demon soon!
My brains are gonna
get sucked through my ears
while I'm still alive!
Yaaah!
No!
Please save me!
Tanjiro: Hey, are you okay?
( Zenitsu wails )
( Groans )
( Sparrow chirping )
( Crow caws )
Tanjiro: You better?
Zenitsu: A bit,
but now I'm feeling
really hungry.
Tanjiro: Don't you have
any food or rations on you?
Zenitsu: No.
Tanjiro: Here.
Take one of these.
Zenitsu: Really?
Thank you so much.
Hmm?
Aren't you gonna eat anything?
Tanjiro: Um, that was all I had.
Zenitsu: Hey, uh,
you take this half.
Tanjiro: You sure about that?
Thanks a lot.
I know what you mean
when you say that you're
terrified of demons,
but you should try
not to worry your sparrow.
Zenitsu: Huh?
You're saying it was distressed?
How could you tell?
Tanjiro: Let's see.
He says you're always whining
about not wanting to go to work,
and you're always
hitting on girls,
and you snore really loudly.
Yup, that covers it.
( Sparrow chirps )
Zenitsu: Wait.
He said all that?
You can understand
bird language?
- Tanjiro: Yeah.
- Zenitsu: No way!
You've gotta be lying to me!
( Crow caws )
Start running! Start running!
Run, tanjiro! Run, zenitsu!
Both of you must head
to your next destination!
Run, tanjiro! Run, zenitsu!
( Zenitsu whimpers )
( Wails )
That crow is talking to us!
¶
( Sighing )
Hey, tanjiro, maybe I
should just hang back for now.
Even if I tag along with you,
I'm not gonna be able
to do anything.
Tanjiro: The scent of demons
is getting stronger.
There's something up ahead.
( Gasps )
A house?
I can smell blood,
but it's strange.
Zenitsu: Wait.
You can smell something here?
Tanjiro: Yeah, but this is
a whole new smell.
Zenitsu: A smell?
I can't say I'm getting that.
What about that sound?
You're able to hear that, right?
Tanjiro: Sound?
( Gasps )
( Children shuddering )
Zenitsu: There are kids here?
Tanjiro: They look scared.
Hey, there.
Is there a reason
you're out here by yourselves?
( Children shuddering )
Tanjiro:
They're definitely terrified.
Guess what.
I have got
something really cool here.
Wanna see it?
Ta-da!
It's a friendly sparrow.
( Sparrow chirps )
Tanjiro: See? Isn't he cute?
( Children sigh )
( Shuddering )
Tanjiro: Talk to me.
Did something happen?
Is this your house?
Boy: No. No, it's not.
This is--this house is--
it--it belongs to a...
Monster.
¶
our big brother got taken away.
We were walking
down the road at night,
and this thing
appeared in front of us.
It went straight
for our brother,
never giving us a glance.
Tanjiro: Did it take him
into that house?
Boy: Yeah. That's right.
Tanjiro: So you two
followed them here?
That's real brave. Great job.
Boy: We used the traces
of his blood to follow them.
That thing really hurt him.
Tanjiro: I see.
It'll be all right.
We're gonna
go defeat the bad guy
and save your brother.
Girl: Is that true?
You'll help him?
Tanjiro: Yes. I promise.
- Zenitsu: Hey, tanjiro.
- Tanjiro: Huh?
Zenitsu: Uh, what is
that strange sound?
It's really unnerving
and never stops.
It sounds like a drum.
Tanjiro: A drum?
I don't hear anything.
( Drum pounds slowly )
( Zenitsu whimpers )
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Children gasp )
( Drumming intensifies )
( Drumming stops )
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Zenitsu gasps )
( Girl wails )
Tanjiro: Just cover your eyes!
( Zenitsu gasping )
Tanjiro: Are you all right?
Can you hear me?
Just hang on!
This is bad.
The wound is so deep.
Boy 2: Even though...
I was able to...
E-Escape from...
That horrible place...
A-And make it here...
( Gasps )
Was it not enough?
Am I still gonna die?
( Tanjiro gasping )
¶
He's gone.
I'm sorry
you had to suffer like that.
Zenitsu: Tanjiro...
By any chance,
would that happen
to be these kids'...
( Demon roaring )
- ( Boy gasps )
- ( Girl whimpers )
( Zenitsu whimpers )
( Drum pounds )
( Children weeping )
- ( Zenitsu whimpering )
- ( Teeth chattering )
Tanjiro: We couldn't save him.
If we'd only gotten here
a little sooner,
things might have
been different.
Uh, hey, is this your brother?
Boy: No.
No, that isn't him.
He was wearing
an orange-colored kimono.
( Tanjiro gasps ) I see.
So it's captured
more than one person.
I promise to bury you
once I return.
Until then, please forgive me.
All right.
Zenitsu, let's go!
( Zenitsu stammering )
Tanjiro: Look, the only people
who can help them
are you and me now.
( Zenitsu whimpering )
Tanjiro: All right, then.
Have it your way.
( Zenitsu shrieks )
Hey! Tanjiro, don't be so scary!
Fine! I give in! You win!
I'll come along with you, okay?!
Tanjiro: Don't let me force you.
Zenitsu: I said I'll go!
¶
boy: Huh?
Tanjiro: In case
you run into trouble,
I'm leaving this box.
If you need help,
it'll protect you.
Okay. We'll be back.
( Zenitsu gasps )
¶
( weeping )
( Flame sputters )
( Zenitsu shuddering )
So, tanjiro,
hey, before we continue,
whatever's in this place
with us,
you'll be sure to protect me
from it, won't you?
Tanjiro: Zenitsu,
I hate to have to tell you this,
but, in my last fight,
I broke a leg and a rib.
Neither of them have
fully healed up as of yet, so--
zenitsu: Wait! What?!
You have broken bones?!
What do you think
you're trying to do to me?!
If you're in that condition,
my fate has been sealed!
I'm gonna d-d-d-die!
( Wails ) This is awful!
What am I gonna do?
I'm finished!
It's all over for me! Yaah!
I can't believe
you have broken bones!
I'm a dead man now,
completely and utterly dead!
- I'm dead! I'm dead...
- Tanjiro: Zenitsu,
you've gotta calm down.
You'll be all right.
Zenitsu: Don't feed me
your empty promises!
Tanjiro: No, it's true.
You're gonna be fine,
because you're--( Gasps )
- Stay away!
- ( Zenitsu shrieks )
Tanjiro: You two
shouldn't be here!
Boy: W-we're sorry.
There were sounds coming
from inside that box.
Tanjiro: Still, I really wish
you hadn't left it behind.
That thing is more precious
to me than my own life.
( Rumbling )
( Zenitsu whimpering )
( Shrieks )
( Tanjiro and girl gasp )
Zenitsu: Oops! Sorry.
- ( Drum beats )
- ( Tanjiro gasps )
- ( Girl gasps )
( Drum beats steadily )
Tanjiro: The room changed.
Or could it be
that we somehow moved
during the beat of that drum?
( Girl crying )
( Tanjiro sighs ) Sorry you
got separated from your brother,
but I'm gonna protect you,
no matter what.
And zenitsu is going to protect
your brother. Don't worry.
What's your name?
Teruko: It's teruko.
Tanjiro: Your name's teruko?
Your parents
picked out a really--
- ( breeze blows )
- ( Gasps )
¶
( footstep thumps )
( Teruko inhales )
Tanjiro: Among all
the different scents
in this mansion,
this is the strongest one.
It's eaten so many.
This one has to be
the master of this place.
Zenitsu: I'm gonna die!
It's over! It's over!
I just know it!
I can't believe
tanjiro and I got separated!
Boy: Teruko, you here?
It's shoichi!
Zenitsu: Hey, hey, hey!
You can't go around
yelling like that!
If the bad guy
hears you and finds us,
it's not gonna be pretty!
Let's just go wait outside!
Shoichi: Huh?
Why would we do that?
Are you trying to escape
all by yourself?
All this constant whining
about dying,
- aren't you a little ashamed?
- ( Zenitsu wails )
Shoichi: It's pathetic
that you're clinging
to the sleeve of someone
who's younger than you.
Why does a coward like you
have a sword on your hip
in the first place?
( Zenitsu gags )
( Groans ) Those words...
They cut me right to my core.
( Gags )
Listen here, you! I'm not
gonna be useful here, anyway...
Shoichi: Let me go!
Zenitsu: So I'm just
gonna go find an adult
- who can help us, okay?
- Shoichi: Let go of me!
Zenitsu: This isn't something
us kids can resolve on our own.
Uh...
No way!
You've gotta be kidding me!
How's this not the front door?!
Did I misremember?
I was sure it was here!
This one?
Maybe here!
Or here!
¶
it's a monster!
( Swordsman grunts )
( Zenitsu wails )
¶
what the heck?!
What's with that look?!
S-Stop it!
¶
( tanjiro gasping )
( Teruko sobbing softly )
If it hadn't been for them,
if it hadn't been
for them and their meddling...
Tanjiro: Teruko...
You gotta try not to scream.
The room might change again,
so don't go far, all right?
Go hide behind those shelves.
Demon: Curses. Curses!
Thanks to them,
he was able to get away.
That prey was mine
and mine alone.
Damn them. Why do
all these unwelcome guests
keep barging
into someone else's home?
It's maddening.
That prey belonged to me.
I found it with my own
two hands on my own property.
¶
those filthy rats.
I'll make them pay.
Tanjiro: Hey, you, listen up!
I'm a demon slayer,
rank mizunoto, tanjiro kamado!
It's my duty to slay you now!
Demon: A child with marechi
that I found myself!
Tanjiro: Got him.
( Drum beats )
- ( Gasps )
- ( Rumbling )
( Teruko screams )
Tanjiro: Teruko! ( Gasps )
¶
I thought this might happen.
The room's been flipped.
So this is his blood demon art.
This entire mansion
is his territory.
( Gasps ) What's this?
There's an odd scent,
but it's not a demon.
( Swordsman laughing wildly )
Better watch out,
'cause, ready or not,
here I come!
( Woman vocalizing )
¶
( tanjiro gasps )
Who is this guy?
He's wearing a boar's hide.
And he's
wielding nichirin swords.
Swordsman:
All right, you monster,
die on the battlefield,
and serve as my catalyst
so that I may become
even more powerful
and soar to new heights!
Demon: Infuriating.
Just infuriating!
( Tanjiro gasps )
Swordsman:
Hope you're ready for me,
'cause I'm comin' through!
¶
( singing in Japanese )