( Insects chirping )
Shinobu: Were you acquainted
with any of these demon slayers?
There don't seem to be
any survivors in this area,
at least.
We were informed that several
of the newer mizunoto
had joined the battle
to combat these demons, but...
They might all be dead by now,
don't you think?
Tomioka: Let's go.
¶
Shinobu: Isn't the moon lovely?
Since we've been given
this joint mission,
let's try to get along, Tomioka.
Tomioka: My only concern
is slaying demons.
Shinobu:
How coldhearted of you.
Well, how about
we split up from this point?
I shall proceed from the west.
Tomioka: Very well.
( Shinobu chuckles )
( Father growls )
Inosuke: Huh?
Father: Don't you
come near my family!
Stay away from them!
( Inosuke grunts )
Tanjiro: Water breathing.
Second form,
water wheel!
( Yelling )
( Singing in Japanese )
¶
( Father growling )
Tanjiro: It's no good.
It won't cut through.
¶
( gasps )
( Inosuke grunts )
Its body is so tough! ( Groans )
( Father shrieks )
Tanjiro: None of
my techniques worked.
This is bad. What do I do?
( Father growls )
I'll say it again
so you understand.
Stay away from my family!
( Growls )
Inosuke: Hey, you!
Eyes over here!
All nine of 'em!
( Gurgles ) Raah!
Damn it!
All that force with just
a single swipe of its arm!
I can't beat him
in my condition.
All this blood loss
is making me dizzy.
( Father growling )
Inosuke: Damn it!
Tanjiro: Water breathing.
Second form, improved,
lateral water wheel!
( Both panting )
( Tree creaking )
¶
( Inosuke gasps )
( Father groans )
Inosuke: What happened?
What's going on here?
Tanjiro: Inosuke! You all right?
Inosuke: Huh?
Wait. He did that?
What a little showoff.
( Father gurgling )
Tanjiro: Okay. I should
be able to cut off its head now.
Water breathing,
the final
and most powerful form!
( Inhales )
( Inosuke gasps )
He's got a different air
about him now.
I can tell
he's about to do something
that's totally incredible.
Tanjiro: Now I'll
finish him off!
Total concentration.
Water breathing.
Tenth form...
- ( Father shrieks )
- ( Tanjiro gasps )
( Father roars )
( Tanjiro groans )
( Inosuke gasps )
Hey, look out!
( Father roars )
( Tanjiro yells )
Inosuke: Kentaro!
( Tanjiro gasps ) Inosuke!
You have to hold on
'til I can make it back!
That's one
of the twelve kizuki,
so you can't die here!
You hear me?!
Promise me that you won't die!
( Inosuke gasping )
( Father gurgling )
( Roars )
Inosuke: Oh, crap!
( Insects chirping )
( Zenitsu inhaling )
( Groans )
( Inhaling )
It's starting to get...
Really hard to breathe now.
( Sighs )
Not only that,
I don't have
any feeling in my...
Arms and legs anymore.
( Wind blowing )
Nezuko, I'm sorry.
Grandfather: Don't give up.
You hear me?
Don't give up!
Zenitsu: Don't give up!
( Groans )
¶
( singing in Japanese )
Who is this?
Shinobu: Hello there.
Are you all right?
( Zenitsu groans )
¶
Tanjiro: Water breathing.
Second form...
Water wheel!
( Groans )
Somehow, I stuck that landing.
- ( Squelch )
- ( Woman shrieks )
- ( Screams )
- ( Tanjiro gasps )
Woman: I beg of you,
please stop!
( Sobbing )
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Sister sobbing )
Rui: What are you looking at?
This isn't a play, you know.
( Tanjiro gasps )
Wh-what are you doing?
Aren't you two
fighting on the same side?
Rui: "The same side"?
Don't go phrasing it
in such an infantile manner.
The two of us are family.
We are connected
by a powerful bond.
Regardless of that, this is
between me and my sister.
If you insist on interfering,
I'll carve you up.
( Tanjiro gasps )
You're wrong.
Family or comrade, as long as
you feel close to one another,
that's all that really matters.
Saying it's childish
if you're not related by blood,
that's not true at all!
Not only that,
but those who are strongly
connected with each other
give off the scent of trust.
But all I'm picking up
from you two
is the scent of terror,
hatred, and revulsion!
That's not something
you can call a bond!
It's a fake, a forgery!
( Demon gasps )
( Rui gasps )
You little...
( Shuddering )
Demon slayer: Well,
would you look at that!
A demon
that's a manageable size.
Even I can deal with a kid.
This is my chance.
Tanjiro:
Hold on a second, please!
Demon slayer:
Don't move in on my prey!
This is how I'll secure
my path up the ladder,
and with more status,
comes more money in my pockets
from on high.
Even with most of my unit
wiped out, I'll dispose of him,
and afterwards
I'll descend the mountain
to claim my prize
for defeating this demon.
Take this!
Tanjiro: No, wait!
Don't do it!
( Demon slayer grunts )
Tanjiro: Cut to pieces
in an instant.
How did he do that?
Rui: Now, then,
what did you just say?
( Tanjiro gasps )
Rui: I asked you...
What did you say to me?
( Women vocalizing )
Tanjiro: Look how scary he got.
It feels like the air
became ten times heavier.
( Chorus vocalizing )
Tanjiro: Inosuke, I'm sorry.
I'm gonna need you to
hang in there a little longer.
I'll be there as soon
as I defeat this demon.
I'll come help you,
no matter what!
Rui: Answer me.
What did you mean?
I demand to hear it from you.
Come now. Explain it to me.
Tanjiro: Sure! I'd be happy to.
What you have
isn't a real bond at all!
( Inosuke panting )
( Distant footsteps )
( Inosuke coughs )
( Father growling )
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Father growls )
( Inosuke gulps )
Not good.
( Wind blowing )
)
( Chorus vocalizing )
Inosuke: Damn it. Hiding away
like a woodland creature,
how pathetic is that?
I've gotta find a way
to turn things around.
How do you cut someone
who's swordproof, anyway?
What should I do? What can I do?
What's the way for me
to get in there and hurt it?
Think! Think! Think!
- Think--
- ( Father roars )
Inosuke: Whoa! ( Panting )
This is bad!
This is really bad!
Until--until he gets back,
I gotta survive somehow.
( Gasps )
Why the hell am I
thinkin' things like that?!
( Father roars )
Inosuke: I don't
have time for this!
( Yells )
Damn you.
( Grunts )
I must have gotten infected
by tontaro's germs!
I can't let my guard down again!
Using my head?
That kind of thing's
not like me at all!
( Yells )
All right. I got you.
( Father squeals )
Inosuke: See?
It was as simple as that.
If you can't cut something
with a sword,
all you gotta do is
pound on it with another sword!
And just my luck.
I have the tools for the job!
( Laughs )
I am untouchable!
( Father growls )
Eh?
Are you running away on me?
Hey, you,
come back here, damn it!
¶
( Tanjiro panting )
Rui: Just so you know,
I'm not going to kill you
in a single strike.
Instead, I'll dissect you
piece by piece.
However, if you take back
what you said to me just now,
I'll make your death
mercifully quick.
Tanjiro: I refuse!
What I said
was the unbridled truth!
I won't take it back,
not on your life!
¶
( demon gasping )
Tanjiro: You're the one
who's in the wrong!
( Gasps )
( Inosuke panting )
Damn it. Where the hell did
that abomination make off to?
( Groans )
It's just a scratch.
This doesn't hurt at all,
and if it doesn't hurt,
it's not a problem!
I've had enough of this.
Time to sniff him out for good.
( Grunting )
- So there you are!
- ( Father shuddering )
Inosuke:
You dung-brained buffoon!
How high did you climb?
Bastard.
You're gonna try and force me
to use my head again, huh?
I don't think so.
( Father growling )
Inosuke: What the...
Oh, I get it!
He's trembling
with fear and dread
at the mere sight of me, huh?
( Laughs )
Well, it's a bit
too late for that!
( Father growling )
¶
Inosuke: The hell?
Now what?
Did--did it just shed its skin?!
( Father roars )
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Growling )
Inosuke: Give me a break.
I'm all about
getting really strong,
but this is too much!
This is looking really bad.
I've never felt this much force
from an opponent before.
A single strike
will pulverize me.
( Father growling )
( Inosuke shudders )
It's hopeless. I can't win.
¶
( Father growling )
Inosuke: I'm gonna die.
( Gasps )
This is the end.
- Tanjiro: Don't die!
- Inosuke: Huh?
Tanjiro: You have to hold on
'til I can make it back!
Woman: Always live your lives
in a fashion where you are able
to hold your heads up high.
I wish you luck in battle.
( Inosuke gasps )
I won't lose.
No way am I gonna lose.
I'm Inosuke hashibira
of the demon slayer corps!
Give me the worst you got,
you dirtbag!
So fast. I can't even see it!
( Father growls )
Beast breathing. Fang three,
devour!
It broke?
- ( Father growls )
- ( Inosuke groaning )
Damn it.
I should have focused more
on my landing
than my breathing technique.
Father: I'll make sure you
can never harm my family again!
- ( Bones creaking )
- Inosuke: I refuse to die here.
Beast breathing. Fang one.
All right, you brute. Take this!
( Father chuckles )
Inosuke: I dug 'em in, but...
It's like
it doesn't even matter.
( Gags ) This thing
isn't even flinching!
( Father growling )
( Inosuke gagging )
¶
Woman: Forgive me.
Please forgive me, Inosuke.
¶
This way, at least
you will have a chance.
Survive!
( No audible dialogue )
Inosuke: Who--
who are you?
( Gags )
( Running footsteps )
( Father groans )
( Inosuke gags )
What was that?
Did he actually cut through him?
Who--who could have
possibly done such a thing?
¶
( Father growling )
- ( Roars )
- Inosuke: So quick.
Tomioka: Water breathing.
Fourth form...
Striking tide.
( Father groans )
¶
( gagging )
Inosuke: A-amazing.
I've--I've never seen anyone
as incredible as this guy.
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Tanjiro grunts )
Good. The stench
is starting to fade,
so now I'm able to detect
the scent of the threads.
I can take him on now.
Rui: Hmph. He's smarter
than I gave him credit for.
He doesn't shrink back in fear.
Not that any of that
will matter in the end.
¶
Tanjiro: Water breathing.
First form...
Water surface slash!
( Gasps )
( Squelch )
¶
( singing in Japanese )