( Boy chuckles, grunts )
- ( Boy 2 grunts )
- ( Boy 3 growls )
( Boys laughing )
Boy 1: Gotcha!
( Singer vocalizing )
- Boy: Nice one.
- ( Laughing )
( Rui coughing )
( Sighs )
( Singer continues )
( Birds chirping )
- Woman: Rui?
- ( Footsteps crunching )
Rui!
What are you doing?
You know you're
not supposed to be outside!
¶
( singing in Japanese )
Rui: Since the day I was born,
I've always been very frail.
I couldn't run.
Even just walking
was a struggle for me.
Eh?
( Narrating ) That is...
Until Master Muzan appeared.
( Singer vocalizing )
Kibutsuji: You poor thing.
I'll save you
from this harsh life.
Rui: My parents
weren't happy about it.
Since I'd acquired
a strong body,
I could never
expose myself to sunlight,
and of course...
I had to devour humans.
Father: What have you done?
What on earth
have you done, Rui?
Answer me!
( Mother sobbing )
Rui: Long ago,
I heard a wonderful story.
There was once a Father who died
trying to save
his drowning child.
( Child crying )
( Wailing )
Rui: I was deeply moved.
Such astounding display
of parental love, a true bond.
This Father who drowned
had fulfilled his role
as a guardian wonderfully,
but I wasn't bestowed
the same kind of devotion.
( Father crying )
Rui: When it came
to my own parents,
they tried to kill me.
( Mother crying )
Rui: All my Mother did was cry,
never lifting a finger
to protect me.
( Squelch )
They must have been imposters.
Our bond wasn't the genuine one
at all, I thought.
Mother: I'm...Sorry.
Rui: She's saying something.
I thought she was dead.
Mother: I'm sorry...
That I couldn't give you
a strong, healthy body.
( Rui gasps )
( Narrating ) Those...
Were the last words
my Mother ever spoke to me.
She was dead.
Father: Rui, listen.
We're going to die with you!
Rui: I was so enraged
he had tried to kill me,
the meaning
of his words escaped me.
But I came to realize
soon after
he intended
to atone on my behalf
for the sin
of having killed someone,
in the form
of taking his own life.
It was a genuine bond,
and that night, I had severed it
with my own two hands.
After all that, however,
Master Muzan gave me
words of encouragement.
Kibutsuji: It was
all your parents's fault
for refusing to accept you
for who you are.
Take pride in your own power.
Rui: I had no other choice
but to see it that way.
I couldn't bear
the weight of what I'd done.
( Sobs )
I knew that I only
had myself to blame.
Every single day,
I missed my parents so much,
I could barely stand it.
Even after crafting
a family of my own,
that emptiness remained.
Because I was the strongest,
I couldn't depend on anyone
to protect me, no one.
The more powerful I became,
the more distant my memories
of being human became as well.
I began losing sight
of what it was I wanted
in the first place.
¶
I sought out a bond that I was
never able to claim for myself,
not in my old life,
nor the new one I created.
( Tanjiro gasps )
This body is giving off a scent,
one of grief too overwhelming
for him to bear.
¶
Rui: So warm.
Hands as gentle as sunbeams.
I remember now, clear as day.
I had wanted to apologize.
I'm sorry.
I was...
I was to blame for everything.
I hope you can forgive me.
I've killed
so many people, though.
Surely I'm going to hell,
aren't I?
Father, Mother...
I can't go to the same place
as you, can I?
Father: That's not true.
We'll be together,
no matter where you go.
( Rui gasps )
¶
Father: Rui.
Oh, Father...
And Mother.
Mother: Darling.
We'll be with you always.
( Rui sobbing )
It was my fault.
All of it was my fault.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry!
I'm so sorry! Forgive me!
( Tanjiro sighs )
- ( Foot stamps )
- ( Gasps )
Tomioka: Don't waste
your sympathy.
It was a demon.
The fact it looked like a child
makes no difference.
It lived for decades,
terrorizing our people.
Tanjiro: If it's for the sake
of avenging those
who were killed,
to make sure
there are no more victims,
I won't hesitate
to bring my blade down
on any demon's neck.
But when it comes to those
who felt despair and regret
from the actions
they took as a demon,
I will never disrespect them!
Because at one time
or another...
They were human,
no different from me!
So please don't step
on his remains!
They're not hideous monsters
at all.
Instead, demons are
hopeless creatures,
tragic creatures.
( Gasping )
¶
( Tomioka gasps )
Isn't she...
( Whoosh )
¶
( Tanjiro gasps )
Shinobu: Oh, my.
Why would you get
in my way, Tomioka?
And after you told me we could
never be friends with demons.
I have to say...
This kind of thing
is exactly why no one likes you.
( Giggles )
)
( Man gasping )
Kakushi: Incredible.
This antidote of Lady Kocho's
is very effective, isn't it?
Kakushi 2: Indeed,
and she prepared it
after a mere glance
at this situation.
She's truly amazing.
As is he.
Kakushi 1: That boy? How so?
Kakushi 2: He defeated
that demon, which in turn,
slowed the circulation
of the poison just a bit.
Kakushi 1: All right!
This should do it!
We're in good shape.
Looks like
they'll all pull through.
Kakushi 2: That's good.
I'd like to wrap things up
as quickly as possible
and leave this place.
Wouldn't you?
Kakushi 1: No argument here.
This mountain has
a really hideous stench to it.
¶
( Tanjiro shudders )
Shinobu: Now then, Tomioka,
would you please move?
Tomioka: I don't--
I don't think I'm disliked.
( Tanjiro gasps )
Shinobu: Oh, dear.
I do apologize.
You're only just hearing
about this now, then?
I'm sorry. I didn't mean
for you to find out this way.
( Tanjiro yells )
( Groans )
- Shinobu: Boy!
- Tanjiro: Yes, ma'am!
Shinobu: What you're protecting
there is actually a demon,
so please move away
before you get hurt.
Tanjiro: No. You're mistaken!
Well, you're not mistaken,
but she's my little sister!
She's my sister,
and that's why...
Shinobu: Oh, my.
Is that really true?
You poor thing.
In that case,
so she won't suffer,
I'll use a gentle toxin
in order to kill her.
( Tanjiro gasps )
Tomioka: Can you move?
Even if it's difficult,
you need to go.
Take your sister, and run.
Tanjiro: Tomioka...
Thank you.
I appreciate this!
Shinobu: Did you...
Just break
the rules of the Corps?
¶
( Tanjiro panting )
My whole body is aching so much,
I wanna scream,
but I have to keep going
and endure it!
Endure! Endure! Endure! Endure!
( Nezuko sighing )
Tanjiro: Does this mean...
I'm gonna have to leave
the Demon Slayer Corps?
Even if she's my sister,
there's no way
they'd let one of their
swordsmen travel with a demon!
Shinobu: I see you're
dead serious about this.
Who would have thought a hashira
would defend a demon?
Whatever your intentions are,
I'm afraid
I don't feel like playing
this game of stalling for time,
and so good day to you.
( Tomioka gasps )
¶
Shinobu: Is this your attempt
at catching up with me?
( Giggles )
I don't have any objections
to you trying to stop me,
but don't forget there's
someone else to watch out for.
Tanjiro: Don't stop running!
Keep on moving!
You gotta run
as far away as you can!
( Groans )
Damn it! What just happened?
I wasn't aware
of my surroundings.
Nezuko!
A Demon Slayer?
( Grunts )
Get out of here, Nezuko!
Run away as fast as you can!
Don't get caught,
no matter what! Hurry!
¶
Slayer: Did she
just shrink into a child?
She's just running away
without even
throwing out an attack. Why?
( Nezuko panting )
Slayer: Well, it doesn't matter.
My orders
are to slay this demon.
Shinobu: Tomioka...
There's something I want to say.
Since the purpose of my attack
was to slay a demon,
it certainly
wouldn't be construed
as a violation of the Corps,
but what you're doing
is clearly against the rules.
You're preventing me
from slaying a demon.
What are your intentions here?
Don't you have
anything to say for yourself?
This will be your final warning.
At least give me
some sort of reason.
Tomioka: As I recall,
it was two years ago.
Shinobu: Are you about
to go into a long-winded story
from the past just to spite me?
It's because of what I said
to you earlier. Is that it?
( Tomioka groans )
( Gasps )
Kasugai:
Message! Message! ( Caws )
I have a message
from headquarters!
Tanjiro and Nezuko
are to be taken into custody
and brought back
to headquarters!
( Caws )
( Shinobu gasps )
Kasugai: Tanjiro
and the demon Nezuko
are to be taken into custody and
brought back to headquarters!
Kasugai 2: Tanjiro,
dressed in a checkered haori,
with a scar on his forehead!
Nezuko, a demon girl
with a bamboo muzzle!
Slayer: Are you Nezuko?
Kasugai 1: Bring them back!
Bring them back! ( Caws )
Tanjiro,
dressed in a checkered haori,
with a scar on his forehead!
Nezuko, a demon girl
with a bamboo muzzle!
Bring them back!
Bring them back! ( Caws )
¶
Kakushi 2: He does have a scar.
Kakushi 1: All right,
let's bring him in.
Kakushi 2: Look. His jawbone
seems to be broken, doesn't it?
( Kakushi 1 sighs )
I feel bad about tying him up.
( Kakushi 3 gasps )
Wh-who the hell is this?
Kakushi 4: I don't know.
A demon? No, it couldn't be.
Kakushi 3: Is it human?
Kakushi 4: He's wearing
our uniform trousers.
Kakushi 3: Oh, wait.
This is a mask. He is human!
Kakushi 4: All right,
let's bring him in.
Kakushi 3: Ah, this guy's
been beaten up really bad.
Kakushi 4: Why's he
strung up like this?
Inosuke: There was
nothing I could do.
On my own, I couldn't
bring down even a single demon.
You know what?
Maybe I'm not that strong.
( Chuntaro chirping )
Zenitsu:
They wrapped us all up, huh?
Who are these people?
They seem to be cleaning up
this place really efficiently.
And that girl there,
isn't she the girl
from final selection?
She has the same kind
of hair ornament
as the lady who wrapped us up.
Kakushi 5: Should we
bring them as well?
Slayer: Yes,
go to the butterfly mansion.
I'll be hunting down
the demons here,
so you can rest easy.
Zenitsu: I think
I've heard of these guys.
They're called the Kakushi.
They clean up the aftermath
of the Corps's
battles with demons.
I've heard
that most of their members
are people whose sword skills
aren't quite as polished.
( Chuntaro chirps )
Zenitsu: Eh?
It's daybreak.
( Singers vocalizing )
Kakushi 1: Wake up.
I said wake up!
You gotta--
hey, can you even hear me?
Come on! Get up!
Are you gonna sleep all day?
Wake the hell up, will you?!
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Vocalizing continues )
Kakushi 1: You're
in the presence of the hashira!
¶
( singing in Japanese )