( Inosuke growls )
Beast breathing.
Seventh form,
spatial awareness.
ｶ
( breathing deeply )
Tanjiro: You find them?
Inosuke: Yeah.
Follow me that way!
I'm sensing
a strong presence over there.
Tanjiro: You are?
Way to go, Inosuke!
( Inosuke stammers )
( Grunts )
Why, you...
We can't get anywhere
with these guys around!
( Murata grunts )
Tanjiro: Damn it. Isn't there--
isn't there any way
we can get out of this?
( Singing in Japanese )
ｶ
( Zenitsu panting )
Nez--n-n-Nezuko.
Nez--where are you?
N-n-n-Nezuko!
( Coughs )
( Panting )
Inosuke: The hell
with this crap!
That's it!
I'm just gonna
demolish them all at once!
Tanjiro: Stop it. You can't!
There must be a way
to save them.
Listen.
We can't hurt these people.
- ( Footsteps crunching )
- ( Gasps )
ｶ
m-Murata?
Murata: Leave these guys to me,
and go on ahead, Tanjiro!
Inosuke: Big talk from the guy
who pissed his pants!
Murata: I never did anything
of the sort, you stupid boar!
Inosuke: Come again?!
Murata: I wasn't even
talking to you, so butt out!
I know I wasn't
very brave back there,
but I'm still a Demon Slayer!
I'll find a way
to hold them off.
I know now
I just need to cut the threads
and that their movement patterns
are very basic,
so I should be fine.
I'll watch out
for the spiders, too.
There have to be people who are
under even greater control
that are closer to the demon.
You have to help them!
Tanjiro: I got it! Stay strong.
Let's go, Inosuke!
( Inosuke grunts )
Hey, let go of me, damn it!
I wanna pound
that guy's face in first!
Who's he calling
"a stupid boar"?
Murata: Oh, shut up!
Stop messing around,
and get out of here!
Inosuke: I'm gonna make you
see stars when I get back!
Mark my words!
ｶ
damn it! I can't wait
to get back and pummel that guy.
( Tanjiro groans )
Stop talking like that!
Inosuke: Didn't you hear him
call me a "stupid boar,"
monjiro?
Tanjiro: My name's Tanjiro!
Anyway, are we headed
the right way?
Inosuke: My senses
have never led me astray.
Although, i--
( growls )
What are
all these annoying threads?
Tanjiro: It must mean
we're closing in on the demon.
( Inosuke grunts )
There's another group here.
( Demon Slayer gasps )
Stop.
( Demon Slayer 2 gags )
Demon Slayer 1:
Don't come any closer.
You have to go and bring someone
here who's a higher rank!
It's the only way for certain
to stop the rest of us
from being killed!
( Crying )
Help us.
( Crying ) I beg you!
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Demon laughs )
( Webs creak )
I wonder
if you can defeat them.
The closer that someone
is able to get to me,
the stronger
these threads of mine become,
as do my precious dolls.
Demon 2: Mother...
( Mother gasps )
Son: Can you really win?
Rui.
Rui: Don't you think
this is taking too much time?
( Mother shuddering )
Rui: You'd better get to it,
or I'm gonna have
to tell father.
Mother: No, I can do it!
You don't have to worry!
I promise to protect you!
So, please, whatever you do,
don't tell your father, not him!
( Crying )
( Women vocalizing )
Rui: Well, then, hurry it up.
( Mother shuddering )
ｶ
Die, all of you!
Just die already!
It'll be hell for me
if I don't get rid of you!
Demon Slayer 1: Run away!
Tanjiro: So fast!
Demon Slayer 1:
I'm being controlled,
so my movements aren't...
( Groans ) My own!
I was never anywhere
near as strong as this!
( Groaning )
( Joints crack )
( Grunting )
Tanjiro: The demon
that's controlling her
has no concern for the strain
it's putting on her body.
( Demon Slayer 1 screams )
Tanjiro: This is cruel.
( Mother gasping )
Stubborn imbeciles.
Take this!
( Webs creaking )
Tanjiro: That sound.
Demon Slayer 3:
Please, end my life.
All the bones...
In my arms and legs...
They're broken,
piercing my insides.
Every time I'm forced to move,
the pain is unbearable.
I can't take it anymore.
Either way, I'll die.
So, please...
Just hurry up,
and finish the job.
Inosuke: I'll take on the job.
Tanjiro: Wait!
( Demon Slayer 1 grunting )
Tanjiro: Inosuke!
We gotta find a way to save him!
Inosuke: Oh, shut up!
You need to stop
your bellyachin'!
Tanjiro: Listen to me!
Inosuke: He's asking us
to put him out of his misery,
all right?
These guys are speedy, too.
If we get caught nappin',
we'll be done for!
Tanjiro: I know that!
Just give me a moment to think.
I don't want to attack them,
but cutting the strings
won't have a lasting effect.
How can we stop them
from moving?
I've got it!
Inosuke: Eh? Hey!
( Demon Slayer 1 groaning )
Tanjiro: Good.
She's following me.
Inosuke: The hell?
Why are you running around
in circles like that?
Quit messin' around!
ｶ
total concentration.
- Inosuke: Huh?
- ( Demon Slayer 1 gasping )
So strong.
Tanjiro: Great!
Looks like it worked out!
Inosuke: Wha...
What the heck
was that just now?!
I wanna do it, too!
Come at me!
( Laughing )
( Demon Slayer 3 gasps )
( Inosuke grunts )
( Laughing )
You see that?!
Whatever you can do,
I can do just as well!
Tanjiro: Sorry.
I must have missed it.
Inosuke: You're kidding!
Tanjiro: I'm a little busy
at the moment!
( Mother shuddering )
Damn! They are
all such useless puppets.
I have no choice
but to unleash that one, then.
Ng )
Zenitsu: Nezuko!
( Panting )
Nezuko!
Where are you?!
( Sobbing )
Nezuko,
Tanjiro,
Chuntaro,
even the wild boar,
where did you all go?!
I'm sorry for everything, okay?
( Sobbing )
( Sniffles )
( Sparrow chirps )
Zenitsu: Chuntaro?
( Chuntaro chirps )
Zenitsu: You decided
to come check in on me?
You're so wonderful
and adorable, Chuntaro!
Not as adorable as Nezuko,
but I'd say a close second!
I really appreciate this!
( Sobs )
( Chuntaro squeals )
Zenitsu: I'm sorry
for everything!
How about we just start fresh
and go look for Nezuko together?
( Inosuke laughs )
Check that out!
I've tossed up more of 'em
than you have now!
Tanjiro: That's good.
Just one more.
Inosuke: Okay. I'm gonna
do it one more time, so watch!
Tanjiro: All right, fine.
I'll watch.
Just try not to hurt him!
Mother: These puppets are weak!
I don't need them anymore!
They're useless!
( Groans )
( Demon Slayer 2 gags )
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Demon Slayer 3 gags )
( Demon Slayer 1 gags )
ｶ
( Inosuke groans )
Damn it to hell.
That thing went
and killed all of 'em!
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Chorus ends )
( Inosuke gasping )
Tanjiro: Let's go.
Inosuke: No arguments here.
ｶ
it's this way!
We'll reach them
before you know it.
Tanjiro: Now that the wind's
changed direction,
my sense of smell is returning.
Then I'll know
exactly where it is.
There! I'm picking up
two more scents!
Inosuke!
Inosuke: I detected that thing
before you did.
I'm gonna hack its head
right off its shoulders!
( Grunts )
Huh?
That thing...
Doesn't even have a head!
Zenitsu: Nezuko!
Where are you?!
( Chuntaro chirping )
( Zenitsu panting )
Where the heck are you, Tanjiro?
You, too, Inosuke.
Don't just leave me here
all by myself
in this terrifying forest!
( Shrieks )
( Birds squawking )
Zenitsu: What was that?
You know what?
This is starting
to make me really mad.
I'm gonna find Nezuko
and then say goodbye
to this creepy forest.
Nezuko!
( Legs clatter )
( Puppet grunts )
ｶ
Inosuke: This thing's
got no weak spots.
Where am I supposed to cut it?
( Gasps )
( Tanjiro annoyed ) Inosuke.
Inosuke: What do we do?
What do we do?!
Tanjiro: Calm down.
Listen closely, all right?
Slash from
the right part of the neck
to the left part of its waist.
It'll be tough.
It's a lot of mass to cover.
That said...
( Inosuke laughs )
Tanjiro: No, wait!
Don't go alone!
Inosuke: It's fast.
( Growls )
( Groans )
I can still dodge it, though!
( Gasps ) That's right!
Those spiders!
( Gasps )
I can't move.
I'm a dead man!
( Gasping )
Tanjiro: Inosuke,
this is a tough one,
but we can do it.
If we put our heads together,
we'll be able to win!
Inosuke: Damn you!
Don't go making me
feel giddier than I already do!
( Chorus vocalizing )
This thing's in my way!
Tanjiro: Here!
Launch yourself!
ｶ
( Inosuke yells )
Tanjiro: Now jump! Go for it!
( Inosuke snarls )
Tanjiro: Total concentration.
Water breathing.
Fourth form...
Striking tide!
You're up, Inosuke!
Inosuke: It seems like he's
got everything figured out.
I gotta say
that's pretty irritating.
It's almost like he
can predict the future.
It's as natural for him
as water flowing from a river.
It's not about going first
for this kid.
It's all about
the battle itself
and watching it flow
like a raging current!
( Grunts )
( Mother gasps )
Tanjiro: Great!
He cut it perfectly.
All right, Inosuke!
You defeated it!
Hmm? What's wrong?
ｶ
( Tanjiro gasps )
Inosuke:
I'll prove to that idiot
anything he can do,
I can do, too!
( Grunting )
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Sniffs )
A scent?
So that's why
you did that, Inosuke!
( Mother whimpers ) No.
That doll was my fastest and
strongest, and they still won!
It's Rui's fault for coming
to me with his threats!
That's why I panicked.
It's not my fault.
( Whimpers )
( Gasps )
From above?
Tanjiro: Water breathing!
First form...
( Mother gasps )
He's going to cut my head off!
Oh, what do I do?
What do I do?!
ｶ
a-although...
If I die, I'll be freed.
I'll find peace.
( Tanjiro gasps )
Fifth form,
blessed rain after the drought.
ｶ
- ( water splashing )
- ( Mother sighs )
- ( Droplet echoes )
- This feeling,
it's like I'm being showered
by a gentle rain.
It doesn't hurt, not at all.
I just feel warm.
I never dreamed my end
would be this tranquil.
And now I'll be released.
( Mother screams )
( Sobbing )
I'm sorry!
I didn't mean
to make you so angry!
Tell me, what was it
that infuriated you?
Rui: It's your own fault for not
realizing what made him angry.
Mother: But how could I?
( Demon laughs )
Looks like mother's
in trouble with father again.
( Laughs )
( Mother shudders )
( Squeals )
No! Stop! No more!
( Sobbing )
( Wind blowing )
Those eyes.
Such kind eyes.
When I was human,
I think there was someone
who used to look at me
with those same kind eyes.
I wonder who that was.
ｶ
I can't remember.
I just know that it was someone
who always cherished me.
I wonder...
How that person is doing now.
( Sighs )
Someone from
the twelve kizuki is here.
( Tanjiro gasps )
W-Wait!
Mother: Be careful.
( Women vocalizing )
Tanjiro: A member
of the twelve kizuki,
they're here on this mountain,
just within my grasp.
( Vocalizing continues )
ｶ
( singing in Japanese )