If the strongest Level 5
in Academy City
is easily beaten by
the weakest Level Zero,
then surely they
would have no choice
but to suspend this absurd
experiment of theirs.
True, that's easier
said than done...
but it's still worth a try.
Don't you agree...
Misaka?
[Music]
Apparently there was flour
inside that container.
Hey, tell me something.
Have you ever heard
of a certain phenomenon
known as a dust explosion?
They can be quite
devastating.
Not fun, huh?
I told you, dust
explosions are nasty.
I'm surprised you lived.
Next time I try
something like that,
I need to remember not to put
myself in the middle of it...
I seriously thought
I was gonna die there.
You should be thrilled...
You accomplished something
nobody else in the
world has before...
Can't believe you
drove me to the point
where I damn near
got myself killed.
Try as hard as you want,
but you're wasting your time.
You won't make it
a step closer...
and let's be honest...
even supposing
you did make it,
what could you possibly
hope to accomplish?
You do know that my esper
power is the ability
to control any vector...?
All I would have to
do is touch you once...
With that one touch,
I could cause the blood
vessels and internal organs
from your body to burst...
Just so you know exactly
what you're up against.
Think about it...
You're still here, in
bad shape, but alive...
Considering that
I'm your opponent,
that's a miracle
in and of itself,
wouldn't you agree...?
Hoping for anything
more than that
is simply asking too much.
So then...
let's remedy that
situation, shall we?!
Good hit.
Damn, that wasn't
what I expected...
an impressively
solid hit...
I'm going to have to give
that one to you kid,
you totally nailed me.
Your turn now!
My right hand is working!...
Damn!
Damn it.
What the hell is going on?
Who is he?
Heh... You're not very
used to losing, huh?
You bounce back every attack
that's thrown at you...
So you usually beat your
opponents quickly...
It's not surprising
that a guy like you
doesn't know his way
around a fist fight.
I wouldn't boast
if I were you...
Now I'm angry!
Uh-oh.
Ten thousand sisters.
They lived as
best they could.
They used up all
their strength...
just to fight you...
They gave every ounce of
life they had inside them.
That was the only purpose
they were ever given:
to wind up as fodder for a
ruthless bastard like you.
Oh really, they lived
as best they could?
They gave every ounce of
life they had inside them?
What are you
talking about?
Now die!
Aw, poor baby,
you fell down.
Did I hurt you?
Can't you see you'll
never beat me?
In the end you're
nothing but big talk...
It's too late to
run away, hero boy.
You'll be nothing but
a stain on the ground
by the time I'm
finished with you!
Compress it...
compress it...
Compress the air.
Wait a sec...
Hah...! That's it...!
I've just had a
fantastic idea!
Hey, what happened to
all that spunk you had?
I need you to stick with
me for a little longer here,
or this won't be
worth the effort.
Accelerator!
Don't even think about it!
N-no.
You can't interfere... remember?
I'm sorry.
I really am...
I know you didn't want it
to wind up like this...
You wanted a
happy ending...
Where everybody's okay,
and no one loses anything...
but that just
isn't possible now.
So, again...
I'm sorry.
My reason for interfering
here might be selfish...
I know that.
But it doesn't
change the fact...
that I don't want you to
die tonight because of me.
No, Misaka!
Plasma?
He's controlling the
wind direction...
gathering it all
in one place...
And forming it into plasma.
Impossible.
I can't do anything
about that with my power.
If I could manipulate
the wind...
But that's beyond
my ability.
The wind!
From what I can tell,
Accelerator is forming
that sphere of plasma
by condensing the
wind around him.
I see...
He has to take into
account the flow of the wind
in order to control
the plasma...
In which case...
You need to wake up...!
There's something important
I have to ask you to do.
It's something
only you can do!
I realize that I'm
asking a lot of you...
but will you please just
wake up and help me?
I'll never ask anything
of you again...
Please...! I can't protect
everyone by myself.
No matter how hard I try,
there's no way...
none at all...
You're my only hope.
Please, I'm begging you...!
Get up and use your power,
not for me...
not for me, but for him!
"I'm not sure I understand
what you're saying.
But for some reason
I cannot explain,
your words have moved me...
So... I am happy to help you,"
Misaka answers.
Did I miscalculate
the wind somehow?
What...? How could this
be happening right now?
I know there were no glitches
in my calculations...
This is too irregular to
be any kind of natural wind.
Impossible.
Hold on... I've
heard about this...
Yeah, that's right...
It has something to do
with dynamo motors turning
when they're hit by particular
electromagnetic waves.
Damn you, you little punk.
I'll kill you.
You think I'm
going to let you?
Hah...! You're way out of
your league here, little girl,
and you know it...
If I wanna do something,
you can't stop me.
Visual acuity can only be
measured up to 20/20, right...?
My situation's like that...
Level 5 is the highest
rank an esper can attain
in Academy City...
So even though I'm better
than the rest of you,
I have to settle for that.
Stand down...
Right now.
Do you understand me...?..
Stand down... bastard.
You just won't quit.
I find that intriguing.
Let's finish this!
He's supposed to
be the strongest.
And I'm the weakest.
Let's see who's
the stronger one now!
What's happening?
W-w-w-what are you doing?
I mean... how did this most
fortuitous event come to pass
while I was sleeping...?...
I can't remember anything
that might have led
up to this situation.
"Just to set the record
straight, asleep or not,
you reached your
hand out toward me...
So... " Misaka then trails off.
You've gotta be kidding...
I swear, the anesthetic
is still in effect
from my neck down...
but apparently I'm so
pathetically frustrated
I'll grope at a
girl's chest even
when I'm numb throughout
most of my body...!
I'm shameless and disgusting!
"Reaching out
for Misaka's hand
was the extent of your
involvement in this situation,"
Misaka explains because
you seem so distressed.
"Bringing your hand
up to this position
was something Misaka
did of her own will...
your actions are neither
shameless nor disgusting,"
Misaka offers reassuringly.
"Misaka was using the
flow of bioelectricity...
I needed to do so
in order to monitor your
brainwaves and pulse,"
says Misaka
explaining her actions.
Really...? Is it still there?
Is my hand still
on your chest?
Because of the anesthetic,
I still can't feel
anything at all.
I can't so much as
move a single finger.
That is just my damn luck!
"Misaka does not
understand...
Is there some abnormality
in your speech center?"
Misaka asks,
expressing worry.
Well...
looks like we all managed
to get out of there safely.
"It is not as
simple as that,"
Misaka begins her reply...
"Regrettably, Misaka is not yet
able to live a normal life
in Academy City,"
Misaka expands upon
her former statement.
You don't mean...
the experiment is still...
"No... that is not the case...
It seems that because of the
sound defeat of Accelerator,
the experiment is indeed
headed for cancellation...
Done," Misaka intones with a
note of finality in her voice.
"The current issue is
not the experiment...
The problem is
Misaka's body,"
Misaka begins
her explanation.
-Your body?
-"Yes...
Misaka's bodies are clones...
They were originally created
by using Sister's cells...
Following creation,
our bodies have been
stimulated for rapid growth
by the administration
of certain drugs,"
Misaka continues.
"By their very nature,
cellular clones have
a shorter lifespan
than normal humans.
Because of rapid growth,
ours have been cut
even shorter than that.
Does that make sense?"
Misaka asks.
"So, it is necessary for
the research facility
to take us in temporarily,
and adjust us each
individually...
Are you even listening?
Your face looks blank,"
Misaka asks, glowering.
Adjust you how?
"It's simple...
They'll perform a hormone
balancing procedure
for our rapid growth...
Also, they will adjust
the mitotic rate
of our cellular nuclei...
This will allow
our lifespans
to be restored
to some degree."
"Well... that's all,"
Misaka says.
I'll leave now.
Hey, wait a second.
This "adjusting" stuff...
is it a cure?
"Do not worry...
I will see you
again soon...
Goodbye for tonight,"
Misaka says.
Okay...
there don't seem to be
any major problems...
but it does appear
that you have an unusual
fondness for hospital rooms.
Well... for the time being,
just get as much
rest as you can...
And I'll be back later.
Sounds good...
Thank you, Doctor.
So... you're awake.
Misaka... is that you?
Are you... one of the...
Here... Get well soon.
Oh... thank you.
I picked out the
most expensive ones
the department store had.
From the price,
I'm guessing
those are some
pretty good cookies.
Don't people always say homemade
cookies are the most tasty?
Oh, is that so...?
Can you seriously picture
me baking cookies?
No, never...
I imagine if you tried to,
you'd make a horrible
mess of the kitchen
and the cookies would all come
out misshapen and disgusting...
That's what you're
saying, right?
I meant baking's
not my style,
not that I couldn't do it!
Calm down!
I'm injured here!
Okay, fine.
Oh, yeah...
I meant to tell you that
your little sister came by
to see me earlier.
Did she?
Well, I'm heading home.
Hey, you know what?
If you had never offered
them your DNA map...
not a single one
of the sisters
would have ever existed
in the first place.
That experiment was messed
up in a lot of ways...
but at least there was something
good that came from it...
your sisters...
You can take
pride in that.
I can take pride, can I?
Even though ten
thousand of them
were mowed down
by Accelerator?
Yes, even so.
I'm sure that none of them
would blame you for it...
Think about it...
Without you, they wouldn't
have a chance at life at all.
So it's okay for you to let
yourself feel a little happy...
You know them much
better than I do.
Do you think they're
the type of people
who would feel gratified by
somebody else's pain...?
'Cause that's not
the impression I got.
Right.
Well, Toma... Is there
something you'd like to say?
I, uh...
nice morning, isn't it?
Hey, lay off! I'm
seriously hurt this time!
I can't take this
kind of abuse!
I'm too fragile...!
Come on...! Show a little
concern for my health, will you?
I was concerned!
I really was...
very much.
I'm sorry.
Silly boy...
You keep taking all these
problems on alone...
You should learn how to turn
to others for help sometime...
If you can't manage that,
then you'll leave me
with no other choice
but to start giving you some
serious lectures on teamwork.
Oh well, dwelling on it
won't make things any better,
so we can just let it
go for now, okay...?
Tell me one thing, though...
What was it that you were
fighting for this time around?
I was fighting for myself.
[Music]
What's supposed to be a
family reunion on the beach
is violently interrupted
by a magical disturbance.
You've gotta be
kidding me...!
That's my mom?!
Next time, "Angel Fall."
When science and
magic cross paths,
a story is born.