On a mission to rescue
the girl Aisa Himegami,
otherwise known
as Deep Blood,
I accompanied a sorcerer
on a raid of the
Misawa Prep School...
Inside, the alchemist
Aureolus Izzard awaited us,
with a power
beyond imagining.
As if things weren't
complicated enough,
now it looks like
Index is in there...!
What's going on?
[Music]
Are you sure? Do you
really have some idea
where this bastard is hiding?
Of course. Do you think
I would just wander
through the hallways
of this place
with no clue
where I was going?
I have to admit,
it's scary...
If this guy can really bend
reality to fit his words...
Damn... How are we supposed
to get Himegami out...?
and for all we know, Index
is in here somewhere now, too.
Even supposing she did wander
in here for some reason,
he's not going to
launch an attack on her
like he did us...
I know that much.
Hold on!
What is it now?!
That's what it is...!
Why didn't I see it!
He's been in hiding
for three years now...
There are some
developments
that he wouldn't know about.
We live in a world of faith
and magic and alchemy...
Yet despite this, injustices
still go unpunished...
Sometimes justice can
only be found outside
the realm of men.
What do you mean?
Patience... In time,
you too will be released
from your earthly sorrows.
Soon, perhaps.
Now you must use the
sweet aroma of your blood
to call them.
Do what you were made for,
and call the vampires here
from their faraway darkness.
My power will not
be used to hurt...
Not anymore.
Himegami!
Index!
Damn!
I have some bad news
for you, alchemist...
Your plan will
never succeed.
Oh... so you've
finally realized
what my intentions here are.
In that case, I expect you
will howl at your own impotence
when I achieve
what I mean to do.
A year ago I'd've done anything
to see your plan succeed...
but I tell you again...
nothing you do now will
help you to save her...
You can't do
anything for Index.
Index?
You speak out of jealousy
because you have failed
her in this... Not I...
I will not fail.
I will save her...
My Index.
She took the weight
of all the grimoires
upon her fragile shoulders...
She could never hope
to escape the spell
that was cast upon her.
But she has stayed strong.
She accepts the fate
decreed by the church......
hoping her own curse would
be a blessing for others.
Hold on... this
guy knew Index?
You see...
the alchemist here
was once Index's
partner as well.
This year you
have that honor...
Last year it was me,
and three years ago...
It was this man...
Aurelous Izzard.
Index's survival
is contingent upon the
annual erasure of her memory.
Without that process,
she will die.
An inescapable fate...
one that her human
body couldn't fight...
However... If her
body was not human,
then things might
be different.
Vampires are unique in that
they are immortal beings...
They store the memories
of innumerable lifetimes
within their brains.
And all those memories
do not kill them...
No matter how many things
they have to remember,
their brains never lose
the power to function.
That's the plan, then...?
You want the vampires
to teach you how they
manage what Index cannot.
Just out of curiosity...
What if it turns out
their technique doesn't
work for humans?
Obviously...
for it to work,
I'll have to remove
Index from her body.
So you're going to turn
her into a vampire.
Is he crazy?
He's using magic
against esper students.
Bending Himegami to
his twisted will.
And now he's
planning this...?!
To turn Index
into a vampire?!
I must.
It may not be ideal,
but it's the only
way to save Index.
Of all people, you
should understand.
You have witnessed what is
done to her every year...
and you know the pain and
horror of that damned ritual.
Just before it happened,
she told me that she
didn't want to forget...
She said even if it meant
going against the church
and her own death,
she didn't want
the memories
she carried in her
heart to vanish...
She was in so much pain
she could barely move.
But she smiled and she told
me she wanted to remember!
Then, nothing I've said so far
has changed your mind... huh?
Well, in that case...
Would you like
to do the honors,
as her current partner...?
Why don't you tell
this misinformed hack
about the recent
change in Index?
Alchemist... you have no idea
what you're talking about.
What's that?
Don't you see yet?
You can't do anything because
she's already been saved...
and not by you.
The title of 'savior'
belongs to Toma Kamijo here.
He's already accomplished
what neither you nor
I were able to do...
but of course, you
couldn't have known that...
having turned your
back on the Church
and spent three years
in hiding underground.
Impossible. There's no way...
Not like this...
with that body...
Not by him...
This boy is no sorcerer...
He's no alchemist to
possess such power!
What could someone
like him do?!
It's an unfortunate fact.
And an unsavory topic for
a member of Necessarius
so I won't speak
at length...
but essentially...
his right hand is something
known as Imagine Breaker...
Despite his appearance,
he possesses
significant power.
If what you say
is true, then...
That's right. All of your
efforts and sacrifices
have come to nothing
in the end...
but that shouldn't
matter to you...
Index is living a
very happy life now.
A happy life with the
partner who saved her.
It's what you always
wanted her to have.
Toma...
To... ma...
I'm here, Index!
Toma...
I'm really hungry.
An apple...
A juicy, red apple...
sounds tasty...
Perfect timing.
You will fall to the
floor, intruders!
You come in here and
trample my emotions.
You sneer at my travails.
Very well...
You will pay for
this humiliation...
You will pay with
your pathetic lives!
Stop, now!
Himegami! Careful!
I get it... I do...
I know what
you're feeling.
He'll hurt you...
he...
But this is wrong...
You cannot do this.
He... doesn't need you.
You cannot...
Just think...
It isn't you.
And I know the real you.
Die.
Himegami!
I wanted magic.
My foolishness
called them.
I'm sorry,
my sweet Aisa...
I'm so sorry!
And then before my eyes...
They all...
just disappeared.
They're all dead...
They are dead
because of me.
I didn't want to hurt
people anymore...
never again.
Is it true?
Can you really use my
blood to save someone...?
And no one will get hurt
because of me again?
There wasn't so much as the
hint of a lie in his smile.
No malice...
Just a simple wish...
to save somebody
he deeply loved.
And so...
I helped him.
Himegami!
Her existence is no
longer necessary.
And as you can see, I've
even kept my promise to her...
As she wished, I
have set the girl free
from the misfortune
of her sweet blood.
What?... You've somehow
managed to negate my Ars Magna?
Impossible...
Her death should've
been irreversible...
What kind of sacred
power do you have
embedded in that
hand of yours?
Stop your deranged
babbling...
You've clearly
been defeated.
It's time to give up.
But...
If you insist on believing
that you can
manipulate reality...
then I guess it's up to me
to show you how
wrong you are!
This floor is really cold.
You will choke.
Electrocute.
Be crushed.
It works... It
nullifies every attack.
So it is true...
Your hand's the
genuine article.
It is consistently able to
cancel out my Ars Magna attacks.
In which case, all I have
to do is use an attack
that your hand
cannot touch
and therefore
cannot nullify.
In my hand, a
gun will appear.
It will be loaded
with magic bullets,
any one of which may
carry your death inside it.
The bullets will travel faster
than the human eye can see.
The shooting will
now commence.
Did you think I'd let
you die so easily?
I'd like to see you
squirm a bit longer.
Magnify previous order!
Ten pistols, with
simultaneous fire!
I told you, I wasn't
done toying with you yet.
Damn.
That was practice ...
Now I'll show you what
my pistols can really do.
Well, what do you know?
You do seem to be
able to use words
to manipulate reality
in any way you wish.
Obviously... Ars Magna
is the strongest power
an alchemist can have...
I can do anything I...
Oh, really?
If so... what could you
possibly need Deep Blood for?
Why would you need her to
attract vampires for you...?
Couldn't you just create
them, without using her?
All it would take is a
few words from you, right?
So why didn't you
do it, alchemist...?
Why didn't you create vampires
using your Ars Magna...?
For that matter,
why would you even need
them at all if you could...
Into the air, you
meddling sorcerer!
Stiyl no!!
I'm wondering...
if there might be
limitations to your power.
Your skin will be
torn from your body!
That's it...!
I see what
Stiyl was doing.
If Izzard can make anything
he wishes become reality...
Then why the
elaborate plan?
Why didn't he use his
power to save Index?
I'm bored with
this game...
I believe I'll
switch weapons.
He didn't do it because
he didn't believe he could.
I'll destroy you
with a sword instead.
He didn't believe, so he
couldn't say the words.
Obviously...
the source of your
self-assurance
is your right hand,
which is also the only
weapon you have.
I think I understand now.
It's quite clear that my
first course of action
must be chopping
off your right arm.
His power to manipulate reality
with words isn't absolute...
It can be undermined.
For this last attack...
my spinning sword
will sever your arm.
He's... laughing?!
What's going on?
Who is this person?
I have a pistol.
It is combined
with a sword.
It will remove the
head of my opponent.
Commence second
spinning blade attack!
No...! Repeat the attack!
Multiplying spinning
blade ten-fold!
An endless array of
executioner's blades.
Dismember his
body immediately!
No...! Impossible...!
He's a mere human...
not even a sorcerer!
Hey, I have a
question, alchemist...
Honestly...
did you think you were
going to win...?
Did you really expect to
defeat Imagine Breaker
with an attack as
pathetic as that one?
You can't work your alchemy
without using those
needles, can you...?
You rely on them to keep any
stray thoughts from interfering.
Is something wrong...?
Come on now, use your words.
-Stay back!
-Why aren't you fighting...?
Can't you control me?
Stay... back!...!
No!
This cannot be...!
My Ars Magna is failing me
when I need it most!
Stop it! Don't think that!
You cannot think that!
No... don't question...!
Believe...! With the power I
have, they can't beat me!
I can defeat them!
You're no match
for me, alchemist.
I've figured it out...
I know the secret
of Ars Magna...
Your power is not making
your words into reality.
This boy is a monster!
No, your power is making
what you believe into reality,
and now that I know that,
I will crush you!
I'm impressed that it
reattached so cleanly.
Your body must be
fantastically adaptable.
Don't look at me, Doc,
you're the one
who reattached it.
You've been urgently
hospitalized twice
in only ten days...
What is it? Do you have
a thing for the nurses?
What are you
talking about...?
Do you really think I
would cut off my own arm
just to flirt
with some girls?
Oh... for a moment there
I thought we might have
something in common...
Never mind.
Yeah...
What a cliché...
He became a doctor because
of the cute nurses?
He's a better doctor
than you'd think
from looking at him.
Yeah, I guess.
I'm not trying to get
all cozy or anything.
But I thought maybe I should
come see how you were.
Oh... sure.
What is it?
The dragon?
It's nothing...
Just the manifestation
of the desperate terror
Aureolus felt
at the time.
What happened to the
alchemist, anyway?
Well, for starters he's
lost all of his memories...
and the ability
to use magic.
I didn't want his death
on my conscience...
so I changed
his appearance
and turned him
loose outside...
It was pretty tricky
getting him out
without the Knights
seeing him, though.
Oh, okay.
Word is that Misawa Prep
School has been shut down...
I was going to say
thanks for everything...
but now it seems kind
of absurd, you know...?
After all, in the end
you merely got Aureolus
to bring ruin
down on himself.
If anything, you
should be thanking me
for my superb
acting talent.
It wasn't easy though...
Surely even you have
to admit that much...
My arm was cut off,
and I had to act like
it hadn't happened
to keep our bluff going.
The pain must've
been intense enough
to put you in a
state of shock.
Thanks to that, you could just
do what needed to be done,
kind of like Aureolus
and his needles.
Do not compare me
to that psycho!
I mean, how crazy can
one guy possibly be?
He comes up with
some twisted magic...
And then tries to
conjure up vampires...
because he wanted
to save her...
to save Index.
So... he was her partner
three years ago, huh?
Toma!
I know what you were up to.
-Up to?
-That's right.
I know you risked your life
in a fight to save Aisa.
Aisa...?
Oh, you're talking about that
freaky pseudo-magician girl...?
Wait a second,
who did you hear that from?
I'd think it
would be obvious.
That was rude...
I'm no freak.
Oh, hi, Himegami...
I, uh, didn't expect to
see you here with Index.
It's not like I wanted
her to come with me
to visit you in
your sick bed.
But she kept saying
over and over
how desperate she
was to thank you.
Why did you do it?
You helped me...
I don't know why...
You could've died...
for some stranger.
I'm just some random girl
you met one day in a
fast food restaurant.
I don't see why I need a
reason to help somebody.
So anyway...
here's the deal...
Quit talking with
your mouth full.
And do you think you could
get off my lap already?
Listen to me.
After a lot of discussion,
it looks like the Church has
decided to take in Aisa.
Hey, hold on...
Are you talking about
the actual church
or your crazy Walking
Church robes?
I can never tell with you.
Sphinx! Where are
you running off to?
You can't bring a cat
with you to the hospital!
I told her she
would be better off
just leaving him
at the apartment.
Hey, by the way
you're talking
it sounds like you've
already been to my place!
Come back!
You come back here right
this minute, Sphinx!
Could we have some
peace and quiet in here?!
What are you doing?
Are you insane...?
Oh, geez, look what
he's done to the wall...!
You never should have
brought him here!
Damn, rotten luck!!
[Music]
Something seems off when I run
into this girl named Misaka
and her identical sister...
There's some strange guy
following the sister around...
What? He's a Level 5 esper?!
Next time, "Mikoto Misaka."
When science and
magic cross paths,
a story is born.