September 1st marked the end
of a turbulent summer vacation.
It turns out our new
transfer student is Index...
wait, no... it's Himegami.
I took Index
and her new friend,
a girl named Hyoka Kazakiri
to have some lunch at
the underground mall.
We probably
wouldn't have gone
if we had known what was going
to happen while we were there.
[Music]
Thank you, have a good day.
Ah, that was officially
a delicious meal...
Now my tummy feels full,
full, full, full, full!
What's all this...?
It looks like a whole
bunch of television sets.
How cool...! I've never
seen a TV like this before!
Um, Index...
So you know, that
isn't actually a TV.
My phone...
Who is it...?
I'll catch up in a sec, okay?
C'mon, Hyoka, let's go!
Yes, hello?
It's... gami...
careful... Ka... iri...
Hey, wait...
Well. We're underground... so...
Oh, wow...!
These are adorable!
So cute, so cute,
so cute...!
Look, Hyoka...!
Aren't these little
things darling?
Oh... yeah!
Hey... look over there!
I love how many costumes
they had to choose from...
It's an impressive
selection.
Yeah... That maid costume
was totally cute too!
Index... Right there.
I think you choose from one
of the costumes they have.
And then you can get
your picture taken
in one of those
photo booths.
Oh, wow...! That sounds
like a lot of fun!
Come on, let's try it!
Um, I don't know
about this...
Hello, Index...?
Where are you guys?
This is amazing!
Look at this...
They even have a Magical
Powered Kanamin costume!
Um... are you really
going to wear that?
Yep, I sure am!
In here, huh?
Hey, Index,
are you in there?
Yikes...! T-T-Toma!
Uh, please wait there.
Don't open the
curtain right now.
Right... I'm not gonna make
the same mistake I made earlier.
That was embarrassing
for everyone.
Hey... Take it easy...
No pushing.
So cool...
Here, we can
split them up...
This can be your half.
Thanks.
So this is what it's like
to be a student here, huh...?
You guys have it made!
Yeah, except for all the boring
classes and hellish tests...
Oh, and then there's the
mountains and mountains
of homework you have to do.
What's that?
Did you hear it?
Yeah.
What's up you guys...?
Is something the matter?
I heard a voice from
somewhere just now.
-A voice?
-Yeah...
It almost felt like it was
talking directly inside my head.
A voice inside your head...?
-That's kind of...
-You, there! Move it!
How much more warning
do you three need...?
I can't believe you're
just standing there.
What's Judgment doing here?
Um... Something wrong?
Oh, brother...
Listen to the telepathic
warning, you idiots...
I'll give you
one more chance.
Here.
You get that...?
Understand the situation now?
Nope... not at all.
This doesn't
make any sense...
I don't know why the message
wouldn't be getting
through to you.
I'll have to explain
it out loud, then...
"Warning...
A terrorist has been detected
in the underground mall."
There's a terrorist here?
That's correct...
We're about to
lower the barriers
and seal off
the whole mall...
It's important that you
evacuate immediately...
Now get moving.
I think we should
take her advice...
Let's get out
of here quickly.
I found you.
What the hell is that?
A creature made from
earth to imitate man.
A golem or protector
of the temple...
It's being made to serve as
an English guardian angel.
Are you saying...
the terrorist they
detected is a sorcerer?
Now... let's get
this party started.
You can scream as
loud as you'd like...
Nobody is going to
hear you in this tomb.
What's happening?
Hey...! Let us
out of here!
What's going on?
Open up!
All right, Index...
take Kazakiri and
go hide somewhere.
You take Kazakiri
and hide somewhere...
The enemy is a sorcerer...
And that means this
is a job for me.
How do you expect
to win in a fight?
You're a tiny little girl!
Listen up...! Do you
think you've survived
this many fights on your
own by being lucky...?
You know perfectly
well you're an amateur
when it comes to magic.
Yeah, right...
How could I possibly
think that...?
I am Toma Kamijo,
the single unluckiest person
on the face of the earth,
so no, I don't...
Not exactly something
to brag about.
Toma, excuse me...
I don't really understand
what's going on...
but if there's anything
I can do to help,
I would like to...
-No way!
-Go hide, Index!
-Quick, Toma, run!
That's strange...
I could've sworn I just
heard a cat meow somewhere.
Me too.
Hey...
What are you doing here?
Taking a quick nap?
How scandalous...!
Such behavior, and
at a time like this.
Explain, Toma.
Exactly who are these crass
girls, and why are they here?
You know them?
Um, excuse me...?
Just who the hell do
you think you are...?
Saying something like that
to people you've never met?
Admit it... I'm right.
You do know Toma,
don't you...?
So, what exactly is your
relationship with him?
What...? What
relationship?
How about you start by
telling me who you are.
Well, uh...
I kind of owe my life
to him and stuff.
Oh, really...?
Don't tell me.
He came to your rescue
without asking
if you needed him to.
-Toma!
-Listen up, you!
Uh, yes, ma'am?!
Would you care to explain
your irresponsible
behavior, young man?
Well... You see...
I, um...
I see now...
I thought something was feeling
a little bit off lately...
Now I learn Sissy has decided
that my love is
insufficient for her needs
and instead given herself, body
and soul, to Mr. amijo here.
That is absolutely
not what's happening!
Well... What now?
What kind of trouble
have you managed
to get yourself
into this time?
How should I know?
Shirai... do you think
you could explain
the situation here?
Authorities have
discovered a terrorist
operating in the
underground mall...
There is a real possibility
of a large-scale battle
breaking out down here...
So I've been charged with
getting all the citizens
who are trapped in the
mall safely evacuated.
They chose me because
I'm a master teleporter.
All right, then
you get to work
getting everybody
out of here...
Meanwhile, I'll see what I
can do to buy you some time...
You're the first one to go.
No arguing!
But don't you understand?
With my right hand, I can render
any power ineffective...
I have no choice but to
stay and see what I can do.
We should also consider the
limitations of my power...
I can only carry two
people each trip.
I'm going to
need some time.
Okay... then please take
Index and Kazakiri first.
Really, Toma...?
You want some quality time
alone with the loudmouth girl?
Is that what you're
trying to say?
Okay then... take Misaka
and Kazakiri first.
Oh, I see......
What you want is to stay behind
with this little freak show.
Damn my luck.
Okay then,
you're going first.
But Kuroko...
Sorry about that...
It's my fault you
got left behind.
I'll be just fine...
I promise.
Forget me; what about you?
Looks like it's starting.
All right...
I hate to do this...
but you need to wait here until
Kuroko comes back for you.
But... what will you do?
I've got a sorcerer
to take care of.
We're not even
making a dent in it.
Not everyone's
evacuated yet.
We have to do something!
You have considerable
strength,
but you're lacking style...
Ellis!
Are you all right?
Are you a student...?!
What are you doing?
You shouldn't be down here.
Well, I'm...
I'm here to...
You're that odd boy
from Miss Tskuyomi's class.
Get back behind
the barricade...!
Right now!
Good afternoon, young man.
Oh, what's this...?
You're the one who
wields Imagine Breaker...
You're not with the key
to the Imaginary
Number School District.
Now what was that
brat's name, again?
Oh, well...
It's not as if she's
the only one I can kill.
I do have options...
I'll be happy to take time out
of my day to kill you instead.
The power of the earth
is under my control....
You will not
survive for long.
With Ellis, the very
ground will fight you.
Damn sorcerer.
There's no need
to be rude...
Call me Sherry Cromwell.
Regardless... you're
going to die here,
but I might as
well tell you
I'm with the
English Puritan Church.
That's Index's church...
Why would one of their members
do something like this?
Simple. Because I
want to start a war...
and this will be
what begins it.
So, for maximum impact,
I want to make
sure everyone knows
that I'm one of
the Church's pawns.
I need a plan, here...
If I could just touch
that thing for a second!
U-Um...
Kazakiri!
What are you doing here...?!
You should be
waiting for Shirai!
Well... I know... but I...
Never mind,
just get down now!
Kazakiri!
What the...
What is that?
My... glasses?
My head...
What happened?
Impossible...
No...! W-what's
happening to me?
Kazakiri...
No!
No, not that way!
Now, Ellis!
Kazakiri!
Come along, Ellis...
Our work isn't done yet.
We have more hunting to do.
Geez...
where could those
idiots have gotten to?
What am I supposed
to do now?
Please let us out!!
I'm worried about what
happened to those two...
but I can't spend
time looking for them
when these people
are trapped.
Kazakiri...
Damn it...
What is that
sorcerer up to now?
I'm kinda busy here.
Oh, good.
Is that you, Kamijo?
Finally, I was
able to get you!
Himegami has been trying to
reach you, without any luck.
She must have called a
hundred times, at least.
-Himegami was calling me?
-Yes...
and there's something important
I need to tell you, too.
Yeah, I'm sorry, but this isn't
really the best time for me...
I have to go.
Does whatever's happening
have something to do
with your new friend?
Please listen to
me for a minute...
We've discovered something
that's very strange...
We don't understand
why or how yet,
but Hyoka Kazakiri
doesn't show up on any
of the security cameras
around the school.
We know that you
were with her...
Can you tell me where, exactly,
she entered the school?
Maybe we can take a closer look
at the cameras in that area.
Wait... can you back up
for a second?
I don't get
what you're saying.
Remember the AIM
diffusion fields
I was telling you about...?
We believe Kazakiri is
somehow connected to them.
Yeah, I remember.
But what do you
mean by "connected?"
Now, keep in mind that this
is all just conjecture...
It has to do with
bioelectricity emissions
and the magnetic fields
that they form...
oxygen consumption and carbon
dioxide expulsion, etcetera.
Basically, we have
all the components
that combine to form a human
being coming together...
in which case... wouldn't
you then expect a person
to be created as a result?
There are all kinds of
espers in Academy City....
And each one is constantly
emitting a slight force
without even
being aware of it.
What if, with so many
fields overlapping,
they begin to coalesce
to create something...?
And what if that
creation is the "person"
we know as Hyoka Kazakiri?
Don't you think that's
a bit of a stretch?
Apparently, there have
been sightings of Kazakiri
going back a long time...
I believe in the
earlier instances,
she was a more
indistinct being...
kind of like what we
imagine ghosts to be.
Maybe... but even if what
you're saying is right,
I don't believe Kazakiri
is aware of it at all.
That's hardly
surprising...
Why wouldn't she believe
she was human...?
She looks like one
and talks like one...
There would be no reason
for her to doubt it.
But regardless of
what she believes...
Hyoka Kazakiri is definitely
not a human being.
She is essentially an
anthropomorphic manifestation
of the AIM diffusion fields.
That's crazy.
Damn...
It's almost too
awful to believe.
Awful or not, it's true.
Do you hear what
I'm saying, Kamijo...?
It doesn't matter
that she's made from
all the component parts
that form a person...
not at all...
Despite whatever
you want to believe,
Kazakiri is not human.
Of course... does
that really matter...?
Why does she have to
be a human being...?
Think about it, Kamijo.
How do you see her
now that you know?
Is Hyoka Kazakiri nothing
more than an illusion...?
Is she just some
soulless image
that happened to
appear one day,
haphazardly thrown together?
Is her presence
so insubstantial
that nothing would change
if she disappeared?
No way...! That's not
what she's like at all...!
But even if she was
some ephemeral phantom
that could disappear
at any moment...
I could never
just stand by
and watch while someone
attempted to harm her.
I'm so glad to hear
you say that...!
I love it when my
little lambs figure out
the right thing to
do all on their own.
It's so rewarding to me...
Keep up the good work, Kamijo,
and I'm sure everything will
turn out all right in the end!
You can do it!
Okay then, bye-bye!
My, my, look what I found.
You're said to be the key
to the Imaginary
Number School District,
but you are a sorry sight.
I imagined
better than this.
I'll never be able to understand
these science-minded types...
jealously hanging onto
something like you.
Why are you here...?
What is it that
you want from me?
Hold on... what's this...?
Am I sensing a
little fear...?
Don't tell me that
you're actually afraid
to lose your sorry life...
Give me a break!
I can't believe you
haven't figured it out yet.
You are not,
nor will you ever be,
a real human being.
There's no need to go all
pale and trembly on me.
Here...
See? This is all that's
going to happen to you.
It's like smashing
an inanimate object.
Are you beginning
to understand?
You're just like my Ellis ...
A monster.
There is no place
for you here
or anywhere else
in the world.
That doesn't mean
she can't be my friend.
Please, Hyoka! I'd love
it if you'd join us!
Okay... we'll split them...
these can be yours.
Now, now, monster,
there's no need for tears.
Crying only makes
you look more pathetic
and that much
easier to destroy!
I'm really sorry
to keep you waiting.
Don't worry...
Everything will be all right.
[Music]
Listen to me, Kazakiri...
Your kindness is
no mere illusion.
It doesn't matter to me
whether you're human or not.
We're going to save you!
Next time, "Friends."
When science and
magic cross paths,
a story is born.