This summer vacation
was an eventful one,
to say the least...
As a result, I did virtually
none of the homework
I'd been assigned
for the break.
My most recent adventure
involved posing as
Zapper's boyfriend
and fighting a sorcerer...
I'm not the only one
who's been busy, though...
Shortly after midnight
on August 31st,
Accelerator had an unexpected
encounter of his own...
[Music]
After losing a fight
to that Kamijo guy,
I seem to have
lost my status
as the strongest esper
in Academy City.
I'm still a
Level Five esper.
And my abilities haven't
lessened or changed at all.
But no matter how many times
I prove myself against them,
these fools keep thinking
they can challenge me.
I'm trying...
but I can't figure out
what the difference is.
Something is
different, though.
I can feel it in the way
people look at me ...
but I can't put
my finger on it...
What has changed about me?
I may be a nun, but I'm
still a girl, you jerk!
I refuse to believe that
the sight of me in the bed
didn't affect you at
least a little bit.
I'm glad I can reflect
that noise away.
Huh...? A tiny
walking blanket...
and it's talking to me...
What does it want?
"Oh, my...
so unresponsive...
That's a pretty
fascinating indicator
of your personality type...
but it doesn't seem like
you're ignoring me on purpose...
and you're not trying
to get away from me."
"So I must conclude
that you're the world's
biggest space cadet,"
Misaka Misaka says,
tilting her head.
Who is this little freak?
Misaka Misaka is
vehemently trying
to assert her own existence,
and by remaining silent,
you're invalidating
her presence!
Huh?
Hold it... you said Misaka?
"Oh...! Misaka
Misaka's existence
has been acknowledged...! Yay!"
Misaka Misaka cries,
congratulating herself.
Short stuff...
Stop the chattering
and take that blanket off.
I wanna get a better
look at your face.
Hold on, you can't
just ask a girl
to take her clothes off
in the middle of the street.
That's downright creepy,
and I have no intention of...
What the...?
Misaka's serial
number is 20001...
She was commissioned
as the final Sister,
and is mostly referred
to as Last Order...
She was supposed to be
used in the experiment
and, obviously, wasn't...
This upsets Misaka Misaka.
She expected things
to be different.
You don't say.
As you well know, the
experiment was canceled.
Its termination meant
that Misaka Misaka
was released from
the incubator early,
so she's tinier than
all the other sisters.
Hey, are you
even listening?
I don't know what you
expect me to do about it.
Since you were the focus
of the experiment,
you've got connections
with all the researchers...
Misaka Misaka thought
maybe you could
contact them for her.
Go ask somebody else.
"Yay...! Finally, a direct
response from you...!
Oh, wait. That was
a flat refusal,"
Misaka Misaka realizes sadly.
But unfortunately,
there's nobody else
for her to turn to,
so Misaka Misaka can't
afford to give up.
"Thanks in advance
for your help,"
Misaka Misaka says,
assuming that you'll give in.
"What a big building...!
Which apartment is yours?"
Misaka Misaka
asks curiously.
Number 304.
"Hello! It's a
pleasure to meet you,"
Misaka Misaka offers
a polite greeting.
Hey, what're you
doing in here?
"That wasn't your apartment.
It's somebody else's
place entirely...
Misaka Misaka is
angry with you now...
You can apologize
by telling me
which apartment
is really yours,"
Misaka Misaka
demands stiffly.
Oh, all right.
It's 307.
Hello! It's a
pleasure to meet you.
You're not the
delivery guy!
"How can you be so mean to a
poor, helpless little girl?"
Misaka Misaka asks,
sticking out her lower lip
and hunching over dejectedly.
What the hell happened
to my apartment?
Oh, wow...
It looks like a hurricane
came through here.
Misaka Misaka is
practically speechless.
Seriously lame.
"So, uh...
Don't you think you should
call Antiskill or Judgment
and report what
happened to this place?"
Misaka Misaka asks,
casually sticking her nose
in where it doesn't belong.
What are gonna do now...?
Given the circumstances,
you might be safer
sleeping on the streets
than staying here.
"Well... That might be true,
but even so, I would
prefer to stay here,"
Misaka Misaka
entreats earnestly.
What...?
Why do you want to?
Misaka Misaka doesn't
wanna be alone...
so... she'd like to
stay here with you.
Suit yourself.
I'm warning you right now,
sneaking into bed
with Misaka Misaka
is absolutely unacceptable,
so don't ev...
Shut up!
"You can tell a
lot about people
by observing their facial
expressions while they sleep,"
Misaka Misaka states with
a chipper note in her voice.
You're still here?
That's just excellent.
It's a beautiful morning...!
Actually, I guess a beautiful
afternoon at this point...
Anyway, I'm hungry...
Do you think you could make
me something yummy to eat...?
If you did, Misaka Misaka
would be really grateful to you!
Um... I'm pretty
sure the kitchen
is in the other direction.
Do I look like somebody who
does a lot of cooking to you?
"I was hoping
you would have an
apron-wearing, whisk-wielding,
domestic side to you,
but I suppose that was
being overly optimistic,"
Misaka Misaka grumbles.
Hey, wait for me!
Misaka Misaka is
wondering something.
Is that your natural hair
color, or do you dye it?
I couldn't tell you exactly
how it works, myself...
It has to do with
skin pigmentation,
the stuff that protects
you from ultraviolet rays.
My esper powers reflect
all those unwanted rays
from me automatically...
So I don't need pigmentation
like other people do.
"Interesting...
So it has nothing
to do with you
wanting to look cool
and intimidating,"
Misaka Misaka says, surprised.
-What should I get?
-I'm getting a headache.
There's so much
to choose from.
They have pizza and burgers
and spaghetti, too...
Ooh, and even curry!
That guy...
Is that Ao Amai?
That bastard...
What the hell could
he be doing here?
"What are you looking at?"
Misaka Misaka
inquires curiously.
Stay focused on
the task at hand!
Do you remember
why we're here?
"Yeah...! We're here to
get something good to eat,"
Misaka Misaka promptly
answers the question.
Thank you for waiting.
"This'll be the
first hot meal
I've ever had in
my whole life!"
Misaka Misaka says
with much glee.
Is this over yet?
What's the matter...?
Why aren't you eating it?
It's proper etiquette
to give thanks for
the food before eating.
Misaka Misaka would like to
do so to show her manners.
Whatever...
Do what you want.
Thanks for all the food!
"This is the most
delicious food ever!"
Misaka Misaka
says excitedly.
Huh...? The stuff they serve
here is freeze-dried junk.
They're not really known
for their fine cuisine.
"That doesn't matter.
What's good is good...
And sitting down at the
table to eat with someone else
only makes it taste
that much better,"
Misaka Misaka explains
philosophically.
Yeah, sure...
I don't understand
what you're doing here...
You do know what happened to
the rest of your little family
when they met me,
don't you?
"My brainwaves are connected
to all other Misakas,
so of course I know
everything that happened,"
Misaka Misaka replies
matter-of- factly.
Then how can you sit here
with me looking so calm?
"The worth of Misakas
was explained to me,"
Misaka Misaka says.
Huh?
Even if an individual
Misaka unit dies
the Misaka Network
will remain intact,
and no important
information will be lost...
But even so, each Misaka
unit has worth of her own
beyond the Network.
There's only one of you in the
entire world, isn't there?
That Misaka was told there
are actually people out there
who shed tears when one
of the Misakas dies...
So we don't sacrifice
ourselves anymore.
Since we have
individual worth,
we can't keep throwing
our lives away.
That's what Misaka
Misaka believes.
And it's all
because of you...
Without you, the experiment
wouldn't have happened...
and souls would've
never been put
inside the lifeless
Misaka bodies...
So Misaka Misaka
is grateful to you.
You're grateful?
You know that's
absurd, right?
Don't you get that
I enjoyed killing you?
Doing it gave me a thrill
each and every time.
That isn't true.
Misaka Misaka has come to
a different conclusion...
You did not
actually desire
to go through
with the experiment...
or so Misaka Misaka
assesses the situation.
Oh, come on. You must be
seriously twisting the facts
to come up with that idea.
I was perfectly happy to
keep on killing you people
for as long as the
experiment was active...
I don't know why you
would think differently.
Think back to all
those battles...
You spoke to Misaka
many times during them.
"So...? Why would
you do that?"
Misaka Misaka says, asking
the obvious question.
Why are you running
away like that for?
Don't get me wrong,
I do appreciate the view.
You've got such a
cute little ass.
I hate to question you
when you're so diligently
performing your role
in an experiment to
increase my strength,
but you strike me as
unnaturally relaxed
given the situation.
I thought we might be
able to kill a little time
before we got to it...
but this is just hopeless.
There's no point
in trying to hold
a normal conversation with you.
In Misaka Misaka's
estimation,
you picked rather strange
times to make conversation.
Generally speaking,
the main reason you draw someone
into conversation with you
is to establish some sort
of connection with them.
"If you were really
only concerned
with the success
of the experiment,
then there would be no
reason for you to converse,"
Misaka Misaka
states reasonably.
I was trash talking.
I don't see how
that makes you think
I was trying to establish
a connection with you.
"Yes... that's the second odd
thing about your behavior,"
Misaka Misaka agrees,
holding up two fingers
to illustrate.
You were consistently
arrogant and rude...
Everything you said was
abusive towards Misaka...
That suggests that your
motivation went beyond
simply making
a connection.
However, the fact that
your words were cruel
does not mean that they
were intended maliciously.
In this analysis, we must
also consider the timing...
As far as Misaka Misaka
can recall,
you always initiated
conversation
before the battles began.
"It was almost like you were
trying to intimidate Misaka
into backing down...
like you wanted
Misaka to say
that she did not want to fight
you," Misaka Misaka observes.
Of course, it didn't work...
The Misakas couldn't
understand
what you were
attempting to do.
But what would you have
done if Misaka had told you
she didn't wish to continue?
Misaka Misaka believes
things would've turned
out very differently.
I'm getting tired of
listening to this crap.
Hey...
"Misaka Misaka's body
isn't complete yet.
Her physical condition
is still less than perfect.
Normally, she wouldn't
even be out of the incubator
at this point,"
Misaka Misaka clarifies
the reason for her collapse.
"Up until now, she has
been able to manage,
so she assumed she
would be all right.
Perhaps she was mistaken,"
Misaka Misa...
Hey...
"What is it...?
Why are you still
standing...?
You're not leaving
already, are you?"
Misaka Misaka
asks, pleadingly.
"There is still a
lot of food left."
Yeah, well after all this talk
I've kinda lost my appetite.
Oh, okay...
Misaka Misaka is
disappointed though...
She had hoped you would
finish the meal together...
She didn't even get
to order dessert.
Yeah, well.
Life's tough, kid.
You should get used to it.
Of all places, this is
where my feet carried me?
Hey.
Hey, Accelerator,
welcome back.
You didn't have to break
the door down, you know...
Your ID is still good
for another 90 days.
It's a little late
to be telling me that.
Right.
I bet you're having
the time of your life,
stuck in this room going
through data all day.
Actually, it's not
as fun as it looks...
I certainly wouldn't
mind the help
if you're here
to volunteer it.
Hah... I'll pass.
So, anyway...
I just came to
get the manual
for adjusting
the Sister units.
And also, I need to borrow some
of your conditioning equipment.
Don't ask why, Yoshikawa.
Think of it as an
outstanding contract fee
for ending the experiment
ahead of schedule.
Something's going on...
I didn't even notice it
until a couple hours ago...
I was just about to begin
purging the bugs in
their personality data
before you barged
into the lab...
-How did you know about it?
-Huh?
About the disturbance
strictly speaking, it should
actually be called a virus.
Hold on... A virus?
What are you
talking about?
Oh, I just assumed that's
why you came here
looking for the manual...
Did I ever explain to you
about the special unit
we developed
called Last Order?
No, you never did...
So, that one's special?
"That one" is, yes.
Last Order wasn't
created to be used
as part of the experiment.
You're saying you
didn't intend for me
to kill all of them
during the experiment?
That's right...
Think back to
the beginning.
Do you remember
how many battles
were projected
to take place
before the experiment
would come to a conclusion?
Exactly 20,000.
Misaka's serial
number is 20001...
She was commissioned
as the final Sister,
and is mostly referred
to as Last Order.
Yes...
She was a unit that
the experiment parameters
didn't call for.
Last Order is the "control
tower" for the Misaka Network...
As such, she was held in an
incomplete developmental state.
Her existence
was kept secret
even after the
experiment had ended...
But somebody
found out about her
and managed to overwrite
the code in her brain
with an illegal program.
Her escape from the
laboratory was an attempt
to prevent that somebody
from succeeding...
It's been seven days
since she got out.
The virus that
I've isolated
is set to trigger at midnight
tonight, September 1st...
If it does activate,
it will run rampant,
spreading through the
entire Misaka Network
and infecting
all the Sisters...
Once that happens,
there will be no stopping it.
We'll be helpless.
What does this virus contain
that's so dangerous?
As far as I can tell...
an order to launch
an indiscriminate
attack on humanity.
Ha! That is intriguing...
Who's behind it?
A terrorist group?
A rouge defense contractor?
Ao Amai.
One of the former Radio
Noise Project researchers...
Nobody else is in
a better position
to understand the Sisters'
personality data than he is.
I saw him earlier outside
a restaurant. Huh.
You can't be serious.
If what you
suspect is true,
how do we go about
stopping the virus
he's planted in her head?
I'm doing everything
I can to figure that out...
but if I can't find a
solution before time runs out,
there's only one choice.
You mean, that kid
is gonna have to be...
Uh-huh...
Her destruction will
be the only option...
but I'm working hard to make
sure that doesn't happen...
Of course, there's always
something you could do, too.
Hah...
In case you've
already forgotten,
I'm the one who killed ten
thousand of the Sisters...
and now you're asking
me to save one of them?
You were not in charge
of the situation.
We're the ones who
directed you to do
what you did to them...
There was no other way
that we could advance
you to a Level 6...
If we'd found a method that
didn't involve the Sisters,
you wouldn't've
had to kill anybody.
But unfortunately,
we had no choice.
That's a nice speech,
but I don't know that
it's enough to convince me
to trust you.
If you don't want
to help with this,
I'm not going to force you.
Right now, there are
two things you could do...
One is solving
the problem entirely
by tracking down Ao Amai
and getting him to give up
information on the virus.
The other would be securing
Last Order and the virus
before it activates and
returning her to the incubator
so we can contain
the threat.
You appear to be familiar
with both Amai and Last Order,
so I'll leave it at that.
Here's the necessary
data on both of them.
Choose whichever
you'd like.
I think I can guess
which you'll go for.
You've always been bigger on
destroying than protecting.
I guess I can't
argue with that.
This isn't exactly
a tough decision...
It's obvious which
one I should choose.
[Music]
With only a short
time remaining
before the virus
is triggered,
desperate measures
may be necessary.
Can Accelerator stop the
virus and save Last Order?
Next time, "Virus Code."
When science and
magic cross paths,
a story is born.