Toma!
Come on, Toma!
I am currently away
from Academy City...
Index and I are staying at
some out of the
way beach resort...
Obviously, this little
vacation was not my idea.
What do you mean
I have to get out of
the city immediately?!
Your recent adventures
have caused quite an uproar
among the higher-ups...
The things you've
been up to...
reflect poorly
on Academy City,
so they want you to
keep a low profile...
at least until the
worst of it blows over.
They've even arranged
a place for you
to stay for a while...
Let's see here...
Ah! There it is...
It looks like a pretty
nice place, don't you think?
I'm going!
I don't care what you say,
I'm coming with you...
You have to take me!
I've never even been
to the beach before!
I told you no... Got it...?
Think you can be reasonable
for once in your life?
You're an illegal
immigrant with no ID.
If I brought you along,
we'd just be stopped at the
gate by Antiskill and arrested.
No, means no,
that's final.
Go on through.
How is that possible?
You call yourself security?!
So, just like that,
I'm on the beach with Index,
and I don't really
understand why.
I have a bad
feeling about this.
I'm guessing they had a
reason for picking this place.
I don't think it was
a random decision.
Toma...
I found a cute hat when
I was out on the beach...
I brought it back here
as a present for you.
Uh... thanks.
Here, try it on.
[Music]
What bad luck, this happening
so soon after you arrived.
It's early in the
season for jellyfish,
but this year they've been
all over the place.
Business has really taken a
nosedive thanks to the outbreak.
I didn't mean to,
I swear...!
I didn't know what jelly
fish looked like.
This is the first
one I've ever seen.
All right, then.
I'll come back in a little
while for the first aid kit.
Oh, sure... Thanks.
Sorry to interrupt.
While you were out there
was a call from the party
that's joining you.
They said that there
has been a delay,
and they will arrive
tomorrow morning instead.
What...?!
That can't be right!
I was supposed to
meet them today!
-I was looking...
-We understand.
Thanks for giving
us the message.
It's not a problem.
If you'll excuse us.
Well, that's
disappointing!
Yeah... this is where I'm
supposed to meet them.
Their names are Toya
and Shina Kamijo.
In other words,
my parents.
Hey, Toma!
Are you ready...?
Let's go!
Miss Komoe must've
arranged this get together
because we don't see
each other often...
My little cousin is
supposedly with them, too.
Hey, tell me something.
What?
Tell me about
your parents.
What are they like?
Wh-What are they like...?
I bet you're a lot like
your dad, aren't you...?
I'm excited to meet them.
I hope they like me.
Well...? Are you
listening over there?
Yeah, I'm listening...
You'll find out what
they're like tomorrow.
Hey... why are you always
so rude to me, Toma?
Would it kill you to tell
me something about them...?
You, Toma Kamijo, are
a cold, heartless, curt,
indifferent, impolite, mean,
inconsiderate young man.
I swear, half the time
I don't know why I bother
putting up with you!
Well... we'll both
find out tommorow.
I can't tell
Index about them.
Since I lost my memory,
I don't know.
I wonder what
they're like...
What kind of son am I...?
How am I ever gonna
pull this off?
And now, the man you've
all been waiting for...
Welcome Hitotsui Hajime!
Hi.
Hey, everybody.
Considering everything
that's going on,
I don't think it's
too surprising
that I'm anxious right now.
Is everybody gonna
finally find out
that I've lost my memory?
Oh well, worrying's not
gonna help anything...
I'll just deal with
tomorrow when it gets here.
Yes?
Oh right.
Thanks!
Toma!
You're looking well, son...
Anything new with you?
Oh... no...
You look good, too.
I've got something
here for you,
if I can just find
where I put it...
I went to India on
business not too long ago.
I got this souvenir
while I was there.
The shop owner told me
it's one of their gods.
It's great, thank you.
Is something
bothering you?
The way you're talking,
you'd think you just met me.
Oh, uh, no, I....
Here, let me get your bag.
You can get your
mother's and Otohime's...
They should be getting
here about now.
We can wait.
So this man is my father.
Sorry we were so late...
I know we said we'd
be here yesterday,
but we just finished
moving in...
You know how
hectic moving is.
We're still
getting adjusted.
You guys moved?
I told you...
last month when we
spoke on the phone.
Oh... right.
All right... I guess I
won't get to see the house
I grew up in...
Oh well, it's fine.
Toma!
Oh... they made it.
So that's my
little cousin.
I'm so happy to see you!
I missed you so much!
I'm so glad we're
all here...!
Are you happy to see me...?
Huh?
What d'you say, Toma...?
Will you take me to
the beach later?
So? Will you?
Well...? You
will, won't you?
Wait... Hold on a minute!
Huh...? Why?
What's wrong?
What the hell do
you think is wrong?
What are you
doing here...?
And what's with this gross
younger sister act you're doing?
What do you mean?
Dad, what are you doing
bringing her along on
vacation with you...?
And how do you even
know each other?
What're you talking
about Toma...?
I've known her as
long as you have.
She's your little cousin
Otohime, isn't she?
You idiot, cut it out...
Stop it... right now...!
Get off my back!
Look at you two.
Toma, there's no need
to be embarrassed.
Otohime just
wants to hug you
because she hasn't seen
you in so long, that's all.
Great timing...
What the hell are
you doing here?
My goodness...
What's happened to your
language, young ma...
When I left a minute ago,
you were sleeping
soundly in the room...
What did you do,
teleport here...?
I mean do you think you're
Kuroko Shirai or something...?
And why are you talking
like some old lady?
Scolding me for
my language,
and calling me young man?
That's enough.
What's gotten into you
today...? Apologize.
That's no way to
speak to your mother.
Well, are you
gonna answer me?
I asked what's
gotten into you.
Explain yourself.
Seriously, Dad...?
This girl right here...
She barely looks old enough to
see a PG-13 movie unsupervised,
and you're trying to tell
me that she's my mother?
Oh, how sweet...
If you keep telling
me how young I look,
I might forgive you for
the way you spoke earlier.
And what about this girl...?
You want me to believe
that this human bug zapper
is my little cousin?
What do you mean?
I'm not a bug zapper!
Yes, that's
what I'm saying.
She's your cousin and
this is your mother...
What on Earth has
come over you, Toma?
What on Earth hasn't
come over me?!
Am I being punked or
something...?! I give up.
Where'd you stash the
hidden camera...?
I don't appreciate being the
butt of your practical joke.
I'm not laughing!
What do you people have
against me, anyway?!
Now, now. Let's just
calm down a minute...
Here, take a look
at this pen...
It changes whenever you
turn it upside down...
-See, the woman's dress is...
-Later!
Hold on, Toma...!
Where are you going?
We're not done talking.
Yeah, wait for us!
Toma, dear!
Mess with me, will he...?
I can't believe that's
what my dad is like.
Welcome to our inn.
We have everything
prepared for you...
Come in and make
yourselves at home.
Thanks... we're
glad to be here.
Somethin' wrong, Toma?
So... you're in on it,
too, Misaka Sister...
How long have you
been planning this?!
Huh?
Oh, please...
pay him no mind...
It's been a while
since he's seen us.
His emotions are
running high.
It's a pleasure to
welcome you to our inn.
Please allow me to show
you all to your rooms.
Now, then. Shall we?
It's right this way.
Oh... It looks like your other
guest has woken up as well.
Ah... beautiful
morning, isn't it...?
Let's hurry and grab
some breakfast, okay?
Come and play!
Come on, hurry up!
And now I'm at the beach
with Mikoto Misaka,
who is wearing a swimsuit
and acting like she's
my little cousin...
Obviously, this little
outing was not my idea.
You're kidding me!
Stop it, Toma.
I can't breathe!
Let me go!
Damn you!
Take it easy, Toma!
This stupid joke is
ending right now!
Why don't we go to
the beach for a swim?
That should cool you
down a bit, ya' think?
We'll settle in and
join you later okay?
Damn my luck.
How much longer can they
keep this farce going...?
This is one elaborate
practical joke.
Are you feeling
calmer, Toma?
I don't understand what's
got you so troubled......
but here maybe
this'll help.
It's a souvenir I picked
up on a trip to Russia...
It's a doll...
and another... and another.
Well? It's pretty cool,
don't you think?
No, it's not even
a little bit cool.
What a shame.
It's really too bad that
you and your father
don't share more of the
same interests, Toma.
Whoa...! What are you...?
Why are you...?
Now that's what
I'm talkin' about!
It looks fantastic
on you...
It's definitely worth
every cent I paid for it.
You mean you're the one who
bought this abomination...?
Is this another
hobby of yours?
Well... You see, when you
travel all over the world
for business like I do,
you develop an eye for
more sophisticated sty...
What do you think
you're doing, Toma?
What do you
think I'm doing?
I've just learned my father's
a disgusting pervert...!
A dirty old man with a
damn Lolita complex!
Oh, hey, look over there...!
Your little friend
is joining us.
Toma!
Not nice!
C'mon, why are you
acting all weirded out?
Toma, dear!
Shut up!
And now for more news...
The president will be
holding a press conference
at the White House in
just a few minutes,
in response to the
recent scandal
What's my doctor
doing on TV?
Komori reporting.
We're live in Washington,
where every eye is on
the president today,
waiting to see
what he will do...
How will he respond to
the latest allegations?
Miss Komoe, what
are you doing?!
Excuse me but
we can't see.
He's flashing a confident
smile for the crowd.
Yes...!We...!Can!
And now Kuroko Shirai,
too...?
What's going on...?
This is getting ridiculous.
It's way too
involved for a prank.
There's no way they went
overseas to stage all this.
If this isn't a
practical joke...
Thank you, young man.
-Have a nice day,
-Good afternoon.
Let's see, here. First you wanna
head straight on up that hill...
Shana is so hot!
He's so lame.
And what's with his hair?
Do you think I should
block his number?
What is this...? What
the hell is going on?
Ah hah! I found you!
Oh, joy.
Here, take a look!
It's us from
last New Year's.
See, that's you and me.
Do you remember me now?
Please say you do.
Hey, is there
something wrong...?
You've been acting
seriously weird all day.
Let's see if
I've got this ...
You're saying this girl in the
picture with me is my cousin.
That's me all right...
Otohime Tatsugami.
That's weird.
She doesn't seem to realize
this isn't what
she looks like.
I don't understand...
It's like everybody's
personality
has been transplanted into
somebody else's body...
Even worse, no one
seems to know it...
How could that happen?
I know what's
going on here...
It's happened
enough lately.
Whenever somebody shows up in a
ridiculous costume like this,
they seem to know me...
even if I have no
idea who they are.
In this situation, I just
need to remain cool and casual.
Yo... long time no...
Question one...
are you the spell caster?
I'll repeat.
Are you the spell caster?
Hold on a minute.
It's too soon to conclude
that he's the one.
Whew...
Looks like we made
it just in time.
Tsuchimikado?!
Oh, and that's an
interesting development.
I look like Motoharu
Tsuchimikado to him.
Yes... however, the fact that
he can correctly identify you
might indicate that...
Oh, I don't think so,
sweetie...
Do you see any traces
of that on Kami's body?
It appears he has eluded
the problem, just as we have.
I am a sorcerer
with the English Puritan
Church's Necessarius...
Kaori Kanzaki.
Our purpose in coming here
is the same as yours:
to gauge the center
of the distortion...
However, it's ridiculous to
think that boy is the caster.
Russian Orthodox Church's
Annihilation Survey...
I'm Misha Kruezhev.
Wow...! Imagine meeting a member
of the Annihilation Survey
here at a beach resort.
Question one...
where is your proof that
he is not the caster...?
Question two...
if he is not the caster...
then who is?
Whoa, I don't understand a
word you guys have said...
and Tsuchimikado, what are
you doing here, anyway?
This boy is not
a sorcerer...
He's an esper...
a Level Zero, at that.
Hey! Hello! Are we just
skipping over the part
where she almost
cut my head off?!
Still annoying, I see...
Lucky me, I get to put up with
your whining all over again...
You haven't grown up even
a little bit, have you?
So she's someone
I know, too....
Maybe I can get
something out of her.
You know I would
really appreciate it
if you could at least tell
me what's going on here.
Just for old times' sake.
I guess I must...
It will be difficult
for us to move forward
unless the major players
understand the situation.
A major player...?
Does she mean me?
Currently, there is a
massive spell at work
on a global scale.
Its format and formula
are still unknown...
For the sake of convenience,
we have named it.
We are referring to
it as Angel Fall.
Angel Fall. Right.
"Sephirotic Tree"...
Have you heard that
term used before?
You might think of it as
a chart of rankings...
It shows the souls of Gods,
the angels, and humans...
Ordinarily, humans cannot
rise to the rank of angels...
Naturally, the opposite
is true as well.
You see, each ranking is
already filled to capacity.
However, one of the angels
has fallen to the
human level, going...
Time out!
Please. Time out for a second.
You don't understand?
That's hardly surprising.
No... I don't...
but, I mean, angels?
Are you messing with me?
Think about it, Kami.
You should have noticed the
effects of the spell by now.
They're pretty obvious.
What effects?
The switching of people's
appearances, for one.
Not everybody looks like
themselves, do they?
When the angel fell
to the human level,
the shift caused our world's
physical manifestations
and inner
workings to alter.
In a game of musical chairs,
the fastest one is the winner...
It's like that, with our
appearances scrambling
to sit down on our
"inner selves."
Oh... You mean that's why
everybody looks so funny?
There's still plenty
that we don't know...
It's not clear who put
this spell into motion
or what their
motivation was...
The important thing
right now, Kami...
is that you're at the
center of the distortion.
You are the prime suspect in
the casting of Angel Fall...
You narrowly escaped
the spell's effects...
Because of this,
your life will likely be
threatened by sorcerers
who are trying to
halt its progress.
However, I find it
impossible to believe
that Toma Kamijo
here is the culprit.
For one thing, he has no magical
knowledge whatsoever...
For another... the traces that
are left on espers' bodies
whenever they use magic are
nowhere to be found on him.
Counterargument one...
He is obviously not suffering
the effects of the spell.
That's easy to explain.
Kami has the ability
to cancel out
any extraordinary power...
Imagine Breaker has set up
residence in his right hand.
Oh, I see...
So that's why.
Wait, Tsuchimikado!
How do you even
know about that?
Valence reading... forty....
nine... thirty... and seven...
together that's
eighty-six.
Accordance....
Water, form a serpent
and strike at the target.
Very well...
I accept his
response as proof
that he should be cleared
of all suspicion...
Young man...
I hereby apologize
for mistakenly turning
my blade on you.
All right. Even though we
know you're not the caster,
the fact remains that Angel Fall
is centered around you
and still growing...
Which means that
there's a good chance
the caster is
somebody close to you.
It's hard to believe
that a single caster
is responsible for a spell
of this magnitude.
Most likely,
there's a ritual site
somewhere behind a magic
circle or barrier.
So, we either have to
destroy the ritual site
or the casters themselves...
Those are the
only two ways
we're gonna bring an
end to Angel Fall.
I still have a question.
What do you have to do
with this, Tsuchimikado...?
How are you involved
in the magic world...?
And how do you know
about Imagine Breaker?
Answer me, already!
It's a simple
explanation, really.
You see, Kami...
I'm a member of
Necessarius, too.
[Music]
To find the caster
responsible for Angel Fall,
Tsuchimikado and I head
to my parents' house,
where we discover
an unsettling truth.
Next time, "Toya Kamijo."
When science and
magic cross paths,
a story is born.