Strong crosswind...
Correcting sights.
Adjusting three
clicks left.
Strong gust...
Vortices from
three sides...
Now readjusting sights
one click to the right.
Target code...
Accelerator.
[Music]
Here in Academy City,
if they find your
coursework lacking,
you get to take remedial
classes during the summer.
Those classes are
held in late July.
Yet here I am
on August 20th,
still stuck taking
summer classes...
Apparently, I made the
brilliant decision
to skip the first
remedial session.
Unfortunately, I have
absolutely no idea
why I missed those classes...
My memory doesn't go back
any further than July 28th.
So now I'm stuck paying
tuition for courses
I don't even remember
skipping in the first place...
What else could go wrong?
I don't have any change.
My rotten luck.
Are you done?
You just gonna stand
there like an idiot?
If you're not buying
anything, move it.
That's a Tokiwadai
Middle School uniform...
Who is this girl?
Geez... you're
one rude chick.
Chick...? I have... a name!
When will you get it
through your thick skull?!
My name is Mikoto Misaka!
I guess I know her.
You're wasting
your time...
That vending machine is
just gonna eat your money.
Yeah, I know that.
There's a trick to it...
I can get a drink
out of this thing
without spending
any money at all.
What kind of trick?
Nice shorts.
This is an old machine.
The springs that hold the
drinks in place are loose,
so you just have
to jiggle them...
The only catch is
you can't choose
what you get this way.
Hey what are
you staring at?
Are all the girls
who go to Tokiwadai
as violent as you are?
Life's tough at an
all-girls school
despite whatever
daydreams you might have.
You know, the machine's probably
broken in the first place
because people like you
kick it all the time.
What is with you...?
It's not like I'm
doing anything to you.
Oh, I see.
So how much cash did the
machine take you for?
Two thousand.
Seriously?! You put that
big a bill into this old thing?
It's not like
I had a choice!
No wonder the
machine kept it!
What an idiot!
Why not just
burn your money?
I can get it back for you.
Oh yeah? How?
Easy. Like this.
Whoa... That's
a lotta drinks.
You didn't get
your cash back,
but I bet even more
drinks'll come out of here
than you paid for
with that bill...
That okay with you?
Why are you running like
a scared little girl?!
Hey!
Here, catch.
You need to pull
your weight...
I think you should start by
carrying some of these drinks...
This is your portion
of the total haul.
You realize by
accepting these,
I'm graduating from innocent
bystander to accomplice.
That's not a role I
want to take on...
Ow!
Hey... if you don't
want this one,
I'll take it
off your hands.
There's something I still
don't get about you...
You've got power but no
confidence to back it up,
so you end up
walking around
looking like a
complete idiot...
You bested Mikoto Misaka.
That's not something a
lotta people can say.
At the very least, I would
hope you'd accept your victory
with some kind of
grace and dignity.
Bested? I beat her
at something...?
Sports, maybe...?
It would be a lot easier
to be a gracious victor
if I knew what the heck
she was talking about...
but this lecture doesn't
make any sense to me...!
Please, let her
stop talking!
Are you having some kind
of mental breakdown?
Come on... Just relax
and drink your soda...
You're lucky to be getting a
present from Master Mikoto...
plenty of girls would kill
to be in your position.
Oh really, would they...?
Are you some
kind of celebrity?
It's not something I chose,
but yeah, I am a celebrity.
I'm surprised
you don't already know
what they call me at
Tokiwadai Middle School.
Is that you Sissy?
Oh, it is you...!
I thought I was seeing
things for a second...!
It didn't make sense for you
to be in a remedial class,
but it was all just a
pretense for this, huh?
What...? I don't know what
you're talking about...
A pretense for
what, exactly?
Don't be coy, Sissy...
I'm talking about this
secret assignation.
Pleased to meet you...
The name's Shirai Kuroko,
and I have the honor of being
Mikoto's right hand gal.
I don't know if
you were planning
to put the moves on her...
but if that is
the intention,
you'll have to clear
it with me first.
Please...!
Are you kidding me?!
Do you really think this
moron is my boyfriend?!
No, of course not!
I know you'd have better
taste than that...
I'm going...
I'm sure I can trust you
not to embarrass
yourself here, Sissy...
Isn't that right?
Kuroko!
If you start spreading
rumors, you will pay!
Teleportation...
Hello, sister.
Another one?!
I'm confused.
She has a twin?
"Not exactly...
I'm her younger sister,"
Misaka quickly replies.
Okay, you're her sister...
but why are you
talking about yourself
in the third person
like that...?
You both have the
same last name.
Doesn't it get kind of
confusing around the house?
"Misaka's name is Misaka,"
Misaka replies in
some confusion.
More importantly... what are you
doing here in the first place?
"You want to
know the reason
for my presence here at
this point in time...
I am in training,"
Misaka answers.
Oh... training...
Hey, little sister...
could I talk to you
for a second...?
We've got some
catching up to do.
Quite a bit.
"Unfortunately, Misaka
has a schedule to keep,
so she cannot
take the time...
It's okay!
Come with me.
Well, we have to
get going now...
You probably should, too.
You don't want
to miss curfew.
That was weird...
What an interesting family.
Hot day...
Cold drinks...
So heavy...
Least I didn't trip.
Whoa!
That's not fair...!
No!
Damn it...! What'd I
do to deserve this?
You're back.
I thought you
and your sister
were going off
somewhere to talk.
Hold on.
I could've sworn she was
wearing shorts earlier.
"You've fallen.
Do you need help getting up?"
Misaka is forced to ask,
somewhat reluctantly.
Oh...
You aren't her.
You're the kid sister...
You know... you sure
look a lot like Mikoto.
"Who's 'Mikoto'"...
Misaka inquires with
polite curiosity...
Ah, yes...
You're speaking of my sister.
So, why're you carrying
around those military goggles?
"Unlike her sister,
Misaka lacks the ability
to follow electron beams
and magnetic field lines
by eyesight...
She requires a device like
this to make them visible.
"Misaka patiently explains
to the ignorant young boy.
Okay...
So, why are you here...?
I thought you and your
sister were off bonding.
"Misaka was there before,
and now she is here."...
Misaka says.
"Where should we take
these beverages?"
Misaka enquires, politely
picking up one of the cans
that are strewn about.
Oh, no... It's okay.
I can handle
this by myself.
"These beverages
do not belong here.
Where should
we take them?"
Misaka repeats.
Huh...? No... honestly,
it'll be okay...
You're not obligated
to help me.
We should act swiftly.
Okay.
Hey...! Mister Toma Kamijo!
My air conditioner's
busted...!
I'm staying here with
my brother for the night.
It's like an old-fashioned
slumber party!
Oh that's cool...
Is he home?
Nope... No idea where he is.
This is Maika...
My classmate Tsuchimikado
is her stepbrother...
Apparently... she's in
training to become a maid.
Maid school must
be rough, huh...
You don't get
summers off, right?
According to
our school motto
a successful maid doesn't need
to take time off for herself...
You have a lot of
drinks there...
Where'd you get so
many cans of soda...?
Did you rob a
vending machine?
I paid for them all...
and because you
asked so politely...
would you like
to have one?
Well... since you offered...
One more thing...
you have to be more careful
hiding girls in your place...
If I were you,
I would make sure
the refrigerator is
always kept well-stocked,
because an appetite
like that little one has
is pretty memorable.
How did you
know about that?
Let's just say that I
never would've guessed
that a nun could
be so noisy.
"Is that the type of thing
you're interested in?"
Misaka asks with a note
of disdain in her voice.
You have no idea.
What are they up to now?
Hey... what's going on...?
What're you doing here?
Are you locked out of the
apartment or something?
Huh...? Oh, it's Toma!
No, we're not
locked out...
Wait a second!
Why did you bring a
strange girl home?
The welcome wagon.
It seems you're a person
who requires many options...
If no one woman is
enough to satisfy you,
perhaps you should
look somewhere else.
Seriously, just tell me...
What are you two doing?
Poor Sphinx is
covered in fleas.
We're just trying
to get rid of them.
So is my place crawling
with fleas now, too...?
Damn it! I knew I'd been
feeling itchy lately.
We've got it
under control...
Calm down.
What is that...?
Some kind of fern?
It's an herb called sage.
It's medicinal...
I'm going to burn it,
and the smoke it produces
will make the fleas go away
and leave Sphinx alone.
Medicinal... sure...
Sounds more like a recipe
for stewed cat to me...
What's that, Himegami...?
Does that go in the stew?
Or what?
This is a magic spray
for removing fleas.
A magic spray...? Really?
You simply aim the
spray at the fleas
and it eradicates them.
You're more likely
to eradicate the cat!
That's a can of
high-strength pesticide!
"What exactly are you
trying to accomplish here?"
"You simply wish
to remove the fleas
without using a toxic
substance, is that correct?"
Misaka asks for confirmation.
I think that
about covers it...
Do you have a plan?
"Yes, I do...
Watch this,"
Misaka instructs.
"I used a specific frequency
to exterminate only the fleas,"
Misaka reports helpfully.
"I believe you can use a normal
insecticide to kill the fleas
that may have infested
your place of residence.
"Though Misaka does suggest
you use it carefully.
Oh... Yeah.
All right, then.
My errand is now complete.
The standard cards
used to test for ESP
were changed after
an experiment done
in the United States in 1992.
Because of the material
from which they were made,
the cards were
easily distinguished
by the fingerprints
left upon them
by the test administrators...
In order to assure the
integrity of the experiment
the cards were...
Hey...! Toma Kamijo...!
Are you paying
attention to me?
Yeah, I'm listening...
but is hearing
all this history
going to increase
my power at all?
Really... He's
still a Level Zero.
You can't make something
out of nothing, can you?
Be quiet...!
Everything in this world
starts out as nothing.
But without
time and effort,
it will remain that way.
Miss Misaka of Tokiwadai
Middle School is ranked third
out of all
Academy City espers...
She began as Level 1
and through tireless
work and dedication
she was able to advance
all the way to Level 5.
She's ranked third...?
That girl?!
What, Kamijo...?
Are you and Miss Misaka
acquaintances?
No... Well, not really.
Oh, hey!
You finishing
remedial lessons also?
Oh... it's you again.
Stupid things...
I really can't
stand those blimps.
Yeah? Why's that?
Because they're nothing
but big computers.
Programmed by the
machine to control us.
The machine...?
Wait... that does
sound familiar...
Gimme a second...
I remember!
Tree Diagram, was it?
Yep, that's what
they called it...
The most powerful
supercomputer ever to exist,
loaded aboard the
great satellite Orihime-1,
which was launched
by Academy City
in order to analyze data
regarding the world's climate.
Well, that's what
they tell us...
but what d'you suppose
the chances are
that such a thing
actually exists?
Huh?
Ow...! Geez...! What
the hell was that for?!
Eh... forget it.
I was just rambling.
Wha...?
Well... I'm headed
this way, so...
That's Mikoto... isn't it?
It's the younger sister...
Man... if you
lose the goggles,
there's no way to
tell 'em apart.
Hi again...
Thanks for helping with the
drinks and the fleas yesterday.
"I do not require any
words of gratitude,"
Misaka informs the boy.
What's up...?
Is that for him?
"Misaka would like
to feed the cat,
but unfortunately,
she cannot do so,"
Misaka concludes sadly.
"She has a critical defect...
one that prevents her
from feeding animals,"
Misaka further explains.
What defect?
"Misaka's body constantly
emits a weak magnetic field,"
Misaka explains.
"It's not strong enough
for people to detect...
but it is a different
matter for animals."
"Unless something
else is done,
the cat will be
taken to the pound,"
Misaka has
unfortunately observed.
Well, yeah...
I guess that's true...
"That is not a kind fate.
Do you know how animals are
treated in such facilities?"
Misaka pointedly enquires.
You're the one
who found him.
So shouldn't you be the one
who gets to give him a name?
-It's "Dog."
-Huh?
"The black cat will
be named Dog,"
Misaka unequivocally declares...
He is a cat... named dog.
Yeah, I get it...
but I dunno...
maybe he should have
a more dignified name?
"Perhaps we should call
him Nelson Mandela,"
Misaka suggests.
That's overdoing it!
How about Schrödinger?
No... You cannot
name a cat Schrodinger.
I'll just be a second.
You can wait
out here, right?
"I believe I understand.
Are you looking for a book
on how to care for cats?"
Misaka asks him,
seeking confirmation.
It's pretty clear I have a lot
to learn in that department.
You remember the flea
situation yesterday, right?
"That was indeed a
regrettable scene...
I'm impelled to tell you,
the improper treatment of cats
is a blatant violation of
animal protection laws,"
Misaka warns
him very sternly.
Hey... come on...
that wasn't me.
"You are just
splitting hairs...
Though you may not have
been directly involved,
the incident did occur at
your place of residence,"
Misaka replies, her
patience now wearing thin.
Sorry.
I'm guessing they're not
going to appreciate it
if I come into the
store carrying a cat.
"I have previously informed
you of my limitations...
I cannot safely
interact with the cat,"
Misaka says for...
You said cats
don't like you
'cause of the magnetic
field, right...?
Well maybe the two of
you can change that...
Could be the start of
a beautiful friendship!
"Honestly...
That is unacceptable.
What kind of person would
so thoughtlessly throw
a kitten around?"
Misaka asks incredulously.
We are all dying
to find out.
Who is the strongest Level
5 esper in Academy City?
We should know soon... huh?
[Music]
Apparently in
Academy City,
they butcher innocents and
call it experimentation...
Hey, Misaka, how much
do you know about this?
Next time, "Sisters."
When science and
magic cross paths,
a story is born.