A Misaka Sister
nicknamed "Last Order"
approached Accelerator
seeking his help.
He later learned that a virus
had been implanted in her head
by a man named Ao Amai.
If the virus is triggered,
ten thousand Sisters will
launch an attack on humanity.
What is he going to do?
Wait, I don't have any scenes
in this episode, either?
[Music]
Accelerator.
That's me now, but I used
to have a normal name.
A first and last name...
Like everybody else.
It wasn't even a
particularly unusual name.
Ridiculous.
The virus that
I've isolated
is set to trigger at midnight
tonight, September 1st...
If it does activate,
it will run rampant,
spreading through the
entire Misaka Network
and infecting all
the Sisters...
Once that happens, there
will be no stopping it...
We'll be helpless.
What...?!
A man in a lab coat?!
Well... yes...
He said he was
related to her...
he was an uncle
or something...
so we thought it was okay
to let her leave with him.
So, um...
is he an acquaintance
of yours, then?
Unfortunately he is.
He did what?!
So...
the virus is designed to
activate on its own, right?
If that's the case,
why would he make a
move on the kid now?
That's just one question
I wish I could answer.
It's possible that he's already
left Academy City, isn't it?
There are any number
of organizations
that would hide him.
Word is that somebody
from the outside
broke through
the security net.
Whoever it was then
slipped into the city.
The Security Code was set
at orange earlier today...
but it's been
elevated to red now.
Nobody is allowed to enter
or leave Academy City...
Which means that Amai should
still be here somewhere.
Hotels wouldn't be safe.
He must be hiding
at a friend's place.
I'd be surprised if
there's anybody left
he could call a friend.
I see what you mean...
He's scum, just like me.
With the closure
of the laboratory,
he's incurred quite
a lot of debt.
I'd guess his
friendships only last
as long as his
money holds out.
Huh...
If he has nowhere
to set up camp,
then he's probably still
prowling around town somewhere.
And I have an advantage.
He's cornered.
A lack of breathing room
tends to make peoples' actions
much more predictable.
Hold on a minute...
You're not going to...
Damn it...!
Nothing's going
my way tonight!
Please... just
a little longer.
Just stay alive 'til
the virus activates!
I have you...
Now what should
I do with you?
You should take it
easy, old man...
You're embarrassing yourself.
Hey, Yoshikawa...
Are you there...?
Yeah, I've got the
kid secured now...
Wait...
Hey... it looks like she's
hooked up to some electrodes.
That's probably one of
the physical exam kits
we use on the Sisters.
Can you tell me what a
BC operating ratio is?
It measures the rate at which
her brain is functioning...
BC stands for brain cell.
These numbers aren't
looking so good.
So... do you think I can use
this physical exam kit thing
to get rid of the virus...?
It could take a
long time for me
to get her back to the
laboratory from here.
Impossible...
We need a specialized incubator
and a learning apparatus
to overwrite her mind.
Huh...? Where are you...?
Driving?
Yes.
I'm on the road right now.
Headed toward
you as we speak.
I thought I could buy us
some extra time this way...
It's quicker than you
taking her back to the lab.
Are you done analyzing
the virus code?
I'd say I'm about
80% there...
I'll be finished before
the midnight deadline.
Honestly...
how much trouble does this
kid wanna cause me...?
This is getting old, fast.
Mi... sa...
Misa... ka. Misa... ka.
Misaka. Misaka. Misaka.
Misa misa misa
misa misa misa....
Um, Yoshikawa...
What the hell is going on?
Quiet a second.
Yeah, that's it, all right...
but it shouldn't
be happening yet.
What is it?
What's happening?
The implanted virus code...
From the sound of it,
it's getting ready to execute.
I don't understand
why it's happening...
We still have four
hours 'til midnight.
This could mean we were
fed false information.
Damn it.
Listen up, Accelerator.
It's too soon to give up...
but you've gotta move
quickly, all right?
What...? You mean there's
something I can do?
Before the virus is distributed
throughout the Misaka Network,
it's being converted
into a host command,
which none of the Sisters
will be able to contradict.
That will take about
ten minutes to complete...
That should be
enough time...
You know there's only
one thing you can do.
Dispose of Last Order.
It's the only way...
Save the world
by killing her.
Damn.
I'm the strongest esper
in Academy City...
but as powerful
as my abilities are,
they're only good for
altering vector directions.
What's more...
I've pretty much only used
them for beating people up...
I don't know how
to do any healing.
Sure, I can touch someone
and reverse the
flow of their blood
and mess with their
bioelectricity, but...
Wait... what was that?
I feel like there's
an idea here...
I have to think.
Bioelectricity...
That's it!
This data stick
could be the key.
It contains Last Order's
personality data
from before she was infected.
Hey, listen...
What if I can
get control over
the electrical signals
in her brain...?
Wouldn't we be able to
alter her personality data
and get rid of the virus?
What are you talking...
You don't mean...
You're suggesting that
you take the place of the
learning apparatus...?
No way.
It should be simple enough
for me to do, though...
I'm a master at
reflecting vectors...
all I'm talking about
is the next step.
Controlling them.
Fine. Let's assume
that you're somehow able
to get control of
Last Order's neural pathways.
That doesn't mean
you'll be able to
completely
eradicate the virus.
There's more than just the
Sisters at stake if you fail.
In this kind of attack the
casualties could be staggering.
The only way to avoid major
loss of life at this point
is to give up
on Last Order...
I know you don't like it,
but we've exhausted
all our options.
Hello...?
Are you listening?
I know I can do it...
Who the hell does she
think she's talking to?
I can collate the
pre-infection data.
Then all I should have to do
is erase any excess code, right?
Okay, this should
be simple enough.
Let's get started.
Poor kid...
She's already been
through hell...
After all the things
they've put her through...
saying "Sorry, we couldn't
save her" just isn't enough.
Collating the
pre-infection data now.
Object code count...
357,081.
I just need to erase all
this nasty virus code...
and that should do it...
The kid should go
back to whatever state
she was in a week ago...
before she ever
laid eyes on me.
Execute command...
Delete!
Delete! Delete!
Code CIIEB.
Resist MA. 83256.
Delta 7. Code ZZ.
From route A to W, V7E8.
Remaining code
count: 173,542.
C.... 2 B A I 9 M C
O R E L 5 S 3 2 H A.
How much of her memory am I
erasing along with the virus?
So what if she doesn't
remember any of it?
The kid's better off
forgetting everything
that happened in
the last week, anyway.
Remaining code count: 23,891.
Just ten seconds
left to go...
I knew this would be
easy enough to do.
Get away...
Don't interfere.
You've gotta be
kidding me...
I'm doing electron
microscope-level precision
work here.
I don't have any power remaining
to divert to reflection.
I could take my
hand off the kid
and use vector reflection
to defend myself...
If I did that, he could
drop a nuclear bomb on me
if he wanted and I wouldn't
get so much as a scratch.
What an idiot...
Did I actually believe
this would work?
I thought I could do it.
I thought I could
save somebody else
and earn a second
chance for myself.
He's dead?
He's really dead!
I don't know how,
but he's lying there, dead,
and I'm still alive!
Error alert.
Immediate action.
Break code from 0000001.
Continuing through
code 357081.
Threat found
and eliminated.
Host command has been canceled
due to illegal process.
Delivery has been terminated...
Subject 20001 ...
beginning reboot process.
It's been canceled...?
The unit's restarting...?
No! The virus
failed to trigger?
What? You're alive?
I see...
That's what you did...
You managed to
reflect the bullet.
Right before it
entered your brain.
That's it, right?!
But what do you think you're
going to do now, huh...?
It's already too
late for you.
You're beyond saving.
Oh, I know that...
I've known it for
quite a while now...
Who would wanna
save me, anyway...?
Like anybody'd waste their
energy on scum like me...
The very idea is so
ridiculous it makes me laugh.
No... I'm done with
wishful thinking.
It makes me sick,
the person I've become...
but that doesn't matter.
It has nothing to do with
that kid, nothing whatsoever.
True, I'm responsible
for killing
more than ten thousand
of the Sisters...
but that doesn't mean
I'm going to sit back
and watch the other ten
thousand die because of you.
Yeah, I know...
Coming from me, you think
it's just lip service...
but I promise,
it's more than that...
It doesn't matter that
you and I are nothing
but human scum....
or what justifications
we might make.
It's not about us.
It's about her.
And I'm telling you,
she doesn't deserve to die!
His reflection's
not working...
He's down for
good this time.
That's just too bad,
now, isn't it...?
Looks like playing the
hero didn't work out for you.
Kudos for trying, but you
didn't have the strength for it.
Not surprising...
People like us weren't
built for noble deeds
and self-sacrifice.
That's just the way
it is, I'm afraid.
Y... Yoshikawa...
You shot me...
I'm sorry about this.
It's a flaw of mine...
I never seem to follow
through with anything.
I'm not being kind, here.
I'm just soft...
I didn't have the nerve to
hit you anywhere vital...
but I don't think I can
let you get away, either.
So I guess I've needlessly
drawn out your suffering...
How ironic it is
that in the end,
my softness has actually turned
out to be a sort of cruelty.
I don't know what happened,
except for what I was able
to hear over the phone.
But it appears that your
plan didn't work out quite
like you thought it would.
Oh him...?
You don't need to worry
he'll be just fine.
I have a rather talented
doctor friend...
You wouldn't guess it
by looking at him...
Poor man has a face
like a frog, I'm afraid.
But he's so good
at what he does
he's actually been given the
nickname Heaven Canceller.
With my friend
as his doctor,
Accelerator should
pull through.
How could you...?
It doesn't make any sense...!
You're a scientist.
You make calculations
and perform experiments
in a controlled
laboratory environment.
You don't point
guns at people!
See, that's the thing...
I sort of fell
into this position.
I never wanted
to be a researcher.
As a matter of fact, I
wanted to be a schoolteacher...
and not some kind
of boring lecturer...
but an instructor who
could really connect...
That's what I always
dreamed about...
being a good teacher.
One who remembered each
of her students' faces
from year to year...
One they knew
they could talk to
no matter what kind of
problems they were having...
who would smile freely,
without expecting
anything in return.
Who would hold back tears
when her students walked
the stage on graduation day...
That's the kind of
teacher I wanted to be.
At least some of that desire
still lingers with me...
I still wanna do
something that's good...
and not because
I'm soft...
not because I'm weak
but because it's right.
So now I'm acting
like a teacher
who would do anything
for one of her students...
That's why
I'm here tonight,
pointing a gun
at your chest.
Well, Amai...
it's over.
I see you're too
frightened to die alone...
and if you had to choose
someone to come with you,
I'm glad you picked me...
because there's no way I was
ever going to let you take
one of those children
with you into hell.
This is my one
good deed...
I only wish there could've
been more in my life.
I have to admit, you don't
seem very soft at the moment...
Unfortunately, teacher...
it won't do you any good.
I'm really alive...?
I can't believe I made it.
Of course you
did, my dear.
What would you expect
when I was operating on you?
I'm not questioning
your ability, doctor,
but I was shot point-blank
through the heart.
That does tend
to be fatal.
To be more accurate...
you were shot in the artery
extending from the heart.
But I'm splitting hairs.
Either way you look at it,
yes, you were basically dead.
If you're going
to thank anyone,
it should be that young man.
It looks like he
was somehow able
to manipulate your blood
flow to keep you alive.
I've seen a lot in my time,
but this was incredible...
He passed the blood from
one opening in your artery
to the other without
spilling a drop,
as if there was an
invisible hose.
He kept it up even after
he'd fallen unconscious...
He held until
you'd reached the OR...
I was able to take
over from there,
but without him,
you would've died.
Unfortunately, he isn't
out of the woods just yet.
He seems to have
taken a lot of damage,
mostly centered around
his frontal cortex...
His verbal and
computational abilities
will be affected...
At this point I can't say
for certain how severely.
His computational abilities...?
That can't be.
What will happen
to his esper powers?
Oh... I wouldn't worry
about it too much.
Dear, don't you know
my credo by now...?
When something seems unworkable,
work something out...
I promise I'll restore the
young man's verbal function
and his powers of computation...
no matter what.
You and your people seem to have
created a many-headed monster
and I intend to make
use of it for this...
They've got over ten thousand
brains linked together...
I think they can spare
some of that mental wealth
to help augment one
person's speaking
and calculating skills.
You mean The Misaka Network.
Last Order! Where is she?
Are you talking about a
young girl with brown hair,
by any chance?
Don't worry. She's safe
and under our supervision.
Now, enough
of my rambling.
My patients won't
heal themselves...
So what're you
going to do now?
What am I gonna do?
It looks like the
city's higher-ups
have found out about this
bloody little incident...
The lab's been
permanently shut down...
and the experiment
completely terminated.
In other words, I'm afraid
you're out of a job.
Oh... I see...
I suppose this means my
life as a researcher is over.
There are other
paths you can go down,
any number of them.
Wait! Please, as a friend...
help the young man
who came in with me.
If you don't...
I'll never forgive you.
Look who you're
talking to, my dear.
An injured body is a
doctor's battlefield...
You'll see... I'm a more
than capable soldier.
I always return
from battle.
And this time I'll bring
a patient back with me,
one who's been fighting
alone all these years.
Hah... In case you've
already forgotten,
I'm the one who killed ten
thousand of the Sisters...
and now you're asking
me to save one of them?
Well, what do you know...?
He was their
savior after all...
Wasn't he?
[Music]
The City's second term
opening ceremony
is rocked by the arrival
of sorcerers...
A mysterious
transfer student
further complicates
matters...
Clearly everything
is not what it seems.
Next time, "Counter Stop."
When science and
magic cross paths,
a story is born.