[MANATSU] Yes...
It's time to put
things to an end.
♪
[MAYURA] You're here!
I don't understand
what's happening...
Why would Masumi
have taken him away?
I wish I knew...
but I can't even
tell where Manatsu is.
That can't be true...
Now calm down a
little and try again.
[MAYURA] I can't...!
I'm telling you...
He won't even look at me!
I'm sorry, you two...
Sagara, Suzuhara, if I may...
I'd like to have a word.
[PROF. SOUDA] My daughter
likes to keep me informed...
She's told me that both of
you are able to see Masumi.
I hoped you could explain to
me what happened with him...
What did he do?
[MIYUKI] We don't know.
[PROF. SOUDA] Do you think you
would be able to summon him
like Mayura and Manatsu do?
I'm sorry...
but what they do
seems to be unique...
I doubt that anybody
could replicate it...
It's not a spell...
it seems more like
an innate gift.
[PROF. SOUDA] In this
situation, I am blind.
I am not able to see Masumi.
It appears that a special
form of atavism has emerged
in my children...
No one from my generation
can offer them guidance.
Their mother is
unsettled by all this.
She hates to hear
them speak of Masumi.
As if, by virtue of giving
birth to them, she can sense
something ominous in the name.
[KISARAGI] Well...
I'm going to turn
in for the night.
I am pretty
worried, though...
About Souda...
He seems like he's the type who
could easily get spirited away.
[IZUMIKO] Spirited away...
[MAYURA] I'm sorry...
This must be a pain.
It was strange,
though...
Manatsu talked about how you
would live a long life...
like he didn't expect
that for himself.
I guess I shouldn't
be surprised...
but see, the thing is...
Manatsu has the same heart
problem that took Masumi
so suddenly.
There's nothing
that the doctors can do
to help him at this point...
I think that's why...
our mother doesn't
like to remember Masumi.
Manatsu is a lot closer
to Masumi than he is to me...
I've always known that.
Even so...
I never imagined that
this would happen...
I didn't know that Manatsu
would choose to leave me
and join Masumi instead.
[IZUMIKO] The problem is...
he's trying too hard to
do what's best for you...
and he's responding with his
heart instead of his head.
If he wants so badly
to do what's best for me...
then he should leave Masumi's
plane and come back here.
You know the whole reason
I want to be the top student
at school...?
To help Manatsu
live a full life!
That's what I really want...
What I've been working toward
for as long as I can remember.
But somehow, he can't
understand that.
[IZUMIKO] Do you have a second?
I need your advice
about something.
Earlier...
you said nobody could replicate
what Mayura and Manatsu
do to call Masumi.
[MIYUKI] That's what I said.
What of it?
[IZUMIKO] The Hime-gami.
[MIYUKI] Slow down...
Why are you
bringing her up now?
Maybe she could help us...
Don't you think she might
know how to summon Masumi?
[MIYUKI] How could you
even suggest that?
[IZUMIKO] I think
it's possible...
Obviously, I can't talk to
her or ask her about it...
I can't, but you can!
[MIYUKI] Stop right there!
This is completely crazy...!
What are you thinking?
I'm thinking about
what it will mean
if Manatsu ends up staying
on the other side.
You mean...
you're referring to the other
plane of existence Masumi made?
Yes...
Know what I thought before...?
That I had dragged you into a
world that you weren't meant
to be a part of...
that you otherwise would've
had nothing to do with.
But then I saw how easily you
associated with Masumi...
and I started to
wonder if I was right.
If I turn into
the Hime-gami...
will you do it...?
Will you talk to her?
[MIYUKI] Hold on...!
Is that something you can do?
I won't know...
not until I try.
Don't be so
casual about it...!
The Hime-gami is dangerous...!
She's so dangerous that I can't
even imagine what will happen
if she does show up.
I'm scared, too...!
The Hime-gami frightens me...
Becoming her isn't
something that I want.
Not at all...!
But we have to try everything
we can think of...!
Otherwise we might
lose Manatsu for good.
And you're sure...?
Completely?
I am...
Mayura's more than my roommate.
She's become a true friend...
She really took me under her
wing and helped me fit in
at school and with
the Student Council...
and now...
I have a chance to show
her how grateful I am.
Don't you see...?
This is the way I can repay her.
[MIYUKI] Okay are you ready?
It's still me.
We didn't switch.
So what, is there
something else we need to do
before we can summon her?
[IZUMIKO] Maybe I'm
standing in the wrong spot.
[MIYUKI] She isn't a cell phone.
[IZUMIKO] Hey...!
I felt something just ...
now...
[IZUMIKO] Strange...
[MASUMI] Hi, Suzuhara...
Did you come back
to keep your promise?
[IZUMIKO] Is that you,
Masumi...?
Why in the world are
you wearing that outfit?
[MASUMI] After seeing
Kisaragi in hers,
I thought it might be fun.
You have Manatsu!
Where is he?
[MASUMI] Here, but further in.
What do you mean,
"further in"?
Togakushi has a bunch
of different layers in it,
you know.
Why are you trying
to break Mayura's heart?
It's not right...!
Now, send Manatsu
back where he belongs!
[MASUMI] I'm trying not
to break Mayura's heart.
Have you seen her...?
Do you know how sad
she is right now?
[MASUMI] If we part now,
her sorrow will be less...
It will pass...
But the longer Manatsu and
I wait to go, the heavier
a burden her grief will become.
Oh, really...?
Is that what Manatsu
thinks or what you think?
We're of a like mind in this.
Over time, I've come
to like being Masumi...
I don't want to vanish.
But I'm well aware that
Mayura wouldn't hesitate
to choose Manatsu over me.
And in that case...
it makes sense for us
to become one before
she is forced to choose.
[IZUMIKO]
But Masumi...
are you going
to vanish?
[MASUMI] As long as I remain in
Togakushi, nothing will change.
Not for me...
but you humans are different...
You seem to change
far more quickly than
I would have expected.
[IZUMIKO] Let me
talk to Manatsu.
I don't think you can...
He's inside a cave.
[IZUMIKO] Oh.
All right...
then you can take me
to the cave.
The night is awfully
deep around here...
Are you certain?
Of course I am...
It was night the last time
we met, remember?
[MASUMI] So, you're the type of
girl who finds her true strength
when she's in a
difficult situation.
Well, you know...
that's very attractive.
Which reminds me,
remember how I asked you out?
[IZUMIKO] Yes, I remember.
But right now,
Manatsu comes first.
All right, all right...
Well, come on, then.
Tell me something...
If, between you and Manatsu,
only one of you could make it
back from here...
Who would you choose?
I wouldn't choose
either of us...
What right would I have
to make that call...?
We both have people
waiting for us.
Here we are.
This is the cave.
You'll have to find
a way to open it, though.
[IZUMIKO] Manatsu...!
its me if you're in
there please come out!
I want to talk to you.
What's this boulder
doing blocking the entrance...?
How could he possibly have
gotten past something this big?
"Spirited behind a boulder"...
These things happen sometimes.
However, it would not have
happened if Manatsu hadn't
been perfectly willing.
He went into that
cave of his own free will.
[IZUMIKO] Right.
Okay.
[KISARAGI] Just as in the myth
of Ame no Uzume no Mikoto...
the tale that tells of this
mountain's beginnings...
dance has the power to purify.
[IZUMIKO] I don't know
what else to try...
Dancing may be the answer.
[IZUMIKO] Please, Masumi...
Do you have a fan I can have?
[MASUMI] I had a feeling
you'd be asking for one.
[IZUMIKO] Manatsu. You shouldn't
become part of this world.
Listen to me...
Nothing would make us happier
than if you were to come back.
Come out of there...
Please!
[singing in Japanese]
[IZUMIKO] Manatsu...
Mayura, your parents,
everyone...
we're all worried about you!
[MANATSU] Don't open the cave!
Masumi is on
the other side...!
It has to stay closed!
Hold on...!
What are you talking about?
But I thought I was with Masumi.
Wasn't he the one out here?
[MANATSU] You see...
I thought we could be one...
We can't...
I should never have considered
it in the first place...
Never...
He wants to break the
boulder and come out.
But wait...
hasn't he already come
to the outside world?
[MANATSU] Masumi is only a
small part of a greater being.
If his entire body makes it out,
he won't be Masumi anymore.
Thank you
so much, Suzuhara...
for coming after me.
Who is...?
Mayura's here.
[MAYURA cries]
I'm sorry.
[MAYURA] I'm still going to hit
you and scream at you later.
But for now...
it's just so good to see you.
[MANATSU] How did
you get here...?
when you didn't have
Masumi with you.
[MAYURA] I didn't need him.
Sagara brought me.
[IZUMIKO] Huh?!
What do you mean
Sagara brought you?
How could he have done that?
We can save the
explanations for later.
Look behind you!
[IZUMIKO] What is that?
[MIYUKI] Hey, snap out of it...
Do you know how to close
the cave's entrance?
[IZUMIKO] No idea...
All I know is that I was
trying to open it by dancing.
[MIYUKI] How about you two?
We don't know either...
We can only summon him.
[MIYUKI] You have got
to be kidding me...
What the hell are
we gonna do now?
[MIYUKI] Just run for it!
[MANATSU] The real Masumi is on
the other side of that boulder!
We're in real trouble...
Once he's out he could
easily devour us.
[IZUMIKO] You have a staff?
[IZUMIKO gasps]
Keep running...!
We'll catch up later!
[IZUMIKO] Oh, no!
[MIYUKI] Monsters
and villains...
Goblins and devils, Dragons
and poisonous beasts...
poisonous insects...
Hear the sound
of my staff...!
Offer me no harm!
Sagara...
you sprouted wings...
How is that even possible?
[MIYUKI] It isn't.
But I can see
them right there.
Well, they aren't real.
Won't you at least try
to explain what you're doing?
Protecting you...
That's the best
I can hope to do.
There's no way I can force
that thing back into the cave.
[HIME-GAMI] So it would seem.
This task is too great for you.
It isn't me!
[HIME-GAMI] Hand me the
staff that you carry.
[HIME-GAMI] You have
suffered long, local deity,
for none have been
able to summon you.
It is not yet time
for your awakening.
But your day will come...
And on that day,
Great Nine-Headed Dragon,
you will be released
from all that binds you.
For now, return
to your slumber.
[HIME-GAMI] This is right.
The Great Nine-Headed
Dragon left one head before
returning to the cave.
You may continue to refer to
the dream seen by that head
as "Masumi." Assuming you are
still able to summon him,
that is.
[IZUMIKO] Lady Hime-gami!
Please ...
If it's possible...
can we...
remain separate
from each other?
Instead of turning
into you like before...
can I remain myself?
Can I see you
and not become you?
[HIME-GAMI] To ask
a question like that...
You still understand nothing.
Ask that of your mother.
I can't...
I never see my mother!
It is you...!
But Mom, what are
you doing here?
Is that really her?
[YUKARIKO] That wasn't
so bright, you two...
What in the world were you
thinking, meddling with
a powerful being like that?
What the Hime-gami
said while we
were on the other side...
Was she trying to say
that she's with you now?
[YUKARIKO] That's
right, you got it...
and that's the reason that
you and I aren't supposed
to see each other
all that frequently...
For now...
I carry the Hime-gami...
but I don't know how much longer
I'll be able to contain her.
[IZUMIKO] Were you okay with
it when you started turning
into the Hime-gami?
Did you accept it
just like that?
Am I being selfish?
Is it wrong of me to want
to be like everyone else?
No, not at all...
Honestly, it'd be strange
if you weren't at least
a little hesitant.
[YUKARIKO] I'm afraid
neither of you realize just
how unstable you truly are.
You must change...
How to do so is the
question that faces you...
It is a deadly question
that everybody who has
spiritual powers
must confront.
I intervened to settle
things for you this time...
So fortunately, your real
trial has been put off
for a little longer.
How can I face it...?
I don't think I'm
strong enough, Mom.
[YUKARIKO] That's right...
But I'm strong enough
for both of us, Izumiko.
So for as long as I am able
to do so, I'll protect you.
But that isn't
going to last forever.
It was good to
see you two...
Stay here and wait
for your friends.
They'll be along.
Wow, Yukariko is really
something else, isn't she?
Yeah, she is...
It's kinda difficult for me
to think of her as my mom
sometimes.
[MIYUKI] She sure is pretty.
Hey, you know something...?
I think you should try to
start making your thoughts
and feelings clearer.
It's like everything
always comes
out of the blue with you.
You're the one who
doesn't tell anyone anything...!
I have no idea what you're
thinking half the time!
You bottle up your feelings and
hoard secrets like they're gold!
Well, that's because--
[MANATSU] There they are...!
Shinkou...!
Suzuhara!
We were so worried,
but you made it back!
[MAYURA] Are you okay?
[IZUMIKO] I'm fine.
I not hurt or anything.
All of a sudden
we were at the shrine...
Standing right in front of
the komainu shrine guardians.
Man, I'm starving...!
I haven't had anything
to eat in two whole days.
There's a noodle
stand by the shrine gates
if you can make it that far.
[MANATSU] I dunno...
you might have to carry me.
[EVERYONE laughs]
[MAYURA] I'll never forget
what you did for Manatsu.
Not for as long as I live.
♪
[IZUMIKO] Miyuki and I returned
home to Tamakura Shrine
to spend the second half
of the summer vacation.
I don't know why...
but out of the blue, Miyuki
asked me to perform a dance
to summon Wamiya.
[MIYUKI] I figured
it wouldn't work.
[IZUMIKO] You did?
Why?
[MIYUKI] Because you were acting
all buddy-buddy with Masumi...
so Wamiya's sulking now.
Huh...?
But how could you know that?
For a while I really
thought we'd seen
the last of Wamiya...
but then...
one day a talking crow
flew into my dorm.
He said he lacked the power to
take on human form in Tokyo...
I recognized the voice.
Is that why you
ended up outside the room
when Kisaragi
performed at the inn...?
And why it looked like you
had black wings after we fled
from the cave?
[MIYUKI] He told me if
we wanted to follow you...
he and I would have
to combine our powers.
I was wondering...
when Souda said you had entered
the school as my partner...
how did you feel?
I mean, do you...
think of me that way?
Well, to be honest
with you, it's hard to say...
In some ways I think
of you as a partner,
but in some ways I don't.
I mean...
it's difficult when I get the
feeling that you stay with me
in spite of what
you really want.
[MIYUKI] Even I wasn't certain
what I really wanted...
I was torn.
That thing with
Souda and Takayanagi...
I don't know...
It made me think I'd be
better off just going to
a normal school...
but then the crow
showed up...
and I began to
question that, too.
May I ask you
something...?
Do you find it at all strange
that Wamiya and Takayanagi
look so much alike?
Huh...?
Why do you ask?
[MIYUKI] It just bothers me
that Wamiya looks so much
like that pompous jerk.
[IZUMIKO] I still don't
see why it's a big deal.
[MIYUKI] To be blunt...
That's the kind of guy
you're attracted to.
Guys who look like
the two of them.
[IZUMIKO] What?!
[IZUMIKO] Just so I know,
when you say "you"...
do you mean me...
or do you mean...