[IZUMIKO] I want to change...
In this small way...
I can.
♪
Turning to the
local forecasts...
You can expect clear skies
throughout the morning hours...
[IZUMIKO] I'm leaving now, Sawa!
[SAWA] All right!
You'll be happy to hear
I'm baking steamed cakes today,
Izumiko.
Really?
[SAWA] Your hair!
I gave it a trim,
that's all...
It was sorta
bugging me.
How am I ever going to
explain this to your mother?
I've gotta go!
[IZUMIKO] Bye, Grandpa!
I'll see you later!
Izumiko...?
[TAKEOMI] Your hair...!
Sorry for being late.
[IZUMIKO] Nonomura...?
I was just wondering...
Is my father staying
in America after all?
I know Mother can't come home,
but I thought, maybe...
[NONOMURA] Apparently, Daisei
received some unexpected work.
[van honks]
[IZUMIKO] There goes my
parent-teacher conference.
[NONOMURA] Your hair...
Huh?!
[NONOMURA] Do your
bangs have anything to do
with these questions?
No, they don't, but...
It's just...
[IZUMIKO] I want to
live in the dorm when
I go to Sototsugawa High School.
So I thought a little
change would be nice.
[NONOMURA] Sototsugawa...?
I know, I know.
Father would rather I enroll
in that high school in Tokyo,
but...
I can't...!
Or rather...
To be honest...
I don't want to.
[IZUMIKO] Does it look funny?
[AYUMI] No way...!
In fact, I think
it's an awesome change!
[HARUNA] Yeah, it's a lot
more stylish than before...
I think it's much better.
[IZUMIKO] Honestly, I wanted
a hairstyle more like yours,
Haruna.
Well, if you want, I'd
be happy to take you
to the salon
I go to...
Of course, that's assuming
you'll be able to get away
from the shrine
on a weekend.
Oh...
yeah...
That's a really nice idea.
[BOY STUDENT 1] Okay, okay!
[YOHEI] Get it!
[BOY STUDENT 3] Got it!
[AYUMI] Hey,
now that you cut your hair,
maybe you can act more
like a normal girl.
Totally...
You want to enjoy
every second of life
at Sototsugawa,
don't you?
Then you're gonna have
to come out of your shell.
You're right...
I need to work on that.
[YOHEI] Dammit!
You coulda
dodged that, ya know!
You should be
apologizing to her,
not complaining!
That's right...!
You know how balls
freak her out!
No, I'm fine, really.
Whoa...!
She put a roof
over those braids...!
That is so lame!
You're such a jerk!
[HARUNA] Why do you get such
a kick out of teasing her?
[AYUMI] Yeah!
Or did you hit her with
the ball on purpose...?
'Cause, if so, that would
be called "bullying."
Don't listen
to those guys...
I like it.
Thank you, Wamiya...
That guy is scum.
[HARUNA] Izumiko?
What's wrong...?
Does your head
hurt really bad?
No...
I've decided
that I would
like to try out
your salon...
I'll ask
Nonomura if
he can take me
this weekend.
Oh...
Is Nonomura the guy
who drives you around?
I've never asked him
to do something like this.
[AYUMI] Look at you,
starting to open up!
Hey, I'll
text you.
Give me your
cell number.
You have one,
don't you?
Oh...
Sorry...
Mine's actually broken...
I haven't bought
a replacement yet.
[HARUNA] Really...?
I could have sworn
you just got a new one.
I did.
But that one's
already broken, too.
[HARUNA] Wow...
Guess you'll have
to get another new one.
This is research for the
upcoming fieldtrip in June...
Use the internet to find
someplace or something
you're interested in,
and then write a report.
So what'll it
be this time?
You do this...
and I'll write both
our final drafts.
You got it!
[NAKAMURA] ...You lose
points for goofing off.
[STUDENTS] Yes, ma'am!
[HARUNA] I'll pull up a map
of a particular area in Tokyo,
along with a travel
agency's web page.
[HARUNA] I still don't
understand why you aren't
any good at using the net.
[IZUMIKO] Searches take me
forever, that's all...
I could never find
something this fast.
[HARUNA] Wow, really?
[MISA] Hey, you two...
I don't think we're
working in partners.
[HARUNA] What's it matter...?
We're just helping
each other out, Misa.
[MISA] You can use
a crutch if you want to...
Personally, I don't
understand why some people
like to slack off.
Don't listen
to her...
She's so
full of it.
--[IZUMIKO] Yeah...
--[YOHEI] Really...?
[YOHEI] How the hell do you
plan on getting there?
Oh, come on,
it'll be easy.
Don't be stupid, man.
We only get two hours for it.
[TOMOYA] That's
plenty of time, right?
[YOHEI] Are you for real?
Haruna...
I think I will try
to find something
on my own.
Are you letting that
snide remark get to you?
[IZUMIKO] But it
was kinda true.
[YOHEI] She put a roof
over those braids...!
That's so lame!
[MISA] Personally, I don't
understand why some people
like to slack off.
[AYUMI] maybe you can act
more like a normal girl.
[HARUNA] Totally...
You want to enjoy every second
of life at Sototsugawa,
don't you?
Don't listen
to those guys...
I like it.
[water drop]
[IZUMIKO] Father?
Wha--...?
Hi, Izumiko...
Have you finally learned how
to use the video chat function?
I don't know...
Is that really you, Father...?
I don't believe it!
[DAISEI] Oh, uh...
I'm at work.
About the conference...
I'm so sorry...
The server kinda went down...
Well, in laymen's terms,
we had a bit of an accident.
[MAN 1] Hey, is that
your girlfriend?
[DAISEI, sarcasticly] Yeah...
we've been together for
about fifteen years now.
[MAN chuckles]
So you really aren't
coming home then, huh?
[DAISEI] No, I'm sorry.
But Sagara is
already on his way...
He should be there any time now.
I don't see why I should
care if he comes...
It's not like he's my guardian.
[DAISEI] Hmn.
Now you're angry.
[IZUMIKO] If you're not coming
home, I don't even want to hear
about this Tokyo school.
Please don't write it off.
I really think you should
at least consider it...!
It's called Houjou
Academy, it's nice.
Who cares what the
dumb school's called?
[DAISEI] It wouldn't be much
of a stretch to say this school
was made for you...!
In fact...
even your mother approves of it.
Really?
You saw Mother?!
[DAISEI] No, but
I'm sure she'd approve.
What did you do...?
Your pretty hair!
You know what...?
I'm perfectly capable of making
my own choices now, Father.
If you can't even make it to
a parent-teacher conference
you can't make decisions for me!
I'm going to Sototsugawa!
Izumiko?
Please try to calm down.
[IZUMIKO] This
can't be happening.
This...
this is wrong.
How can I be talking to Father?
Oh no!
The power...!
I have to hurry and
shut off the power!
[STUDENTS gasp]
What happened?
You too, Haruna?
Excuse me...!
I can't turn my PC on.
It lost power!
Same over here.
[NAKAMURA] What on
earth is going on?
[MISA] I keep pushing the power
button, but it won't work.
What's wrong Suzuhara?
[HARUNA] What is it...?
what's the matter?
There's no
need to cry...
Just tell me what
happened, ok?
It's my fault...
It's all my fault.
You're think you're
responsible
for the power outage?
[footsteps]
[P.E. TEACHER ]
Where's Ms. Nakamura...
A man's coming in a helicopter.
He has business with Suzuhara.
Huh?!
[helicopter in the distance]
All right, Izumiko.
I'm here for you.
There's nothing
you need to worry about...
Just leave everything to me.
You made it back here
quickly, Sagara.
[YUKIMASA] Yeah,
I thought I would come here
straight from the airport...
Impeccable timing, huh?
I'm confused...
Who is this...?
Is this man really an
acquaintance of yours,
Suzuhara?
[IZUMIKO] Yes, ma'am.
But...
he certainly doesn't
look much like a guardian.
[YUKIMASA] You don't think so?
[PRINCIPAL clears throat]
[PRINCIPAL] Surely you
understand our position...
As a precaution, we can only
allow students to be checked out
by family members.
[YUKIMASA] And I take it
you're the principal...?
Nice to meet you, I'm Daisei
Suzuhara's old friend...
My name's Yukimasa Sagara.
And I'm Sekine...
This is Nakamura,
she's a teacher here.
[YUKIMASA] Suzuhara asked me to
look after his daughter for him.
I'm afraid I don't have
anything to verify my identity.
[PRINCIPAL]
Pardon me for asking...
but how old are you?
[YUKIMASA] I turn 33
this year, actually.
Believe it or not,
I have a son the
same age as Izumiko.
Is that the truth?
Yes, ma'am...
There you go...
I think I can fill in
for her father, huh?
[IZUMIKO] I wonder if
Wamiya saw me fly off.
Sagara, did
Grandpa really say
that this was okay...? Us
flying by helicopter, I mean?
[YUKIMASA] Of course...!
Time was of the essence.
And you know about how
I broke the computer lab, right?
There's no need for you
to worry about that...
I'm sure your father
can deal with it easily.
I've never talked
with him over a PC
like that before...
I'm used to them totally
freezing up on me anytime
I touch one.
[YUKIMASA] Nothing
around you has changed...
If there has been
any sudden change...
it's with you.
Like how you cut
your hair, for instance.
[YUKIMASA] Did Yukariko
say you could?
What does mother have
to do with cutting my hair?
[YUKIMASA] Well, she was the
one who first put it in braids,
when you were a very young girl.
Besides, there are those
who consider hair
to be a source of
spiritual power.
[IZUMIKO] What do you mean?
I have spiritual power?
[YUKIMASA] I was
speaking hypothetically.
The fact that you made the
decision to cut your hair
is proof enough that
you've changed...
We saw each other
not long ago...
yet you seem different somehow.
[IZUMIKO] Sagara...
Do you think I'm weird?
I just want to be
a normal girl, that's all.
[YUKIMASA] And you
can do that if you go
to the local high school...?
Sototsugawa?
[IZUMIKO] Yes, I think so.
[YUKIMASA] Very well...
Believe it or not...
I have nothing against
prioritizing your happiness.
More backup is
arriving tomorrow...
Although...
I can't say how helpful
he's going to be.
[MIYUKI] Izumiko...
Suzuhara...?
That's me...
Sorry, but who are you?
You're seriously
Izumiko Suzuhara...?
He dragged me all the way out
to the boonies on my vacation
to see you...?
Is he crazy?!
I can't believe it...!
The Princess Deity...?!
Who would call this
the Hime-gami?!
Hime-gami...?
Where do you
think you're going...?
You shouldn't
wander around here.
Oh...
Izumiko!
Do you remember this little
monster...? This is Miyuki.
It's been about ten years
since you saw him.
Uh...
No, I'm sorry.
[YUKIMASA] And you?
[MIYUKI] Just the braids.
I had no idea you were
a mountain bumpkin still
running around with
your hair in pigtails.
[YUKIMASA] Hey...!
What'd I tell you
about watching your mouth?
Miyuki here is the
additional backup
I told you about earlier.
My goodness, Miyuki!
What a surprise...!
And just look how
big you've grown!
It's nice to
see you again.
You were always such an
active boy, as I remember.
You couldn't sit still
even for a minute!
You'd climb the sacred tree
and get stuck up there...!
And you were always
making Izumiko cry...
To think I was actually worried
about how you'd turn out!
You know how boys are,
but he's finally
starting to mature.
[SAWA] Oh, I forgot...!
I made some steamed cakes...!
Didn't you used
to love them, Miyuki?
Why don't I just
run and get them?
Oh, thank you
very much, ma'am!
[door shutting]
Now, what the hell's
this all about?
Whatever do you mean?
I mean you suddenly
acting like a dad...
And that thing
you said earlier
about me
being backup.
Tell me Izumiko,
what do you think
about Miyuki here?
Do you think you two
could become friends?
Friends...?
Well, uh...
And there
you have it.
That's her in
a nutshell...
You can see
it, can't you?
Will you quit acting
like you're here
to be our
matchmaker...?
Geez, you're starting
to give me the creeps.
I would never
hook you two up.
For one thing,
there's your social status.
If you wanted a
relationship with her,
the best you could ever
be is her servant.
Huh...?!
You've gotta be kidding me...
Has anyone even used that word
in the last hundred years?
[YUKIMASA] The word may change,
but the relationship doesn't...
Izumiko has the right to
choose, but you and I do not...
That's what I meant
when I said "servant."
Why are you saying
all this stupid stuff...?
'cause she's supposed to be
the "Hime-gami" or whatever?
[YUKIMASA] Izumiko here is a
girl destined to be protected...
by a great number of people.
This cowering dog?
This is the first time
I'm hearing about any of this,
too, you know!
That's because you
don't really need
to know about it...
This is our problem,
Izumiko, not yours.
Our problem...?
You're not including me
in this equation, are you?
[YUKIMASA] Naturally...
Why do you think
I brought you here?
The initial plan was
for you and Izumiko to enter
Houjou Academy, where you
would meet each other.
Things may have been
less awkward then...
However... it seems as if
the plan needs to change.
If Izumiko says she would
prefer a local school,
we must respect her wishes...
To help her feel more
comfortable with you,
I want you to transfer
to her school.
Transfer?!
You know something,
Yukimasa,
I'm starting to think
you've lost it!
You exist for the sole
purpose of serving Izumiko.
And what am I
supposed to do,
just smile and go along
with everything...?
All for the sake of some
mousey, ignorant hillbilly?!
Look, I don't like
this, either!
[SAWA] Are you leaving?
Oh...
Hi, Takeomi...!
I'm just going to take a quick
walk, if you don't mind.
[TAKEOMI] I didn't get
to speak with him for long,
but Sagara's son seems
like a promising young man,
doesn't he?
[SAWA] He completed his
mountain training when he was
just thirteen years old.
I only wish he had
come here instead of Haguro.
Why did Sagara say I'm a girl
destined to be protected
by a great number of people?
Or that Miyuki
should be my servant...?
None of it makes
any sense to me.
He's a Mountain Monk...
Trained to search for and
safeguard spiritual powers.
[IZUMIKO] A Mountain Monk?
Oh my goodness!
[YUKIMASA] His mountain training
has made him a bit cocky
and careless at times...
He tumbled down a cliff
not too far from here...
Luckily I went looking for him.
[SAWA] We must see to his--
[YUKIMASA] Sorry,
just one thing first...
Miyuki.
I've decided that I'm
going to be transferring
to the local middle school...
I would impose upon
you for a bit longer,
I hope that isn't
too much trouble.
think it would be a
good experience...
I injured myself
because I was arrogant...
My accident has helped me
realize that I still have
a great deal left to learn.
[SAWA] I must say, it's been
a while since we've had such
a lively dinner...
It's a pity Yukariko wasn't
able to be here for this.
[IZUMIKO] Where is
Mother right now, Grandpa?
The last I heard,
she was in Okayama...
but she should be back
in Tokyo before too long.
[IZUMIKO] Okay...
[YUKIMASA] Miyuki
usually lives on his own,
so he's dying for
some family fun.
Isn't that right?
It is.
[SAWA] Would you
like seconds, Miyuki?
[MIYUKI] Please...
I'd love some.
[MIYUKI groans]
Uh...
is it that bad?
Just waiting for the
meds to kick in.
You don't really want
to do it, do you...?
to transfer to my
school, I mean.
So...
why?
It won out over
getting killed.
Yukimasa is one
crazy bastard...
But he'll have to
do worse than that.
I have no intention of
giving up that easily...
I'm gonna keep fighting...
I swear it.
If you just told
Grandpa the truth,
I'm sure he would--
[MIYUKI] No use...
Yukimasa's the one
calling the shots.
Yes, but...
[MIYUKI] Jeez!
You're so pathetic.
You don't know anything...
You can't do anything...
You've never done a single
thing on your own, have you?
That's why you let everybody
else take care of you...!
Right?
No, I--
Nothing pisses me
off more than weak,
helpless people like you!
I...
I know there are things about
myself I need to change.
[MIYUKI] Great.
So you know...
Doesn't mean you'll do anything.
Are you sure you want
to talk to me like that?
[MIYUKI] What, you want
to tell Yukimasa...?
Fine by me, go ahead and tattle.
[YOUNG MIYUKI] Come on...!
Just catch it!
[YOUNG IZUMIKO cries]
[YOUNG MIYUKI] What?
Why don't you want
to catch the stupid ball?
Go ahead and tattle
if you wanna!
I remember the last
time you came here...
You threw your ball
at me over and over again...
That was you.
[MIYUKI] Yeah...
that rings a bell...
I saw a pathetic little girl
with ridiculous braids,
and I thought I'd help
by toughening her up...
I didn't do it because
I felt obligated.
And I'd never do anything
like that for you now.
Look, it's obvious
that Yukimasa is giving
your academic future
precedence over mine...
But I don't see what the
hell's so special about you.
I have no idea...
I never thought there was
anything special about me,
either...
[MIYUKI] All right, then we
agree on one thing, at least.
[NAKAMURA] I'd like to introduce
our new transfer student,
Miyuki Sagara.
Because of some
recent family issues,
I'll be staying at
the Tamakura Shrine...
Therefore I must give
Suzuhara special thanks.
But I certainly hope
that we'll all get along.
♪
[IZUMIKO] Ca--
Can I please
hold your hand?