[MAYURA] Hey, we're here.
Did you find anything?
[MANATSU] Nope.
We took a quick look around,
but so far there's nothing.
[MAYURA] The item
the curse relies on
is probably buried somewhere...
Assuming it's Onmyouji.
So you think
Takayanagi is
responsible
for this, then?
[MIYUKI] I can't see him
sitting back and doing nothing,
can you...?
He's probably been
planning this for a while.
Now that you mention
it, just before
the clothing demo I asked
Hodaka Murikami if there
was anything on campus...
He said it seemed much more
comfortable now than before.
[HIME-GAMI] Do not be afraid.
Nothing is here...
There are no what you call
"vengeful spirits" about...
If there were,
then it would be I.
I wonder...
[IZUMIKO] What I think is
that the ghosts of the people
who died in Hachiouji Castle
are on campus now.
[MIYUKI] Haunting it
like vengeful spirits?
Something's
by the library...
I can sense it!
[MIYUKI] I'll go check it out.
[MANATSU] Hold on...
I'll come, too.
Are you sure?
I'll be fine.
[MANATSU] Hey...!
Shinkou!
Wait for me!
I'm really sorry
about this...
about getting you involved in
something so dangerous, I mean.
Don't be sorry...
I want to help
however I can.
It's only fair...
After how you've
been there for me.
[approaching footsteps]
[MIYUKI] Got it.
I found a cursed vial...
Wasn't Takayanagi
in the Science Club?
Ready to
summon Masumi.
[MAYURA] Yeah.
Whatever Onmyouji
curse this is, it won't
be as powerful as Masumi.
Takayanagi shouldn't
have gotten so cocky.
[MAYURA and MANATSU]
Protect me and purify me...
Guide me and deliver me.
Prepare me for the
divine spirit's coming.
Shelter me now
and give me strength.
Yeah, that's more or
less what I was expecting.
[MASUMI] What?
My outfit's not a surprise?
So, Masumi, if anything
happens tomorrow,
do you think you
could fill in for me?
And show off
to the other kids...?
Totally!
♪
[GIRL 1] Wow...!
This is amazing!
[GIRL 2] This outfit
is heavier than I expected!
[GIRL 3] But why do I have
to dress up like a peasant?
[BOY 1] You look
great, though...!
I mean it.
[OKOCHI] Just as a reminder,
the battle games will be split
into two main groups...
The generals will face off over
the board game, backgammon,
while the foot soldiers are
out competing in the field.
Forty to sixty students
will be dispersed throughout
six places on campus.
Each game will include two
rounds where the teams try
to capture each other's flag.
We'll reassign the foot
soldiers based on the tally
of their flags for
the final battle...
which is going to be the
balloon popping competition.
It's the last day
of the festival...
so let's all stay focused...
We don't want anyone
getting hurt.
[MIYUKI] Suzuhara!
Where were you
assigned first?
I'm supposed to start
off with the Seminar House.
[MIYUKI] Here...
Take this.
You've kept it
this entire time?
[MIYUKI] No one ever
told me to give it back.
Will I be able
to use it?
You have to believe you'll
be able to get through
when you call...
I've already added all the
committee members' numbers...
but if you can reach my
cell, that's the way to go.
We have no way
of knowing what's
going to happen today...
but if you run into
any trouble out there...
please don't try to handle it
all on your own, okay?
Promise you'll call me...
If I can't reach you...
at the very least
I can offer advice.
[gasps]
[GIRL 1] What's that
above the library?
[BOY 1] That big,
silver thing?
[BOY 2] Who could make that?
[BOY 3] It's pretty cool!
[MIYUKI] What in the world?
Where did that come from...?
Look, check in with me
later if you can, okay?
It won't hurt to try.
[OKOCHI] It's the
Science Club's.
[IZUMIKO] Huh?
They didn't ask
permission to fly it until
the very last minute...
I'm amazed they
got it up in time.
I'm so sorry...!
I have to go!
Hey...!
I have to try.
[MIYUKI] It's me.
Can you hear me?
[MIYUKI] About time...!
What kept you?
[IZUMIKO] Can you see the hot
air balloon from where you are?
It's just...
I heard the
Science Club made it.
[MIYUKI] Yeah...
I checked with Hayakawa.
They registered it
and everything...
Can you sense
anything coming from it?
[IZUMIKO] It's
too soon to say...
but...
the air around it
does feel heavy.
[MIYUKI] It's right above
where the cursed vial
was buried, too...
I'll keep an eye on it.
This is nice.
Talking to someone on a cell.
It makes me feel more like
I'm an ordinary girl.
Things are changing...
I'm going to come closer and
closer to being a normal person.
[MIYUKI]
"A normal person", huh?
At the end of the day,
is being normal that important?
[IZUMIKO] It's all
I've ever wanted!
It really doesn't bother
me if you don't want to
become the Hime-gami...
I don't think anyone
would blame you...
She even said something along
those same lines before.
I'm not interested in
what the Hime-gami said.
I'm trying to talk
about what I feel.
[MIYUKI] Sounds like
you both agree...
so what's the big deal?
[applause]
[MIYUKI] At any rate,
do your best to be
invisible today, okay?
[IZUMIKO] Yeah, I know!
[MIYUKI] You've gotta avoid
getting yourself dragged into
Souda and Takayanagi's battle!
[IZUMIKO] Jeez, I know,
already stop it.
Yeah, you say that now,
but you tend to put yourself
in compromising situations...
Stay away from that guy!
[TAKAYANAGI] Did you...
want to hang up?
[TAKAYANAGI] I don't care
one way or the other...
Sagara can hear
our conversation.
[IZUMIKO] Don't cower down...
That's what he wants.
I see that you've made
some new shikigami buddies.
Don't sound so cross...
I would love nothing
more than if you were
to make friends with them.
Would that be so difficult?
You know those
things make my skin crawl!
[TAKAYANAGI] You think I'm a
cold-hearted monster, don't you?
An evil person who kills his
pets in order to turn them
into shikigami.
But...
You were there...
The one who truly killed
Ricardo was Souda's brother:
the divine spirit sibling.
Which do you
find more brutal?
[TAKAYANAGI] Souda thinks
she understands so much,
but she has a narrow
view of the world.
It's amazing that she thinks she
can control a divine spirit.
That sounds like the
pot calling the kettle black.
You're the one with shikigami.
Souda doesn't see
the big picture.
I bet she's never even once
stopped to consider what
it would take to expand her
powers to a global level...
Unfortunately she's only
concerned with the assets
already within her grasp.
So tell me something...
In your estimation...
Why has the academy
chosen to accept
so many foreign
exchange students?
[TAKAYANAGI] In
this day and age...
the East and West must
tear down their barriers.
We must pursue philosophies
that will be effective
on a global scale.
"God said, 'Let there be
light'; and there was light."
"And God saw the
light, that it was good;
and God divided light
from darkness and called
the light Day."
[IZUMIKO] Sagara,
can you hear me?
Are you still there?
[MIYUKI] Are you an idiot?
Don't argue with Takayanagi...!
I'm on my way right now!
Please stay away...
You have to...
or we're all doomed.
[hangs up]
[REINA] And the winner is...
Nobuyuki Kosaka!
[CLAUS] Are you all right?
You're pale.
[IZUMIKO] Y-yeah...
I am.
Now what was that about...?
You aren't afraid
of Claus here, are you?
Sorry about that...
I haven't spent much time with
people who aren't from here,
that's all.
If it helps,
I promise I'm like the
least scary guy ever.
[MIYUKI] What the
hell is she thinking?
It's nice you can smile
like a normal girl
when you want to.
It's unbelievably
beautiful when you do.
[MIYUKI] Arguing with a guy
like that is a mistake.
She doesn't stand a
chance against that jerk!
[IZUMIKO] I was building
a wall between us...
but I'm starting to know better.
I apologize but
I have to get going.
I have an idea...
maybe before the final round
starts, you can stop by.
[MIYUKI] How am I
running back downhill?
[MIYUKI] Another
Onmyouji spell?!
Wamiya!
You're here, right...?
You've got to do something!
[WAMIYA] Well, we can't
approach the Hime-gami.
Really?
And why not...?
Because you don't
feel like it...?
Isn't it your job?
[WAMIYA] Remember how Suzuhara
told me to stay away from her?
Words like that really
have an effect on me.
So you're saying this is
because of Suzuhara's spell?
[phone vibrates]
[KISARAGI] Sagara...!
Where are you?
Get back to the
library right now!
[OKOCHI] Attacking general:
Angelica Bernard!
[applause]
And the defending
general: Ryouji Sasaki!
[applause]
Ready...
fight!
[IZUMIKO] I never realized
how freeing it could be...
casting aside old
hatreds like this.
Poor Mayura...
I wonder if she'll
lose this battle.
Well, if she does...
I'll be there to console her.
[MIYUKI]
...call me...
Why do I feel like I'm
forgetting something?
[OKOCHI] The attackers
win two rounds!
[BOY STUDENT 1] All right!
[GIRL STUDENT 1] Angelica
can really play, can't she?
[BOY STUDENT 2]
Man, I'm starving!
[BOY STUDENT 3] Let's
go grab some food, then.
[OKOCHI] Hey, is this Hoshino?
It's Okochi...
Yeah...
The Attacking Army won twice...
[ANGELICA] Hello, Suzuhara.
Comment ca va?
Let's go see Takayanagi.
[ANGELICA] You know...
I love Japan...
That's why I came
to this school...
The more I learn of your
country, the more I want to...
That's part of why I am
such a 'fan' of Takayanagi.
[ANGELICA] That and
the way he looks...
Do you agree?
[IZUMIKO] Oh, well, I, uh...
actually...
[IZUMIKO] How would I describe
the way I feel about him...?
I've guess you could say...
I've...
had my eye on him...
[ANGELICA] Takayanagi has
taken the time to teach us
many things...
Take a look at that battle...
Notice anything about it?
What is going on down there?
[ANGELICA] Yes...
I knew you'd be able to see.
[IZUMIKO] There are so many!
What did you do...?
Have you transformed
the students somehow?
Those are just ghosts...
and they're
perfectly harmless...
They're not scary...
Look again.
You're not really
afraid of them, are you?
[MAYURA] What's the
matter with you...?
You've got a weird
look on your face.
[MIYUKI] A spell's been
placed on the hill...
It stops me from getting past.
What are you
talking about?
I think Takayanagi has
something up his sleeve...
Suzuhara needs to
stay away from him.
Now I'm getting
worried...
Do you want me
to call Masumi?
No offense, but you
used to have a much better
poker face than that.
Now is not the time
for teasing...
If Suzuhara changes her mind
and sides with Takayanagi,
you're going to have some issues
of your own to deal with.
You're not very confident
in her, are you?
[MIYUKI] It's not like that!
[MAYURA] Sagara...
Listen...
above anything else,
you care about Izumiko.
And above anything else...
I care about Manatsu...
Sound about right?
[MIYUKI] What are
you getting at?
[MAYURA] Do you think
we could pretend that you
and I are engaged...?
I mean, it would
be totally fake.
[MIYUKI] Huh?
[MAYURA] Someone from
Togakushi came to see me.
I don't see what that
has to do with anything.
[MAYURA] I'm expected to
marry as soon as possible...
to secure a future heir.
But given my situation,
marrying somebody just
isn't an option for me...
You know...
the same way that you
and Izumiko can't become
an official couple.
Wait, what are you...?
[MAYURA] She told me it would
cause too many problems,
so you can't be together...
That's why you haven't
been totally honest about
your feelings for her,
isn't it...?
I think we could both use
a façade to hide behind.
Of course, I would make
sure Izumiko knew exactly
what we were doing...
She would approve.
Look, there's something
you don't know about her yet--
She already told me
about the Hime-gami, Sagara...
That's precisely why I
chose you for this plan.
[GIRL STUDENT 3] I know
we can do better than this!
[BOY MESSENGER]
Princess General...
I'm begging you...!
We really need your
strength out there!
I think we should finish
discussing this later.
Okay, fine.
[BOY STUDENT 4] Yeah!
Here we go!
You can do it!
[MASUMI] I am the
Princess General!
And I will lead
this army to victory!
[BOY STUDENT 4]
You tell 'em, Princess!
[BOY STUDENT 5]
Yeah, let's go!
[ANGELICA] Did you know she
can walk through phases...?
She is extraordinary, isn't she?
[TAKAYANAGI] My little
birdies have informed me
of the most interesting rumor...
Apparently, there's a girl
here on campus who's as good
as a World Heritage.
She's more like a divine
spirit than anyone else.
I'm still waiting for you
to explain what you intend
to do with all the ghosts
you've got gathered here!
[TAKAYANAGI] There's
nothing much to do...!
What you see is actually
the mental energy emanated
by the academy's students.
[IZUMIKO] Energy you
forced them to emit...
You're trying to create
another plane, aren't you?
[TAKAYANAGI] The reason you
noticed the other phase
is because of your unique
ability to pass through them...
Humans with the eyes
of Saniwa generally try
to distance themselves
from spirits...
but you blithely draw near them.
I have to admit,
at first I thought
you were a shikigami!
[TAKAYANAGI] But
things have changed.
We're on friendlier
terms now than before...
So you'll let me get to
know you better, won't you?
And what would you
say if I refuse?
[TAKAYANAGI]
Why would you...
You've already decided
to ally yourself with me.
[IZUMIKO] When
did that happen?
[MAYURA] Well...?
Did we regain some ground?
[MIYUKI] You must've
had luck on your side.
That was Masumi...
You mean you
really couldn't tell?
[MIYUKI] I didn't know divine
spirits were good at backgammon.
[MAYURA] No,
that's not it exactly.
We just noticed that there
was something diminishing
the Defending Army's luck.
So Masumi swooped in and shooed
away whatever was responsible.
[MIYUKI] Something related
to Onmyouji, I take it?
Yeah, probably!
[MAYURA] Using Masumi's
powers is starting to
take its toll on me, though.
I bet I'm gonna be
bedridden tomorrow.
[MIYUKI] I'm going
to check on Takayanagi.
[MAYURA] Sagara!
Have you been thinking
about what I proposed earlier?
[TAKAYANAGI] This is it in
a nutshell: We must seal away
anything that is dangerous
and make the world into
a place that can be
controlled by humans.
That is essentially
the duty the world
has bequeathed
unto all Onmyouji.
[IZUMIKO] That's strange...
Why was I so afraid
of them before?
Now then,
tell me something...
It's about that time when
we were in the Media Room
and Ricardo was first dispelled.
It wasn't Sagara, was it?
[TAKAYANAGI] Sagara...
Sagara...
[IZUMIKO] Sagara...
Miyuki...
Miyuki...!
How could I have
forgotten about him?
Something's off...!
This isn't right!
It's not natural!
Protect yourself!
Rin...
byou...
tou...
sha...
kai...
jin...
retsu...
zai...
zen.
Qu'est-ce
qui se'st passe?
[CLAUS] Incredible...!
She's breaking free...!
I can't believe it!
If you believed you
could control me so easily,
you were wrong!
Now, let's not overreact here...
We were all getting
along splendidly.
Calm down and we can talk...
You agreed to join us
of your own free will.
[IZUMIKO] No I didn't!
I would never agree
to join you...!
Don't try to tell me otherwise!
[TAKAYANAGI] You may
have doubts now,
but I'll win you over
as many times as it takes!
[IZUMIKO] Not a chance...!
Not when I know with every
fiber of my being that what
you're attempting
to do is wrong!
Those shikigami, The
local ghosts you've summoned!
You're manipulating anything
that isn't human...!
But none of the beings
here want to be used by you!
Such arrogance...
is unforgiveable!
What is she?
Can a human really have
this kind of power?!
How is this
even possible?!
[IZUMIKO] Oh, no...
At any rate,
do your best
to be invisible today, okay?
[IZUMIKO] Everyone
here has seen now.
Things are changing.
I'm going to keep coming
closer and closer
to being a normal person.
[IZUMIKO] They've seen...
They know who and
what I truly am.
[HIME-GAMI] I am responsible
for the destruction
of the entire human race...
How can I possibly be human?
[IZUMIKO] If they know that...
Then I'm finished...
They'll capture and kill me
like they did before.
Please go away!
Don't even look at me!
Don't touch me...!
Just leave me alone!
Wait a second...
when you say that, are you
talking about Izumiko?
[MIYUKI] That's right...
and I think you should
probably do the same.
[explosion]
[STUDENTS freaking out]
What do you think
just happened?
I have no idea.
♪
[MIYUKI] Suzuhara...!
Will you bear the weight of the
Hime-gami's burden alone...?
What happened to wanting
to be a normal girl?