♪
[MANATSU] Suzuhara...
This is Masumi.
[IZUMIKO] Hello...
It's nice to meet...
you.
Nice to meet you, too...
I can't tell you how happy it
makes me to find somebody else
who can see me...
I'm so glad I dressed
appropriately.
You call that appropriate?
[MASUMI] Of course...
When I'm at Houjou,
shouldn't I wear the uniform?
[MANATSU] Sure, but...
[MIYUKI] You can see Masumi...?
So what does he look like?
Different from the shiki?
[IZUMIKO] Yeah...
Totally different.
[MANATSU] ...please, try not
to ruin my reputation.
Don't worry, we'll be
fine waiting here.
I've already told him
where to be...
He's lower level than I am...
So if I say "come,"
he has to obey.
[IZUMIKO] He wasn't
dispelled, then.
What an unimpressive line-up
we have here...
I assumed you were
brighter than this, Sagara.
You should know by now that
you can't bring me down.
No, we're just spectators
this time around...
Souda here is the one
you should talk to.
[TAKAYANAGI] The
little brother, huh...?
It's a pity about what
happened to your sister...
Though, she did poke
her nose into my business.
[MANATSU] So, what?
Putting curses on people
is a hobby of yours?
[TAKAYANAGI] A curse?
Call it "the power of my
influence." She only got hurt
because her ill intent
toward me bounced back at her.
[MANATSU] Oh, please...
You hurt my sister.
No way I'm going to
let that go unpunished.
[TAKAYANAGI] And what exactly
do you plan to do about it...?
You don't stand a chance
against my shikigami.
And, yes, I know
you've got a spirit
there with you...
but what's the point? Surely
you don't think yourself capable
of using it without
a shiki binding...
It would devour
anyone who tried.
[MANATSU] I'd
never stoop so low.
See, I'm not like you...
taking pleasure from the
fear and pain of others.
That sounds like someone
who's afraid of power.
You're wrong...
I just don't like petty games.
If there's somebody
I want to punch...
I do it myself.
How barbaric.
If things turn nasty,
don't blame me.
Do my bidding at once!
Ricardo...!
Heed me now and break his spell.
You idiot...!
You released the shiki?!
What have you done...?!
Even I can't control them once
they've been set free like that.
[MANATSU] How many pets did you
kill to create that shiki...?
Yes, I know how they're made,
and you should be careful...
Their grudges live
longer than you.
But you're the one
who's in danger...
They target the person
who unraveled the shiki.
Yeah...?
Is that right?
[TAKAYANAGI] You have
to defend yourself...!
Or he'll kill you!
[MANATSU] Oh, dear...
I don't know how to.
[TAKAYANAGI] What have you done?
It's in their best interest...
to be devoured in this way.
[TAKAYANAGI] You
aren't a human...
You can't be...
[MASUMI] So you
finally caught on, huh?
Just for the record,
I'm abiding
by Manatsu's wishes...
Oh, and, my name's
Masumi, by the way.
I want what
my siblings want.
I don't fight for them,
but with them.
[slap] Is the message
sinking in...?
I am not like [slap]
your shikigami...
Do you understand that?
[MANATSU] That's the
trick with Masumi...
You always have to let
him steal the limelight.
He's pretty pissed off...
Let's leave him alone for now.
[MASUMI] She looks so
peaceful when she's sleeping.
[IZUMIKO] You took
off your bandages.
[MIYUKI] Yeah...
It wasn't much of an injury.
We gave Takayanagi the choice
to apologize or shut down
his website...
Not surprisingly,
he opted for the latter.
[IZUMIKO] Yeah?
Really?
Really.
And it's good news
for the whole school...
The Student Council election
will be much fairer now.
Kisaragi is the current VP.
Supposedly, she's
running for President.
[IZUMIKO] So Takayanagi gave
up his candidacy altogether?
[MIYUKI] He sure did...
The Soudas must have
done a number on him.
Yeah, the triplets
really were amazing,
weren't they?
And I think I can tell the
difference between shikigami
and divine spirits now.
[MIYUKI] Yeah?
How so?
[IZUMIKO] Divine spirits
exude purity and freedom.
It's been a long road,
but I'm glad
I came to this school.
[MIYUKI] Oh?
[IZUMIKO] I've always
felt like I was weird--
like I stuck out...
It made me self-conscious...
But Mayura and her brothers
are special, too.
And you never see them
brooding about it, do you?
I think I have a lot
to learn from them.
You and Mayura
have gotten really close
in such a short time...
I'm happy for you...
You've always wanted
friends, right?
And they allowed us to
see their ultimate trump card...
They didn't have to do that...
But unless you want
to lose your new friends,
Don't tell them
about the Hime-gami.
And why not?
Because of Mayura...
I'm pretty sure that
she knows my powers
aren't particularly
impressive...
That's why she feels so
comfortable being friends
with me.
Right now she thinks
you and I are partners.
Let her keep thinking that.
[IZUMIKO] But...
I don't know about
keeping secrets...
[MIYUKI] How much
does it matter...?
I'm inept...
Feel free to use my
shortcomings to your advantage.
[IZUMIKO] Okay.
So he doesn't mind if other
people think I'm his partner.
Wait, so...
was that him, then...?
Did he protect me?
[MIYUKI] I wonder how much
all this training I'm doing
is really going to
teach me in the end.
I mean...
If you stop to consider it...
I'm a lot closer to
Takayanagi than I am to Souda.
[IZUMIKO] But...
I thought Takayanagi upset you.
Yes, he did...
Very much.
[IZUMIKO] Then I guess
I'm still confused.
[MIYUKI] Forget it.
It's not something
you need to understand.
Yeah, well,
what if I want to...?
Please.
I'm not asking
for too much, am I?
I just want to know
what you're thinking!
[MIYUKI] About
the only thing
on my mind
right now is how
the school will
handle Ricardo's
sudden disappearance...
Surely they'll notice.
They'll probably say the
obvious: that he went back
to Brazil.
MSF...
Sorry, have you
heard of the MSF?
[IZUMIKO] No...
I haven't...
What is it?
I don't know
all the details,
but...
sounds like-
[YUKIMASA] I've happened upon
the princess and her page.
A secret meeting, huh?
Oh, hello...
Did you come to
visit the school?
[YUKIMASA] No...
I'm a part-time instructor...
This is where I work.
[IZUMIKO and MIYUKI]
Hold on?! You work here?
Seriously...?!
Does anybody here actually
buy half the crap you say...?
I mean, you've never
held a real job!
[YUKIMASA] I go
where I'm needed.
Something you might
understand eventually...
And right now, the
princess needs a real
knight to protect her.
Not a pathetic page boy.
Why do I even bother...?!
This is ridiculous...!
I'm not anyone's pageboy.
Ugh, seeing you makes me sick!
Sagara, don't...
[GIRLS gossiping]
[GIRL 1]
I heard he went to MIT!
[GIRL 2] I heard
he used to be a model!
[GIRL 3] Yeah,
well, I heard he has friends
at the embassy!
[GIRL 4] I heard
he's a martial arts master.
[IZUMIKO] Um, so...
Sorry, I thought I
should check with you...
but people are going
to talk, y'know...
What should I say when
word gets out that
the new teacher's your dad?
[MIYUKI] I think the new teacher
can answer his own questions.
[IZUMIKO] I haven't had a
chance to talk to him yet.
[MIYUKI] He's here to
protect his princess...
I don't think he really
cares what you say.
[IZUMIKO] But I'm
asking about you...
I want to know what you're
thinking about all this.
[MIYUKI] All right, then...
I'll tell you.
[MIYUKI] I'm thinking
I want to be left alone.
Yukimasa is a jerk.
I don't want people to
associate me with him...
And, if they see me
talking with you...
they might think I'm on
friendly terms with him...
like you obviously are.
[IZUMIKO] Oh... kay.
[MIYUKI] Ah, Kisaragi!
Got a sec?
[KISARAGI] Oh...
hey, Sagara...
What's up?
[MIYUKI] You mentioned earlier
that the Executive Committee
was shorthanded, and I'd
like to join if that's okay.
Wow, that would be fantastic.
Thank you so much!
[IZUMIKO] All right.
It's not like I lost anything...
I mean, we never could have
stood together as equals.
I was alone...
from the beginning.
[YUKIMASA] I'm handing
back your quizzes.
[IZUMIKO] I still don't
understand why everyone
wanted me to go to Houjou...
I mean, what's so special
about this school that
you want to work there?
[YUKIMASA] It's a trial...
One for which we gather
students such as yourself...
We're searching for people
who must be safeguarded
for the sake of the future...
It's still in the
preparation phase.
Think of it like World Heritage
sites, but for humans.
[IZUMIKO] I don't really
understand what you mean
by that.
[YUKIMASA] Let me explain.
Humans who can communicate with
divine spirits are currently
considered an endangered species
When humans lose
the ability to communicate
with spirits completely...
it's likely that humanity
will be expelled from
the Earth's environment.
The point of this
project is, of course,
to prevent that.
As soon as the testing grounds
are free of stressors,
and everything is well-balanced
and in harmony, I will be able
to take my leave once again.
[IZUMIKO] Um...
Can I ask...
why you and Miyuki
don't get along?
[YUKIMASA] Now there's
a loaded question...
Well, if it helps,
I'll say this...
I haven't coerced him
when it comes to you.
[IZUMIKO] Really?
But you said before...
that he's my page...
[YUKIMASA] Poor kid.
He just can't
take a joke.
[FEMALE TOURIST] Sorry?
Would you mind...
a photo?
[WOMEN go gaga]
Certainly!
[MAYURA] Oh, yeah?
Seriously...?
And why would you
invite me to join you?
I dunno, 'cause you're
pretty well known amongst
the high school students.
You've got more
influence than most.
[MAYURA] That's
all well and good...
but what are you really after?
Hey, Izumiko...!
Miyuki just asked me to join
the Executive Committee.
What do you think I should do?
I'm sorry, I...
have to go see a teacher.
[MAYURA] Are you okay?
[IZUMIKO] A sun shower!
[singing in Japanese]
[IZUMIKO thinking] That's right.
I already know how
to pick myself back up...
I just have to listen
to my own voice...
Instead of using all
my energy worrying about
what other people think.
[singing stops]
You're Suzuhara...
aren't you?
[IZUMIKO] Huh...?
Yes!
I'm the new
Student Body President,
my name's Honoka Jean Kisaragi.
Oh, uh...
I was in the middle
of practicing a few
of my own
traditional dances...
Would you care to
come and watch me?
There's someone
here I've been meaning
to introduce you to.
[MIKOTO] Hey, Sagara.
Oh, hey, Kanzaki...
What's up?
I was just wondering
about Izomiko Suzuhara.
Didn't you two enter
this school as partners?
What's she like?
More or less what you
would expect from a girl from
the mountains who wears glasses
and pigtails all the time.
I just don't get it.
Why did he pick her over Ichijo
Takayanagi or Mayura Soda
for that matter?
It doesn't make any sense.
Well, good afternoon...
It's a pleasure to meet you.
[KISARAGI] This is
Hodaka Murakami.
He's an actor...
His family is
known for kabuki.
Thanks to the family
business, I have to repeat
a year due to
poor attendance.
[KISARAGI] He was the first
Student Body President.
[MIKOTO] If you ask me...
I think the secret Student Body
President is interested in her.
Wait, the secret...
what...?
Who do you even mean?
[MIKOTO] Never mind...
But from what I've seen,
he clearly possesses a lot
of influence around here...
I mean, really...
It's like we have two
Student Body Presidents.
[HODAKA] Can you perform
the Kagura dance, Suzuhara?
[IZUMIKO] Huh?
[HODAKA] I would
really like to see it
if you don't mind.
[IZUMIKO] No, please...!
I really couldn't.
[HODAKA] And
why not...?
You think we'll
laugh at you...?
Or, maybe...
Maybe what you're most afraid
of is that we'll find out
what you truly are.
Honoka here
was just like you.
Within you is a greatness
that should come out
with every gesture you make...
But you can't
seem to unleash it.
Tell me, Suzuhara...
have you ever worn make up?
There's meaning behind
the stage make up we don.
Painting your face has
a lot in common with casting
a spell, you know...
When a person's face is altered,
they enter a different state
of self.
Just set your
feelings free...
Can you sense it?
Your face is meant
to be seen by others.
[IZUMIKO] I'm sorry, but I don't
think I can dance for you now.
I hope that will change someday.
Maybe you would like
to let your hair down.
[door slams open]
[MIYUKI] What the hell
are you doing here?!
[IZUMIKO] Sagara?!
[MIYUKI] You're Hodaka Murakami?
I'm Miyuki, a first year
in the Executive Committee...
You know, right...?
You know about
Suzuhara, don't you.
And is there a
problem with that...?
I'm a judge.
I possess the power of a Saniwa.
I can tell which deity has
taken possession of someone.
[MIYUKI] I don't care
if you're a judge!
I still don't want
you coercing her!
And yet you are
interfering with her life.
Do you have that right?
[MIYUKI] I do.
No!
Are you my
partner or what?
But you told me
not to talk to you...
You don't want to be linked
to your dad through me!
Yeah, I said that...
But that doesn't mean you should
go do whatever you want...
At least with Yukimasa, we know
what his ulterior motive is.
I wouldn't even be here
right now if you hadn't
snapped at me like that!
You two can
really fight...
It's almost like
you're a couple.
[MIYUKI] We're no--
[IZUMIKO] We're no--
[IZUMIKO] Oh, wow...
That's all stuff I've
been wanting to say...
I've needed to say it...
but I never could...
not until now.
[explosion]
No, not again.
[HIME-GAMI] This area is weak.
It seems there is
no barrier here.
You and I have met before,
in the very distant past...
Hundreds of years ago.
You crave it, after
all this time, do you not?
The sight of me.
No matter the era,
the deity of performances
serves the fan, not I.
Furthermore,
you are not the arbiter.
That choice belongs to...
Izumiko.
Miyuki Sagara.
I will remember
your name, henceforth...
For now, take my hand.
There is something important
that I must ask of you.
Please, do not allow me
to come to life...
I beg of you.
Don't let her
become the Hime-gami.
Please.
I don't understand
what you mean.
It's painfully simple...
All of humanity is
going to crumble...
because of me...
I am the source of its demise.
♪
[MIYUKI] I expect you to keep
your end of the bargain...
In exchange...
I won't keep any
secrets from you.
Yes, very well...
I can certainly see why
you want to keep this quiet.
[MIYUKI] In that case
I'm taking her back.
[HODAKA] Suzuhara. If you
ever need to ask advice
from someone...
I do hope you'll
feel free to come to me.
Although...
you should come alone.
What happened...?
I wish I remembered.
[MIYUKI] It takes a while after
it's over for you to remember...
doesn't it?
[IZUMIKO] I need
to braid my hair.
Go on ahead.
[MIYUKI] Please don't
expect anything from me.
I can already tell...
I'm not up to this...
I'm not somebody who can
support another person.
[IZUMIKO] Yes...
I know that...
I don't expect anything.
I have no idea what
the future will hold...
and I don't know what
I should be doing...
I don't even know
where I belong.
I understand that...
I don't know what's
to come either, but...
I know what I hope for...
That I'll be able to stand
on my own someday...
I want that...
But even so...
[IZUMIKO thinks] I'm
glad you came today.
[MIYUKI] I just noticed...
your lips are red.
[IZUMIKO] That's Sagara...
He doesn't tell
anyone everything...
Not even me.