[OKOCHI] So this
year's festival theme
is The Warring States
Period, from the fifteenth
and sixteenth centuries.
On the first day, we will
announce the stage events
and open the booths, which will
be judged by popular vote.
The points earned by this vote
will be distributed accordingly
for the following day's event...
the Warring States Game.
[OKOCHI] Now...
the president would like
to make an announcement.
As the Board of
Directors has suggested...
Ojitero Houjou is going to
be the theme for the battle
on day two of the festival.
Yeah, sorry,
but what's that?
[OKOCHI] The ruins of
the Hachiouji Castle from
the late Warring States Period
are located near here.
The master of that
castle was Ujiteru Houjou,
the last warlord
to defy Hideyoshi.
He lost in the end, and
was ordered to commit suicide.
Supposedly the battle
was super bloody!
[KISARAGI] Okay, that's enough!
You already ranted about this
in the Director's Room...
What we need to decide
today is how to incorporate
the pivotal battle into
some sort of a combat game.
Keep in mind that we
don't have that many days left,
so we'll want to make sure
we manage our time well.
And, naturally,
I'll be counting on you
to help out with that.
Okay?
Hey, Kisaragi...!
I, like, totally forgot
to tell you something!
Hayakawa...!
I'm in a meeting!
[HAYAKAWA] Oh, my bad...
Festival Committee Director
requesting assistance from
the Executive Committee.
It's lookin' like we're
gonna be short-handed for
the Warring States
traditional clothing demo.
[KISARAGI] Luckily, I already
planned on lending you
some members from the committee.
Great, this should
be easy, then...
Do you have a warlord and
a princess we could borrow?
What, models?
Sure.
A little eye candy will
really get the party going...
I bet the crowd would just
eat Souda up if she was
our princess model.
Oh, please.
She couldn't model
to save her life.
Excuse me?
[HAYAKAWA] Anyway, I'll
let you talk it out...
Thanks a lot!
One of these
days that guy is going
to give me a migraine.
[MANATSU] You're not supposed
to stand out, remember?
[MAYURA] I didn't say 'yes'!
I think you'd be way
better as the princess model.
That's ridiculous...
as student body president,
I could never do something
like that.
♪
[IZUMIKO] "The date
was June 23rd, 1590...
an immense number of Hideyoshi
troops surrounded the castle.
Nearly defenseless, the castle
was taken in a single day...
Ujiteru was not present, and
a mere three thousand people
were within the castle walls."
[TAKAYANAGI] Hello, Suzuhara.
Did you enjoy Togakushi?
I have a piece of
advice for you...
You should side with me
instead of Souda.
Oh, yeah?
And what makes you say that?
[TAKAYANAGI] The real battle
is going to be decided during
the school festival.
What do you mean?
[TAKAYANAGI]
The school will open.
During the course
of the festival,
the academy's barrier
will be down...
People from the outside
will come and go freely.
[IZUMIKO] Meaning...
you'll get help from the adults?
[TAKAYANAGI] That's not
necessarily what I meant, but,
really, none of us will be
standing here on our own
at that point ...
That's as true for you
as it is for me.
Did I keep you, Ichijou?
[TAKAYANAGI] No.
I just arrived.
[TAKAYANAGI] Give
it some thought...
Wouldn't you like to
join me and my forces...?
The invitation extends
to Sagara, as well.
Make the right choice...
You don't want to end up like
Ujiteru and his followers.
"The women in the
castle took their own lives
and their children's...
The waterfalls ran red
for three days and--"
[FEMALE GHOST] Milady!
[FEMALE GHOST] Milady...!
Milady!
[FEMALE GHOST] Milady!
Who's there?
Who do you call?
Say my name...!
Please, say my name!
Or else I won't
know who I am!
[IZUMIKO faints]
[YUKIMASA] Izumiko!
Ah, Izumiko...
You're awake, then.
[IZUMIKO] Why are you here?
As it happens,
I have my nursing license...
You're in good hands.
[IZUMIKO] What happened...?
I was researching Hachiouji
Castle, and then...
I don't remember...
[YUKIMASA] You overexerted
yourself this summer...
Honestly, I think you should
have spent the entire
summer vacation at Mt. Tamakura.
[IZUMIKO] I know.
I'm sorry.
I realize now what happened
at Togakushi must've been
a big deal...
since it brought mother
out in the open.
[YUKIMASA] That's not all
you've noticed, is it...?
A large-scale experiment is
about to take place on campus.
And there's a high
probability that
something dangerous will occur.
It is imperative
that you trust us.
We exist for the sole
purpose of protecting you.
So please don't forget that.
[IZUMIKO] Just so I know,
when you say "you"...
Do you mean me...
or do you mean...
the Hime-gami?
They're one and the same...
So, both, I guess.
[IZUMIKO] I don't
agree with you...
She and I aren't the same...
Togakushi proved that.
[YUKIMASA] That's because
we still have Yukariko.
I believe you will
become the Hime-gami
who removes her veil...
and that could very well
mean that you will be
the final Hime-gami.
Don't you see...?
You're going to become
a princess deity, Izumiko.
[IZUMIKO] Sorry, I have
a hard time believing that.
Even Miyuki
doesn't think there's
anything special about me.
[IZUMIKO] I just
realized something.
I want Miyuki to think
of me as a normal girl.
Not someone special.
But if he decides
to dedicate his life
to serving the Hime-gami...
I'll lose that
opportunity forever.
My son hasn't made
a very good page so far.
The time has come
for him to face facts...
The Hime-gami has
already chosen him.
When?!
[construction sounds]
I need to head over
to the dressing room soon.
[IZUMIKO] So tell me...
why did you agree to fill in
as a model for this?
[MAYURA] It sounded easy enough,
and it doesn't hurt my cause
to be on the Festival
Committee's good side.
Also, Manatsu's out of the way,
off practicing archery...
Which is a good thing because
he hates it when I dress up
for some reason.
I bet Masumi can't get
enough of it, though, huh?
[IZUMIKO] Have fun!
[MIYUKI] Got a second?
[IZUMIKO] What's up?
[MIYUKI] I wanted to know what
you're doing for your costume
on the day of the festival.
[IZUMIKO] My costume?
The Executive Committee's
wearing all black, right?
I don't mean that...
I want to know how you plan
to deal with your pigtails.
I'll probably be wearing
a hat, so I should be
able to get away with
putting them up in a bun.
[MIYUKI] So you're not
going to unbraid them...
no matter what?
I'm not sure.
What are you saying...?
How can you not be sure?!
In Togakushi, I realized
that I can unbraid
my hair without changing...
without becoming the Hime-gami.
[MIYUKI] But still-
I don't want
to spend my whole life
with my hair in braids!
I have to let it down someday.
And I would just like to be
prepared for what'll happen
when I do.
Oh, come on...
Is this a belated
rebellious stage?
[IZUMIKO] I have to learn
to look after myself...
There won't always be
someone there to help me.
I like your
determination...
but I think you might be
forgetting something...
Onmyouji spells, mantras,
and Ninja techniques...
they're all essentially
the same thing.
Spiritual self-defense...
As far as we know, you aren't
able to use your power
to defend yourself.
And as for her...
I think the Hime-gami usually
uses a lower god for protection.
Unfortunately, you don't
have anything like
that to work with...
Do you know what spells
Onmyouji, Shugendou, and Ninpou,
or ninja techniques,
all have in common?
No, I don't know
what you're talking about.
First, there's Kuji.
Rin...
byou...
tou...
sha...
kai...
jin...
retsu...
zai...
zen.
Then there's another version...
Hayakuji.
Rin...
byou...
tou...
sha...
kai...
jin...
retsu...
zai...
zen.
I think it's a good
thing that you want to start
looking out for yourself and
fighting your own battles.
But you need to learn at least
one form of self-defense first.
I want to learn.
Please teach me.
[HODAKA] Good afternoon!
It's nice
to see you again.
Can't place me, huh...?
Hold on a second.
Maybe this will help.
[IZUMIKO] Is that you, Hodaka?!
Shh...!
Let's keep it on the down-low.
I don't want the others students
to know I'm here today.
So you're here
in your official capacity
as one of the judges?
[HODAKA] I was curious to
see how they were preparing
for battle...
So I thought I would
drop by and watch.
[IZUMIKO] When you say "they,"
are you talking about Takayanagi
and his supporters?
Maybe I am,
maybe I'm not...
But Souda seems to be
putting up quite a fight.
Ultimately, how she uses you
may be what determines whether
she wins or loses.
You're a bit of an
unknown entity, you see.
Like a hidden treasure
with mysterious properties.
How's the snotty brat...?
I mean, your partner...
You have truly been
paired up with somebody
unworthy of you, huh?
If you're talking
about Sagara...
He's doing fine, and
he's every bit as snotty
as he's always been.
Is that what you want to hear?
Whoops.
Did I hit a nerve?
Not at all.
Now, that's a lie.
You're angry.
As you know,
my position is such that
I'm not allowed
to assist anyone.
That said, I am terribly curious
to see what role you're going
to play in the festival.
[FEMALE GHOST] Milady!
Milady!
Hurry!
You have the ability
to see what others can't,
don't you...?
Well, can you see anything
besides divine spirits...?
Ghosts, for example.
I believe only those who
are able to see many things
are referred to as Saniwa.
Well, then, can you tell me...
is there something on campus?
It feels much more
comfortable than before.
[ORIKUCHI] Suzuhara!
Good, I found you...!
We need you in the
dressing room, quickly!
[ORIKUCHI] Our middle school
model won't be able to make it.
I think she had a family
emergency or something.
So...
I kinda need to ask a favor...
You aren't talking about
having me model, are you?
I'm gonna fill in there.
But I was supposed
to MC the program.
Could you take my job...?
All you have to do
is read the script...
Occasionally, throw in some
adlib or ask the speaker
for a comment.
If those are my
choices, I'll model.
That's probably a better plan.
Have fun, okay?
Are you all right...?
I know this wasn't something
you were expecting.
[MAYURA] I don't really
think this is a set-up...
but I can't be too sure.
A set-up?
[MAYURA] We don't know
who Takayanagi's recruited
to his side, do we?
[DRESSER] Hi there!
[MAYURA] Just be careful.
[DRESSER] I'll be
dressing you today...
Wow...!
Your hair is so long...
First change into
the under-kimono,
and then I'll
do your make up.
Do you think...
I could put a wig
over my braids?
[DRESSER] No, sorry.
I'm afraid you'll
need to take them out.
[IZUMIKO] Did somebody plan
this to make it easier
for the Hime-gami to appear...?
What should I do?
Of course!
Rin...
byou...
tou...
sha...
kai...
Jin...
retsu...
zai...
zen.
I can do this.
I know I can.
[HODAKA] So, how have
you been lately...?
Doing well?
Should be interesting.
I cannot wait to see.
[MAYURA] Hey, Hayakawa!
Oh... hey!
Souda, you came...!
Man, is it good to see you.
Boy, you sure oughtta
brighten up the auditorium...
Oh...
I'm sorry...
May I ask the name
of this other princess?
[MAYURA] Surely your
memory's not that bad...
You met her along with
the rest of the committee.
[HAYAKAWA] I did...?
Wait...
Hold on, are you Suzuhara?
Oh, wow!
[ORIKUCHI] Thank you for
your patience, everybody.
At this time, I would like to
invite our models to please
take the stage.
[applause]
Oh, my goodness.
Would you look at that?
[IZUMIKO] You
don't have to worry.
I'm not switching
places with her.
I can't let that happen
in front of everyone.
[ORIKUCHI] And now, let me
introduce our volunteers...
First up, modeling for
Toshije Maeda, we have--
Oops...!
Uh, Hi...!
So, my name's Hayakawa.
Aaand...
what else...?
This hat is
surprisingly heavy...
And hot, too!
[laughs]
[BOY STUDENT 1]
Who's that girl?
[BOY STUDENT 2]
On the end...?
Beats me.
[IZUMIKO] Am I insane?
What was I thinking...?
Letting myself get
dragged into this.
No, I'll be fine...
Besides, I know how
to defend myself now.
Hey, over here!
Look at the camera, please.
Not only is Souda modeling,
but so is Suzuhara...!
Best clothing demo ever!
[IZUMIKO] I saw you with Hodaka.
What were you talking about?
[MIYUKI] We were wondering what
the chances were that you were
going to do something crazy.
Well, I didn't
do anything crazy.
What the heck was
going through your head when
you agreed to be a model?!
There are plenty of other
girls who could've done it!
Thanks a lot.
[IZUMIKO] I pulled it off
without a hitch,
and this is how he reacts?
I just can't win with him.
Didn't you realize there are
people out there who would love
to use your game of dress-up
as an opportunity to summon
the Hime-gami...?
I bet you never
even considered it.
Even Murakami was stunned that
you left yourself wide open
like that.
[HIME-GAMI] Stunned, was he...?
In that case this
was not his doing.
[MIYUKI] I don't see what
the big deal is, anyway.
What's wrong with braids...?
I mean, it's not like
they're all that bad.
[HIME-GAMI] Oh...?
They're "not all that bad," eh?
[MIYUKI gasps]
[HIME-GAMI] I find them
quite stifling, actually...
but perhaps one must
become used to them.
[MIYUKI] It happened...!
Why now?
[HIME-GAMI] A short skirt...!
My legs feel so free...!
How wonderful...!
I could walk for hours.
What a splendid feeling...
It took quite a while, but
here I am, at long last.
Why do you wear
a look of such apprehension?
Are you not pleased
to see me again...?
I thought you would be.
The real Suzuhara
is good enough for me...
thanks.
Oh, come now,
you needn't be shy...
It finally happened...
I can now synchronize with this
body as if it were mine...
Today is a day to be celebrated.
This is my right hand...
It is with this hand that
I give to the masses.
This is my left hand...
It is with this hand that
I accept offerings from
the heavens.
I find both meet my needs...
Yes, quite satisfactory...
Now then...
which of my hands
would you prefer?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
[HIME-GAMI]
Which would you hold?
Hey, listen...!
You need to return to--
[HIME-GAMI] Snub me and face
my divine wrath, Sagara...
Is that understood?
This is the first time
I have been able
to move about freely...
As such, I wish to take a walk.
Hey...
Oh, crap!
[HIME-GAMI] Say something.
[MIYUKI] What should I say?
Fine.
I have a question, then...
When you're here,
where does Suzuhara go?
[HIME-GAMI] I would not know...
It does not interest me.
[MIYUKI] Why does it take a
little while for Suzuhara
to remember what happened
when you take over her body?
Do you know that?
[HIME-GAMI] Perhaps remembering
is too much trouble...
Enough of this.
I do not like it when
you speak of other women...
If, for example...
I was to speak of
nothing but Yukimasa...
how would you feel then?
[MIYUKI] No way...
that's a totally different--
[HIME-GAMI] It is not...!
When I am enjoying the present,
do not spoil my fun...
I have so little.
[MIYUKI] Are you happy now...?
This is Hachiouji
Castle's keep...
You said you wanted
to come here.
[HIME-GAMI] So I did.
[HIME-GAMI] Do not be afraid.
Nothing is here...
There are no what you call
"vengeful spirits" about...
If there were,
then it would be I.
[MIYUKI] Does that mean...
Are you a human who passed away?
[MIYUKI] Did you die
filled with regret?
How could I have
passed without regret...?
After what I was
responsible for...
I brought humanity
to its demise.
[HIME-GAMI] I despaired for what
my species did to the world...
I destroyed it
along with myself...
But...
after I had lost my body...
I learned that I was able
to travel through the past.
I yearned for help...
From the very core of my
being, I cried out for it.
If the future is not
to end in destruction...
I must find someone...
someone who can understand me.
After an experiment that spanned
more than a thousand years,
I found that only my brain and
ovaries had been preserved.
They had become what
is known as World Heritages...
However...
humanity's dire future
remained unchanged.
World Heritages?
Thrice I have done this...
Thrice I have passed like
this through thousands
of generations of women...
Because I lack
a body of my own...
I am gradually beginning
to forget who I am.
And so I doubt there
will be a fourth time...
This will be my final chance.
You aren't
actually a deity, then...
You're a human woman from
Suzuhara's family line,
aren't you?
I am responsible
for the destruction
of the whole human race...
How, then, can I be human?
Do you want to know
how frightening my power was...?
I was murdered for it
in my second future...
They killed me and
placed me on display.
[MIYUKI] What a
terrifying thought.
You must understand me...
My abilities make me the
antagonist of the human race...
I side with those who
fight for the planet,
rather than for humans...
I am searching for people
who can comprehend that...
and will hold me back.
[MIYUKI] Yukimasa...
Yukariko...
the Mountain Monks...
that's what they do?
And you want me ...
You want my help
with this, too...
Can I please have some time to
think about it before I decide?
Do not be ridiculous.
Wamiya is intended to serve me.
I'm in the Sagara family!
[HIME-GAMI] True...
and yet you are also Wamiya...
Do you not recall how
beautifully you melded
at Togakushi?
I can remove
him from you easily.
Miyuki Sagara
here does not seem to care
for you much.
[WAMIYA] Trust me,
the feeling is mutual...
I can't stand him, either.
I only decided to stay
with him because he was
so utterly helpless
and pathetic.
[HIME-GAMI] Oh, yes...
It has never been in your
nature to look after humans...
has it?
[WAMIYA] I know you're
starting to forget things,
but that's fine...
I just want you to know
I'm here to help you
in whatever way you need.
Now you are treating
me like a doddering old lady...?
That is enough...
Return now.
Look...
I'm going to have to put
some serious thought
into Wamiya, too...
Now, please...
will you please
return Suzuhara to me?
And if I do not want to?
You cannot force me
to leave against my will.
I am protected
by a self-defense spell.
You remember.
The one you taught me earlier.
Besides, what more
could you want
than what you have now...?
Time alone here with me.
I release you!
Return now from
the field of battle!
Izumiko!
Come back to me...!
I know you...!
Please...!
You have to make
the right choice!
♪
[IZUMIKO] It sounds
like you'd rather spend time
with the Hime-gami than with me.