And as we ride to certain death,
we trust our successors
to do the same for us.
Because my soldiers
do not buckle or yield
when faced with the
cruelty of this world.
My soldiers push forward!
My soldiers scream out!
My soldiers rage!
[SCOUTS screaming]
--The commander!
--Ride. Don't look back!
Keep charging!
[SCOUTS yelling]
♪ Opening Song ♪
[ZEKE TITAN]
How sad.
To be deprived of the chance
to learn from the past.
King Reiss stole their memories
of the outside world,
and this is the tragic result.
They're doomed to repeat
the same foolish mistakes.
And in the end, all of them
will go to their deaths.
Young and old, pouring out of
the walls in a suicide charge.
[ZEKE TITAN]
Because if they're going to die,
they may as well do so proudly.
What bullshit!
[ZEKE gasps]
[ZEKE TITAN]
I crushed it into dust?
Ha, ha. What's gotten into me?
Why am I getting so worked up?
You're not like
your father, remember?
You need to find
joy where you can.
So now, I'll turn them all into
proud little chunks of meat!
The second volley's coming!
Fire!
[MARLO]
It's coming.
Is this how I die?
[MARLO]
I wonder what Hitch is doing?
Knowing her, she's
probably still sleeping.
[MARLO]
Sounds nice.
But why am I thinking about
her at a time like this?
[SCOUTS screaming]
[ZEKE TITAN]
Yeah! Game over!
Ha! How'd you like that?
I thought I'd change up
the pitch a little.
I'd call that a shutout.
[SCOUTS yelling]
[ZEKE gasps]
[SCOUT 54A yelling]
Fire!
Foolish.
You really think those little
toy guns are going to help?
[SCOUTS screaming]
[ZEKE TITAN]
And all that screaming.
What good could
that possibly do?!
[SCOUTS screaming]
How sad.
Poor, pathetic things.
[ZEKE]
Hmm?
What's this?
My Titans have fallen?
[LEVI growls]
[gasps, grunts]
[yells]
[LEVI yells]
[ZEKE]
Huh?
A single soldier might
pose a threat to me?
Yes. Captain Levi is dangerous.
[ZEKE]
Is this Levi?
--[ZEKE] My nape!
--[LEVI grunts]
[ZEKE gasps]
What the?
I can't see!
[ZEKE]
Did he take out my eyes?
[LEVI grunts]
[ZEKE gasps]
My legs!
What's wrong? Not enjoying
yourself so much anymore?
[LEVI grunts]
[ZEKE]
Tch. I'll harden!
I won't make it in time!
[LEVI]
Come on, let's have some fun!
[LEVI grunts]
[BOTH yelling]
[yells]
[screams]
After transforming, if your
body's severely damaged,
it's too busy healing to let
you resume your Titan form.
Isn't that right?
[ZEKE groans]
Hey. I asked a question.
It's only polite to answer.
[LEVI]
I can't kill him yet.
There must be someone out
there who's still alive.
It doesn't matter if they're
on the brink of death.
I can inject them and
make them a Titan.
[LEVI] Then we just
have them eat this guy,
and the Beast Titan's
power is ours.
If there's one person still
breathing, I can save them.
[LEVI gasps]
[LEVI grunts]
[gasps]
[LEVI]
Hey. Where are you going?
Stop.
Go, now! Rip him to pieces!
It hurts!
They were right about you, Levi!
You are dangerous.
But you must've used all
your weapons up by now.
You'll die like
the rest of them!
It may have been a hard-won
fight, but victory is ours!
Hold on.
I made a promise to
Commander Erwin...
...that I would kill you
no matter what it took.
I promised!
[LEVI grunts]
There's no way.
I'm alive? How's that possible?
The others!
[FLOCH]
Hey!
Is anyone else out there?
[JEAN]
That bastard.
What'll take to put
him down for good?
Why won't he just stay dead?
What the hell do we do
against something like that?
[JEAN]
Hey, Armin.
I think getting Eren
out of here safely
might be the best
we can hope for.
[ARMIN]
He's thinner.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[ARMIN]
The Colossal Titan.
He's gotten a little thinner.
Guys! It's exactly
like Hange said!
Our best bet
against the Colossal
is a battle of attrition!
You remember her
experiments with Eren?
He could only transform
up to three times.
If that's the case
for a 15-meter Titan,
a 60-meter might be
even less efficient!
And then there's his steam.
I think he must be burning
through flesh and muscle tissue
to produce it.
Everything except
for his skeleton.
[JEAN]
So, what are you saying?
[MIKASA]
Armin.
[ARMIN]
I have a plan.
The rest of you need
to draw Reiner away.
Eren and I will defeat the
Colossal Titan ourselves.
[BOTH gasp]
The two of us can do it.
Trust me on this.
All right, then.
You leave Reiner
to us and get going.
Sure took ya long enough.
You had me thinkin' we
were all gonna die here.
[EREN]
Couldn't tell you why, but...
...when I think about the
freedom that we all lost...
...I feel strong and fearless.
[ARMIN] If this plan goes the
way I'm hoping it will, well...
...I won't get to visit the sea.
[ARMIN]
I couldn't tell you why,
but when I think of
the outside world,
I feel courage flow through me.
[ARMIN grunts]
Eren, wake up!
The sea is waiting for us.
[ARMIN] Okay, that's
the plan, more or less.
So now we just
have to execute it.
If we can succeed in tricking
Bertholdt, then... we'll win.
The day will be ours.
[JEAN]
Understand?
We're leaving Bertholdt to them.
We have to trust
they can handle him.
As for us, we need to keep
Reiner at a safe distance.
Fly just close enough to
him to get his attention.
[MIKASA, CONNY, SASHA]
Got it!
[SASHA gasps]
[BOTH groan]
[CONNY]
He ignored us?
Damn it!
It looks like he's
focused on Eren.
[MIKASA grunts] Then we'll
just have to kill him!
Mikasa!
[MIKASA grunts]
Hey!
If we can't get
Reiner's attention,
we'll have to finish
him off right here!
Our job is to protect
Eren and Armin!
Yeah. I know that.
We've only got
three Thunder Spears.
That's all, but...
We've gotta try anyway!
Because there's no way we're
gonna win if we don't fight!
[REINER]
Something hit me.
But what?
A single attack
took out my knee.
I can't remember much
after that moment.
I'm gonna blow this
whole area away.
If you can, lie down with your
Titan body facing upwards.
[REINER]
Bertholdt.
I'm confused.
What the hell happened to me?
I don't know what's going on.
I don't have much
strength left, but...
...I do know Eren's over there.
As long as we capture him,
that means we got
what we came for.
[REINER]
Right, Bertholdt?
[REINER] I'll deal with these
idiots as quickly as I can
and then head over
to back you up.
[BERTHOLDT] The four of
them who went that way
must be after Reiner.
So, the only ones who
survived the blast
were the members of the
104th who were with Eren.
[BERTHOLDT] Honestly, I was
hoping they would have all died
in the blast, but...
...I'm used to having to
fight for what I want, Armin.
What's the point of waking Eren
when he's all
battered like that?
[BERTHOLDT]
These are your final moments.
I'm interested to see
how you'll spend them.
The real question is,
how long can I hold out?
It's on me.
If I give up too soon,
the plan will fail,
no matter how good it is.
[EREN gasps]
Hold on.
Armin, are you...?
Sorry, but I can't die till I
get a chance to look at the sea.
So I'll have to let go before
things get really bad, okay?
The rest will be up to you.
No big surprise.
I mean, I've never
exactly been a hero, so...
[EREN]
No. You're wrong.
You just can't see what I do.
Don't worry. It'll be okay.
In all the years we've
known each other,
have I ever lied to you?
And I promised that we'd
go to the sea together.
[ARMIN]
So no matter what happens,
stick to my plan till the end.
[EREN gasps]
Shit.
[BOTH gasp]
[ARMIN]
Eren!
I knew it.
This battle's already been won.
He probably has a
severe concussion.
I doubt he can even
stand up on his own.
[BERTHOLDT]
Enough of this.
Let's end it.
[growls]
[ARMIN yelling]
[grunts]
[BERTHOLDT]
Armin.
You fought well to the very end.
But it's over now.
Eren! Armin!
No. They have their own job.
We need to focus on Reiner.
[JEAN]
If we're going to take him out
with just three Thunder Spears,
this is the only way.
We'll initiate the attack
while he still can't move.
It might not work.
But win or lose, this ends now.
[REINER]
Bring it on.
[JEAN yells]
[JEAN]
Reiner!
First, I act as bait.
[gasps]
[JEAN]
Conny and Sasha will follow
with two of the remaining
Thunder Spears.
and aim for Reiner's
jaw from both sides!
[CONNY yells]
Sasha!
Jean!
[MIKASA]
One of them missed.
[JEAN]
If we blow off his jaw,
that should leave
Reiner's mouth wide open.
Mikasa should be able to
aim the last Thunder Spear
at his nape from
inside the mouth.
[MIKASA]
It's not open.
Doesn't matter.
I have to try anyway.
[BERTHOLDT]
I don't understand.
How is he still holding on?
His anchor should've come loose.
He shouldn't even be
able to get this close!
[ARMIN]
I knew it.
His bones aren't being consumed!
The anchors stay put if
they're not in muscle!
But most importantly,
he's stationary.
He can't move his body
while he's emitting steam!
[BERTHOLDT]
Really, Armin?
This is how you want it to end?
Smart as you are,
this is the best plan
you could come up with?
Flailing in midair.
Being scorched to death.
[ARMIN]
I can't breathe!
I have to let go.
No! Not yet! It's not enough!
I have to keep fighting.
Buy more time!
[BERTHOLDT]
What's the point of this?
A diversion?
But Eren's still collapsed
there on the ground.
Mikasa and the others
have their hands
full with Reiner.
Just a last, desperate act.
All right.
If this really is
the end for you,
I'll do my best
to make it quick.
[ARMIN screams]
[ARMIN]
Hold on!
Don't let go!
Entrust it all to Eren.
[ARMIN]
My dreams.
My life.
Everything!
The only thing I have
to give is this!
[ARMIN]
He'll make it.
Someday... Eren...
...will reach the sea.
[ARMIN]
He'll reach the sea...
...for both of us!
[CONNY]
Mikasa! It's too risky!
[HANGE]
No, it's perfect!
[CONNY gasps]
[HANGE grunts]
[ALL gasp]
[MIKASA]
Hange!
Now's your chance! Get him!
No, she can't!
Reiner!
It's over!
[BERTHOLDT]
It's over.
Now, it's just Eren
and the horses.
[gasps]
[BERTHOLDT]
What the?
A hardened Titan?
[BERTHOLDT gasps]
Gotcha!
[yells]
[BERTHOLDT]
It was a diversion!
Eren tricked me into thinking
he was out of the fight.
Armin was buying him time,
giving him the
chance to harden--
to make a replica
Titan in his place.
[BOTH gasp]
[BERTHOLDT] They did it...
to make me lower my guard.
So Eren... could
sneak up behind me...
...and attack.
In all the years we've
known each other,
have I ever lied to you?
Dammit. I should've
known how far he'd go.
[ARMIN crying]
[EREN] Hey, why don't
you put up a fight?
Huh?
They pick on you 'cause
you won't hit back.
You fine with losing forever?
[ARMIN sniffles]
You're wrong.
I'm not losing.
Huh?
Because I don't run.
[EREN]
So, what's your name?
[ARMIN gasps]
[EREN]
Armin, you are a hero.
You're the bravest of us all.
♪ Closing Song ♪
[NARRATOR] The remaining
Scouts manage to
turn back their enemies.
But their victory
comes at a heavy price,
leaving them paralyzed
with despair.
Next episode: "Midnight Sun."