[EREN grunting]
[EREN]
Shit!
Oh. You’re awake. I’m glad.
Just hang in there
for a bit. We’ll be okay.
[EREN]
At least Historia’s all right.
[CHRISTA]
Eren, listen.
My father has always
been humanity’s ally.
His only goal is to keep the
people within the walls safe.
It’s clear to me now
that we misunderstood him.
He didn’t deny anything.
It’s true that
he went after the Scouts,
and his people
did kill Pastor Nick.
But he did that
because he had no choice!
Everything he’s done,
he did for the sake of humanity.
[ROD]
Thank you, Historia.
Please let me explain the rest.
[EREN]
It’s coming back to me.
Yeah. The last thing I remember
is the two of them.
How long has it been?
Captain. Armin.
What happened to the Scouts?
[EREN gasps]
[EREN] What’s the deal with
all these glowing pillars?
They just keep going.
I can’t even tell
if its day or night.
[EREN] Wait, there’s something
else about this place.
It feels familiar somehow.
Have I been here?
[ROD]
If you were wondering, no.
You’ve never been here before.
Although, you may
recognize it nonetheless.
[EREN]
What’s that supposed to mean?
Um, Father?
Could you explain to Eren?
Of course. I intend to.
But before that, there’s
something I’d like us to try.
This could make him remember
without us saying a word.
[EREN gasps]
[EREN]
What is this? Who’re they?
These aren’t things I’ve seen.
No.
Whose memories are these?
[EREN]
The key!
No. Why?
[TITAN roars]
♪
Dad? What happened to you?
[yells]
[ROD]
Well?
Do you remember?
Have you learned
of your father’s sin?
♪ Opening Song
[birds chirping]
[FRIEDA]
That’s amazing, Historia!
Just look how well
you can read now!
Thank you,
but I only learned how
because you were
here to teach me.
Ah. That runny nose of yours
needs some tending to.
I guess the next thing
I should teach you
is how to act more ladylike.
Blow into this.
Ooh! Now that’s what
I call a job well done.
--[CHRISTA] Hey?
--[FRIEDA] Hmm?
[CHRISTA]
What’s it mean to act ladylike?
[FRIEDA]
Hmmm. I’m not exactly an expert,
but... I’d say the young lady
in your book has it down.
[CHRISTA]
Christa?
Yeah. Is she one of
your favorite characters?
[CHRISTA]
Mhm.
Christa’s always
thinking about other people
and helping them out
in whatever way she can.
That’s what I think
makes a proper lady.
You’ll find pain and suffering
everywhere you look
in this world.
So do your best
to make things better.
Treat people with love,
and they’ll love you in return.
Well that’s how you act.
So I wanna be just like you.
Huh?
Do you think
that if I try real hard
I can grow up to be like you?
[FRIEDA exhales]
No need!
You’re already perfect!
No need to change a thing!
[BOTH laughing]
I’m sorry, Historia,
but I have to go now.
That means you need to
forget all about me again.
Until next time.
[CHRISTA]
Huh?
Huh. I wonder who that girl is.
What’s wrong? Are you all right?
How could--? How could
I forget? In all that time.
I was never alone. I had her.
She was always there for me.
She gave me books.
Taught me to read and write.
She was so kind to me.
So how could I forget about her?
I take it you’re
talking about Frieda.
[CHRISTA]
Frieda?
If it was a kind-hearted
young woman
with long, black hair,
then I would imagine
that it was Frieda Reiss.
She was your half-sister.
She must have been
worried and gone to
check up on you
from time to time.
If she was
erasing your memories,
know that she did it
to protect you.
So, that’s why I forgot her?
That’s right. But touching
him seems to have
brought those memories
back to you.
An unexpected side-effect.
Father, where is she?
Do you think we could
visit her sometime?
I’d like to tell her thank you.
If she hadn’t
been there for me, I--
I wouldn’t have had anyone.
I need to thank her.
[ROD] Frieda is no longer
of this world.
At one time,
I had five children.
But five years ago,
my wife and our children
were murdered by a man
named Grisha Jaegar.
Your sister was killed
by Eren’s father.
[ROD] Grisha had the ability
to transform into a Titan.
I still don’t know
where he obtained it.
But his goal was to steal
something from the Reiss family.
What Grisha sought
to obtain was power.
[FRIEDA grunts]
[ROD]
The power of the Reiss family
which resided within Frieda.
[TITAN GRISHA roars]
[ROD] Frieda’s Titan was by far
superior to all the others.
In theory, she had
unsurpassable power.
However, at her young age,
she lacked the experience
to wield it properly.
And because she couldn’t
unleash her true potential,
Grisha ate her, and in
doing so, stole her power.
But that wasn’t enough.
He then turned his gaze
to the children.
He wanted to eradicate
the Reiss family.
He started by crushing
Dirk and Abel,
who were fourteen and twelve.
He trampled my wife as she held
our ten-year-old Florian.
He squeezed the life
from my eldest son, Ulklin.
Through some curse or miracle,
I alone managed to escape.
It’s not fair.
She didn’t deserve that.
Why would he do
such a terrible thing?
[footsteps]
[KENNY] Hey, hey, hey!
What’s the holdup?
Whatever you’re talkin’ about,
we don’t have time for it.
Thing’s are goin’
straight to hell outside.
Do explain.
What’s been going on?
[KENNY] Well, the Scouts
started a coup d’état,
and all the other regiments
have taken their side.
Everyone found out that
ol’ King Fritz was a fake.
And now his whole council
has been arrested.
Yup, it’s been a royal shitshow.
[BOTH gasp]
[KENNY] Matter of time
’til they show up here.
So you’d best get a move on.
All right then, I will.
Now take the Anti-Personnel
Control Squad
and defend the entrance
at all costs.
[KENNY]
Uh...
[ROD] I already told you that
the ceremony can’t be done
in the presence
of you or your crew.
[KENNY] Aww! Where’s
the trust, Your Majesty?
Did I make ya mad?
Fine. Sorry. I’m just
so worried about you.
I trust you.
It’s because of that trust
that you’re here. Now go.
I feel the same, Your Grace.
[KENNY]
Tch.
[ZACHARY] From now on,
whenever you eat,
you’ll be digesting your meals
from the bottom up.
As always, you’ll wear
the finest of clothes,
but only from your feet
to your knees.
And so you don’t get lonely,
I’ll take you out once a week
to be paraded to the public.
It’s so beautiful.
This may well be the finest
work of art man has
ever conceived.
All those decades of planning it
have finally paid off.
Just wait. Art must be
completed by its audience.
You must be seen by the people,
the same ones you tyrannized.
And that will be my masterpiece.
[AURILLE] Zachary!
You’ll pay for this tenfold.
The blood of slaves
runs through your veins,
and nothing’ll change that!
You will never be the
equal of a noble like me.
[groans]
Soon enough, you’ll forget
any of this happened.
I bet you’ll even
forget how to shit!
As long as we’re on the subject,
why don’t you tell me if
you nobles really do shit gold?
I’m sorry, what was that?
Your mouth’s full!
[PYXIS]
This could end badly.
All the members
of the king’s council
are telling us the same thing.
It’s just as your
late father speculated.
The Reiss family has the power
to alter people’s memories
as it suits them.
From what I’ve been told,
aside from those of a few noble
bloodlines that’re immune,
whole cities could be
affected at once.
[gasps]
So they could still--
In the event that Lord Reiss is
able to obtain Eren’s "Scream,"
this uprising of ours will
amount to absolutely nothing.
If you ask me, that’s why
the council members
have been so cooperative.
They don’t think it’s
worth getting beaten.
[ERWIN] Right. Because if this
ability should come into play,
we’ll forget
everything they told us.
Although, I’d imagine
that they’d prefer
whatever torture
we could throw at them
if they knew
what would await them
once they’re
given up to Zachary.
I don’t understand him.
To think that he would
dedicate so much
of his life to such
a morbid goal.
So then, you knew
what he was planning?
[PYXIS] Mmm. ’Twas a
slip of the tongue.
I suspected.
At the very least I knew
his motives were perverse.
And unlike you, I’m none
too fond of gambling.
Also, unlike you...
...I’m willing to die
if it means protecting
what’s left of humanity.
The only reason I backed you
was because I believed it
to be the best choice
for the human race.
Had the government
passed my little test,
I was prepared to make a stand
against you and Zachary.
To think, we just stood
as comrades in a coup d’état,
and I’m already
talking like this.
I once heard in a
song that someday
humans would stop fighting.
When will that be?
[MALE SOLDIER 43A] Commander!
The wagons are ready, sir.
Troops are standing by.
We await your command.
Peace between men
will never be certain.
Not until our numbers
fall to one or less.
[PYXIS chuckles]
Shit.
Here I was hoping you might have
something optimistic to say.
[ERWIN]
Your attention!
Soldiers of the Survey Corps,
our mission is to recover
Eren and Historia.
We will now
make for their location,
believed to be the chapel
on Reiss’ land!
[LEVI] You should understand.
This is Kenny the Ripper.
If he’s there,
he’s our biggest obstacle.
In terms of his threat level,
it’s like you’ll be fighting me.
Or wait. With those weapons
of his, he’ll be stronger.
Then he’s unbeatable.
At least for us.
Maybe we should wait and
meet up with other soldiers.
No chance in hell.
Right. Course not.
If we wait for reinforcements,
then Eren might get eaten.
You know, based on what
the captain just told us,
the odds won’t be
entirely in Kenny’s favor.
--You really think so?
--Yeah. His squad is
well-trained, but we have
way more combat experience.
Have to ask. How is it
that you lived with
Kenny the Ripper but know
next to nothing about him?
Did the two of you never talk?
Not much. I only just learned
the man’s last name.
Dunno if you heard,
but it’s Ackermann.
Might be a relative of yours.
[gasps]
I remember my parents
saying that
my dad’s side, the Ackermanns,
were persecuted when
they lived in the cities.
My mom said her
ancestors were eastern.
Her family’s appearance made it
difficult for them to fit in.
Both groups were chased
deep in the mountains
near the edge of the walls.
That’s how my parents met.
But my father never told me
why the Ackermanns
were persecuted.
He looked the same
as all of you,
so I don’t think
he was of a different race.
Tell me this:
Have you ever suddenly felt
a "power" awaken inside you?
[gasps]
I have.
[LEVI] This has happened
for Kenny Ackermann as well.
Suddenly, out of nowhere,
he felt an absurd
amount of strength
surging through him.
And in that moment, he knew
just what he needed to do.
And it’s happened to me too.
Makes me wonder.
[KENNY]
Fess up, Gramps.
C’mon. You’re dyin’ anyway.
Ah, Kenny. I take it
you were just out
killin’ more of
the Military Police.
[KENNY] Yeah. If you’re
talkin’ about those goons
what were snoopin’ around here,
they’re in the ground
helping the trees grow now.
[coughing]
Speakin’ of trees and such,
there’s a branch of the family
that moved south to Shiganshina.
Guess they should’a changed
the name when they left,
’cause they’re still
gettin’ screwed with.
So of course,
they’re still poor as dirt.
What in the hell happened to us?
I thought that
the Ackermann clan
used to be the king’s
personal bodyguards.
Now the whole damn family’s
on the verge of extinction.
So why don’t you tell me what
you did to piss off the king?
C’mon, won’t ya tell your
sweet grandson one last story?
[KENNY’S GRANDPA coughs]
What sweet grandson
are you talkin’ about?
Surely not the infamous
"Kenny the Ripper"
who’s been
terrorizin’ the capital.
It ain’t that the monarchy
hates us or has any cause to.
They’re just
afraid of us, is all.
Reason bein’ we Ackermann’s
are one of a few families
the king can’t quite control.
What do you mean by that?
[KENNY’S GRANDPA]
Can’t tell ya the whole story,
’cause I don’t know it.
But it’s true that
our family was once
honored and trusted by the king.
More than that,
from what I was told,
we Ackermanns were once
the king’s sword.
For generations,
each king has passed
the Power of the Titans
to his successor.
Huh? Power of the Titans?
What’s that?
[KENNY’S GRANDPA]
I don’t know how it works,
or what all else there is to it,
but this power allows the king
to wipe out human memory.
To erase the past.
Only a few noble
bloodlines are immune.
Among them, there were
two groups that decided
to turn their back on the king.
One of these groups
was the Eastern clan,
and the other was
our own Ackermann clan.
Hence all the persecution.
And nothing can end it.
[coughing]
[KENNY] Ain’t the heartwarming
story you wanna hear
on your deathbed,
but I found my little sister.
Kuchel’s been working at
a brothel in the underground.
She got knocked up
by a customer.
I couldn’t convince her
to get rid of the thing.
[coughs]
[KENNY] Oh, hell.
Who’d wanna be born into this
piece of shit world, anyway?
There isn’t a dream you could
have worth sufferin’ through it.
[HANGE]
Found it. A hidden door.
Reiss and Eren
should be inside.
Hopefully the layout’s
close to what I predicted.
[LEVI]
These presents better pay off.
Considering the time
we spent prepping them.
[CAVEN]
We count at least seven enemies,
and you can bet
Captain Levi’s among them.
As you all know, last time
we caught Levi by surprise.
And then he killed
twelve of our comrades.
The government’s
been overthrown,
which means
we’re the fugitives now.
So I wouldn’t count on
getting any backup.
We’re in some deep shit.
In this tiny, screwed-up world,
dying is preferable
to what we would get
if we decided to surrender.
But here’s the thing:
That’s what life in the walls
has always been.
Nothing’s changed.
We’ve got a foe we can’t beat.
So we stand by and wait
for them to break through
our walls and kill us.
We fought to be Military Police,
and then Interior Police.
And now we’re Kenny’s elites.
We did this to find purpose
in our meaningless lives
in this meaningless world.
I see no cause
to stop believing now.
If Kenny and his dream
can’t turn this game around,
he’ll flip the board.
’Kay. We should be
ready to go now.
All right then.
Is everyone here ready?
’Cause you’re all about
to dirty your hands.
♪
Guess that’s a yes.
♪ Closing Song