[KRUGER] Each of the Nine Titans
has a name to describe it,
and that includes the one you're
about to inherit from me.
[KRUGER]
Throughout history,
this Titan's marched
in the vanguard.
It has ever pushed forward,
seeking freedom.
And for freedom's
sake, it fights.
Therefore...
...it's called the Attack Titan.
[HANGE] Eren has commanded
Pure Titans once in the past,
to escape from a dire situation.
[EREN] If someone with royal
blood is turned into a Titan,
then it might be
possible for me to use
the Founding Titan's powers
while touching them.
But if the military knew
it was a possibility,
what would they do to Historia?
[KRUGER]
Build a family.
[GRISHA]
Huh?
[KRUGER] Be it your wife,
your child, or even a stranger.
Love someone in those walls.
If you can't do that,
it'll only repeat itself.
This cruel history.
These foolish mistakes.
They'll repeat.
You have to see this through.
Complete your mission and
save Mikasa and Armin.
Mikasa? Armin? Who are they?
I-I don't know.
They aren't from my memories.
♪ Opening Song ♪
[BRASS 59C]
Our foe is the world.
[BRASS 59A] That information
should stay in this room.
If it became public
knowledge, there'd be chaos.
Yes, I concur.
Regrettably, we can't
let this get out
till we fully grasp
the situation.
Shall we deceive the
people once more?
That's what you're
suggesting, right?
That we keep our citizens
complacent and blind,
as the late King did?
If we do that,
then by what ideals did
we oppose King Reiss?
What right did we have
to seize his crown?
Then let's announce it.
[COURT gasps]
It's only fair.
This is information that
the people once knew,
before my predecessor
stole it from them.
As the people of the walls, all
of us will share the same fate.
Which is why we must now
unite as one and work together.
[PEAURE] The monstrous Titans
that have menaced us so,
are in fact, human.
They're known as Subjects
of Ymir, or Eldians,
and we share a common ancestry.
When our King erected
these walls 100 years ago,
he altered our memories
using Titan powers,
so as to make us think
that beyond the walls,
humanity had gone extinct.
In truth, there are countless
people beyond the walls.
But when it comes to
us Subjects of Ymir,
they believe that we
are a race of devils.
[PEAURE]
In the near future,
the enemy will invade our lands
in order to obtain the
resources beneath us.
Their plans began
five years ago,
when they used the Colossal
Titan to breach Shiganshina.
I know the article's
already published,
but is all of this as
credible as you claim?
[HANGE]
At the very least,
it addresses most of
the doubts and questions
that we've had this whole time.
I know it's not the
truth we would hope for,
but it's what we have.
'Preciate it.
[HANGE] So how are
people taking the news?
It's a mixed bag.
Some just accept it.
Some laugh it off.
Some lash out at the military
and insist it's all
a great conspiracy.
Just as you feared,
things have become
somewhat chaotic.
Makes sense, but there's
really no helping that.
It's our job to explore
and report our findings.
The taxpayers can treat that
information as they will.
That's something we've improved
since the King was deposed.
I couldn't be prouder of
the work you've done.
[HANGE]
Huh?
Not only as a citizen
of the walls, but...
...one working stiff to another.
Uh--thank you.
Uh-huh. Then why don't
you fluff us up a bit
in the next article you write?
I have to ask,
what happens to us now?
[ROY] We've looked at the
Titans with fear, with hate,
with the wish in our hearts that
they would disappear forever.
And now we've learned
that this is
how the people of
the world look at us.
We're not human to them.
We're monsters.
[ROY] They'll attack us,
just as they did before.
Why wouldn't they?
[ROY]
This hell will repeat itself
until the last of us are dead.
[COURT chattering]
[HITCH] Well, if it isn't the
brave heroes of the walls.
[JEAN]
Hitch. Surprised you came.
[HITCH] I just wanted to watch
you guys get your medals.
I see.
Marlo was...
[JEAN]
...very brave, right to the end.
I know.
Isn't that right, Floch?
You should tell her.
Yeah, sure.
I rode right beside Marlo.
Just like me, he joined
as an urgent recruit.
But unlike me, he was brave,
and a natural leader.
Our situation was hopeless.
It seemed to us that the Scouts
were on the verge of ruin.
Just as our fear was giving
way to panic and despair,
he stepped in and
inspired us to push on.
Yeah?
[FLOCH]
He was an amazing person.
I know. And that's why...
Well, it's probably why
he never listened to me.
But in the end,
I'm sure he wished that
he'd never volunteered.
[gasps]
Thanks for that.
I'll laugh if you guys
screw up the ceremony.
Hey! Why did you tell her that?
Because.
Somebody has to speak
the truth around here.
Listen.
I heard about what
you did, Floch--
how hard you fought to ensure
that Erwin would be revived.
That's right.
You should be dead,
and Erwin should
stand in your place.
I'm not alone in thinking that.
All of us do.
Everyone who read that report
had the same thought.
Why wasn't Erwin the
one that was saved?
What do you know about
Armin to justify saying that?
Not a damn thing!
Yeah, you're right.
I'm not a childhood
friend of his.
Hell, I'm not his friend at all.
But I can still tell you why
he's the one standing here now.
It's 'cause you
two got emotional
and Captain Levi did the same.
You made an irrational choice.
You treated that syringe like
it was yours and wasted it!
He's alive because you
think your friends are
more important than
the rest of us.
[gasps]
All right. I think it's
time you shut your mouth.
Eren.
I bet even at your core,
you're always completely certain
that you're in the right.
That's why you wouldn't give up.
You're like a little kid
who won't listen to reason.
Eren. Just leave
him be, all right?
At least Mikasa acted
like an adult out there.
I saw her give up in the end.
[MIKASA gasps]
[JEAN] Jeez! What the
hell's wrong with you two?
Hey, Floch. Let's not do this
during a memorial for
our fallen comrades.
What's done is done,
so there's no sense in
dredging it up again.
As for you two.
You might not have acted
against your superiors,
but you didn't try to stop
Eren and Mikasa either.
You didn't do
anything but watch.
[JEAN, CONNY gasp]
[FLOCH]
Medals? For what?
A memorial for who?
When you guys start
rebuilding the Survey Corps,
you'd better tell your
recruits the truth,
or else you'll just end up with
cowards like me in the ranks.
What the hell are
we supposed to do
now that we've lost Erwin?
I know that I'm just fodder.
I understand that my life
is expendable, but still.
I should get to call
it like I see it...
...and to decide if this
cause is worth dying for.
[gasps]
I think Floch is right.
[EREN, MIKASA gasp]
Commander Erwin's the one
who should've been saved.
Maybe he could've turned
this situation around.
I can't though.
[EREN]
How can you be so sure of that?
I don't know what
choice was right,
so I won't pretend to.
None of us know what
the future might hold.
I mean, we can barely imagine.
Think about it.
If we rode straight from Wall
Maria, what would we find?
The sea.
Yeah, that's right.
We'd find the sea.
A place we've only
dreamed about.
Water that glows like
fire, fields of ice,
giant rocks that
take days to climb!
How can we be sure of anything
when there's so much
we haven't seen yet?
On the other side of the wall,
freedom is--
[LEVI]
All right, you brats.
It's time. Line up.
[EREN]
What did we find in that cellar?
Was it hope?
[EREN]
Or was it just despair?
Our enemy is
tremendously powerful.
If nothing changes
for the better soon,
that calamity will
only repeat itself.
I'd give up my life
in a heartbeat
if I was certain
that in doing so,
I could make a difference.
[EREN]
But...
...I'm not about to
sacrifice Historia's.
[EREN] I can't tell anyone
about this, so what should I do?
[GRISHA panting]
[GRISHA] I'm an Eldian who
came from beyond the walls!
[GRISHA panting]
[GRISHA] I'm a Subject of
Ymir just like all of you!
King of the walls! I beg you!
Kill the Titans
attacking Wall Maria.
Please, before my wife
and children are--
before thousands of your
people are eaten alive!
Eren?
[NARRATOR]
Hange's "executioner from hell,"
which had been crushing
Titans day and night,
went silent just as the
snow began to stick.
[NARRATOR] Months later,
when the snow started melting,
the military formally
announced that Wall Maria
had been cleansed
of Titans at last.
[NARRATOR] By the time the
elevators on Trost's walls
were freed for use,
and work had begun on
paving the main road,
there were flowers in bloom,
and butterflies
dancing between them.
[NARRATOR] Maria's refugees
were finally permitted to
return to their homes
roughly a year after
what had been called
"humanity's first
victory" in Trost.
[NARRATOR]
And so, six years after
the Colossal Titan's
first devastating attack...
[NARRATOR] ...the Scouts
resumed their expeditions,
exploring the world beyond
the walls once again.
[LEVI]
It's just as you thought, Hange.
Most of the Titans had
already gone inside Wall Maria.
We've all but wiped them out,
and it only took
us a single year.
Then let's push
straight forward,
exactly as we'd planned.
[birds chirping]
[gasps]
A Titan!
So one actually showed up?
Let's take a look!
It's over there.
[JEAN]
Huh?
[CONNY] Doesn't look
like it can move much.
Even with those limbs,
it still tried to drag itself
to the wall, bit by bit.
[FLOCH]
Hey! Careful!
It was shipped to paradise,
which means it's
a fellow patriot.
[gasps]
[EREN]
Let's go.
We're close.
Just hang on.
Is it okay to leave this here?
Shouldn't somebody kill it?
Shit!
[EREN]
I'm sure of it.
This is the place where
they'd turn the Eldians Titan.
[EREN]
Which means, just up there...
[gasps]
--[CONNY yells]
--[SASHA] Ow!
--[CONNY laughs]
--My eyes! They burn!
[JEAN gasps]
That's salty!
Woo, hoo, hoo!
Wow. Is this actually
full of salt water?
Huh? What could that be?
Hey, Hange!
You shouldn't touch it,
it might be poisonous.
[MIKASA gasping]
[ARMIN]
You see, Eren?
It's just like I told you.
[ARMIN]
A body of water so big
that merchants could
spend their whole lives
and still not get
all the salt out.
That's what I said we'd find,
and now it looks
like I was right.
[EREN]
Yeah.
The sea.
It's so damn big.
Yeah.
Hey. It's like you said, too!
On the other side of the wall--
[EREN]
There's a sea.
And just across that sea,
freedom's waiting.
[EREN] That's what I
always believed, at least.
[EREN]
But I was wrong.
I know what's waiting
across this sea now.
It's our enemies.
[EREN]
Everything we've seen
has been exactly as it was
in my father's memories.
[EREN]
Hey.
If we did cross the sea,
and we killed our enemies...
After that, would we
finally be free?
♪ Ending Song ♪