♪ Opening Song ♪
[ROD] All right Historia,
it seems we're finally alone.
Father.
I'm sorry for making you wait.
Listen, Historia.
I imagine that this will
sound strange to you,
but Frieda isn't entirely dead.
Your sister's memories
are still alive.
Would you like the chance
to meet her again?
Yes!
[GRISHA] Understand, Eren?
Think of your mother.
You can avenge her!
[EREN yelling]
[CAVEN gasps]
[CAVEN]
Here they come.
[CAVEN gasps]
Wait.
What are those?
[CAVEN]
Shit.
Damn it.
Gunpowder.
Judging from those fires,
the barrels must have
bags of oil on them.
This could get ugly.
[LEVI grunts]
--Here they come!
--Shoot 'em down!
--[gunshot]
--[MALE SOLDIER 44B] Huh?
Signal flares?
[CAVEN] We can't shoot
if we can't see our targets.
Twenty-four. Thirty-two.
Thirty-five total! In the
upper parts of the pillars!
Continue the plan! We'll take
them all out right here!
Everyone scatter!
Let them spread out,
then surround them!
[SASHA grunts]
I can't see shit!
[coughs]
Damn it! Where'd they go?
[ARMIN] The Anti-Personnel ODM
gear has a big weakness.
The anchor points in the same
direction as the gun,
so once its deployed,
the gun can't be aimed again.
[ARMIN] Which means
that while the user's moving,
they're vulnerable
to an attack from behind.
[MALE SOLDIER 44B]
Huh?
--[JEAN yells]
--[MALE SOLDIER 44B groans]
[groaning]
[yells]
Look over there! Fire!
[MALE SOLDIER 44C]
I missed?
Lost him!
[CONNY grunts]
[MALE SOLDIER 44C groans]
Die!
[FEMALE SOLDIER 44A groans]
Sasha!
Conny! Get back into the smoke
before they shoot you!
Take this!
Damn it!
[ARMIN]
But their greatest weakness
is that once
they've fired twice...
...they need a few seconds
to reload their weapons.
[CAVEN]
We're getting slaughtered.
Damn, she's fast!
[FEMALE SOLDIER 44B groans]
--[MIKASA grunts]
--[MALE SOLDIER 44E groans]
[MIKASA grunts]
[CAVEN] Once they've
closed the range gap,
swords have the advantage.
[MALE SOLDIER 44G grunts]
--[MIKASA grunts]
--[MALE SOLDIER 44G groans]
[CAVEN]
We have to stop them!
[MALE SOLDIER 44H,
44I, 44J groan]
[CAVEN] At this rate,
they'll wipe us out!
[KENNY]
Woo hoo!
Hey Levi.
I don't exactly
have time to waste on ya.
But I just can't have ya
getting' any further.
So be it.
I'll just have to play.
Catch me if ya can, boy!
You're a lively one. Damn.
[KENNY]
Tch.
[gasps]
[MIKASA yells]
♪
Ain't you tired of
this game yet? All right.
[KENNY]
I taught ya this one.
When you're chasin' your enemy,
you shouldn't just
stare straight ahead!
[KENNY yells]
Here, dimwit!
[LEVI yells]
[KENNY grunts]
--[LEVI grunts]
--[KENNY groans]
You bastard.
That really hurt.
[CAVEN]
They know our weaknesses.
Maybe I can use that.
[grunts]
Huh? Those shots weren't
even close to hitting!
Heh. It looks like I've found
another reckless spirit!
[gasps]
[groans]
[CAVEN grunts]
[yells]
[HANGE groans]
[ALL gasp]
[JEAN]
Hange!
Now! We'll re-form our defense
at the fallback point!
Time to regroup!
[LEVI grunts]
Stay out of our damn way,
you little runt.
Let it down!
You guard the ritual site!
Will do. You try not to die.
[distant rumbling]
[ROD] It sounds like
the enemy's drawing near.
This is it, we need to hurry.
--Right.
--[EREN yells, muffled]
[EREN yelling, muffled]
What's the matter?
Why are you glaring like that?
Because, he's realized
what it is that we have to do.
The power his father stole
for him must be returned
to its rightful place.
Historia.
That place is with you.
[EREN yelling]
The cavern we're in now
was built around a century ago
using the Titan power
of our ancestor.
The very same power was employed
to build the three walls.
And it's thanks to those
enormous walls
that humanity has survived.
The voice of this
"Founding Titan" reached out
to touch the people's hearts
and altered their
memories forever.
Understand that although
a few bloodlines were exempt,
even their knowledge
was lost over time.
Today, humanity knows nothing
of the world before the walls.
The only exception is
your sister, Frieda Reiss.
Frieda possessed far more than
the power to become a Titan.
She knew what this world
was once like.
And she knew what brought it
to its current state.
She was only fifteen years old
when she took the burden
of that knowledge upon herself.
It was eight years ago,
that she performed the ritual.
In this very chamber,
she ate her uncle.
My younger brother.
[ROD] In doing so, Frieda
inherited the Founding Titan
and the memories of this world.
As her uncle had before her.
As our ancestors have
for a hundred years.
Does that mean--?
[sighs]
It's true.
Had she survived,
Frieda could have used
her tremendous powers
to eliminate
humanity's woes with ease.
In time, she could've
wiped the Titan scourge
from the face of the world.
But then his father came
and stole that power away.
[EREN gasps]
[ROD] Now, that power
resides within Eren.
But it's wasted with him.
The Founding Titan's might
can only be wielded
by a member of our bloodline.
As long as he remains
the vessel for that power,
this hell will never end.
[CHRISTA gasps]
Then...
[KENNY] Hey, hey, hey,
just a damn minute!
[ROD]
Kenny.
Sounds like you said that
if someone who isn't a Reiss
eats Eren, they won't get
the powers of the king.
Yes, that's right.
So then, what?
Even if I do turn into
a Titan and eat Eren,
it ain't gonna do me any good?!
What are you saying?
Let him go!
What the hell's gotten into you?
Do you think I'm lying?
No, I don't. I waited
a long time for this day
because I knew
if there was one thing
you weren't lying about,
it was the succession ritual.
Damn. You prick.
You knew what I was
after this whole time.
And you knew I didn't have
a chance in hell of gettin' it.
But'cha went ahead
and used me, huh?
I'm very grateful. When my
brother first brought you
into his service,
I thought it was just one of
his foolish whims, but y--
You keep on
talkin' shit about Uri,
and you can kiss this half
of your head goodbye!
[CHRISTA] Stop it!
Get away from my father!
[ROD groans]
Come on. This is pitiful.
Don't you get it yet, Historia?
Your daddy doesn't give a damn!
He brought you here so he can
turn you into a monster.
And after that he's gonna
make you eat your buddy Eren.
If that's my duty
then that's what I'll do.
[KENNY]
Yeah?
[CHRISTA]
Yeah. I've decided.
I'll eat Eren and
bring my sister back!
I'll inherit
the world's history,
and exterminate
every last Titan!
If that's my duty,
then... I'll do it!
Damn it, Historia,
think about this.
What the hell has this
old bastard ever done for you?
--[metal scrapes]
--[gasps]
Only reason he picked you up
is 'cause of that
royal blood of yours.
This piece of trash
is too scared to turn
into a Titan himself.
That's why he forced
his brother and daughter
to do it for him!
That's the kind of man
your daddy is.
[KENNY]
Ah.
He's wrong, Historia.
That isn't the truth.
It's essential that I do not
become a Titan myself.
You mustn't believe him.
I'm the only man alive
you can trust.
[KENNY]
Hmm. Is that so?
--[CHRISTA] Father!
--[ROD coughing]
Kenny. You served me well
up to this moment.
You're free now.
Go find another
purpose for your life,
and live out your years.
That'd bore me to death. So...
Kenny. Just what
are you planning to do?
If she wants to
turn into a Titan,
well, then that's
her choice to make.
But I say the boy
should get a fair shot.
[EREN gasps]
[KENNY] They can both turn
Titan and fight it out.
If Historia wins, well,
then you'll have your peace.
But if Eren takes her down,
the situation stays the same.
--[EREN gasps]
--[CHRISTA gasps]
[KENNY] Go on livin' for
the sake of drawin' breath?
That doesn't sound like
any kind of life to me.
Historia! Take this injection
and you'll become
a powerful Titan!
If you can remember,
it's not enough
just to bite him anywhere.
To take his powers, you have to
consume his spinal fluid!
[CHRISTA gasps]
[KENNY]
Reckon I'd better step back.
Go on, you have to hurry!
[gasps]
[CHRISTA]
Eren, why?
Why aren't you transforming?
You're gonna fight back,
aren't you?
You can't just let me.
[CHRISTA]
Defend yourself!
Historia! This is your chance!
It didn't have to be like this.
Huh?
All that death
could've been avoided.
Five years ago, if Dad
hadn't done what he did...
Your sister.
She would've been able to
do something to stop all this.
But because my dad chose
to steal your family's power
from its rightful owner,
countless people
ended up getting killed.
[EREN] Armin's grandpa.
Thomas, Nack, Mina, Milieus.
Marco. Everyone on Levi Squad.
The people of Stohess.
The soldiers
who came to save me.
And Hannes.
I can never atone
for all of their pain.
That never should've happened.
Those days I spent in training.
That stupid dream that
I could see the world.
And me. I shouldn't
have happened.
[EREN]
If nothing else,
then at least let it
end at your hand.
Take your power back,
then use it to save humanity.
[EREN]
It's all up to you.
Eren. I remember.
When you said I was a
normal girl, I was so happy.
I see. This your idea
of trying to be nice?
What's wrong, Historia?
Are you scared?
All you have to do is inject
the liquid into your body.
[CHRISTA]
Wait. Father.
For a hundred years
we had the power,
but we didn't use it.
Why didn't our family
do something?
If we could control the Titans,
then why didn't we
liberate humanity?
That's because the same king
who built this world
within the walls for humanity,
wanted us to live in fear
of the Titans for all of time.
The First King believed this
to be the only path
to lasting peace.
But I can't tell you why.
Because only those who've seen
the world's memories can know!
Many years ago, my brother
and I pleaded with our father
to free humanity
from the Titans.
We asked him
time and time again.
However, he would not
fulfill our wish.
[ROD] Eventually, the time came
for one of us to succeed him.
After my brother
completed the ritual,
when I looked into
his eyes, I understood.
My brother wasn't there.
He had become something greater.
An omniscient being,
exempt from death,
who built and rules over
the world we live in.
Do you know what
such a being is called?
God.
There is no other word
aside from God.
So now it's my sacred duty
to bring God back to this world,
and then to offer up my prayers.
I'm praying right now, Historia,
for God to return and
lead mankind once again!
[YMIR]
Christa.
I have no business telling you
how to live your life.
It's not my place.
So I guess
when you break it down,
this is really just
more of a hope.
Christa, live a life
you can be proud of.
[ROD yells]
What have you done?!
--[crack]
--[groaning]
[CHRISTA]
God my ass!
If it's such an honor
to become him,
then why didn't you
do it yourself?
I'm done with your shit,
and I'm not gonna
let you murder me!
[gasps]
[laughing]
That's the spirit!
This is gettin' good!
The hell are
you doing, Historia?
Setting you free.
No, stop! You can't!
If you don't kill me, then
everyone else'll keep suffering!
Just eat me already, damn it!
I can't live like this,
so end it!
Shut up, dumbass!
Stop your crying! I don't care!
I don't care about
killing all the Titans!
And I don't care about
freeing mankind either!
I'm starting to
get sick of humanity!
I say let 'em
get wiped out by Titans!
And if that makes me
an enemy of humanity?
So be it. I don't care if I'm
the worst girl who's ever lived!
You get the hell out of here.
I'll deal with the rest.
[groaning]
[ROD]
Father.
Uri. And Frieda.
I'm coming. Just wait.
♪ Closing Song ♪
[NARRATOR]
Rod Reiss becomes a Titan.
To protect Mikasa and
the others from a cave-in,
Eren is forced to make
yet another hard choice.
Next episode: "Outside the
Walls of Orvud District."