[CHRISTA yells]
[NARRATOR] The true king
within the walls, Rod Reiss,
found his schemes laid to waste.
While Levi Squad was
successful in rescuing
both Eren and Historia.
However...
Seeing his hopes dashed
on the ground before him,
Rod Reiss himself
became a Titan.
[CHRISTA] I just wanted to
believe my father was right.
Even more than that,
I wanted him to like me.
But it’s time for me
and him to part ways now.
[MIKASA] Once you’re queen
you can punch that smug runt
right in the face.
[CARSTEN] How can we evacuate
the people in such a short time?
That’s not part of the plan.
The people of Orvud District
will need to stay
exactly where they are.
♪
♪ Opening Song
[CARSTEN] What the hell
are you thinking, Erwin?
If we don’t get these
civilians out of the city,
they’ll die by the thousands!
That hulking monstrosity
will be a stone’s throw
from the wall by morning!
That Titan is an Abnormal.
Right, and what the hell
does that even mean?
It behaves strangely.
Unlike most Titans we encounter,
it’s only attracted
to large groups of people.
Hence the word "abnormal."
Put simply, given the choice
between a few soldiers
right next to it and a distant,
but densely populated city,
it’ll choose the city.
So if we were to
evacuate Orvud’s populace
to the interior
of Wall Sina right now,
the Titan would
change its course,
destroying the wall and
anything else in its path.
Left unchecked,
it would make for the city
with the greatest
density of people, Mitras.
The ensuing rampage
would deliver
a devastating blow to humanity.
As we rode for Orvud,
we had Eren Jaeger attempt
to use his recently discovered
power to control Titans.
Rod Reiss’ Titan
didn’t react in any way.
Stop moving, now! I said stop!
Hey, I’m talkin’ to you!
Hey asshole! Ya hear me?
C’mon, you stupid old bastard!
Why won’t you listen?
[gasps]
If we’re to stop this thing,
it’ll have to be outside
the walls of Orvud District.
For that to happen,
we require the citizens here
to act as bait.
However, this doesn’t
change the fact
that our first and
foremost duty as soldiers
is to protect the people.
[ERWIN] In the event that we’re
unable to halt the target,
we’ll take measures to
minimize civilian losses.
We’ll announce a district-wide
evacuation drill tonight.
The people will be gathered
away from the outer wall,
ready to escape
if the battle is lost.
It seems there’s
no other choice.
The body of this Titan is
the largest we’ve seen yet.
As such, it presents
an easy target.
Our wall-mounted cannons
should prove highly effective,
but if we can’t bring it
down with artillery...
...the Scout Regiment will
throw everything we have at it.
[FEMALE ROSE SOLDIER 46A]
As part of this drill,
dummy Titans and
cannons will be utilized!
This will be a
large-scale exercise
like nothing you’ve seen!
However, we ask
that you remain calm,
follow our instructions
and remember--
[MALE OLD MERCHANT 46A]
Ma’am. I really gotta go get
my store ready for the day.
Can’t you let us go home?
You won’t have
any customers today.
--Take the day off.
--I’ve got a living to make.
[MALE ADULT CITIZEN 46A]
This is Northern Sina,
why are we having drills?
[MALE ADULT CITIZEN 46B]
The military ousts the king,
and now this?
[MALE ADULT CITIZEN 46C]
What do you mean?
I’m saying that the military’s
only doing this
to demonstrate their power.
Now that the fake king’s gone,
they wanna remind us
that they’re in control.
You mean they’re
puttin’ us through all this
just to flex
their damn muscles?
[MALE ADULT CITIZEN 46B]
Yeah. At this point, I think
I prefer the fake king.
Even if he was incompetent.
[distant rumble]
[MALE ADULT CITIZEN 46D]
Hey! Look over there!
[CROWD murmurs]
[FEMALE ROSE SOLDIER 46A]
Smoke?
Fire!
Well. How’d that do?
[MALE ROSE SOLDIER 46A gasps]
Fire!
[ERWIN] Looks like the field
cannons are even less effective.
[LEVI]
Makes sense.
The cannons on the wall
have a way better angle,
and they didn’t
do shit to it either.
What’s the problem?
Unprepared soldiers.
Scraped together cannons.
And shallow leadership.
The Titans have always
attacked from the south.
Not only is this a northern
garrison, it’s in the interior.
Therefore, I can
tell you for a fact
this is the best we’ll get.
[LEVI] Yeah. That much
is painfully clear.
And of course your strategy for
getting us through this battle
comes down to a gamble.
Just like every other plan
that you’ve come up with.
[HANGE]
Erwin! I brought the goodies!
All the gunpowder, ropes,
and netting I could find!
We still need to
put it together, though.
Ooh! Got this too.
There’s another one just
like it a bit further down.
[HANGE] The trigger’s held
in place, so once fired,
it’ll wind itself right back up,
just like ODM gear.
So. We do any damage?
Imagine a swarm of
cicadas pissing on it.
Then we’ll actually
use these things. Exciting.
Captain Levi.
Jean. Sasha. Conny.
You handle that side.
[ALL]
Yes, sir!
How should we
approach this? Lemme see.
Think of it like
we’re wrapping up
a nice gift for someone special.
I believe you heard
from Levi, Historia.
Assuming we live through this,
we’ll have you become
the queen who rules
this world within the walls.
So naturally, I can’t have you
fighting on the front line.
I doubt that plan will work.
The people won’t bow
to a queen in name alone.
They aren’t that naïve.
Exactly what are you suggesting?
[CARSTEN]
Fire!
[EREN] Historia. It’s amazing
how strong she’s become.
Let me act like the...
[EREN] At first I thought
she was the weakest of us.
But no.
I was the weak one.
[EREN] Somewhere along the line,
I decided I was special.
And ’cause of that,
when other soldiers
died for my sake,
I accepted it as natural.
And the same goes
for my Titan powers.
I hated Titans
more than anything.
But when I became one
I thought nothing of it.
Because I wanted to believe
that strength was my own.
That’s the thinking
of a weakling.
[EREN]
Where’ll we go from here?
So what if I’m able
to reseal the wall?
I’m still not
about to save mankind.
I’m not special. I’m nobody.
But really,
it’s humanity that got
the short end of the stick here.
’Cause they’re stuck with me
as their trump card.
Hey.
[EREN] Take a look
at those kids down there.
They’re just like us
on that day.
Yeah. We were clueless too.
We had no idea a Titan
taller than the walls
was about to attack us, either.
They might end up
seeing the same sight
that we did that day.
Thing is,
it’s different this time.
Those kids will have soldiers
who are ready to protect them.
Those kids will have us.
[HANGE] Yeah, stack that one
up on the edge.
[MIKASA grunts]
[MIKASA] Eren. We’re running
out of time here.
Keep your hands busy.
[EREN gasps]
--Eren!
--[EREN grunts]
[ARMIN] Hey! Stop!
Why are you--?
[EREN groans]
Were you making a wound?
It’s not time yet.
It wasn’t that. I just
needed to beat the shit
out of a useless brat
real quick.
With any luck,
he’s dead and gone now.
The enemy is moving! Adjust your aim!
Our target is
the back of its neck!
[CARSTEN]
Fire!
Well done!
We’ve torn into its flesh!
One more volley, and we--
[SOLDIERS groaning]
So hot!
Damn it. That’s just our luck.
[LEVI]
The wind must’ve shifted.
What do we do?
I can’t see, Captain!
It doesn’t matter--
the target’s right beneath us!
Keep shooting!
[CARSTEN gasps]
That wasn’t enough.
[gasps]
It’s a Titan.
[ALL gasp]
[SOLDIERS yell]
[ROD TITAN roars]
--[CITIZENS screaming]
--[MALE CITIZEN 46A] Titan!
[MALE ROSE SOLDIER 46H]
Please! You have to stay calm!
[MALE CITIZEN 46B]
Shut up!
[CITIZENS screaming]
We’re falling back!
Everyone run!
Shit. It’s breaking through.
The city I grew up in...
...is about to be devastated.
The Garrison has done its duty.
Let the Scouts
take it from here.
--Looks like we’re up, Eren.
--Right.
[EREN]
Armin. There’s one more thing
that’s different from then.
Huh?
It’s not all we’d hoped for,
but it’s something.
Mankind has an ace
up its sleeve now.
[KIDS panting]
[KIDS gasp]
Wait a second. Another one?
[EREN TITAN roars]
All set, Commander!
On my mark.
[roars]
Now!
[SASHA]
Take this!
[ROD TITAN roars]
All right! It’s losing balance!
[ROD TITAN groaning]
Eren! Go!
[KIDS gasp]
[LEVI] So you’re saying,
that to take this Titan down,
we’re gonna stuff
gunpowder down its throat
and hope that’s enough to
destroy the nape of the neck?
That’s correct.
With all the heat
the bastard’s making,
I’d expect the powder to
ignite without a detonator.
Although a lot of this
is banking on the Titan
hanging its mouth open.
An explosion outside of
the nape may not penetrate.
The flesh inside its throat
is softer. More vulnerable.
But the target
may protect that point.
It’s been dragging its face
along the ground.
Frankly, we don’t even know
that it has a mouth to open.
That’s the gamble this time.
[ROD TITAN roars]
[EREN]
I’ve got you!
[EREN TITAN roars]
Go! Deploy your ODM gear
and finish it off!
[ERWIN]
Gigantic though it is,
its vital point is
still one meter high,
and ten centimeters across.
[ERWIN] Unless we destroy that,
it will regenerate,
and form another shield of heat.
We cannot waste this chance.
Where is it? Which one?
[gasps]
Historia?
[ERWIN]
I understand your reasons,
but I can’t approve you
entering combat.
Please, sir. I have to!
I’ve finally found my purpose--
the duty I was actually
meant to fulfill!
That’s why I’m
standing here right now!
Well, at any rate,
with my body as it is now,
I can’t exactly stop you, can I?
[gasps]
[CHRISTA] I’m sorry, Commander.
I know this is selfish.
But this is the first time
I’ve stood against my parents.
The first fight I’ve
ever had with my father.
[CHRISTA yells]
[CHRISTA gasps]
[ROD] Father!
You have to listen to me!
You could easily eradicate
the Titans for good!
So why? Why won’t you
just do it?
I can handle it, brother.
It’s fine. Pray for me.
[ROD] Alma, you’re the
only one who understands.
You can leave it to me, Father.
I won’t lose to the ghosts
of our ancestors.
[ROD]
Oh, God.
[gasps]
[ROD groans]
♪
[CHRISTA panting]
[MALE CITIZEN 46B]
The Titan’s been destroyed.
[MALE CITIZEN 46C]
Hey. You okay?
[MALE CITIZEN 46D]
You’re not injured, are you?
[MALE SOLDIER 46A]
It looked like
you dealt the final blow.
[CHRISTA] Was that real?
Or did I imagine it?
Am I acting for myself?
Or am I still
just someone’s tool?
[CHRISTA]
I... don’t know. But...
I’ve always just
gone along with things.
Till now, at least.
It’s okay.
My name is Historia Reiss.
And I am your rightful queen.
[KENNY panting]
I must apologize.
For I cannot die on this day.
[URI]
Please. Forgive me.
You’re not deaf, are ya?
Can you hear me or can’t ya?
Got a name?
Because of that, I’ll do
anything he needs me to.
Are you any different?
What do I care? It’s fine by me.
[CAVEN]
Captain Ackermann!
No! Get back!
[KENNY groans]
[groaning]
[panting]
[footsteps]
[LEVI]
Kenny.
Ah, shit. Not you aga--
[coughing]
Found what’s left of your squad.
It looks like they were
crushed in the cave-in.
I guess you were
the only survivor?
[KENNY]
Mm. Sure looks that way.
[LEVI]
Report back. I’m fine alone.
[MALE SOLDIER 46A]
Understood, sir.
[LEVI] Between the burns
and the blood you’ve lost,
there’s nothing
that can save you now.
Oh, yeah?
I wonder.
[clink]
[gasps]
♪ Closing Song