Oh, no.
[CONNY] Look at all those
houses up in the sky.
One of 'em could be
yours, right, Eren?
How's it feel to have your own
roof over your head again?
Get it?
[CONNY laughing]
Sasha, could you
smack him for me?
[CONNY groans]
It doesn't look like
Bertholdt knows our location.
You're right.
He's just scattering
burning debris
to turn Shiganshina
into a sea of flames.
[EREN]
That bastard.
You're back.
And this time you wanna
burn down my city?
[SASHA gasps]
Hey, Armin!
Your orders? C'mon!
What should we do?
[BERTHOLDT]
I can tell I'm right.
I mean, just look at
the way you're shaking.
You're scared outta
your mind, aren't you?
Jean, can you take over for me?
What?
[ARMIN]
I don't know what to do.
I'm worried I'll screw up.
I made a mistake thinking
we could talk to Bertholdt,
and look where it got us.
Please, Jean!
You're better suited for this!
[gasps]
Move.
Make for the river!
Everyone aboard Eren!
Conserve our gas!
[JEAN]
Eren.
At some point, we'll have to
get Bertholdt's attention,
but until then, you need
to stay out of sight.
--Hey, Armin.
--[ARMIN gasps]
[JEAN] I'm all right
with judgment calls,
but I don't have some genius
plan for getting us out of this.
In the end, you're the one
we're gonna be counting on.
♪ Opening Song ♪
[whirring]
[gasps]
This area's all mopped up.
The only ones left
for us to eliminate
are way up at the front.
But I still don't see
how we're going to
take down the Beast Titan.
It doesn't seem like
he's got any intention
of budging from that spot.
That's true.
Looks like the
big guy's a coward.
Not that he ever had
any balls to begin with.
Save your energy.
We can finish off the rest
of the runts out there.
Let's go!
[SCOUTS]
Yes, sir!
[LEVI]
Shit.
That explosion just now...
Are Hange and the
others all right?
Or did they get caught up in it?
[LEVI] I need to get to
the other side and--
[grunts]
[gasps]
[SCOUTS screaming]
[LEVI gasps]
[ZEKE TITAN]
Hmm.
That one was a little higher
than I would've liked.
Huh? Oh, good work.
Leave it there.
No problem, we'll just consider
the first pitch a warm-up.
I'm going for nothing less
than a perfect game today!
[ERWIN gasps]
Frontal bombardment!
All troops, take cover now!
--[MARLO gasps]
--[SANDRA] What the--?
Damn it!
Get down!
[DIRK groaning]
[DIRK gasps]
--[SCOUTS screaming]
--[LEVI grunts]
[ERWIN gasps]
Guys, any idea what the
hell that sound was?
So does the enemy have
cannons or something?
If so, there's gotta
be a hundred of them!
Calm down, everyone!
You're scaring the horses!
[LEVI]
The Titan's throwing boulders!
[ALL gasp]
[MARLO]
Captain Levi!
Move, now!
Take the horses and
retreat to the wall.
[ALL gasp]
Yes, sir!
Move! Stay out of the
line of fire! [grunts]
[FLOCH screams]
[LEVI]
You wanna die? Get up!
Commander!
How's it looking?
Terrible.
The front line
of houses is gone.
He decimated them.
If he keeps throwing those,
everything will be leveled.
We won't have anything
left to hide behind.
[LEVI] And we can't retreat
to the other side of the wall?
[ERWIN]
No.
The Colossal Titan is
already heading this way,
setting fire to
everything in his path.
Theoretically, we could scale
the wall to evade the stones,
but the horses can't.
We retreat here, and there's
no hope for victory.
What happened to Hange's group?
Is Eren all right?
I don't know.
Most of them are gone--
caught up when the
explosion occurred.
We've sustained a great
many casualties.
[ERWIN] The Beast Titan
directed the small Titans
in such a way that our soldiers
would group up in one place.
Dirk Squad, Marlene Squad,
and Klaus Squad
were engaging the small Titans,
which put them in
the line of fire
when he launched
the bombardment.
They were all wiped out.
[ERWIN]
In other words,
our remaining forces on
this side of the gate
consist of you new Scout
recruits, Captain Levi, and me.
No others.
[SCOUTS screaming]
[SCOUT 53C]
We're doomed!
So what now?
Do you have any kind of plan?
[JEAN]
Yell at him, Eren!
We can't let Bertholdt get
any closer to the wall!
[EREN TITAN yelling]
He heard you.
[JEAN]
The bastard's ignoring us.
He's heading straight
for the wall!
So what do we do now, Jean?
If he gets there--
We're not letting him.
Hey, Eren! Tackle that
lanky jerk's leg!
Hang on.
Do we actually have
a plan for this?
With that steam he puts out,
he can make our
ODM gear useless!
It won't connect!
You think I don't know that?
I'm well aware, but we have
to give it a try anyway.
We can figure out his
weakness as we fight!
I can kill him.
You just keep him distracted.
Conny, give me your
Thunder Spear.
[CONNY]
Uh--sure thing!
Listen, Armin. Odds are,
we're still gonna need
a plan from you.
So stop moping and
observe him from afar.
We have to believe
we can win this!
[ARMIN]
Right!
[JEAN]
Now! Scatter!
[EREN]
How dare you look down on me!
After what you've done,
you should be on your
knees begging for mercy!
Whoa. He pushed him!
You can do it, Eren!
Knock him on his ass!
[JEAN]
There must be a way.
We just have to find it.
[gasps]
Huh?
[BOTH gasp]
[MIKASA]
Eren!
[EREN groans]
[LEVI]
Damn it.
That's Eren up there.
There's only one Titan that
could fling him like that.
The Colossal.
[MIKASA gasps]
Eren's not moving.
He's still alive, though.
Focus on keeping
Bertholdt off him.
That might have been
pushing it too far.
That's what'll happen if we
charge at him without a plan.
Now what?
Unless we can turn
the tables somehow,
this operation will fail,
all of us will die,
and eventually,
humanity will fall.
Well, screw it then.
Plan or no, I'm not
just gonna sit around
and wait to get slaughtered.
Let's take the fight
to him! [grunts]
[BOTH grunt]
[JEAN] He doesn't know about
the Thunder Spears yet!
Sasha and Conny will
help me distract him!
Mikasa, you go for the kill!
[CONNY, MIKASA, SASHA]
Right!
Hey, freak-show!
You forget your skin somewhere?
You look so gross!
No one wants to see
all that, ya pervert!
[JEAN] This distraction
is way too obvious.
But we only need one good hit.
[MIKASA grunts]
[MIKASA gasps]
[JEAN grunts]
[gasps]
[MIKASA groans]
[BOTH grunt]
[JEAN, SASHA, CONNY yell]
[ARMIN]
Guys!
Is there nothing we can do?
That steam even knocked away
the Thunder Spears mid-flight.
[coughing]
Conny!
Damn it. I breathed some
in and burned my throat.
[MIKASA grunts]
[ARMIN]
Mikasa! You're hurt!
It isn't bad.
A bit of shrapnel from
the Thunder Spears got me.
Figured something out yet?
Huh?
Tell me. Is there a way
that we can fight back?
[gasps]
[ARMIN]
I don't know.
[ALL gasp]
[ALL gasping]
[SCOUTS yelling, sobbing]
[LEVI] This place is gonna look
like a honeycomb before long.
The Beast Titan
knows where we are.
Erwin.
If there's no chance that we can
turn this around then tell me,
and we can still cut our losses.
Go shake the shit out of
Eren till he wakes up.
Have him run away with as
many people as he can carry.
Then we'll have at
least some survivors.
[SCOUTS yelling, sobbing]
[MARLO] It's our job
to guard the horses!
Why'd you let yours run away?
Shut up!
Like it even matters now.
What was that?
Those other scouts
were insanely strong
and all of them
died in an instant!
What chance do we have
where they failed?
There's no reason
to guard the horses.
Because there's not gonna be
anyone left to ride them home!
[SCOUTS gasping, murmuring]
There was a point when
it all made sense.
If everyone just cowered
behind the walls and waited,
then someday Titans would come
out of nowhere and wipe us out.
It was obvious that
someone needed to
bite the bullet and fight.
It would be dangerous, yeah,
but the soldiers who did it
would be risking their lives
to protect their loved ones.
So when the recruiter asked us,
"Which of you has the courage?"
I actually thought
I could do it.
Thought I'd be some kinda hero.
I didn't get it.
I didn't know.
I thought that if I died,
it would at least have some
meaning... but it won't.
It didn't for the others.
They're just gone.
You know what?
I bet almost everyone ends up
having that same final thought.
I was so stupid for coming here.
Why did I think
I'd be different?
[FLOCH sobbing]
You could tell what's left of
the recruits and Hange's group
to run away on horseback.
They won't have much of a
chance, but they'll be decoys.
They can give Eren
a shot at escaping.
Tell me.
How would you fit
into this plan?
I'm gonna go after
the Beast Titan.
I'll draw him away somehow and--
You can't.
You won't even make it near him.
Probably not.
But, if you and Eren
make it home alive,
then there will still be hope.
All things considered,
I feel like that's the
best we can ask for.
We've been brutalized.
To be honest, sir,
it seems like this
battle will be
where the Scout Regiment
gets finished off.
Yes.
If we had no way to fight back,
then you would be right.
[gasps]
Is there a way?
There is.
[LEVI] You could've
mentioned that before.
Care to explain why you
kept your shitty mouth shut?
The plan could go a few ways.
Best case, you'll have
a decent chance of
killing the Beast Titan.
But for it to succeed...
the recruits and I have to die.
[SCOUTS screaming]
The Survey Corps may survive.
But regardless,
most of us will end up dead.
Frankly, we're almost guaranteed
to be defeated, no matter what.
The recruits and I will
be staking our deaths
on the slimmest
chance of victory.
[ERWIN]
For this to work--
to convince these youths to
charge toward their deaths--
it would take an expert con man
and a whole slew
of blatant lies.
[ERWIN] If I don't lead
the vanguard myself,
then none of them will
have the courage.
Which means I must be
the first to charge.
And the first to
be slain as well.
So I'll never learn the truth.
Huh?
[sighs]
I just... wanted to
reach that cellar.
Everything I've done
up to this point,
I did in the hopes that
this chance would come.
I dreamt... that I'd
get to prove I was right.
[ERWIN]
Many times,
I thought that death would've
been easier, but then I...
I think of the questions
I needed answered.
They're what I lived for.
And now those answers are no
more than a coward's leap away.
[ERWIN]
I'm so close, but...
Can you see them, too?
Our comrades. They're
all standing around us.
They've been watching
us all this time.
They want to know what we did
with the sacrifices
that they made...
What became of the
hearts they gave...
[SCOUTS screaming]
But that's probably
just in my head, right?
Of no more import than
a child's bad dream.
[LEVI]
You led us well.
Fought hard.
No one else could've
gotten us this far.
I'll make the choice for you.
Give up on your dream
and charge to your death.
Lead those crying children
straight to hell.
I'll reach the Beast
Titan and tear him apart.
[gasps]
--[SCOUTS yelling]
--Huh?
[ERWIN]
Charge!
[ERWIN yells]
Huh.
I didn't expect them to
lay down and die, but...
A suicide charge?
For some reason I thought
they'd do better than that.
All right. Fire!
Is that smoke?
Oh, it's from those
signal guns they use.
Incoming. Spread out!
[SCOUTS yelling]
I'm about to announce
our final mission.
All troops, line up!
[SCOUTS gasp]
[ERWIN] We're going to
mount a cavalry charge,
rushing the Beast
Titan directly.
Clearly, this will make
us ideal targets for him.
So we'll wait until the
moment he's ready to throw,
and then we'll fire our
smoke signals together.
That should somewhat
reduce his accuracy.
While we distract
the Beast Titan,
Captain Levi will get in
position to dispatch it.
Does anyone have questions?
[LEVI]
What?
You want me to go after
him with just ODM gear?
He's standing in the
middle of a field.
I can't fight without a
house or tree to hook on.
You're wrong.
Huh?
[ERWIN] There happens
to be a line of objects
at just the right height
for your approach.
[ERWIN] Use his thralls
to advance unseen...
[LEVI grunts]
[ERWIN] ...and assassinate
the son of a bitch.
[LEVI grunts]
[SCOUTS yelling]
[LEVI]
I'm sorry.
[SANDRA gags, vomits]
There's no point
standing around.
We'll only be showered
by more boulders.
Ready your horses,
on the double!
Be honest.
Are all of us...
riding to our deaths?
Yes, we are.
And since we're dying anyway,
you're saying that
it's better...
...if we at least die fighting?
I am.
But wait, if we'll die anyway,
then who cares what we do?
We could just disobey
your orders...
...and it wouldn't mean
a thing, would it?
Yes, you're precisely right.
[gasps]
Everything that you
thought had meaning--
every hope, dream,
or moment of happiness--
None of it matters as
you lie, bleeding out,
on the battlefield.
None of it changes what a
speeding rock does to a body.
We all die.
[ERWIN] But does that mean
our lives are meaningless?
Does that mean that there was
no point in our being born?
Would you say that of
our slain comrades?
What about their lives?
Were they meaningless?
They were not!
Their memory serves as
an example to us all!
The courageous fallen!
The anguished fallen!
Their lives have meaning
because we, the living,
refuse to forget them!
And as we ride to certain death,
we trust our successors
to do the same for us.
Because my soldiers
do not buckle or yield
when faced with the
cruelty of this world.
My soldiers push forward!
My soldiers scream out!
My soldiers rage!
♪ Closing Song ♪
[NARRATOR] For friends
who gave their hearts.
For friends who gave
up on their dreams.
Until everything burns out,
they'll charge through the chaos
to spite the fear
they've been taught.
Next episode: "Hero."