[TOWNSPEOPLE chattering]
[GRISHA] The fateful day
that I, just a naive youth,
was made to face the
truth of this world.
[CITIZEN 57A]
Move it, you vermin.
[BOTH gasp]
[CITIZEN 57B] Ya can't get
away from these devil-bloods.
[CITIZEN 57A]
Damn Eldians are crawling around
as they please now.
Grisha.
It's all right, Fay.
We've heard worse before.
Look there!
It should be just
past that hill.
[BOTH gasp]
[FAY]
It's so big!
[KRUGER] Are you kids here
to look at the airship, too?
[GRISHA gasps]
Uh, yes, sir!
[KRUGER] You're from the
Liberio Internment Zone?
Let's see your exit permit.
Huh? Our permit?
We don't have one.
[KRUGER] If you entered the
city without permission,
then you need to be punished.
[GRISHA]
Yes, sir.
Hard labor? Or a quick beating?
A beating, please.
Brother!
Ah. 'Cause you don't wanna
trouble your parents, right?
That's right.
My sister didn't wanna come
but I dragged her with me!
Please allow me to take
her punishment, too!
Very well.
[GRISHA groans]
[FAY gasps]
Grisha!
--[KRUGER] Here's another!
--[GRISHA groans]
[GROSS]
Sheesh. Go easy on him, Kruger.
[GRISHA coughing]
[GROSS] Come on, dear.
Let's get you back home.
--[KRUGER grunting]
--[GRISHA gasps, groans]
It was wise of you two
to leave your armbands on.
Kids or not, Eldians
who take theirs off
get a one way trip to paradise.
Sorry. I'll go back home now.
[KRUGER]
Wait.
You came to see
the airship, right?
You may as well do
it while you can.
[GRISHA]
The next day, my sister...
...was found on the
banks of the river.
[GROSS] I showed the girl
to the gates of Liberio
and then I went on my way.
I was busy with work, you see.
And Eldian children shouldn't
be roaming about the city
without permits
in the first place.
I find it disturbing that
your son doesn't know
what it means to be
of his bloodline.
I mean, you have
been teaching him
so that he can feel the weight
of your ancestor's sins,
now haven't you?
[GRISHA]
I couldn't prove it,
but I knew that man from
Marley Public Security
was lying through his teeth.
We had stumbled upon him
while he was slacking
off on the riverbank.
How busy could he have been?
Mother was silent in
her grief, but father...
[GRISHA'S FATHER]
Please allow me to thank you
for your guidance, sir.
I assure you, I'll heed it
and teach my foolish
son to know better.
[GRISHA]
He demeaned himself to this man.
I began to hate that
Marleyan, and my father,
so much that it
made my head spin.
But more than that,
I cursed my own foolishness.
[GRISHA'S FATHER]
1,820 years ago,
our ancestor Ymir Fritz
made a contract
with the Devil of All Earth,
and obtained the
Power of the Titans.
Upon her death,
Ymir's spirit was split
into the Nine Titans.
These Titans defeated the
great nation of Marley,
and conquered the continent
for themselves,
under the name of
the Eldian Empire.
Thus did this land's
Dark Ages begin.
The subjects of Ymir
deemed all the other races
inferior to their own,
and violently oppressed them.
They stole wealth and land,
forced other people to
bear their children,
and wiped out some
bloodlines entirely.
This ethnic cleansing continued
for around 1,700 years.
But the fallen nation of Marley
planned to use Eldia's arrogance
to bring it down from within.
And it worked.
Marley brought seven of the
Nine Titans under its control
and used them to win the Great
Titan War just 80 years ago!
The Eldian King at the time
erected three walls on
the island of Paradis,
and he fled there along with
a great many of his people.
Our ancestors were abandoned
and left behind on
the mainland, but,
despite our history,
the gracious people of Marley
let us live and stay
on their land.
[GRISHA]
My father was talkative
for someone who had just
lost his daughter.
As he stood there,
shaming his forebears,
and idolizing his oppressors,
he looked just like
a whipped dog.
That officer was telling lies.
[BOTH gasp]
The truth was inconvenient for
him, so he told lies instead.
Quiet. The walls of this
house are paper thin.
Know what?
He prob'ly took Fay and--
Silence!
[GRISHA'S FATHER]
I told you.
Our ancestors were heinous
sinners, understand?
They committed genocide
against all other races--
Fay and I didn't do
anything like that!
We were just walking outside!
[GRISHA sobs]
Why are you doing this?
What's wrong with you?
Why are you so eager to
get us all shipped away?
[gasps]
[GRISHA'S FATHER]
We ourselves did nothing.
But to those who've been
victimized for generations,
you and I are
devils nonetheless.
We should count ourselves lucky
that they let us live
quiet, humble lives
here in the internment zone.
I beg you, Grisha,
please don't force the
rest of this family
to meet the same fate as Fay.
[GRISHA] I still wonder
which was truly in the wrong.
The world I lived in? Or me?
[GRISHA]
'Kay.
I understand.
[GRISHA]
Perhaps it was both.
I was ignorant and foolish.
[GRISHA] The world was twisted
and maddeningly unfair.
[GRISHA]
I discovered my own path in life
when I was 18 years old.
It was around the time I was to
take over my father's clinic.
[GRISHA] What's that
scar on your shoulder?
This is what marks
me as a patriot.
[GRISHA]
Hm? A patriot?
[GRICE]
Your sister was killed
by a Marleyan Public
Security officer.
[gasps]
That's a verified fact
from our informant
in the government.
There are some things
that you need to hear.
[GRISHA]
It can't be!
How could they do that?
[GRISHA] When I learned the
truth of my sister's death,
I swore to myself...
[GRISHA]
...that I'd show these Marleyans
who the real devils were.
I saw that my ancestors'
so-called sins were justified.
That to set the world
right as it had been,
Eldia would have to be restored.
[GRISHA] Our informant within
the Marleyan Government
was called "The Owl."
He led the Restorationists
without ever showing himself.
Come. I've discovered the truth!
Our ancestor Ymir awakened
the Power of the Titans,
and used it to tame the
wilderness, carve out roads,
and to make bridges
to span the mountains!
She didn't oppress other people,
she helped them to prosper!
[COMRADE 57B] So the history
we were taught as children
was just a hoax!
Marleyan propaganda!
Impressive, Grisha.
How'd you read this
ancient language?
Oh, no. I haven't deciphered
much of the writing at all yet.
Then how do you know
that all this is true?
Huh? Because it's obvious
just from looking!
And because I believe
in our founder Ymir
with all of my heart!
We're not devil-bloods,
we're God's children!
[COMRADES]
Yeah!
My comrades!
The Owl's sent us a new ally.
[DINA]
Hello. It's good to meet you.
I am here as a descendant
of the royal family.
The last on this continent.
Dina Fritz.
[GRISHA]
When we locked eyes,
I decided to allow fate to
steer my life where it would.
[GRISHA] Dina was all
that remained of a branch
of the royal family that
refused to flee the continent.
She taught us secrets
about the Titans
that only royalty
had known before.
We believed that she had
shown us the path to victory.
[GRISHA]
I'm sure of it!
The King brought the Founding
Titan's power into the walls!
If we take that power, then we
can control all other Titans,
and crush Marley
once and for all!
But wait, if the King was able
to wield such an absolute power,
then why'd he run away
in the first place?
[DINA] That's simple. It's
because he refused to fight.
In the midst of the
Great Titan War,
the 145th King forsook his duty
to restore order
on the continent,
and moved his capital
to a distant island.
All our pain, all these
years of anguish,
it can all be traced
to the moment
our King renounced conflict.
Let's fight again.
[DINA gasps]
The true royal family stayed
right here on the continent
and held their ground for Eldia!
It's time we brought the
Founding Titan back to them!
Against its power,
Marley will crumble.
We'll restore Eldia and
live proudly once more!
[ALL yelling]
[GRISHA] The next year,
the two of us married,
and were blessed with a son.
His name was Zeke.
Our royal child, Zeke.
There's no doubt in my heart
that that someday he'll
lead his people to victory.
[GRISHA] Years pass by,
and people change.
As the world around
us rapidly advanced,
a turning point came
for the Restorationists.
Now, listen up, you Eldians!
We'll soon begin
recruiting new...
[GRISHA] The Marleyan government
required Subjects of Ymir
to become Marleyan warriors
capable of serving as
vessels for the Nine Titans.
[GRISHA] We've received a
new message from the Owl.
He says the reason Marley's
making these moves
is to prepare for an anticipated
struggle over resources
as military technology
keep advancing.
Marley currently leads the world
using the power of
its Seven Titans,
but they may soon grow obsolete.
An enormous cache of fossil
fuel lies beneath Paradis.
Marley can't afford
to let it lie unused.
But, 80 years ago,
the King of the walls
left behind this warning.
"If you ever interfere
with our affairs,
the millions upon millions of
Titans sleeping within the walls
will flatten the entire world."
As long as he can
make this threat,
none dare to confront him,
at least not directly.
So, the Marleyan government
has the same objective as we do.
They'll try to
infiltrate Paradis,
and then seize the Founding
Titan for themselves.
[COMRADE 57D]
What do we do?
With things as they are...
Yeah. Marley'll
get it before us.
If they actually do it,
we'll lose any chance we had
of bringing Eldia back!
It's bad, but we still
have a path forward.
I'll send my son, Zeke,
to become a Marleyan warrior.
You see, Zeke?
Almost everything
that you've been told
by the Marleyans was wrong.
But you have to obey
their every order,
and you have to do it
better and faster
than anyone else around you.
All of us here are
counting on you
to save Eldia from disgrace.
'Kay. I understand.
[GRISHA] But I should've
known, better than anyone,
what a wretched sin it is
to impose your beliefs
on your children.
[GRISHA] I saw him as
a child of royal blood--
as Eldia's greatest hope.
But did I ever see him as Zeke?
As the boy he was?
[GRISHA]
At any rate,
Zeke chose to protect himself,
as well as his grandparents,
by turning in both of his
naive, foolish parents
to Marley Public Security.
[KRUGER]
Here we are.
[gasps]
So this is... paradise.
[KRUGER]
That's right.
This is Marley's penal
colony for you Eldians,
called Paradis.
You'll serve a life sentence
for treason on this island...
...once you've
become a pure Titan.
[GRISHA screaming]
Answer me! Who is the Owl?
Please! No more! I don't know!
I've told you
everything! Please...
Ah, I'm disappointed
to hear that.
We'll do another then.
[GRISHA screams]
[GRISHA]
I met you once before,
when I was just a child.
[KRUGER]
You still remember that?
Yeah. I could never forget it.
Not after what you two did.
Please, sir, just kill
me now! I can't--
Shut up and keep walking!
Please don't make me a monster.
[GRISHA gasps]
Wait, Grice?
Shit. How the hell did
this happen, Grisha?
Why in the world would Zeke
decide to betray us?
Isn't he your son?
Damn it.
Entrusting everything to you was
the stupidest thing I ever did.
It's all over now!
We're finished because of you!
Say something!
I'm so sorry.
Why did we put all our hopes
behind a naive fool like you?
[GROSS] Looks like
we've got a lively one.
You're free to go.
Grice, no!
[GRICE groans]
Grice! Hang in there!
[GROSS]
Run straight north!
If you're fast enough,
there's a chance you'll
make it to the wall!
But Sergeant Major Gross--
[GROSS] Hmm? This must be
your first time out here.
We do this to be sure the
Titans we make leave the area.
They'll chase him
for a good while.
But they always catch
'em in the end.
Kruger knows. Eh? Right?
[KRUGER]
Yeah.
[GRISHA]
It's him. There's no doubt.
That's the bastard
who killed my sister!
Well, we've got a whole
bunch to turn this time,
so let's get a move on.
[gasps]
[GRISHA]
You can't--
[COMRADES groaning]
[COMRADES gasping]
[GRISHA]
No!
No, don't do this!
Guys, please! You can't!
You have to stop it. It's Grice!
[GROSS] Turn him already
before my ears start bleeding.
I'd like to interrogate
this one a bit further.
You can continue without me.
[GROSS]
Ah. This one's a woman.
Too bad. If only
you weren't a devil.
[GRISHA]
Dina?
My darling.
Why'd they bring you here?
I talked.
I told them every last
thing there was to know!
This woman's of royal bl--
Shut your mouth!
[GRISHA grunting]
[GRISHA] Don't tell me--
Is he trying to cover this up?
Good grief.
He'd've shut up ages ago
if you'd just turned him.
Grisha. I promise.
No matter what form
I might take,
I swear I'll come find you.
[GRISHA screams]
Well isn't that romantic.
I'm sure you'll make
a great Titan couple.
No! Dina!
[GRISHA gasping]
[EREN gasps, screams]
[BOTH gasp]
[EREN gasping]
What was that?
Who am I?
And where--?
Hey. Just calm down.
You're still in the stockades.
You and Mikasa, because of
your insubordination.
[MIKASA] Were you having
a nightmare? Or--
Yeah. I guess I was.
When you woke,
you asked who you were.
[MIKASA]
It's true.
Also, you look like...
you're crying.
[EREN]
I feel strange.
Like I just woke up from
the longest dream of my life.
Hold on.
That was no dream.
It was real.
Just now,
I was somehow reliving
my dad's memories.
That Titan.
It was you.
[BOTH]
Poor Dina.
[GROSS laughs]
Look at that!
Your woman's forgotten
all about you.
I guess she fancies that Grice
fellow more now, eh? [laughs]
Shut up!
Did you say something?
[GRISHA]
It was you!
Fifteen years ago!
You fed my eight-year-old
sister to your dogs!
It was you!
Tsk. I'll take this
one off your hands.
You can just head
back to the ship.
Uh, understood.
[SOLDIER 57A]
What was that about?
[SOLDIER 57C] The Sergeant
Major's putting some time
towards his hobby.
It's best to leave
it at that, rookie.
Kruger.
If you've finished
your interrogation,
I'd like to see this one dance.
Huh? Wait, what?
I remember you, too, now, son.
So I'm gonna let you go
out in a special way.
We'll turn this guy into
a 3- to 4-meter Titan,
then the two of you can fight.
But why?
Why do something like that?
Do you get some sick pleasure
out of watching people
get eaten alive?
I wouldn't call it pleasure.
I just find it interesting.
Does that sound
a bit crazy to you?
Well, the fact is,
most people wanna see cruelty.
Don't get me wrong,
I think peace is
a wonderful thing,
but something about it
just feels lacking.
We've pushed death
out of sight and mind.
Now that's no way to live.
Death is always near in nature.
And some might think me abnormal
for investigating such things.
But to them I'd say I faced
this cruel world head-on.
And because I bothered to deepen
my understanding of death,
I can accept it
when my time comes.
[COMRADE 57G groans]
See, it's about education.
My boys learned from watching
their dogs eat your sister.
[COMRADE 57G screams]
Do you not... feel any remorse?
Well, I guess I get
what you mean.
If something that horrible were
to happen to one of my children,
my heart would break,
no question.
You poor devils.
It's a shame you had
to be born Eldian.
[gasps]
[GROSS] Look. That is
your people's true form.
All it takes is some
Titan spinal fluid,
and any one of you will turn
into a man-eating monster.
The whole of humanity
would feel safer
if you Eldians would
just disappear.
We wish we could eradicate
you from this world.
You what?
I have no trouble
sleeping at night,
'cause I'm not really
killing humans.
If you had restored Eldia,
you'd be butchering us
Marleyans right now.
Where's your remorse,
you murderous devil?
You're lying.
You've always lied,
but I know the truth.
Our founder Ymir helped this
continent to prosper. She--
Yeah. I've heard it before.
Say, since your history's
so wonderful,
why don't you share it
with your friend down there?
You can't do this to me!
I'm a human being!
Ooh, hear that?
Your sister's calling for you.
[screams]
[GROSS groans]
[GROSS screams]
[KRUGER sighs]
[GROSS screaming]
[KRUGER] So is it as interesting
as he said it was?
Wait. Why'd you do that?
Because I'm the Owl, Grisha.
Watch closely and don't forget.
This is how we of the
Nine use our power.
[SOLDIERS gasping]
♪ Closing Song ♪
[NARRATOR] The true role
of one of the Titans
is revealed through Grisha.
And the yearning for freedom
that spurred his
predecessors forward
is passed down to Eren.
Next episode: "Attack Titan."