My business with you is over!
Why don't'cha
take a look above you?
[MALE SOLDIER 41A, 41B groan]
[ROGER hollers]
--[HANGE grunts]
--[ROGER groans]
[MALE SOLDIER 41C groans]
Now where are Eren and Christa?
[MALE SOLDIER 41C gasps, coughs]
You can't win.
If you don't turn yourselves in,
then every last Scout we
captured will get the noose!
[ERWIN] I entrusted something
to Commander Pyxis.
What happens next
is out of my hands.
It'll be your choice to make.
Yours and theirs.
♪ Opening Song ♪
[MALE CITIZEN 42A]
That's a lot of wagons.
What's all that about?
You mean you haven't heard yet?
Pretty much all of
the military higher-ups
are meeting inside the castle.
They're finally disbanding
the Scout Regiment.
See? They're building
those gallows
to hang the commander from.
He's probably getting his
final judgement as we speak.
[ERWIN] When facing your enemy,
you can't just guard
with a shield. You need a spear
to dispatch the threat.
If you disband
the Scout Regiment,
it will be akin to humanity
tossing its spear aside.
Suppose that in this very
instant Wall Rose was breached.
[CROWD yelling]
[ERWIN]
Once again, half of humanity
would be forced to flee.
This time to Wall Sina.
But the earlier evacuation
left us with only
a few more days' worth
of supplies at best.
And when they run out,
locals and refugees
will be forced
to fight for survival.
Wall Rose and Wall Sina.
All of humanity would split.
And a civil war
would quickly erupt.
Even if the walls
are not breached again,
Wall Rose is suffering from
a perpetual shortage of food.
It may not be Titans
that breach Wall Sina.
It's entirely possible that
the residents of Wall Rose
will do it first.
[SOLDIERS gasp, murmur]
[ERWIN]
Wall Maria must be reclaimed.
If humanity is to have
any hope for the future,
then that is the way.
And you think
that such an undertaking
requires the Scouts.
[ERWIN] Our duty
as Scouts has ever been
to charge forth at the enemy.
Cowering in wait behind these
walls will solve nothing.
That's my belief.
Unless you have
some sort of secret plan
by which we might
overcome this ordeal.
A-hem. Commander, it seems
you misunderstand what this is.
The reason we brought
you here is not to discuss
our future within the walls.
Nor is it on account of
something as simple as a murder.
Clause Six of
the Charter of Humanity.
One must never prioritize
their own gain
over humanity's survival.
You've broken
the most sacred of laws.
Indeed. You have refused
to hand over Eren Jaeger
time and time again.
And through this selfish action,
you've violated our charter.
But Eren is vital for
the reclamation of Wall Maria!
That is not for
the Scouts to determine!
Eren Jaeger is a Titan
whose abilities
are far from understood!
To shelter him within our walls
is to put all
of humanity at risk.
And the very idea of
allowing a single commander
to have control
of him is absurd.
As shown by the way
you maliciously
schemed against the state.
Not only did you
feign his abduction
in order to conceal
his whereabouts,
you also slew Dimo Reeves
when he learned too much.
This amounts to blatant treason.
It's not a stretch to describe
you as a threat to humanity.
[GERALD]
Commander Pyxis.
The Garrison and Scout Regiments
frequently risk their lives
side by side
on the front lines.
How are we to know that you
aren't working together now?
I am deeply disturbed
to hear that you believe
we would align ourselves
with the Scout Regiment.
There is nothing more senseless
than humans killing each other.
In this cramped bit of world
that's been left to us,
it would take but a single
spark to engulf all.
Just before the battle
to retake Trost began
I said as much
to the men I lead,
and then sent hundreds
to their deaths.
If the Scout Regiment
is that fatal spark,
then it should be
smothered at once.
[NILE gasps]
Think about it. What if
the Titans did manage to
break through the wall only to
find next to no one inside it?
The poor monsters might
have to go hungry.
Ha! A-hem.
Very well, then.
Let's begin deliberations.
Your Majesty.
With your permission.
[NILE] Erwin. Is this
how you want it to end?
Now then, in the king's name,
I'll announce
your final judgment.
Commander Erwin Smith.
You have been found
guilty of violating
Clause Six of
the Charter of Humanity.
Your sentence is death.
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[AURILLE] Your execution
will be carried out at once.
Take him.
[NILE]
Erwin, is this what you wanted?
What about your dream?
[SOLDIERS gasp]
Wall Rose has fallen!
The gates have been breached!
[gasps]
[ANKA]
It was just like Wall Maria.
The Armored and Colossal Titans
appeared out of thin air
and broke through both gates
in Calaneth District!
Currently, countless refugees
are flooding this way
from the East.
Secure an evacuation route!
Order all available
Garrison troops to make for
the eastern front
and defend the people!
We must get those
evacuees into Wall Sina!
Hurry and go! Saving the people
is our highest priority!
--[SOLDIERS] Sir!
--[AURILLE] No, wait!
[PYXIS]
Hm?
I want every last gate
to Wall Sina closed off.
Not a single refugee will
be allowed inside this wall!
[NILE]
U-Uh. But all those people.
Everyone in Wall Rose will die.
You're commanding us to stand by
while half of humanity
gets devoured?
Like Erwin said,
if we let them in,
then we'll end up
in a civil war.
The rule of law must be
protected above all!
The government mustn't fail!
Uh! We can't be sure.
That's only a possibility--
there's no guarantee that w--
It's enough that
the possibility exists!
Our authority is and
must always be absolute!
Now follow your orders!
[PYXIS]
Mm.
Damn it. To think that
the wall would end up
getting breached
at a time like this.
Although, there is
a silver lining here.
We've already secured the power.
Before too long,
the vessel will take it
and then our problems will end.
Very well.
This is far from ideal,
but there's no point
in losing our composure here.
We still have one wall, and
Lord Reiss should be back soon.
Agreed. We're still
safe for now.
We have our orders.
Let's get those gates closed!
Hold on.
The refugees are coming now!
[SOLDIERS murmuring]
[ERWIN] Who should decide?
Who has the right?
What's taking so long?
Go do your duty!
Ignoring my orders
is an act of treason!
Then I guess I'm a traitor.
--Say what?
--But sir.
I can't. I am a citizen
of Wall Rose.
I refuse to shut the gates
on those people!
--You dare to d--
--[ZACHARY] I stand with him.
[AURILLE, NILE gasp]
[AURILLE]
Pr-Premier Zachary.
Did you find the way
they reacted surprising?
Or was it expected?
Surprising? Not a bit.
Premier Zachary.
What's the meaning of this?
That report you all
just heard was fabricated.
There's no cause for alarm.
As of this moment,
there have been
no reports of any Titan attack.
[AURILLE] Uh! Bastard!
This was all a farce?
[PYXIS]
It wasn't his plan. It was mine.
[AURILLE]
Pyxis?
It would appear that
most of the Interior Police
are off rounding up
Scouts somewhere.
Which worked out nicely for me.
What are you saying?
When you asked me,
I declared to you in earnest
that the Garrison Regiment
is not aligned
with the Survey Corps.
But I forgot to mention
something else.
We are not aligned
with your assembly either.
[gasps]
That's right. Although I agree
with Erwin on several points,
I was still willing to put
my trust in your government,
so long as you could
prove yourselves to be
the better choice for humanity.
Because you have
knowledge that we don't.
About both the Titans
and the walls.
Had you shown that you
actually gave a damn
about protecting
the people you govern,
I would have
stood by and watched
as you sent Erwin
to the gallows.
In fact, depending on
the choice you made,
all of us were prepared
to forfeit our lives.
However. You've made it clear
that our suspicions
were correct.
It's true that we soldiers
know next to nothing
about the Titans
and their powers.
But I daresay
that despite this fact,
humanity is safer in our hands.
What? Don't be such a fool!
Just what do you expect to
accomplish by threatening us?
You'll fail. The people
will never obey you!
The monarchy has ruled
for over a hundred years.
You would never gain
the support of the nobles!
It would appear that you've
misunderstood what this is.
You see, it's far more
than a mere threat.
It's a coup d'état.
Interior Police
have been subdued.
The capital is secured, sir.
Well done.
[gasps]
[ZACHARY] To be a soldier
can sometimes mean
obeying your commander
over your king.
And that's especially true
when the king's a pretender.
He'll be exposed and replaced.
[AURILLE]
This is real? You plan to--
Don't think for
one second that this coup
has a sliver of legitimacy!
Given the scenario
you were presented with,
your choice
to close Sina's gates
broke Clause Six of
the Charter of Humanity.
[gasps]
Furthermore, you installed
a puppet king in order to
seize the reins of power
for yourselves.
This crime is known as treason.
♪
[AURILLE grunts]
Shit! Wake up!
What, is it dinnertime?
Oh, shut your mouth,
you stupid oaf!
Well, Erwin. Looks like
you managed to pull it off.
Wait. You don't seem happy.
I'm thinking.
Humanity is on a new path.
One far more dangerous
than the last.
[LEVI]
Huh?
[HANGE] And there you have it.
The coup was successful.
Premier Zachary
now has full control
of the capital and government.
For the time being at least,
the nobles seem
to be staying in line.
Okay, but what about
the incident with Mr. Reeves?
We got a public confession out
of one of the Interior Police.
Reeves' son Flegel really
pulled through for us.
[FLEGEL]
Come on! Don't you get it yet?
The government doesn't give
a shit about saving any of us!
You can face the truth now,
or you can die wishing you had!
We have to do this!
If Titans attack again,
all the things you're
protecting will be gone!
There'll be no company.
Our families will die!
Let's print the truth
before that happens!
[HANGE]
It's all written right there.
The abuse of power. The bogus
charges against the Scouts.
And that King Fritz was both
a puppet and a fraud.
It's clear that we
only acted in self-defense.
In short, we're no
longer criminals.
[JEAN, CONNY, SASHA, ARMIN gasp]
[JEAN, CONNY, SASHA, ARMIN
cheering]
That can't be. They beat us?
[LEVI] Looks like
Erwin's gamble paid off.
That it did. But it wasn't
just Erwin who gambled.
Many people had to make
a lot of hard choices
for this to work.
[LEVI] Whereas my choices got
three of your people killed.
I'm sorry.
Here's the thing--
the Interiors may have lost,
but not all of them know it.
They still have Eren,
and Historia, too.
We need to find them quickly.
Right. I think I know
where they might be.
[LEVI]
Hm?
[HANGE] Let's get there
and put an end to this fight.
[NARRATOR]
Largely due to Erwin's actions,
it was declared that
the old system of rule
would be dismantled.
[NARRATOR] Once the military
had secured the capital,
they made the
announcement immediately.
The declaration was
given from the very gallows
that Erwin was meant
to be executed on.
[NILE]
That's right.
It's exactly as Premier Zachary
explained in his speech.
Please understand
that our objective here
is not to establish
military rule.
We intend to replace Fritz
with a monarch
born of the true
royal bloodline.
They'll be responsible
for leading humanity,
and that includes us.
I get what you're saying,
but frankly,
why should the people
believe that your king
is any more legitimate
than the one you deposed?
[MALE REPORTER 42B]
I'm sure you understand
that the people
are quite concerned.
No one knows who
to trust at this point.
[ERWIN]
For the sake of humanity,
it might've been better
to let that government stand.
Like Commander Pyxis was saying,
they have far more
knowledge than us,
and they've kept humanity
going at least this far.
Even if they would've
watched as half of
the human race perished,
it's better than
letting us go extinct.
Should I have given up?
Let them take Eren?
Surrendered my life,
and put my comrades at risk,
and put my trust
in their selfish wisdom?
Too late now.
Instead, I endangered us all.
Your duty is as painful
a burden as ever, I see.
Perhaps death would've
been easier for you.
So tell me, why didn't you
do as you just described?
--I'm not sure--
--Why don't I tell you
my own reason?
I've hated those arrogant
bastards for a long time!
Those self-assured pigs.
They'd feed from gilded troughs
and pretend their shit was gold.
Know what? I think I might
grow to like them.
Now that the day I've dreamed of
has finally come to pass.
Well, at any rate,
if you hadn't done it today,
I would've given it
a shot myself
before I kicked the bucket.
I honestly couldn't care less
about how this coup of ours
ends up affecting
the fate of humanity.
Heh. I guess I'm quite
the scoundrel, huh?
I'm telling you this because
I know that you're the same.
You made the choice
that would keep you alive.
Some part of you
decided that humanity's fate
only mattered if
you could live to see it.
I must be incredibly
conceited to think that.
It's your turn to answer now.
Why did you risk it all
just to bring them down?
I've had this dream.
Something to prove.
Ever since I was a child.
[MIKASA] Hange. You said you
might know where they are?
Oh, yeah.
Guess I should explain how.
Erwin gave me this Scout report
from an investigation
on Lord Reiss' land.
It details a certain incident
that occurred five years ago
on the Reiss Estate.
Five years?
That's right. It was the day
Wall Maria was breached.
I'll summarize
the most important parts
from the beginning.
So, as far as
regional lords went,
Lord Reiss was fair and
well-respected by the people.
He had five children.
The most well-known of them
was his eldest daughter Frieda.
She was a down-to-earth girl
who even the peasants adored.
But five years ago,
on that night, disaster struck.
With the fall of Wall Maria
having plunged the world
into chaos, bandits
raided and set fire
to the only chapel around.
Unfortunately for them,
the entire Reiss family
had gathered there to pray.
And so, the entire family
was massacred
by bandits that night--save one.
Only Rod Reiss managed
to escape with his life.
To top it all off,
this incident occurred
just a few days
before Historia's mother
was killed by
the Interior Police.
So we know that
in the immediate wake
of losing his family,
Rod Reiss sought out Historia.
And something tells me
that it wasn't out of
a newfound paternal affection.
Well, she is of royal blood.
Or do you think that bloodline
has some other secret?
It's possible,
but I'm not sure yet.
What really stood out
to me at least,
was the fact that large parts
of the chapel were destroyed.
The chapel was built from stone.
It would take a lot of time
and effort to destroy it.
If it was bandits, they'd have
taken what they could
and made a quick escape.
Also, Lord Reiss
was the only witness.
No one confirmed his story.
Then Lord Reiss
rebuilt the chapel with
his personal fortune
almost immediately.
What was his rush?
When you think about it,
the story could only make sense
if it involved a Titan attack.
It may turn out that
I'm jumping to conclusions,
but it's suspicious enough
to merit investigation,
and it's the only lead we have.
[gasps]
[jingling]
[EREN]
What the hell?
[HANGE]
Before the night is over,
Reiss' land will be
crawling with our soldiers.
Unfortunately, we can't
expect him to wait that long.
We have to get there
as soon as possible.
Before Eren ends up
in someone's stomach.
[ARMIN] A Titan gains
intelligence and the power
to transform by eating a human
being with that power.
If that's actually true...
How and when did Eren
first become a Titan?
And who did he have to eat
to gain his powers?
[EREN grunting]
[EREN]
Shit!
Historia?
♪ Closing Song ♪
[NARRATOR]
Mikasa and the others head for
Lord Reiss' chapel
to save Eren.
Meanwhile, a captured
Eren learns a secret.
He learns of his father
Grisha's unforgivable sin.
Next episode: "Sin."