[screaming]
[GRISHA] He squeezed
the soldier's lives out
as if he were juicing fruit.
And then, he cast the
scraps into the sea.
[GRISHA] I suppose I ought
to explain what the sea is.
It's an enormous
body of salt water
that covers 70%
of our world's surface.
♪ Opening Song ♪
Hold on. You said
you were the Owl?
Yes, my name's Eren Kruger.
As you just observed,
I have the power of
one of the Nine Titans,
which proves that I'm a Subject
of Ymir, just like you.
You got into Public Security
by pretending to be a Marleyan?
But what about the blood tests?
With the help of a doctor,
they were quite easy to pass.
Doctors make good spies.
In all honesty, you're
a fine example of that.
But considering your results,
I see why Grice
lamented as he did.
[GRISHA]
I have no excuses.
I was a bad husband, a worthless
father, and an imbecilic man.
So explain to me.
Why am I the only one left
standing as a human?
My wife Dina was special.
A Subject of Ymir
with royal blood.
She could've made full use
of the power of the Titans.
And if you hadn't shut
me up, she'd still be--
Tell me why! Why did
you save only me?
Let go. You're just
making your hands worse.
I'm grateful for your concern,
but I didn't notice much before
when you were cutting
off my fingers.
So? Why didn't you transform
into a Titan earlier?
If you'd made your move sooner,
they'd be fine right now!
What was the point
of waiting for them
to be turned into monsters?
[KRUGER panting]
What's wrong?
Why do you look so pale?
It wasn't only your comrades.
I've severed
thousands of fingers
from fellow Subjects of Ymir.
I've created countless Titans
from men, women, and children.
All the while telling
myself it was for Eldia.
I'm sorry, Grisha.
Time is short.
I'm entrusting you
with this last task.
There's no one else I can
trust to see it through.
[KRUGER] That day,
when I first met you outside,
you may wish you
could take it back.
But if not for what happened,
you wouldn't hate Marley
nearly enough to come this far.
So is that the reason
why you chose me?
It's part of it.
The country. Your
father. Yourself.
You bore it all such hatred.
The look in your eyes could've
burnt the world to ash.
I felt that same
rage for a time.
The branch of the royal
family that stayed behind
started a revolution,
and my father was a
staunch supporter.
It failed.
Not only did they
accomplish nothing,
all of them were burnt alive.
I was still young.
I couldn't help.
I just peeked through the
closet door and watched.
After that day,
I swore I would take revenge
and restore the Eldian Empire.
But all I've managed to do
is cut the fingers
off my fellow patriots,
kick them off this wall, and
watch the humanity leave them.
I had to do these heinous deeds,
or else I would've been
found out as the Owl.
I'm not sure I've
changed since that day.
Perhaps I'm still a child
looking at the world
through a cracked closet door.
So go on and tell me.
This task... What exactly is
it you're asking me to do?
I want you to make your
way into the walls
and take the Founding
Titan by force.
After you've inherited
my Titan, that is.
You want me to... what? But I--
You'll have to eat me
alive as a Titan.
That's also how you'll
steal the Founding Titan
from the royal family.
But why don't you do it?
[KRUGER sighs]
Anyone who inherits the
power of one of the Nine
will perish 13 years later.
And that's how long
it's been for me.
He said that was the rule.
Called it the "Curse of Ymir."
The first Titan, Ymir, died that
long after getting her powers.
Since none can surpass her,
we have to do the same.
So I have 13 years to live.
And you...
I've only got
eight left. Not even.
[MIKASA]
No. You're wrong.
There's been a mistake.
It can't be true.
If someone with the
powers of one of the Nine
should die without passing
it on to a successor,
the power will be inherited by
a baby born after that death.
A Subject of Ymir, of course.
For that to be the case,
it seems all of us Eldians
must be connected
by something we can't see.
There was one successor
who said there were paths--
paths that the naked
eye can't observe--
through which Titan
flesh can move,
along with memories
and the will to act.
These paths are countless.
They reach far,
and in many directions,
but they all meet
at one coordinate.
[KRUGER, EREN]
The Founding Titan.
There's not a
Subject of Ymir alive
who isn't connected
to the coordinate.
Speaking of Ymir, who do
you think she really was?
[KRUGER] To the Marleyan State,
she's the devil's pawn.
But to the Eldian Empire,
she was a miracle of God.
There are those who believe
that she touched the
source of all life,
and who am I to say
they're wrong?
Huh?
The sole truth of
this world, I've found,
is that there is no truth.
Any one of us can
become a god or a devil.
All it takes is for
people to believe it.
You're the one who sent us Dina,
claiming she was of
a royal bloodline.
Was that a "truth"
of your creation?
Unfortunately, Dina's royal
heritage was objectively real.
Then why'd you
let them turn her?
That'd be because
she had royal blood.
I couldn't risk letting
the Marleyans get her.
She had to go before Zeke
could tell Marley more.
Even so--
Even so?
The enemy would've forced
Dina to bear their children
for the rest of her
miserable life.
Would that have been better?
I didn't save our comrades
because they couldn't
reach the walls alive.
Only one of the Nine can make it
past all those mindless Titans.
I've done my duty. Now do yours.
To be perfectly honest,
I don't think I'm
fit for the job.
You're going to do it.
Look at the sergeant.
He was eaten alive by a Titan.
And afterward, you asked me if
watching that was interesting.
Well, that's not the
word I'd've used.
Each moment I spent listening
to his screams was unbearable.
I-I didn't know
what I was doing.
If I had realized that this
was the price of freedom,
I wouldn't've paid.
[KRUGER sighs]
[KRUGER]
Stand.
Fight!
If you want to restore
freedom and dignity to Eldia,
then stand!
I just... can't.
[KRUGER]
I brought this from your home.
Look at it.
No, I can't.
[KRUGER] So you can't fight,
or stand, or even look.
What's wrong with you?
Marley cut your balls off?
There's no point in trying to
make me remember my old hatred.
Everything is gone now...
Except my sins.
[KRUGER]
Those are all you need.
The main reason I chose you
was because of that day,
because you went
beyond the walls.
If you hadn't taken
your sister's hand
and run past the gate that day,
you would've ended up running
your father's clinic,
and your sister might
be married by now.
She might even
have had children.
But you'll never know what
she would've become.
Ever since you tread forbidden
ground and took her with you.
Ever since the day I first
kicked a patriot off this wall.
We've known that we'd
have to keep fighting
to pay for our sins.
Even in death. Even after.
[KRUGER]
That's right.
You chose to start this story.
[KRUGER] Each of the Nine Titans
has a name to describe it,
and that includes the one
you're about to inherit from me.
Throughout history, this Titan's
marched in the vanguard.
It has ever pushed forward,
seeking freedom.
And for freedom's
sake... it fights.
Therefore...
...it's called the Attack Titan.
What's that all about?
"It's called the Attack Titan."
That's what you
just did, remember?
No.
[HANGE]
Huh?! Come on! He did!
Am I the only one who saw him?
No, but... I think he was just--
[HANGE] Just what? Who the
hell were you talking to?
No one. It's nothing.
You said the name of
your Titan, right?
Are ya practicing ways
to introduce him, or--?
Let it go, Hange.
He's 15 years old. We all go
through a phase like this.
[HANGE] A phase where we mutter
weird crap while posing?
[ARMIN] Hange, I'll
explain it to you later.
It's not right with him in here.
[HANGE]
Oh, it's that kinda phase.
What the hell do you want?!
Get out.
What?
But I'm not done. I still
have ten full days left.
I'm satisfied.
Hange just gave you
ten days worth of pain.
We talked it all over with
Premier Zachary, so don't worry.
If we keep the brave heroes
who toppled the Armored and
Colossal Titans jailed,
it kinda sends a bad
message, you know?
Plus, you were only
defying the morons
who had the Beast and Armored
Titans at their mercy
but let them get away!
That isn't true.
[EREN]
Did you lose some weight?
That's odd.
We had plenty to eat.
You look... well enough.
Yeah, I guess.
[LEVI]
Let's go.
Get dressed already.
Wait, where are
we going, Captain?
A state meeting.
Her Majesty has come to Trost.
[YMIR]
To my dear Historia.
As I write this, Reiner's
standing at my side.
He knows this is a love letter,
but he's still sneaking peeks.
Honestly. It's no wonder
the creep's still single.
That said, he did
give me his word
that he'd deliver
this letter to you.
He says he owes me for the time
I doubled back to save him.
I'm sorry about then.
I never would've imagined myself
choosing those two over you.
I'm going to die soon,
but I'll die without regrets.
Or that's what I'd like to say.
Truth is, I do have one.
It's that I never
got to marry you.
With love, Ymir.
[CHRISTA gasps]
[EREN]
These paths are countless.
They reach far, and
in many directions,
but they all meet
at one coordinate:
The Founding Titan.
[gasps]
Wait. What was that?
[HANGE]
Something wrong?
No.
I take it this is all she wrote?
Yes.
I doubt that she
would be permitted
to write anything that might
be beneficial to our cause.
Could there be a secret message
that no one can see except you?
Some kind of code?
[CHRISTA]
I don't know.
But frankly, that doesn't
sound like her.
Heh.
That idiot. What's with her?
So ridiculous.
Playing it off whenever
she got embarrassed.
I could never tell with her.
[knocking]
[LEVI]
It's us.
Come in.
Your Grace.
--Your Grace.
[CHRISTA]
Oh, stop it. Please.
I'm not actually ruling yet.
But wow. You've been
through so much.
Meanwhile, I've done nothing
but watch the south
sky and wait.
It's an important duty of yours,
just to keep safe and well.
Yeah. He's right.
Yeah.
[CHRISTA] It's good to
see that you're still
acting like yourselves.
Well, that might just be that
it hasn't sunk in for us yet.
Why don't we get
the ball rolling?
[ZACHARY] The Early Life
of Grisha Yeager ,
The Extent of Our Knowledge
of Titans and Their History ,
and Information About the
World Beyond the Walls .
The only people who
know these books exist
are those who are
in this room now.
These texts were obtained
through the efforts
of the nine Scouts before us,
and the 199 others
who were lost.
On this day, and in
the Queen's presence.
I'd like for all of us to
assess our situation,
and come to an agreement about
our next course of action.
Scout Regiment
Commander, Hange Zoe.
[HANGE]
Sir.
The Scouts have suffered
a brutal, staggering blow.
In exchange for the
lives of many heroes,
including Erwin Smith,
we have retaken Wall Maria
and seized control of
the Colossal Titan,
with all its fearsome strength.
That said, we humans
living inside the walls
have just learned how
precarious our situation is.
I'd be relieved if Titans
were the only monsters
we had for enemies.
Unfortunately, the true nature
of the foe we face... is human.
It's a whole civilization.
One could say that it's
us against the world.
According to these books,
we're of a special race
that can turn into Titans,
called the Subjects of Ymir.
We ruled the world once,
and some fear we will again.
So despite our past
century of pacifism,
most in this world would
like to wipe us out.
[KRUGER] If Marley takes
hold of the Founding Titan,
the Eldian race
will be finished.
But if they try, the king in
the walls will stop them.
The king in the
walls won't fight.
[GRISHA]
Huh?
[KRUGER] "If Eldia is
driven to sin once again,
it shall perish,
as is meant to be.
I've made a vow, renouncing war
through the Founding Titan."
He said that to the royal
family still on the continent,
and then he closed his gates.
But what about the Titans
he threatened to send
out from the walls?
It was the last warning he gave.
[KRUGER] Those words were
simply meant to deter an attack.
They afforded him a
brief time of peace.
The king of the walls stole
his people's memories,
and told them that beyond the
walls, humanity was gone.
Surrounded by fools
of his making,
he tells them
they're in paradise.
A king that can't protect
his people is no king.
You must find that coward
and strip him of the
Founding Titan's power.
That's the mission
I'm entrusting to you.
Doctor Jaeger did manage
to achieve this mission,
and he passed the Founding
Titan on to his son Eren.
The Founding Titan's full might
can only be brought to bear
when the power is possessed
by someone of royal blood.
However, when a royal comes
to possess the Founding Titan,
they're overpowered by
their ancestor's will,
and they continue down
the path he set before them.
Such is the power of
his vow renouncing war.
However, Eren has commanded
Pure Titans once in the past
to escape from a dire situation.
So despite his lack
of royal blood,
it's at least conditionally
possible for Eren
to wield that power, too.
[EREN]
That's right.
If only for an instant, it felt
like everything connected.
Why? Why only then?
I'm here as a descendant
of the royal family.
The last that stayed.
My name's Dina Fritz.
--[HANGE gasps]
--There's no way!
You scared me.
What is it? What's wrong?
[EREN]
Oh, uh...
I just...
If you've something to say,
we would be glad to hear it.
Actually, it's nothing.
Huh?
Sorry for interrupting,
Commander.
Oh. I get it now.
That's right.
It would appear
that Jaeger here
is going through
an awkward phase.
He speaks out of turn and often
makes a nuisance of himself.
[ZACHARY]
Ah. I see.
That's rather unfortunate.
But he is at that age.
Eren?
[EREN] I haven't told those
two about it yet, either.
About how the Titan who killed
my mother and Hannes
was actually someone my dad
had been married to.
The thing is, I can't
talk about it here.
If someone with royal blood
is turned into a Titan,
then it might be possible for me
to use the Founding Titan's
powers while touching them.
Who knows... It might
not work at all.
But if the military knew
it was a possibility,
what would they do to Historia?
[KRUGER]
Build a family.
[GRISHA]
Huh?
After you've entered the walls,
you should start a family.
[GRISHA]
What are you talking about?
I'm still married to Dina.
And you're about to
transform me, right?
So won't I just
forget everything
you're telling me now, anyway?
[KRUGER]
That's not always the case.
And it's possible
someone else'll see it.
Huh?
[KRUGER] Be it your wife,
your child, or even a stranger.
Love someone in those walls.
If you can't do that,
it'll only repeat itself.
This cruel history,
these foolish mistakes...
They'll repeat.
You have to see this through.
Complete your mission and
save Mikasa and Armin.
Mikasa? Armin? Who are they?
I... I don't know.
They aren't from my memories.
♪ Closing Song ♪
[NARRATOR] They believed freedom
could be won through war.
Knowing the truth
about humanity,
when they finally reach the sea,
what will they make of
the world beyond it?
Next episode: "The Other
Side of the Wall."