[clanging]
Commander. We're good to go.
Now! Drop it!
[footsteps]
[SOLDIER 46A panting]
Captain Levi!
What? You look like
you're gonna shit yourself.
We've found Kenny Ackermann--
he's still alive!
[LEVI gasps]
♪ Opening Song ♪
[KENNY grunting]
[KENNY] For a long time,
I actually figured I was
the strongest man in the world.
[KENNY]
So this is a Titan.
I guess they really do exist.
Within the walls, no less.
[neighs]
Good! You hold him
right there, Uri!
Hold on, Rod. Don't shoot.
[KENNY grunts]
[URI] Someone must've
told him we'd be here.
Probably a council member.
We need to determine
who it was.
[ROD] Fine. Make him
talk with your power
and I'll shoot him after!
That I cannot do.
This is a guess, but still,
I'm fairly certain
that this man's part of
the Ackermann clan.
Which means,
that his motivations
for raising a blade at me...
...are entirely his own.
[KENNY grunts]
Uri!
If you're not willing
to kill the bastard,
I'll do it for you!
Argh, shit!
Hey, are you really
the king, or what?
Why don't'cha do the magnanimous
thing and let go of me?
Get your big hand off me!
I gotta get outta here!
C'mon, just gimme
one more chance
and I'll do it right next time.
[KENNY] Against such
overwhelming power,
I had nothing.
After all, he could've
crushed me to death
at any moment.
Violence was all I had,
and for the first time,
it'd failed me.
[KENNY] ...blown a new hole
in your pampered, royal ass!
[KENNY]
Lookin' back on it now,
I don't think my
family's persecution
was all that big a part
of what drove me.
[gasps]
No. Why'd you--?
[KENNY groans]
You hurt my leg.
Hey. Uri!
You're crazy. What'd you
let him go for?
Your voice won't work
on an Ackermann.
We have to kill him!
[KENNY grunts]
[KENNY gasps]
[KENNY panting]
[URI] Considering...
the persecution that
your family's been
put through on my behalf,
you've a right to hate me.
That said, I must apologize,
because I cannot die just yet.
[KENNY gasps]
[URI]
Please. Forgive me.
Even within the tiny
world of the walls,
I couldn't build paradise.
I'm such a fool.
[KENNY]
He was an omnipotent king,
and he bowed down
to a piece of trash like me.
His Titan form had
shocked me plenty,
but when he bowed, that rattled
something inside me
like nothing ever had before.
I asked if he had any use
for my blade, and Uri nodded.
[KENNY]
Next time the council met,
the man who tipped me off
about Uri was gone.
In his place sat
the Reiss' new dog,
legs kicked up on the table.
I had found myself
a new line of work.
I felt a bit pathetic
for doin' it, but that did
bring an end to
the Ackermann's persecution.
Now, walking around
in broad daylight was still
more risk than it was worth.
But I had fewer enemies.
Kuchel, huh?
Ah. Well if you mean Olympia,
that woman's been sick
for so long now that even her
old regulars quit usin' her.
[door creaks]
[KENNY]
Whew, you look rough.
Damn, have you lost some weight?
You're like a skeleton.
Hey Kuchel?
--[BOY] She's dead.
--[KENNY] Huh?
[KENNY]
And you?
Are you alive?
Ah, gimme a break.
You're not deaf, are ya?
Can ya hear me or can't ya?
You got a name?
Levi.
It's just Levi.
[KENNY]
Mm. I get it, Kuchel.
That's prob'ly a good call.
The family name
did you no favors.
Well, I'm Kenny.
That's my only name.
Me and your mother
knew each other.
It's nice to meet'cha.
[KENNY] The only thing
Kuchel left behind
was an unsociable brat
on the brink of death.
I wasn't so heartless that
I'd let the runt die, but
I wasn't about to step in
as a parent either.
There wasn't much
I could teach the brat.
Figured grippin' a knife
was a good place to start.
Then it was gettin'
along with others.
And how to say hello.
How to swing a deal.
And how to swing a knife.
I taught him everything
he'd need to know
to survive in the underground.
I figured he might try
and make a go of it
on the surface someday,
but when the time came,
well, that was somethin'
he would have to do himself.
[URI]
Join me.
Let us pray for
peace in this world.
[KENNY]
Interior Police?
Ah. So you're with
the MPs then, are ya?
Apologies. I bet I killed
a fair few of your pals.
And yet look at you now.
The king convinced you
to change your ways.
The grace and glory of our king
are truly boundless.
[KENNY] Yeah, he's somethin'.
Seems like he's just about
everything to you, eh, Sannes?
[SANNES] Because of that, I'll
do anything he needs me to.
Are you any different?
Why did you choose
to serve the king?
That's tough.
I dunno. Prob'ly because
he's the strongest around.
[KENNY] Yeah. In our world,
the one on top
is whoever can prove
that they're the strongest.
--[blow lands]
--[VICTIM 47A groans]
[KENNY]
All you need is power.
If you have that,
then at the very least,
you won't go out
like my sister did.
[thud]
[URI]
I don't have much time left.
[KENNY]
I could'a told you that.
Funny how you're a monster,
yet you still can't beat
disease and old age.
Seein' you die'll be a letdown.
That isn't what I meant.
Eh?
[URI] This power will soon
pass to Rod's children,
and I will live on inside
of their memories.
What the hell is that
s'posed to mean?
You can give that power away?
[URI] Kenny, in the
not too distant future,
this world will crumble.
In humanity's fading twilight,
it's my wish
to build us a paradise.
You believe in violence,
do you not?
It's the unavoidable truth
of our world. Although...
On the day that we first met,
something turned us
from mortal enemies to friends.
What was it?
Huh. No idea.
But I'll tell ya this.
If you hadn't squeezed me in
that stupidly big hand of yours,
I'd have stuffed your skull
full of shit for sure.
You had to really wear me out
before I'd be your friend.
Yeah. The world's
unavoidable truth.
Even so, I believe
in the miracle
that happened between us.
[KENNY] Me and Uri
never quite saw eye to eye.
Not on that.
[KENNY] Just like he said,
the monster was passed on.
Only took a glance for me
to know he wasn't gone.
Rod's daughter preached
to anyone who'd listen.
That same talk
about love and peace.
His words from her mouth.
How'd they find the time
to talk about such useless shit?
Is it a luxury that only
the powerful can afford?
Would anyone feel that way
if they just had that power?
What about... me?
My name is Kenny Ackermann.
Not a fan of the name,
but I've also been called
Kenny the Ripper.
That's because I've slit
so many MP throats like yours
that I got bored of it.
But a lot's happened since.
And as of today, it looks like
I'm gonna be the captain
of this new Anti-Personnel
Control Squad.
Nice to meet'cha.
Huh?
So yeah, I realize
it doesn't make sense.
If I were you,
I'd be pissed, too.
Bein' led by a crazed killer
who's not even
from the military.
--It doesn't matter.
--[KENNY] Hmm?
The wall fell two years ago.
We've given up
on fighting the Titans.
Instead we'll fight each other
over what little land
we have left.
That's the whole reason
this squad was created, right?
That's what all of us
are here for.
We followed the rules,
climbed up through the ranks,
and now here we are.
What do I care? It's fine by me.
[KENNY chuckles]
Heh. No need to worry.
I didn't really
ask for this squad
because I wanna
fight the Scouts.
No, that was just a little
pretext I thought up.
Somethin' to make those
jackasses on the council
nod their heads.
So why are we here?
I'll tell you why.
It's all for a grand dream!
[KENNY]
That godlike power.
Whoever gets their hands on it
suddenly becomes compassionate.
Would it be the same
for a bastard like me?
I gotta know.
What does it feel like?
From that vantage point,
what is it you could see?
Could trash like me...
...ever be able to see this
world in the same light you did?
[KENNY]
Well... Uri?
[URI]
Kenny.
[LEVI] Between the burns
and the blood you've lost,
there's nothing
that can save you now.
Oh, yeah?
I wonder.
--[clink]
--[gasps]
[KENNY] Swiped this sucker out
of Rod's bag back in the cave.
Seems if I just stick myself
I'll turn into
a big, strong Titan.
One of the dumb ones,
unfortunately.
But for a while,
it oughtta keep me... alive.
[LEVI] You had the time and
strength to inject yourself
before I got here if you wanted.
Why didn't you?
Fair point.
I guess I'm just scared.
If I don't inject
it right, then...
I might turn out the same
as Rod. All messed up-like.
I know you're not just sitting
here waiting to bleed to death.
Surely you have a better
excuse than that.
Well, runt, the thing is,
I don't feel like dyin'
without my dream comin' true.
But... I see now.
[KENNY] After all this time,
I think I see why he did it.
Huh?
[KENNY laughing]
We humans, we're all the same.
Every last one of us.
For some it's drinkin'.
For some it's women.
For some, even religion.
Family. The king.
Dreams. Children.
Power.
All of us had to spend
our lives drunk on somethin'.
Else we'd have no cause
to keep pushin' on.
Everyone was a slave
to somethin'.
Even him.
[KENNY coughing]
[gasps]
So. What's your poison,
runt? Heroics?
[LEVI grunts]
--[KENNY exhales]
--[LEVI] Kenny.
Tell me everything
you know about the king.
The First King.
Why didn't he want
mankind to survive?
Don't know, beats me.
That said, I know that's
part of the reason...
...that we Ackermanns
decided to turn coat--
[KENNY coughs]
So apparently,
that's my name as well.
Tell me. Who are you?
What were you to my mom?
Heh. You dumbass.
I'm just her brother.
[KENNY coughing]
[LEVI]
That day. Why?
Why did you leave me?
Because. I just wasn't
cut out... to be somebody's dad.
[LEVI gasps]
Kenny.
[CROWD cheering]
[CITIZEN 47A]
Did that girl really bring down
a Titan bigger than the wall?
[CITIZEN 47B]
Yeah! All the people
of Orvud District witnessed it!
[CITIZEN 47C]
As small as she is,
she still saved us
from that Titan?
[CITIZEN 47D] Her father ruled
as king from the shadows,
but she brought
his tyranny to an end!
Long live the true
ruler of the walls!
[CROWD]
Long live Queen Historia!
You need to let me be the one
to deal the killing blow
to the Titan.
Because then, we'll have a
story the people can get behind.
A story to unite the walls!
[ERWIN] To think that she
actually dealt the killing blow.
[CROWD cheering]
[EREN] Wait, you're actually
doing it? For real?
Yeah. I am.
Come on. It was just a joke.
Right, Mikasa?
After you've smacked him,
you should tell him this:
"I dare you to hit me back."
Real helpful.
If it's not a serious
grudge, let it go.
If I can't even do this, then
how can I call myself a queen?
[JEAN] That's the spirit.
Pound that runt!
[CHRISTA gasps]
[yells]
Uh.
[ALL]
Aaah!
[chuckles]
Did that hurt?
Well I'm queen now, so too bad!
If you have a probl--
--[LEVI chuckles]
--[ALL gasp]
Thanks, you guys. I needed that.
[BERTHOLDT panting]
[BERTHOLDT]
Reiner!
[BERTHOLDT grunting]
[thud]
[BEAST TITAN]
I won. Which means that
we'll wait to rescue Annie.
Retrieving the Coordinate
is our priority,
as it should be.
And if we wait right here,
well, it'll come
to us on its own.
[exhales]
♪ Closing Song ♪
[NARRATOR] They believed
themselves to be special.
When a certain man
imparts old tales,
Eren learns more truths about
his father Grisha's past.
Next episode: "Bystander."