[KENNY]
Long time, Levi.
Still a runt,
or have you grown some?
[KENNY]
Woo-hoo!
Nope. Don't look like you've
changed much at all, boy.
Kenny!
[LEVI grunts]
Boom!
[LEVI grunting]
♪ Opening Song ♪
Those gunshots? [gasps]
Are we being attacked or what?
Just stay down. Hiyah!
[KEIJI, CHRISTA, EREN gasp]
[CHRISTA groans]
[EREN gasps]
Historia!
[EREN groans]
Eren! [groans]
Hiyah!
[whirring]
[LEVI gasps]
[LEVI] Shit. They predicted
our every damn movement.
[gasps]
[LEVI grunts]
[LEVI]
Of all people,
why the hell would you
work with the MPs?
[LEVI grunting]
[BOTH gasp]
[MALE CUSTOMER 39A]
It's Levi of the Scouts!
Make yourself at home, sir!
[KENNY]
Ready or not.
[LEVI]
Shit. If this keeps up,
I'll lose my team,
Eren, and Historia.
[KENNY]
It's the damnedest thing.
I seem to be smellin' a rat
in this fine establishment.
Come on out, little rodent.
The sheriff is here!
And I aim to exterminate
all the vermin I can find.
Bang! Bang!
[BARTENDER 39A]
Eek!
[KENNY]
Oh, come on! You here or not?
[LEVI]
Right here, Kenny. Been a while.
I really thought
you'd be dead by now,
what with all the MPs
you were butcherin'.
But now you're
great friends, huh?
[KENNY] Yeah, well,
adults do plenty of things
kids like you can't understand.
Oh, right. My mistake.
You're s'posed to
be an adult now,
but you're still such a runt
it's hard to tell. Heh.
Always hoped that I might get
to see you in action someday.
I can't say I'm
disappointed, either.
Seems you still remember
every trick I taught ya.
But didn't I ever tell you
what happens to a cornered rat?
[clicking]
[KENNY] 'Cause if I had, you'd
know that wherever you run,
you'll find a bullet waiting.
[KENNY]
Hey, Levi.
[KENNY] You must've become
a scout for a reason.
And I think I know what that is.
[KENNY] We were forced to
survive in that little hellhole.
Giving everything we had
just to stay alive.
So when we found out just
how big the world really was,
you can bet it hurt like hell.
But ya know what saved us?
We found something
we enjoyed doing.
It's just that simple.
Every man needs himself a hobby.
May be the only source
of fulfillment
he'll ever find in
this wretched world.
[LEVI]
Oh, I see.
Is that why you blew off
my people's heads, then?
'Cause it's fulfilling?
[KENNY]
Yup. To achieve my grand goal,
I'll kill as many
as get in my way.
And you're no different.
You kill too when
it benefits you.
[LEVI]
Yeah.
[KENNY gasps]
[MALE SOLDIER 39A]
Wait! It's the captain.
Thanks for the help, old man.
Huh? A chair?
[MALE SOLDIER 39B groans]
Damn! Fire!
[LEVI grunting]
I hear shooting!
--[CONNY] Huh?
--From there!
[SASHA] I-I heard
close to a dozen shots!
Do you think that they
ran into some trouble?
It seems likely.
The captain gave me a message.
As of now, it's not just Titans.
We're fighting humans, too.
Huh? You don't mean...
[CONNY]
Hey!
[gasps]
[NILE] Are they running
a training exercise?
[MALE SOLDIER 39E]
Commander. You're needed
to check some papers.
[CAVEN] Captain. You finally
bit the dust or what?
[KENNY]
What a dumb question.
How would I answer
if I was dead, Caven?
[KENNY chuckles]
Brat got me good.
I forgot that bar owners
are allowed to keep guns
to protect themselves.
Looks like the runt grew up
more than I figured.
That's lovely, sir.
Like hell. The boy's
a thorn in my ass.
My dream's slipping
further and further away.
Look! There they are!
[ARMIN]
Captain Levi!
[MALE SOLDIER 39F grunts]
The hell is that?
[MALE SOLDIER 39F groaning]
[LEVI]
Follow the wagon!
Right!
[LEVI] Listen up!
These soldiers were trained
to fight other people.
They've already
taken out three of ours.
If you hesitate for so much
as a second, you'll be dead.
The moment you see an opening,
go for the kill.
--Yes, sir.
--[JEAN gasps]
--[MERCHANT 39A gasps]
--[LEVI grunts]
[MALE SOLDIER 39G groans]
Tch.
Armin! Secure the
wagon with Jean!
We'll keep you two covered.
Uh--sir!
He killed him.
Come on!
[gasps]
[FEMALE SOLDIER 39A groans]
Don't move!
Stop.
[JEAN gasps, groans]
[gasps]
--Jean!
--[gunshot]
[RODERICH]
It's a shame that nothing
came of our chat with Erwin.
We're no closer to finding
Eren Jaegar or Historia.
At this rate,
all of our actions against
the Scout Regiment will
prove to be for nothing.
[AURILLE]
True.
So, do we know what
kind of information
they might have gotten
out of Pastor Nick?
No helping it. If our
questions get specific,
we'll risk giving them
information they didn't have
in the first place.
No. What they learned
is irrelevant.
All that matters now is
what they tried to learn.
The Charter of Humanity
is clear on this.
We'll deal with them
as the law dictates.
[door opens]
[ALL]
Hm?
This is from Lord Reiss.
[gasps]
He's captured Eren and Historia.
And he's going to
take direct action
against Erwin and
the Scout Regiment.
He requires no assistance
at this time.
[NILE]
That's the last of it.
If you want any of your
personal effects returned,
ask for them later.
No. That's fine.
But if you have a moment,
I'd like to talk.
I'm not really in the mood
to reminisce about old times.
[ERWIN]
Why so cold, Nile?
We were like brothers
back in our days as cadets.
Quite soon, this tiny world
of ours will be changed.
Will that change
bring hope or despair?
Can we trust the crown
with the future of humanity?
Who should decide?
Who has the right?
Who will you trust, Nile?
Erwin. Tell me.
What are you planning to do?
[ERWIN] I'll make a gamble,
same as always.
[ARMIN retching, coughing]
[ARMIN panting]
[ARMIN]
Was it like this for you?
[gasps]
[ARMIN sniffing]
I'm sorry.
[MIKASA]
It's okay.
[ARMIN]
I'm sorry. I--
[gunshot]
[JEAN gasps]
[thud]
[LEVI]
Shit! Armin! Jean!
[ALL grunt]
[gasps]
Let 'em go.
We're running on fumes.
No!
[BOTH grunting]
Eren!
What's wrong? Did all this
filth kill your appetite?
[ARMIN] No. Jean, there's
something I don't understand.
What's that?
[ARMIN] When I turned
around to try to save you...
...that woman already
had her gun to your head.
It's... funny. How could I
have shot before she did?
I don't know.
[LEVI] You shot first
because she hesitated.
--[gasps]
--[LEVI] It's simple.
[ARMIN gasps]
I'm sorry, Armin.
You wouldn't've had to save me
if I'd just done my job.
[ARMIN]
I know what it is.
The woman I shot back there.
I bet she was a
really kind person.
She must've had a lot more
human empathy than I ever did.
I pulled that trigger so easily.
Without a thought.
I'm...
A killer.
And now that your hands
have been soaked in blood,
the person you once
were is gone for good.
[MIKASA gasps]
Why would you say that?
And you shouldn't
regret it for one second.
Because if you'd chosen
to keep your hands clean,
Jean would be a corpse
on a cart right now.
[JEAN] I'll tell you why
you pulled the trigger.
Because your comrade
was about to die.
Armin. Everyone on our
squad survived today
because you got
blood on your hands.
Thank you.
Captain Levi, I, uh,
I thought it was wrong
for us to fight
other humans, sir.
I thought it was wrong that
you'd ordered us to do it.
I mean, we became soldiers
to protect people.
But now, I see that
I was in the wrong, sir.
Next time, I swear I'll shoot.
[LEVI] I never said anything
about what was right or wrong.
My moral high ground's
shot to hell.
I have no idea who's
in the right at this point.
Now then, I think it's time we
heard what our guest has to say.
[REEVES gasps]
Mercy, please!
I'm just an old man
they use to move cargo.
I didn't want to, but they--
[MIKASA]
I've met this one before.
[MIKASA] He seemed to be
a prominent merchant.
[REEVES gasps]
[LEVI] Yeah, I know him.
Dimo Reeves, right?
[REEVES grunts]
This damn job was forced
on us by the Military Police.
And now that we
completely botched it,
they'll plunder
the Reeves Company
for everything its worth.
First, they'll kill me,
and then they'll
set up "accidents"
for all my employees.
My dumb son, too.
[FLEGEL gasps]
[LEVI] You just gonna
lay down and take it?
There's a reason Trost recovered
from that Titan attack.
It's largely because
of jobs and money
brought in by
the Reeves Company.
Tell me, if your company
were to disappear,
how many would survive
the coming winter?
So, what? You want
me to join you?
[LEVI] We just need to know
where Eren and Historia are.
If you're in contact with
the MPs, I think I have a plan.
And can you give me your word
that the people of Trost
won't end up starving to death?
[LEVI]
I can't guarantee it. That said,
I believe they'll have a better
chance with us than without.
[horse neighs]
[HANGE]
About time the bastards left.
Our situation just got worse!
I have two things
to report, Commander.
First, Eren and Historia have
been abducted by the enemy.
Three from my squad were
killed in the fighting.
I'm about to meet
Captain Levi and follow up
on a lead he might have as to
their current whereabouts.
[ERWIN]
Understood. What else?
Eren remembered a
conversation he overheard
between Ymir and Bertholdt.
But, if this is
actually true, then--
Shit. I feel like my
head's gonna explode.
--[MOBLIT] Are you okay?
--[HANGE groans]
[ERWIN]
What's the problem?
[HANGE gulping]
Unless we recover him quickly,
Eren will be devoured.
[SANNES]
Hey! How'd you find 'em anyway?
They found me. I promised
them that I'd cooperate,
and for some reason
they believed me.
Are we there? [gasps]
[gasps, groans]
Reeves, you piece of--[groans]
Sorry, gents. That's how it is.
What happens now?
Do you think this means
we'll be safe? Or what?
There's no guarantee.
Say what? Then why'd we do it?
A good merchant has to
learn to trust his nose.
And not just to
smell easy money,
but to sniff out the potential
for future profit, too.
Once you have, you bite
and you don't let go.
You remember that, son.
I made it! You haven't
finished yet, have you?
No. Haven't even
gotten my feet wet.
Sannes! I'm only a novice
at human torture,
but while I lack experience,
I plan to give this job my all.
Hold on! At least
tell me what you want!
Who the hell tortures someone
without asking questions?
[LEVI] Oh, yeah. We do
have some questions.
Where were Eren
and Historia taken?
What do you want with Historia,
and what is the Reiss family?
[HANGE]
Come on!
Can't you see that we're
in a time crunch here?
[SANNES screaming]
[JEAN]
Here we go again.
[SASHA] The screams seem
a lot louder than they were
when the captain did it.
[CONNY] I know it's to
save our friends, but...
...it still makes me sick.
Let's face the facts.
We're criminals now.
[ALL gasp]
Our last enemy wanted to eat us.
We don't have an excuse like
that for killing these people.
It's just that their
views are different.
No. It's just that
they're in another group.
[ARMIN] And for that,
we'll take their lives.
Armin.
We're not good people.
Not anymore, at least.
[HANGE] Sorry. I don't have
your knack for peeling nails.
Just how many did
you have to rip off
to get so good at it?
More than I could keep track of.
Within these cramped,
squalid walls,
war has never broken out,
and I can tell you why.
It's because we of
the First Interior Squad
dirtied our hands to
protect the king's peace!
A teacher too smart
for his own good.
A stupid couple
who tried to fly.
A whore who screwed
the wrong man!
No matter how
they'd beg or plead,
we erased them
to protect humanity!
You should be on
your knees thanking me!
In all my years,
I've never seen anyone
take such pleasure from
human suffering as you!
You're both monsters!
But I'm determined to
face you without fear.
Do what you will.
For I--I have my faith.
And I believe in the king and
in peace within these walls.
I believe that every last
one of my wretched deeds
was justified, but...
To think that it
hurt this much...
[SANNES] If you're going
to torture me to death,
get on with it.
That sounds like a fitting end
for this blood-stained life.
Time for a break.
Ugh. Damn it all.
I'm starting to
feel sorry for him.
[RALPH]
Quit shovin' me. It hurts.
[gasps] Ralph!
How pathetic can you get?
Can't believe you started
talking after just one nail.
[SANNES gasps]
[LEVI] Sannes doesn't
have any nails left.
He's a real soldier.
Like I care. He can get
tortured all he wants.
The guy never shuts up
about peace and the king.
The rest of us all
hate his damn guts.
Just do us a favor
and kill him already.
[gasps]
[LEVI] We're gonna
have to keep him around
until he's verified
what you told us.
Yeah? Well, you got everything
you wanted out of me,
so why don't you
lay off already?
Oh, and about my cell.
It'll have a bed, right?
[SANNES sighs]
[HANGE] Ready, Sannes?
We're gonna try it again!
This isn't easy for me either,
but I'll be the best
torturer I can--
Reiss is the true royal family.
[REEVES] So much for
keepin' a low profile.
How long is that
boy gonna take?
[exhales]
Ya know, the one thing
a merchant should never
sell out of is trust.
[REEVES groans]
Was it wise to do that
without asking where Levi is?
[KENNY] He'll show up
no matter what we do.
[CAVEN]
How do you know that?
'Cause I raised him, that's how.
Levi Ackermann's not one
to give up the chase.
[ARMIN] You mean the rightful
heir to the throne is...
...Historia?
[HANGE] That's correct.
And based on that knowledge,
we're assuming that she and Eren
have been taken to Lord Reiss.
[LEVI]
That's him.
[ROD]
Historia.
I can't tell you how sorry I am.
[gasps]
♪ Closing Song ♪
[NARRATOR]
One girl's tortured past
holds a secret that could
change the fate of a kingdom.
Once this secret
is known to Erwin,
he remembers his own past.
Next episode: "Old Story."