"Calligraphy"
All right.
Now, we're practicing calligraphy,
so write down your favorite thing.
Due by the end of the day.
Well, I know what I'm writing.
Grilled meat.
My favorite.
Having trouble deciding?
Sorta.
Did you figure out what you're gonna write?
Hmmm... Not just yet.
I know.
How about we both write down something
that we want from each other?
What we want from each other?
Uh-huh.
Hmm...
Okay.
What I want from Takagi?
Hmm...
"Teasing Prohibited"
Duh!
For her to stop teasing me!
This'll be a good way to tell her off!
Wait.
Now that I think about it, that might actually backfire.
She'd probably call me a wuss and make fun of me more.
I need to find a way to make her
sorry without provoking her further.
This is harder than it should be.
You done? Because I am.
Cool.
Let's show each other.
"Status Quo"
"Restraint"
Howdya like this?
"Restraint"?
Uh, yeah.
With what?
I can't really help if you don't specify.
Uh... Well, it's, uh, a few different things.
She clearly doesn't get it.
But then again, at this point if she did get
it, she'd probably get upset.
This is tricky.
So what about you?
What do you mean by "status quo"?
Oh, you don't get it?
Well, it means you're easy to tease,
and I want you to stay that way, 'Kay?
Red alert! She's going on the offensive!
It's an ambush!
If that's how she wants this to go, fine.
Two can play at that game.
I'm ready for it now.
Are you okay with a do-over?
Yeah, sure.
Get set to get wrecked, Takagi!
I'm about to fight fire with fire!
So, did you finish?
Almost.
This should make Takagi realize
that she isn't exactly kind to me.
"Kindness"
Can't misinterpret this!
Forget what I said before, now I want to upset you!
Huh... What should I write?
Ho-ho what's this?
Having trouble coming up with something?
Perhaps if you were a bit kinder,
it'd be easy to come up with a
nice, wholesome request from me.
Oh. I wanted to tell you earlier,
you have really nice handwriting.
It has an interesting flare.
Have you been taught calligraphy?
Uh, no, not really.
Hmm?
Well, either way,
I like it a lot.
Here.
Uh...
Thanks.
That's weird.
She's being so nice all of a sudden.
What's going on?
Could it be?
Is Takagi actually nice,
and I just haven't noticed it until now?
No way.
I'd have picked up on that.
Nishikata, stay still for a second.
Huh?!
Huh?
Got it.
Something was on your face.
Okay!
I think I have something to write now.
Do you like my beautiful artwork?
You're a weird guy, you know that?
What?
Okay.
I'm done.
How about you show me yours first?
Uh... Why not at the same time?
Just show me already.
" Don't tease me"
Ahhh...
I was a little more obvious this time, at least.
You really do have interesting handwriting.
That's all you have to say? Come on.
I'm trying to spell it out for you.
Stop teasing me.
What? I can't!
You didn't even give it some thought.
All right, I'm sorry.
I'll hold back from now on.
Thank you.
So what's yours say?
Curious?
Then let's see.
Here.
"You have ink on your cheek"
When she touched my face.
Didn't you just say that you'd hold back from now on?
Yeah, but I said that after I already set this up.
"Seasonal Change of Clothing"
So hot.
Yeah, I guess so.
We should start wearing our short-sleeve uniform soon.
Yeah. I guess so.
Let's just tell Sanae that we're gonna
start wearing them tomorrow, sound good?
Yeah, I guess so.
You guess what?
Huh?
Hey.
Long sleeves?
Aren't you hot?
What?
We said that we'd all change
our uniforms at the same time!
Come on!
Wait, we did?
Yes, we did!
You forgot?
Hmm?
Yeah.
"The next day"
Ahhhh! It's a lot cooler
wearing short sleeves, isn't it?
Yeah, I guess so.
Hey.
You guess what?
Hey, Sanae.
Good mor... ning.
I thought you said
we were all gonna change our uniforms together?
Uhh...
Uh...
I guess I forgot to tell you.
I wanna ask you to let me go,
but I know I deserve this, so...
"English Translation."
Junko says,
"That's right. Walk down this street to
the post office and turn left there."
You will see the station.
It takes five minutes from here.
Somehow I have to get back at Takagi today.
But the ever-present question is: How?
I haven't made a jack-in-the-box in a while.
No, I don't have enough materials.
At this point, I wouldn't finish in time, anyway.
Uhh.
Let's see, who should I put on the spot?
Nishikata.
Huh?
Uhh.
Yes, sir!
Don't "Huh? Yes, sir!" me.
Hurry up.
Don't worry, it's 16.
Huh?
Sixteen!
You don't even know what class you're in, kid?
It's English, not Math!
I told you to read aloud!
Uh... I'm sorry, sir.
Forget it. Sit down.
I told you we were on line 16.
Way to drop the ball there.
Yeah, right, you were intentionally
vague, so I'd mess it up.
Really.
I didn't think you'd actually mess that up.
Called it.
What's wrong?
Are you preoccupied with something?
You could say that.
Mind if I ask what it is?
Ehh.
It's really not worth mentioning.
Huuuuh...
Then...
Were you thinking about something naughty?
Wha...?!
No way! Of course not!
Really?
I would never!
Not in a million years!
What kinda guy do ya' think I am?!
I know. I know.
You were just trying to think of new way to
get back at me for all the teasing I do, right?
Nuh-uh.
No idea what you mean.
I know I'm right.
You were looking at me earlier, so...
...it wasn't that hard to figure out.
If you already knew, then why'd you ask?
'Cus it's fun to see how you react when I mess with you.
So what?
Did you come up with a good idea?
Hmph!
Yup, sure did.
You see, I came up with the perfect plan.
Oh and this time it's absolutely foolproof.
So...
Hmm...
I'll believe it when I see it.
She's not worried at all.
It's like she can read my mind,
so she knows I don't have a plan!
Spill it.
What's this plan of yours?
What idiot would tell you that?
Oh fine, how about just a hint?
I'm not telling you!
Just pay attention.
Wait, today's the eighteenth.
The teachers always call on the kid
whose student number matches the date.
And today that's Takagi!
If I can get her attention away from
class, she might get
in trouble for not knowing where we are in the textbook!</font>
Hey, Takagi?
D'you eat breakfast today?
Whadja have?
Yeah, mountain yam over rice.
Why ask?
Ehh.
Just curious.
So you like mountain yams?
Yeah, I like 'em.
I usually have energy all day
when I eat them in the morning.
Huh.
Yeah, I kinda getcha.
What'd you eat?
Me?
Uh, I had...
Bet you can't guess.
Hmm, I wonder.
Rice?
Rice? Why's that?
Well, I didn't peg you as a toast kinda guy.
Am I wrong?
No. You're right, I had rice.
It's working!
Just keep her attention off of the lesson!
So uhh... you on team rice?
I want someone to read the next page aloud.
Today's the eighteenth, so how about Takagi.
Here we go! Heh heh heh.
You don't know where we are, do you?
Do you?
"I will not do such a thing."
Thank you. Very nice.
What?
Hmph.
Nice try.
Wh-What are you talking about?
Man, she's good!
I can never seem to get her!
Gotta come up with another plan.
Maybe I can take it back to basics and
hit her with the old jack-in-the-box?
No, I don't have the materials!
Been over this!
Okay.
What is it this time?
Uh? It's, uhh...
Nothing, forget it.
By any chance, were you thinking about me again?
No, not really.
Not in so many words.
Plus, why would I think about you?
That'd be weird, wouldn't it?
Oooh, then you were thinking something naughty.
No! I swear!
I know.
I'm always thinking about you, though.
Hey, you're blushing!
No I'm not.
And gimme a break.
You're just always thinking about
different ways to tease me, aren't you?
Eh...
Why did she take so long to answer?
Today's June eighteenth.
If I add the month and date together, it's 24.
Number 24!
Nishikata!
"Pool"
It's the first day we get to go in the
pool, but all I can do is watch.
Why'd I have to hurt my hand?
It's just not fair.
They're all having fun without me.
Right?
And of course this happens on the
first day that they let us swim.
It sucks!
So you're sitting out too, I take it?
Mm-hmm.
For you it's because of your hand, yeah?
How'd you hurt it?
Yeah.
Well, you know, things happen.
I bet you tried to pet a cat, but then it bit you.
Huh?! Wait, how did you know that?
I made an effort not to tell anyone!
I'm actually right?
I just took a shot in the dark!
You are something else!
So what's your excuse?
Why are you just watching everyone swim... today?
That reminds me.
Any girl who sits out during
swimming is usually on her period.
According to the textbook,
it causes abdominal pain and discomfort.
So says Takao, the King of Health Class.
Oh, uh, it's nothing, forget it.
I shouldn't ask.
It's not really any of my business anyway.
You wanted to ask why I'm not
swimming today, didn't you?
Of course she heard me.
Oh. Hey. How about because I figured out your reason
is your hand, you take a shot at guessing my reason?
You're not feeling good?
You have to be more specific than that.
No. Forget it.
I wasn't actually gonna ask you.
Oh?
Then are you admitting defeat?
All right, fine.
I might as well take a guess.
Only one, though.
Well, not that you'd get it with more tries.
She's got me cornered now.
Is she this confident because
she thinks I can't say "period"?
Because if that's it, I'll show her!
I'll say it ten times!
But wait, this is Takagi we're talking about.
It could be a trap!
Even if I gathered my courage and answered, "Period"!
I know what'll happen!
No, and that's very rude of you!
So that's out of the question.
But knowing her, she probably already has
an idea of what's going through my head.
I'm hesitating, that's enough for her to figure it out.
But if I don't answer at all,
well, I think I know how that'll go, too.
You don't even know the reason why a girl
is sitting out when she could be swimming?
Ha! That means I win, then.
Is this a trap or not?
Is she making it seem genuine so I'll fall into a trap?
Or is she making it seem like a
trap, so I'll worry and mess up?
Agh. I'm just going around in circles here!
This sucks.
What was with that face before?
And was she gripping her stomach or what?
Okay, what else could it be?
Maybe an injury?
I don't know; it doesn't seem like it.
It doesn't really look like she's
feeling too sick to be exercising either.
Then that leaves.
What's left?
No.
They don't know how good they have it.
They get to goof around and cool off in the pool.
Meanwhile I'm here in the heat using
all my brain power to battle Takagi.
Come on, Nishikata, we don't have all day.
You're not just checking out all the
girls in their swimsuits, are you?
What? Of course I'm not!
Are you sure about that?
Because you know what I heard?
Boys are usually looking at girls' chests.
Whatever, then I'm the exception!
I could never say this out loud.
But Takagi doesn't have a very big chest.
I heard that small-chested girls are...
...sensitive about it.
So you probs shouldn't bring it up.
So says Kimura, the King of Early Lunch.
Could it be that she's not swimming because
she has some sort of complex about her body?
Like, she's self-conscious?
I had a feeling you wouldn't figure it out.
That means I win today, too.
Oh, Takagi.
I do know why.
It's obvious that you're just
self-conscious about your chest!
Ugh! Yeah, right!
Like I could ever say that!
It's beyond rude! It's super rude!
The only answer I have left is that she's on her period!
But that's plenty rude, too.
What do I do?
You're still thinking it over?
We have to go back inside soon.
No!
They even say in the textbook that it's
nothing to be embarrassed about! It'll be fine!
You got this.
Just say it with your head held high!
It's now or never!
The reason you're sitting out in swim class is...
...you're on your period.
Incorrect.
And that's pretty rude to say to a girl.
Uh! I just thought that since it was
mentioned in our health textbook, it might--
Man Nishikata, your face is bright red!
Then is it actually
because she's self-conscious about her chest?
That's all I got!
Ahhh... Too funny.
Upsy-daisy.
And for the record.
Being too self-conscious about my chest...
...is also incorrect.
Wha...?!
Excuse me!
I changed my mind, is it okay if I swim?
That's fine!
Uh... I don't get it.
Then why was she sitting out?
Okay.
Now that I've gotten my fill of funny faces.
It's time for a quick swim.
Oh, don't tell me you were sitting out that
whole time just so you could tease me more!
Hey. When your hand heals...
...then we can swim together.
It's cold!
I won't fall for it.
When we do swim together,
I'd bet anything she's gonna mess with me again.
After all, that's the kind of person she is.