If you're ready, hold on tight.
Sure.
When we first started practicing
tandem riding, the hardest part
was Takagi holding on to me.
Don't tickle me; you're gonna make us fall over!
I wasn't tickling you.
I just held on a little.
But if you thought I was, your ribs are ticklish.
It's just because of how your hands are touching them.
Change the way you're holding on.
How's this?
Don't you think that's a bit too close?
No.
I'll fall if I'm not close.
Oh, come on.
Don't get self-conscious.
I'm not! I'm just overheating when you're right
up against me, it's already a thousand degrees.
Anyway, just do me a favor and don't grab on so tight.
But you literally told me to hold on tight a minute ago.
All right, then.
Why don't you just show me how
you want me to hold onto you?
Hurry it up.
We're gonna run out of time to practice.
Uh. I guess something like this works?
But now we've overcome our hurdles!
And finally...
...we've mastered tandem riding.
Yeah.
Looks like we're done.
I mean, we wanted to learn to ride together, and we did.
So there's no need to practice anymore.
Uh. Mm-hmm.
Are you, by any chance, like, kinda bummed?
Huh?! I dunno.
Relieved, then?
It'd be rude to say I'm relieved we're done,
but if I say I'm bummed out,
she's just gonna tease me even more.
A little bit of both options.
Hey. No fair.
Well, what about you, huh?
What about me?
Well, I'd say I'm not that bummed out.
Oh, cool.
Tomorrow, let's finish up our homework at the library.
Huh?
We can check each other's work.
Uh. Okay.
Vacation's ending. Real soon.
On the other hand, our next term is starting.
Yeah.
I wonder when we're actually getting that typhoon.
"Typhoon"
Oh man, it's so windy!
Whoa, that's really high!
This typhoon is crazy!
I don't know why, but I feel really excited!
Now wind, blow harder and harder!
Perfect timing!
I feel like I'm controlling this huge gust!
So awesome!
Now, gale.
I command thee...!
Morning, Nishikata.
Good morning, Takagi.
This wind is really something, huh?
I probably should have tied my hair back.
Uh. Yeah, I bet that would have helped.
I was just checking the direction of the wind.
You realize I didn't ask what you were doing.
Come on!
Why does she always have to see
me at the worst possible times?
So what were you doing?
I just said, I was checking the direction of the wind.
Weird.
That's not what it looked like to me.
"Now wind, blow harder and harder!"
I could have sworn I heard that.
Me? No way, that would just be ridiculous.
Watching someone else do it makes
me realize how embarrassing it is.
So, why were you checking the
direction of the wind, then?
I just thought it'd be good to know.
Given that the wind's so strong.
So I won't fall over!
Yeah?
But you had both hands raised up so high.
Like, "Wow!
I feel like I'm controlling this huge gust of wind!
So awesome!"
I'd bet that's what you were thinking.
That's even more embarrassing.
By the way, do you notice anything different?
You're not riding your bike?
That it?
Uh-huh.
Question is:
Why do you think I'm not riding it today?
Because there's a typh--
If you guess right,
I'll keep quiet about your little performance earlier.
I won't tell a soul.
We've been over this,
I was checking the wind's direction.
You have until that plastic bag gets here.
Are you serious?
I have a time limit?
I have no choice but to get this right.
She wouldn't be asking such a simple
question if there wasn't a twist.
So I can rule out anything obvious like,
"It's dangerous to ride a bike in a typhoon."
Think. Think!
Some other problem that a strong wind would cause.
Bike.
Wind.
Could it be her skirt?
Your... Your...
I can't bring myself to say that out loud!
It's too awkward!
And... you are out of time.
The correct answer is that it's
dangerous to ride a bike in a typhoon.
Sorry!
Huh?
What?
Seriously?
You read into things too much.
Okay.
Let's get going.
This wind is so strong.
Yeah.
Kinda gets you excited, doesn't it?
Yeah. I mean, I don't really
know what you're talking about.
Hmm?
Come on.
Doesn't it make you want to shout?
Raise your hands to the sky!
"Now wind, blow harder and harder!"
This sensation!
It's like I'm controlling the storm!
I am the great Wind King, ruler of this world!
I shall blow the school away
to the far ends of the earth!
Hey, I never went that far!
So you weren't just checking the wind's direction.
Uh...
Well, whatever.
Let's race to school!
Hurry up!
So strong!
Huh? Wait up, Takagi!
You always try to get a head start!
For some reason,
Takagi was really energetic this morning.
"Marathon"
All right!
Let's do this!
How are you so full of energy?
I thought you hated marathons.
Nah.
I'm looking forward to it!
In fact, let's race, Sanae!
Okay.
How about if I win, you don't get to eat any lunch?
Yeah.
Bring it on!
Wait. You sure?
You know Sanae is really fast, don't you?
Yeah, but I'm in the zone!
Uh-huh...
What's the point of running a marathon?
It's not like we're ever gonna run this
much after we're finished with school.
It doesn't make any sense.
So lame.
You said it, dude.
You look enthusiastic, Nishikata.
Nishikata.
You sure you're up to this?
Ha! 'Course I am.
It was my idea to begin with.
'Kay.
See ya later!
You and Takagi sure are close.
Huh?!
Are you going out with her?
What are you talking about?
Don't get the wrong idea, Kimura!
I'm only competing with her because the
winner gets to order the loser around!
Wait. You're racing each other in the marathon? But...
It's none of your business.
Judging by that reaction,
I wouldn't put money on the two of them going out.
Yeah, I mean, if they were going out...
Nakai! How are you feeling?
Pretty darn good!
And it's all thanks to you
training with me every single day!
Let's destroy this marathon!
Yeah!
They'd be acting something like that.
All right, gather 'round!
I'll never understand why we have to do this.
Just accept it already, Kimura.
Empty your mind.
Run with an empty mind.
Calm yourself and avoid wasting unnecessary energy.
I've got you this time, Takagi.
I've jogged every evening for
over two weeks just for this day!
Come rain.
Come wind!
There's no way I'm gonna lose after all that prep.
Oh! Empty your mind.
Empty your mind.
Hey, Nishikata!
I figured you would have sprinted way ahead of the pack.
Oh yeah?
Sorry, but pacing yourself is the key.
But clearly you don't get it.
You look unfazed, but you sped up because you
couldn't see me ahead of you and panicked, right?
Hmm?
I was running slow until now because
I wanted to give you a handicap.
Handicap?
Wait, did she just read my mind?
Well, I'm going on ahead.
Huh?
I can't have lunch.
And I'm already so hungry.
I started out too fast.
That's right.
You'll see, Takagi.
If you keep running that fast,
you're gonna lose your pace just like her!
And all I have to do is keep up my pace.
Wait.
But what if Takagi is actually
good at running marathons?
If she is, I'm screwed!
I don't have the time to empty my mind!
Is she already running back?
She's that much faster than the boys?
I lost my pace, but I caught up.
If you manage to touch me,
then you can be the winner.
I can't touch her in front of all these people!
Who knows what they'd think was going on?
Takagi, you sneaky little...
You deliberately made me lose my pace!
Ugh...
Takagi.
I'll give you a different win condition, too.
If you can run 50 meters ahead of
me, the crown is yours!
You mean that?
Hook, line, and sinker!
I hope you're ready!
Because I'm gonna destroy your pace this time!
You're finished!
Cool!
I win, then.
All the girls are supposed to turn back here.
"Girls turn back here"
Good luck!
You boys still need to run two more kilometers.
Oh, that is so not fair, Takagi!
That's why I asked if you were sure!
We're recording your time Nishikata; don't stop running!
What'd I say?
Your sides start to hurt and you get hungry.
As far as I'm concerned, absolutely nothing
positive comes from running a marathon.
If you used all that energy to run instead of
complaining, you might be able to go a little faster.
Why would I do something so pointless?
You really think running is
more pointless than complaining?
I just wanna eat lunch.
I'm hungry too.
I'm starving.
"Ribs"
Takagi messed with me a ton today.
Again.
Man.
You'll get yours.
What's up?
Stop staring.
I can't get over that.
You have such ticklish ribs!
She does this every time there's an opportunity.
Yeah, sure, my ribs are ticklish.
But aren't everybody's?
I'm not special.
Hey, Takagi.
Hmm?
Wanna make a bet?
I'm thinking whichever one of
us laughs first is the loser.
Yeah, why not?
If it's all the same to you,
I'd like to start right now.
Okay.
I've got you now!
You have no idea what I've got in store, do you?
Looks like both your hands are
occupied holding your bike.
Too bad.
You're at a disadvantage.
If you think you can protect your ribs with only
your elbows you've got another thing coming!
Oh. By the way,
so you know, my ribs happen to not be ticklish.
Made you look!
Wow. No laugh?
That was too close for comfort.
And did she say she's not ticklish?
That's a bluff if I've ever heard one.
She's wide open!
Then could she be telling the truth?
No.
My best option remaining is to just
go for it and find out that way.
Is something wrong?
Huh?
All good. It's, uh, nothing.
This is kinda embarrassing.
Should I really touch her like that?
Wouldn't it be sexual harassment?
Hmm?
Better hurry up, or I'll get you again.
Huh?!
What the heck?
I thought I had the perfect plan all worked out.
How did I not realize it had such a pitfall!
It's too risky to go through with.
I'll keep my distance and maybe this can end in a draw.
Hey.
That face isn't fair!
I win.
I'm really dropping the ball today.
I can't believe I forgot that
Takagi makes such good funny faces.
Well then, what should I make you do this time?
Huh? There's a penalty for the loser?
You said, "Wanna make a bet."
Of course there is!
Now, let's see...
You can't eat rice for the rest of your life.
Huh?
That's brutal!
Don't worry, I'm just kidding.
You can't read 100% Unrequited Love.
Huh?
That's pretty cruel, too.
Well how about this, then?
You have to poke my ribs.
Uh?
Uhh. Wait, that's my punishment?
Mm-hmm.
Okay, then.
Hmm?
That's it!
I see what's going' on here!
She wants to enjoy me getting
embarrassed and struggling to touch her.
Not on my watch!
Come to think of it.
This might actually be the first
time I've ever touched her.
Anywhere but her shoulder, I mean.
No, don't think about it.
You're just poking her!
It's not a big deal!
You okay?
See?
Told you.
My ribs aren't ticklish in the slightest.
Yeah.
My armpits are pretty ticklish, though.
I definitely can't touch her there!
"Regret”
I totally forgot!
About?
This is absolutely terrible!
What's terrible?
We didn't do our test of courage over the summer--ah...
Oh yeah, I guess we didn't.
Let's do it today after school!
We just gotta!
Uh, I guess that's okay.
You feel that? It's so haunted!
Ooooh...
Are we really going in there?
Yes!
They're too excited for this to be a test of courage.
It's so dark!
Uh-huh.
Oh!
A hole!
Oooh.
Huh? A paper talisman!
For the spirits!
Yeah.
Look at that!
What's a steel barrel doing in here?
Uhh?
This isn't scary at all.
What? No.
It's super scary!
Yeah, no.
Whoa, look!
I found a Frisbee!
Lucky!
That's weird to find this deep in.
It's kinda chilly in here!
You think it's a ghost?
No, we're just out of the sun
and the wind is blowing through.
This is so fun!
Oooo!
Whaddya doing; don't chase me!
Are you happy we did it?
Mm-hmm.
It was such a classic summer vacation adventure!
Sure, whatever that means.
But it sucks.
Summer vacation isn't coming back any time soon.
Yeah.
I'm not used to you being so bummed out Mina.
Talk about a downer.