The day has come.
I've waited so long!
And finally, I got my first cell phone!
And contact added.
Thanks, man.
Sure thing.
You got a cell phone?
Right on cue!
Oh cool, you got the latest model?
I was thinking of upgrading to that one, myself.
Do you mind if I take a look at it?
Not at all.
Wow. It's lighter than mine.
I've been waiting for this!
With a cell phone,
I can tease her in all sorts of new ways!
Of course, I've got one plan in mind already.
You're going' down, Takagi.
Ooo.
That's a cool feature.
Thanks for letting me check it out.
No prob.
Uhh...
Huh?
Ah, it's nothing.
I thought Takagi was gonna ask me for my email for sure.
What now?
Something wrong?
Huh? Nope!
Hmm?
Man.
If I can't get in touch with
her, I can't execute my plan!
Wait a second, why don't I just ask her then?
Why didn't I think of that earlier?
It's so obvious!
Hey, Takagi?
What is it?
I, uh...
Uh...
Your email address?
Hmm?
Never mind, wasn't important!
What's going on?
Why am I so nervous all of a sudden?
Get it together!
I'm just trying to get Takagi's email address!
I didn't really think about it before.
But if I'm asking a girl for her email.
Isn't that kinda like...?
Yes, it is!
Hey, Nishikata.
There isn't something you want to ask me, is there?
No, not at all!
Nope! Not a thing! Really!
Hmm...
Funny.
I was certain you wanted to ask me for my email.
She knows!
Wait!
This might be my chance!
All I gotta do is say, "Actually,
you're right," and I'll get exactly what I want!
You've grown too careless.
Uh.
Actually, yeah, you're right.
I am? Then why'd you lie about it?
Are you embarrassed?
Or what?
Huh?
She found a way to flip this one on me.
Uh. Who, me?
Embarrassed? No way.
Hmm?
I think you are.
It's just good to have in case something happens.
If what happens?
I dunno something.
So who else did you ask?
I'm not the only one, am I?
Nah.
So far Kimura and Takao.
And Nakai.
That's all?
It's only been a day.
Yeah, yeah, I'm sure you've figured it out by now.
You're the first girl I've asked, whatever!
Just hurry up and give it already, this is killing me!
So what?
Do you want to message me?
Of course not!
I just want your stupid contact info,
so I can tease you when we're not at school!
It has nothing to do with wanting to talk to you!
Seriously!
That's all!
It's nothing weird, I swear!
I knew it had to be something like that.
Well, your plan to tease me has been thoroughly crushed.
Do you still want my email?
Yeah.
To make up for teasing me.
Help me clean up next week when I'm on day duty.
I didn't tease you, though!
I was going to tease you!
Well, yeah.
But if I hadn't found out, you would have eventually.
Y-Yeah.
Then it's a deal.
I'll talk to you soon.
When I get home.
She'll talk to me when she gets home?
Does that mean she's gonna
tease me when I'm at home too?
I wish I had a cell phone.
But I asked my mom if I could get one yesterday
and she said I was too young to have a phone.
Of course, she'll say no when
you ask her out of the blue.
You do say things out of the blue a lot.
Hey, that's not true!
For your information, I've wanted one forevs.
How long is "forevs"?
Umm...
If I had to put it into words,
a week?
So in not-Mina time, it's been three days, give or take?
Either way, that's still way too sudden.
Dude what's up with that picture?
It's ridiculous!
So dumb!
It's Super Ponpoko!
Pon, pon, Po-pon, pon! Pon, pon, Po-pon, pon!
But there's no denying a lot
of kids have them these days.
I guess I kinda want one, too.
I know, right?
I wish we all had 'em!
We should totally all bug our
moms till they buy 'em for us!
You want one too, right, Sanae?
No. Not really.
What?
Why the heck not?
We could message each other and stuff!
Because, hold on,
I have one.
What? How did that happen?
Sometimes I get home late from my club,
so my parents wanted me to have it.
That makes sense.
Still, you should have told us when you got it.
I know!
If I tell my parents Sanae has
one, maybe they'll buy one for me!
Hey. That's not a bad idea.
I'll do the same thing.
This time my mom'll agree for sure!
Then I can get a group chat going!
And I can download tons of games
and play them until I fall asleep!
Group chats are the worst
That childish attitude is why your
parents don't wanna get you one.
I'm not childish!
Hit me with a scary story!
What, you think not getting
scared means you're not childish?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah. So what? It's true!
Just tell me one, okay?
Late one night.
You get a call from an unknown number on your new phone.
You answer it and hear something soft.
A faint groaning of some sort.
You quickly hit "end call,"
and never hear from that number again.
That's goo--
But you're just so curious, you have to call back.
Why?
But this time,
you hear nothing on the other end of the line.
What a relief.
At the end of the month.
You look at your phone bill and
find a hundred thousand yen charge.
If that happened my parents would kill me!
You're gonna kill me if you keep screaming like that!
Huh? Good morning, Nishikata.
Hey. Morning.
I see you decided to keep your promise.
I appreciate that.
Well, yeah.
Let me help.
Sure, thank you.
You're looking tired today.
Really?
Guess so.
Were you up late again?
Watching a recording of 100% Unrequited Love ?
Huh? No!
Really?
What was it, then?
Nothing worth mentioning.
Were you messaging some of your friends?
Uh. Kinda.
What about?
That's weird.
It's unusual for her to pry into something this much.
Wait a second.
Fun, right?
I mean, messaging your friends when
you get your very first cell phone.
Honestly, I was hooked when I got mine, too.
And then before you know it,
you end up getting in trouble for doing it too much.
Takagi messaged someone enough times to get in trouble?
Who does she know that well?
Oh yeah?
With a girl from class I assume?
Nope.
Calm down.
She's tricked you with something like this before.
The last time I rode on the back of someone's bike.
I was riding with my dad.
I know!
Was it your dad?
Why would I get in trouble for texting my dad?
Touché.
Curious?
Not really.
If you tell me what you chat about with the boys,
I'll tell you who I was talking about.
Sound like a deal?
I don't care that much.
Wait...
I can kill two birds with one stone.
Sorry about this, but your fun stops here, Takagi.
Actually, yesterday we were sharing videos.
Mostly funny ones,
but there were a couple others mixed in.
Hmm?
Like what?
Yes, yes, by all means, keep taking the bait.
I'll send her that link that Kimura sent me.
It's thanks to this goat
I didn't sleep well last night.
Did you send me something?
Yeah.
It's a video of a cute animal
someone sent me last night.
It's not some pervy site, right?
Of course not!
Huh...
Let's see then.
It's so scary that you'll be at a loss for words!
Just give it a second.
Nishikata?
Yeah? What's up?
Do you like this stuff?
Like, do you look at it all the time?
Huh? Huh?!
Whoa, whoa, hold on, why is that on your phone?
What even is that?
It's definitely not what I sent you, is it?
Nope. Just thought I'd ask.
Huh?!
Now then, let's take a look-see at what you sent.
'Kay?
This is pathetic, she got me again!
Huh? It is an animal video.
Aww.
He's kinda cute.
Is he a goat?
Good, good, she's let her guard down.
Here comes the fun part.
That's it! That's the part!
Cower in fear, Takagi!
Oh. Scary.
Huh?!
Yeah. It is, right?
Crazy scary.
Yeah, then again.
It's not that scary when you watch it in the morning.
I'll give her that.
Huh... So this is what you guys talk about.
Boys are into such weird things.
So I held up my end.
What did you talk about with who exactly?
Mmm...
Just the usual stuff.
That doesn't answer the question, and you know it!
It doesn't?
Well, I talk with someone that starts with "Kuh."
Heh.
That's your clue.
"Kuh"?
Like, Kaede?
Wrong.
After that, is "zih."
Kuh-zih?
Kazi?
Wait, Kazi?
That boy?
No, it's not Kazi, either.
But the last bit is "in."
Kuh-zih-in?
What?
Ninety-seven.
Ninety-eight.
Ninety-nine!
Freakin' Takagi.
I really thought I'd be able to
get back at her for once, today.
But somehow, she outplayed me yet again.
No.
The day's not over yet.
It didn't work in the morning,
but I bet it will at night.
There's an even scarier video Kimura
told me about after school today.
Since it's scary, I haven't watched it myself.
But this will surely freak her ou--
How does she always know?
Why do I get the feeling
I'm gonna have to do more push-ups after this call?
Hello? Nishikata?
Yeah?
I was thinking it's about time.
Uh. About time for what?
For you to send me a scary video.
Huh? I dunno what you're talking about.
Huh?
Get real, Takagi.
You think I'm gonna reveal my plan just like that?
This battle is far from over--
Just you wait until after we get off the phone.
Huh?!
That's what you were thinking.
What? No. Not me, I wasn't.
Really?
Yes, of course, really.
Then, are you going to go to sleep soon?
Uh, yeah. Probably.
I see.
I was just about to do that, too.
Oh. Cool.
This feels kind of weird.
Huh?
I don't think we've ever talked
to each other at night before.
Kind of makes my heart flutter.
See you tomorrow, then.
Good night.
Yeah.
G'night to you, too.
Nishikata?
Yeah?
You haven't hung up yet.
Why not?
I dunno, I think you should hang up first.
I called you.
So you're supposed to hang up.
And why's that?
Okay, okay, on the count of three.
We'll both hang up.
One, two...
Liar.
C'mon, you didn't hang up either!
Man. Two nights in a row I can't sleep.
Those cats are fighting.
Give me like two minutes, Takagi!
What are you doing?
Good. Just like that.
Stay put right there for me, kitty-cats.
Yes, that's perfect!
Great. Add that to my collection of blurry photos.
What's with you?
Into photography now?
No, not particularly.
I'm just competing with the guys to
see who can take the best picture.
Has anyone already taken the lead?
Yeah, Kimura's unbeatable with this.
Whoa!
Gotta admire the commitment.
Funny pictures are great.
Mm-hmm.
Wait! I've got an idea!
Let me take a picture of that funny face you do!
Huh?
That can totally beat Super Ponpoko!
Help me out!
Hmmm...
I'll agree on the condition that
you do anything I ask of you.
Huh? What kind of "anything"?
The word pretty much covers it all.
Scary!
She has what it takes for me to win, but...
Oh. By the way...
That's the one!
I did the face.
That was your chance.
Wait! Do it again!
No can do.
No, it's okay.
I know her.
She enjoys this too much.
She'll want to do it again!
I'll just act as though I'm upset to lead her on.
Hey, guess what?
I knew it!
Here's my chance!
Really?
You had a toy snake on you?
That's a great picture.
Huh!? Wait, you took my picture?!
Hey! Delete that!
No way!
It's too good!
If you do anything I ask,
then I'll delete it for you.
Come on, Takagi!
That was a cheap shot, and you know it!
Wow. I got such a great picture.
Do you wanna see it?
No, I definitely don't.
Just look!
You had burst mode on?
Cool, huh?
The way your face changes?
Takagi, you're the worst!
I know!
I'll take a picture of her laughing with
her mouth hanging wide open, just like that!
That'll teach her!
Do I look okay?
Well, we're even now.
We're not even close to even!
If you want me to delete this shot,
then you gotta delete yours, too.
Nuh-uh.
I'll keep it.
So you don't have to delete my picture, either.
Wait.
But that's not the point.
Well, see ya.
Yeah.
She had fun.
But I didn't get a single
funny picture to show the guys.
Hey, Nishikata?
Do me a favor, and don't show my picture to anyone.
It's embarrassing.
Yeah, right.
Like I could show this to anyone!
What would people say about me having a photo like this?
It's not worth keeping!
Better delete it.
She did say it's embarrassing.
So maybe I can use it for some
kind of blackmail one day.
Might as well keep it.
"Cell Phone"
"Horror"
"Picture"