Forget the test!
I'm gonna die if I have to study any longer!
I'm hitting' the arcade.
Well, we can't let you go alone!
Hey, Nishikata, are you coming'?
I don't know about you,
but when I study for too long, it just doesn't stick.
Uhh.
Sorry, I think I'm gonna stay.
You've made your choice!
Later!
What are you guys gonna play?
Whichever gets me one of those cute figures.
Man.
I'm jealous.
But I can't think about them.
I have to get a good grade on my next test!
Or else!
Hey.
Can I sit here?
Studying for the test?
Yeah. I am.
I just saw your friends leaving as I came in.
Yeah.
We were all studying together for a while.
Ahh...
Well I heard them talking,
and I figured they were on their way to the arcade.
Are you not going with them?
I don't have time to play around like they do.
If I don't score within the top
fifty of my grade on this test.
My parents are taking away my video games.
Huuuh.
I see.
Oh, no!
Why am I telling her everything?
Now that she knows, she's totally
gonna distract me from studying!
Nice going, me.
I.. was just kidding?
About what?
Ugh. Forget it.
Anyway, don't interrupt me this time.
That's mean.
You say that like I'm always getting in your way.
That's because you are!
Well, yeah. It's 'cuz it's so
fun to tease you, Nishikata!
Should I study somewhere else?
No, if I did that, I'd basically be letting her win.
I just realized.
You're not studying?
Nope.
I like to limit myself to two hours of studying a day.
Oh.
I shouldn't be surprised.
She easily scores in the top
ten of our grade all the time.
But, what does she have up her sleeve?
This is Takagi we're talking about.
She's definitely gonna try to mess with me.
I mean, how could she not?
It's practically in her blood!
Hmm? What's up?
Huh? Oh, nothing, just thinking.
It's not like I was looking at you.
I just kinda spaced out--
By the way, you got that one wrong.
Problem six, where it says, "Solve for x
over negative two plus three y." That one.
You mean it's not 15?
Mm-hmm.
What? Really?
Substitute the numbers.
Was that wrong?
No. So then...
Here we go.
Uh... What are you...?
It's easier to teach you this way.
So, x equals negative 16...
"Easier to."
She's teaching me?
What is she planning?
Write it out. Go ahead.
There's a negative times a negative
and don't forget order of operations.
It's "PEMDAS" remember?
Oh yeah!
Then let's see.
It's five!
Yep. That's right!
Oh! And for these next ones, you should be able...
She's amazing.
She can figure it out with just a glance.
Hey. I appreciate this.
I was really struggling with this page before.
Why don't I teach you from the beginning?
She's gonna teach me the whole thing?
I'm saved!
No, something's fishy here!
Why is she being so nice?
She's never this nice unless she's teasing me!
Hey, Takagi.
Why are you being so nice to me today?
Hmm?
What do you mean?
Well, you're just being kinder than usual.
So...
Oh... Right.
I am always teasing you in the middle of class.
I would feel really bad if your
grades went down because of me.
Nishikata.
I'm sorry for teasing you every single day.
Let me help you get a better grade.
Takagi.
I don't believe it.
You've finally seen the error in your ways!
All right, let's go for it!
Thanks for the juice.
No, thank you.
I made huge progress on my math
today, because I had your help.
Now I'm less likely to have my games taken away.
Maybe Takagi is actually a good person, after all.
Really.
Thank you so much for today.
Oh, no.
You shouldn't thank me.
Since what I taught you, won't be on the test.
Wha... Hey! Hold on!
You're good at substitution now, right?
Yeah, and a lot of good that'll do!
Gimme back that juice right now!
Oops, I already opened it.
You literally just opened it!
Pass your answer sheets forward.
I think I did pretty well.
I should've gotten a 90 at least.
Hey, Yukari?
Can you teach me this?
I just can't seem to do well in English.
Huh? You make it sound like
you're good at everything else.
No, I'm just extra bad at English!
Anyway!
Help me out here!
In this part--
Sorry, no can do.
I want to review before the next test, too.
Huh?! But you always help me study between tests!
This time is different.
If I can get a 90 or above on everything,
my parents are buying me any game I want.
Cool. So this part's been really tripping me up.
Were you listening?
I don't have the time to teach
you guys this stuff last minute.
Meanie!
Buzz off. Shoo.
What's more important?
Our friendship or some stupid game?
Yeah, what she said.
Sure you can play video games,
but you can't teach them like you can your best friends!
Yeah, what she said.
Now that those two academic train wrecks
will leave me alone, I should review.
All right, I'm handing out the next test.
Take one and pass it back.
Okay, I've thoroughly reviewed the
material right before the test.
Now that I've got English fresh in the
brain, this'll be a--
Math?
Here.
Did you study at all this time?
Next.
Saitou.
You're looking nervous over there.
No, I'm not.
Takagi.
Yes!
You did very well, as usual.
She's so smart.
Sounds like you did fine Takagi.
Can we compare answers later?
Sure.
So.
You get a good grade?
Yeah, but not a hundred percent.
That sounds about right.
But I got this one in the bag, too.
Next up, Nishikata!
Right!
You can do a little better next time.
Was it that bad?
As if you care at all!
You're the one who taught me
stuff that wasn't on the test!
All up on your high horse because you got a good score!
Whatever!
Hey. Hey!
Guess my score.
And I'll guess yours.
Whoever gets closer will win.
You're always proposing this stuff out of nowhere.
But okay.
Uh... Is it around 50?
Hmph!
You underestimate me too much, Takagi.
You think so?
Okay, then did you get above 60 percent?
I'll take that as a no.
How did she know?
Give her your poker face.
Confuse her with your world
class, unwavering poker face!
Did you get above 55?
That's a yes.
Why?
That leaves everything between 55 and 59.
I have to keep her from guessing the exact score!
Okay, then.
Fifty-six?
Or...
Fifty-seven?
Fifty-eight?
Fifty-nine?
Yup.
I got it.
You got a 56.
Uhh. Is that the answer you're going with?
Mm-hmm.
Ready to know the truth?
I got a 59!
Sucks to be you!
I guess you were sorta close, though.
Hey, quiet down.
The only thing that sucks is your grade.
You're right; I'm sorry.
Fifty-nine, huh?
Looks like I was off by three.
All right.
Now it's your turn to try and guess my score okay?
If it's within two percent.
Then you're the winner.
Bring it on!
I'm gonna figure it out based on her reactions.
The teacher praised her a second ago,
so I bet that means she got above a 90.
Is it... like, a 92?
Uh...
Huh?
What kinda reaction was that?
How about a 95?
Ninety?
Or was it 92?
Uh...
She is so faking it!
I'm not gonna fall for that!
She'd never make her reaction so obvious!
She's mocking me.
I'm gonna do everything within my power to win this!
Maybe if I focus more on her expression.
What? What's wrong?
Hmm? Oh, nothing.
I was just thinking about something.
We've been staring at each other for a long time.
Why are you turning away?
Aww come on, that was a cheap shot!
I can't look at you after you say that!
Think. Just think.
Anything that could clue you in.
That reaction she gave me
before was so fake it's painful,
which means she probably wants me to think she got a 92.
That also means it won't be between 90 and 94
because they're all within a two point difference of 92!
And like I thought before, the teacher
praised her so it must be above 90 percent.
And she said it wasn't 100,
so that means it's gotta be between 95 and 99!
Perfect.
Flawless victory!
Takagi.
I know what grade you got on the test.
You scored a 97 percent!
Wrong. I got a 92.
Wha?! Come on!
You really don't trust me enough.
I guess I gave you that three-point
handicap for nothing, huh?
Coast is clear.
Find everything okay?
Four hundred and twenty yen is your total.
You're quick with that exact change.
Want a cov--?
No, thank you.
A bag--?
A rece--? -- No, thank you.
Operation successful.
Now to begin phase two: Get home and read it!
Oh hey.
Good morning.
Takagi?
What is she doing here?
I'm taking a walk.
Did she just read my mind?
What are you doing here all by yourself?
This is bad!
I can't let her see what I just bought.
I'll have to deny it all the way to my grave.
Oh, nothing.
It's just that I wanted to buy a
book, but they were sold out--
Wait, wait!
What if she saw me at the register?
Reel it in!
So I decided to buy Fierce!!
Ultimate Soccer!! volume eleven instead!
The perfect answer!
Boys love that series, but I've never
met a girl who'd give it the time of day.
You won't care to ask more about it.
I'm on a roll today.
Fierce-Soccer ? Cool, let me see!
Huh?!
Uh, but I haven't read it yet.
Can I at least see the front cover?
No!
'Cuz I haven't had a chance to look at it yet, either.
And it's my manga.
Then, let's look at it together.
I happen to like looking at it alone.
Awww...
I wouldn't have thought she'd be this interested.
At this rate, she's gonna blow my cover.
Better get away from her and quick.
I'll see you around, Takagi.
Huh?
Hello?
Hey, we ran into each other.
Let's walk together.
Okay, fine.
It's pretty unusual to run into someone at the
bookstore so far from home this early in the morning.
I can't let Takagi see this manga and yet here it
is, three feet from her in my backpack!
I feel like my heart's in my throat.
I wish I were home already.
Hey.
Nishikata.
Are you lying to me about anything?
Are you lying?
Uh, um...
You didn't buy Fierce-Soccer, did you?
I bet you bought something that you're so
embarrassed to have, you had to lie about it.
Shut up.
That's not...
It's just some manga for girls, right?
100% Unrequited Love ?
Okay. There's no point in denying it now, but...
...how in the world did you figure it out?
Just luck.
I happened to be passing by when I
saw you at the register checking out.
And I could see what you got.
She knew the whole time and was playing me.
Is it because you like the anime?
I didn't know you read that kind of stuff.
Uh, wait up!
Please keep it a secret,
I really don't want anyone to know.
Catching it on TV is one thing, but if people found
out I'm actually buying and reading the manga,
I'll be a laughingstock.
Hmm...
What should I do?
I mean, you did lie to me.
And that's extra bad,
considering I've never lied to you before.
But I won't tell.
Huh? You're messing with me.
What do you mean?
I'm serious.
Please don't tell anyone!
Yes, sir!
Why are you so enthusiastic?
It feels fake!
You're so persistent.
Uh... Then how about this?
I know your secret,
so it's only fair that I tell you mine, too.
That'll make you feel better, right?
Since you'll have collateral.
Huh?
I guess.
All right.
Come closer.
Okay.
Truth is I've always kind of liked you.
Huh?
Huh?! What did she--?
What?
You're bright red!
You blush so quickly.
It's classic.
Since you lied to me at the bookstore.
I figured I'd lie to you as payback.
Oh, a lie.
You shocked me for a second.
That was a lie.
Of course it was. Duh, right?
See yah!
I'm turning this way now.
"Duh," right.
I'll see you later, bye.
A lie, huh?
Oh, and Nishikata?
I want to read 100% Unrequited Love too,
so let me know when you're done and I'll borrow it!
Ahh! Don't say it so loud, Takagi!
This downpour came out of nowhere.
I wonder if it'll stop soon.
Hmm...
Well, I hope so.
Aww. Even my socks got wet.
How about you? Are you dry?
Oh man, I can kinda see through her shirt.
You hear me?
Uh. Yeah, I heard you.
Yeah.
Calm down, just calm down!
If she realizes I'm panicking,
I'll be branded a pervert!
Boy, I sure hope this rain will stop soon.
I wanna be home before five,
so I can catch an anime that's on then.
It's Fierce-Soccer , by the way.
Oh yeah?
That's the one you bought at the bookstore, right?
Or no, I'm mistaken. That's 100% Unrequited Love.
You promised me you were never
going to bring that up again!
What, I can't talk about it?
You know your own secret.
I hope this clears up fast.
Uhh. Yeah.
Aw man.
This got a little wet, too.
Hey, do you have your P.E. shirt on you?
Uh. Yeah, why?
Do you mind if I borrow it?
I'll give it back.
I want to change out of this.
Huh? Wait, what?
You want to change into my P.E. shirt?
Like, right here?
Yup. My shirt's wet; I feel all gross.
But aren't you--?
And besides, I know you're having
trouble deciding where to look.
Busted.
Can you turn the other way?
Y-Yeah.
You managed to stay pretty dry, huh?
How? Oh.
Did you use your bag as an umbrella?
Mm-hmm.
Good thinking.
I had to hold my bike, so I couldn't do that.
Yeah, that makes sense.
You know, you can look if you want.
Huh? I can look?
What are you trying to say?
Because I'm done changing.
Why are you so flustered?
She's screwing with me.
Hey.
Wanna make a bet?
We can bet on whether or not the rain will
stop by the time the town clock strikes five.
The loser has to do anything the winner wants.
Why not?
Okay, what's your bet?
That it won't stop in time.
Cool.
Then I bet it will.
If the rain stops,
I can go home and watch Fierce-Soccer.
If it doesn't, I get to order Takagi around.
It's win-win!
There we go.
I feel much better now that I've changed my shirt.
Thanks a bunch, Nishikata.
Yeah, don't mention it.
It does smell kinda sweaty, though.
Of course it does, it's been super-hot out!
Whoa.
That shirt touched my skin and now it's touching hers.
Agh! Stop it! What am I thinking?
--A cat. -- Oh. Hey.
Are you trying to get out of the rain?
Come here.
He's cute, but be careful.
He scratches.
Do you want me to give you your shirt back?
No. I'm fine.
Why don't you wear my P.E. shirt?
Huh?
It did get a little wet,
but it's better than what you've got on.
And now,
The shirt that touched Takagi's
skin will be touching mine.
Are you done yet?
Come on, you're not supposed to look!
For some reason this feels naughty.
It smells good.
I guess I win.
What should I make you do?
Oh, well.
At least, Fierce-Soccer 'll be on when I get home.
I'll do what she wants and hurry back.
Oh, I know!
Huh?
Now that it's stopped raining,
let's go somewhere before we head home.
Wait, I wanted to--
The bet was, the loser does what the winner wants!
Let's go.
Why?!
"Studying for the Test"
"Test"
"Test Results"
"Bookstore"
"Shelter from the Rain"