A brand new issue.
Day-one purchase.
Here you go.
Thanks, Mom.
I have a few stores I want to browse,
so let's meet back here when you're done.
Gotcha.
And don't get anything too showy, okay?
I won't.
Thank you, come again.
Volume five of 100% Unrequited Love !
I wonder what type I should try on first.
Hmm...
Actually, what type does he like?
I can't wait to get home and read this cover to cover!
Nishikata!
What are you doing here?
Uh, shopping?
Same as you.
Again?
Why does she always have to show
up at the worst possible time?
I swear, she's gotta be following me or something!
No.
Now's not the time to think about that.
I need to focus my energy into making
sure she doesn't find out what I bought.
Anyway, I saw you leaving the bookstore.
Here it comes!
Gotta think quick!
Did you buy something--?
So you're shopping? That's cool! Whatcha getting?
That was too close a call.
I hope changing the subject is
enough to get out of this alive.
Mainly, a bathing suit.
A bathing suit?
Are you blushing?
No, it's just hot in here!
Hey.
What kind of girl's bathing
suit do you think looks best?
Uh, what kind of...? Why you asking me?
I-I don't know, they're all probably fine.
You've seen 'em all?
You're quite the connoisseur.
No, you don't get it!
I mean that I couldn't care less!
I'm not some expert!
Hot in here?
Yes, it's hot in here.
Typical. Of course, she messes with
me the second we bump into each other.
All right, I'm gonna go home now.
'Kay.
At least, I was able to hide the manga from her.
You just bought the new volume
of Unrequited Love, right?
Could I borrow it?
I was so close!
Was she watching me?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You don't? Was I wrong?
Hey, wait.
There's no way she could have seen from
outside with the register where it is.
She's bluffing.
Dodged a bullet there.
Yeah, totally wrong.
You couldn't be more off.
Oh yeah?
Then what did you buy?
Uh, Robot Zombie ?
Yeah, sure, whatever, that!
It's like, the last thing a girl would be interested in!
It's way too ridiculous!
Yeah, right.
You bought Unrequited Love, didn't you?
Yup! Sure did!
Gah!
N-No.
Let me see it, then.
Man. She backed me into a corner again.
This is what always happens.
No matter what I do,
I can never beat Takagi at her own game.
Wait, I take that back.
Okay, but first, shall we make a bet?
Hmm?
We can bet on whether or not the book
I bought is 100% Unrequited Love.
I say our usual condition applies.
If you're wrong, you have to do whatever I tell you to.
Fine with me.
And if I get it right, then you do whatever I want.
Yeah, okay.
So, then what is it you think I purchased?
Heh.
It's all in the presentation.
It's your move, Takagi.
I'm sure my level of confidence will
have you second guessing yourself.
Huh?
Nishikata sounds so much more confident than normal.
Maybe it's actually not 100% Unrequited Love !
Oh yeah. If she's gonna find out anyway,
I might as well teach her a lesson in the process.
Think you can just get me like that again?
Nuh-uh. I've learned.
Know what?
I'm gonna bet that it's Unrequited Love.
Huh?
Y-You sure about that?
Mm-hmm.
Let's see it.
Awesome!
I got it right!
I don't know how she saw through me that time.
I should just go home and read this.
That'll make me feel better.
Ugh. I'll see yah around.
Where do you think you're going?
Help me out.
I need a bathing suit.
We said if I won.
I'd get to tell you what to do, didn't we?
I have to help her pick one?
Hot in here?
Yes, it's still hot!
Which one do you like most?
Uh. They all look nice to me.
Will you actually look and pick one?
You did lose our bet.
I don't think she realizes what she's asking of me.
It's embarrassing just being here!
I can't look directly at the bathing suits!
Oh. Check it out.
What do you think of this one?
I guess I just have to pick one
if I want to get this over with.
I-I think that one's nice.
Oh?
In that case, I might as well try it on.
Huh?
Stay right there.
I'll only be a minute.
What am I doing?
How did I end up in this situation?
Right now, just beyond that curtain.
Takagi is taking off her...
How's it look?
I dunno, fine?
That's all?
I'll try on another, then.
You mean you're not done?
Until you tell me I look good in one.
No, I'm not.
Huh? Tell her she looks good?
That's way too embarrassing for me to say!
Hey, Nishikata.
Sorry, can you hand me that bathing suit?
Huh?!
The yellow one I was looking at.
She's covering herself, does that mean?
It's to the left of that one.
Uh-huh, that's it.
Just a few feet to my right.
She's totally naked.
Sorry again.
Thanks a bunch.
Oh, gimme a break!
That was totally on purpose!
But forget that, I need to get out
of this store as soon as possible.
If someone from school sees me here with Takagi,
I'll never hear the end of it.
Wow, there are so many!
All right! How's this one?
Uh.
Oh. Hi, Takagi!
Hey, Mano!
Hey, Nakai.
Uh, hey, what's going' on?
You're here to get a bathing suit?
Yeah, I assume that's why you're here, too?
Ow...
Hey, Mano, it's embarrassing being here.
Can we hurry it up already?
Wha?! We've barely been here five minutes!
If I rush, I might miss something I'd really like!
Hmm?
How 'bout we come back later?
What? But you said--
It doesn't matter.
See you later, Takagi!
'Kay!
Don't worry, the coast is clear.
They're gone.
Oh. Is that so?
You get so shy sometimes
What do you mean?
No I don't.
Well then.
Back to trying on more, I assume.
We should probably hurry up and pick one of these out.
Otherwise, you'll die of embarrassment.
Oh, shut up. I'm fine.
So...
...which of these do you like better?
Uh. I dunno, whichever you like, I guess?
Then how about this one here?
Think this one's good?
Uh-huh.
I keep coming back to this pink one.
Do you think it's good too?
Uh-huh.
And this one-piece?
Mm-hm.
Wanna go swimming together sometime?
Uh-huh.
It's a date.
Okay.
I'll buy you something to drink later.
You're burning up again.
Yeah, I mean, it is super-hot in here!
They should really fix the air conditioning!
The ocean!
We swimming' or what?
Of course we are, come on!
Water.
We got the waves!
We got the sun!
We got the seaweed.
Stop Sanae. It's all gross and slimy!
What are you doing, Yukari?
What does it look like I'm doing?
I'm pumping air into this.
But we're at the beach.
You should at least go for a swim, first.
I wouldn't be doing this if I
could just jump in the water.
Ah! What, you can't swim?
You do sit out during swim lessons.
Though you'd probably learn if you didn't.
Whatever.
Just go have fun, I'll be there soon.
Shoo. Shoo.
Ah! That was fun, but I'm wiped!
Yeah, let's take a break for now.
Huh?
What happened?
You okay, Yukari?
Yeah, I'm okay.
But I managed to break the pump somehow.
So I was blowing it up on my own, and I got winded.
Man, Yukari, do you ever have
fun, or do you just suffer?
You don't know my life!
And just for that, I'm not gonna
help you with your homework anymore!
Hope you can do it on your own!
You what?
But I can't!
Please have mercy!
I won't make fun of you anymore!
Crying won't get you anywhere.
Nishikata, are you making
progress on your summer homework?
Uh...
Yeah.
I guess you could say that.
Oh?
Hey, wanna do our homework together?
Uh. Yeah, sure, that's cool.
But I have plans in the afternoon.
That's fine.
Let's just work on it until noon.
You can copy my answers.
Huh?
Okay, then where should we do it?
At the library?
Or, wait. We wouldn't have very
much time to get our stuff, then.
You're over-thinking this.
We could just go over to your house.
What is my life?
Out of nowhere, Takagi,
a girl is coming to my room!
Are we going in?
Sorry. Spaced out for a sec.
This place is nice.
You don't have to be polite.
My parents aren't here anyway.
This feels like a dream.
Is this a dream?
Takagi is actually in my room.
It feels so surreal.
What's wrong?
You spaced out again.
Oh.
It's nothing!
Hey!
It's your favorite girl's manga!
Aww, you found me! Squeal!
You have every volume!
Huh?!
Don't touch that!
S-Sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
Well, you know, because we were just so--
You like this, right?
If you like something, you should just admit it.
What does she mean?
"This" as in her being in my room?
How am I supposed to respond to that?
Maybe this is a dream after all!
100% Unrequited Love.
You do like it, right?
There's really no need to hide it.
That's what she was talking about?
Now that I've had a chance to look around,
this room just screams "you."
Is that supposed to be a compliment?
Hmm...
No, not exactly.
But either way, I like it.
W-Want to start our homework?
Read my mind!
Oh right.
But I only have one desk.
Do you have a folding table or something?
Yeah, but they're all being used in different rooms.
Too bad.
Then should we sit in the same chair?
Uh...
Huh?!
I'm just messing around.
Oh, I know.
We could use your bed.
Uh. Um.
Move this.
And we've basically got one big desk right here!
You okay?
Oh, yeah, I'm fine.
Good idea.
Ohh?
What's the problem?
Lay off.
No problem.
Come on.
Let's start.
Wait, I'm sitting there, too?
So, hey, uh...
Remember what you said about your answers?
Of course, they are right here.
Awesome, thanks a ton!
Though, I only grabbed these.
Kanji writing drills.
That's so not fair; you tricked me!
No, I didn't.
That's enough.
Let's work.
Wait.
If we're just practicing kanji,
was there ever any reason to do our homework together?
Oh no! I saw this exact thing on 100% Unrequited Love !
Jeez. I don't know why I have to make
curry with this jerk of all people!
He makes me so mad!
Um. You can let go of my hand now.
Why would I want to do something like that?
C'mere.
Let me see that face.
Squeal!
I can't do that!
You can use it.
It is your eraser, after all.
That's my bad.
Uh. Okay.
Your hand.
Sorry!
You want something' to drink?
Like tea?
You want tea?
Mm-hmm.
Coming' right up!
Thanks for having me.
All she did was mess with me.
I think.
Bye!
I'll come again.
Huh?
She'll come again?
Maybe... I should clean my room.
"Shopping"
"Bathing Suit"
"Ocean"
"Room"