( Overlapping chatter,
laughter )
Blue fire: I can’t believe
what i’m hearing.
We’re here to ask
a bunch of criminals for help?
There’s no way
the association approved this!
Sitch: But they have!
We’re in a crisis,
one mankind will never overcome
unless we band together
and unite as one!
Our current heroes,
comprised of 390 class cs,
101 class bs, 38 class as,
and the 17 of class s,
are clearly not enough!
No one expects you
to work for free.
You will be compensated
for every individual monster
you defeat!
Heavy tank loincloth:
Compensated?! That’s madness!
The association is putting
their faith in this trash
to help the world?
Criminal: And what
makes you so special?
I’ve killed more people
than you’ve met, Mr. Hero.
Wanna try me?
Heavy tank loincloth:
These little wimps...
( Criminal groans )
Heavy tank loincloth:
Have no heart at all.
- ( Garou chuckles )
- Sitch: Listen. We have no--
garou: Well, now, look at this.
Color me impressed.
She’s good.
Her prophecy’s spot-on.
She knew a god-level threat
like no one had ever seen
was on its way.
But meathead there’s
got a point.
All of these nobodies combined
wouldn’t be enough
to take me down.
Sitch: Huh?
Tell me, who are you?
Garou: The name’s garou.
Wrecked a ton
of so-called tough guys,
and I guess you could say
i’ve got a thing for monsters.
Want a demonstration?
Come at me,
and i’ll take you all down.
Let’s find out
who’s the strongest in here.
Now don’t make me wait all day.
Bring it on.
- Sitch: Cease this foolishness.
- Garou: Foolishness?
Sitch: We don’t need you.
Get lost.
Garou: I can’t believe
you treat your guests this way,
Mr. Big shot of justice.
Let me show you how it’s done.
Each and every coward here
is cordially invited
to a little slaughter party.
Sitch: I’ve got a job
for you three heroes.
Toss this joker out.
Magicman: With pleasure.
( Gags )
( Heavy tank loincloth roars )
Huh?
Garou: Tough break, grandpa.
Looks like you forgot to put
some heart into that punch.
The only thing
that really matters
is that the strong are strong!
Night-night, gramps!
( Criminals laugh, chatter )
Criminal #2:
Now that’s how you do it!
Criminal #3: Hell, yeah!
You showed him!
- Garou: Huh?
- Criminal #4: All right!
Garou: What are you vermin
cheering about?
You’re all gonna die, too.
Criminal #5: Wait.
What did you just say?!
Criminal #6: We’re supposed
to be on the same side here!
Garou: Not true. Heroes are
always late to the party,
while monsters
take the initiative.
They appear without warning,
out of the blue.
Listen up.
You’re on the humans’ side,
while i’m
on the monsters’ side.
Blue fire: A human
who calls himself a monster?
You’re delusional.
I’ll burn your body to ash!
( Winces )
Garou: These little tricks
certainly liven things up,
but once you see through them,
they’re ugly.
Blue fire: My arm!
Sitch: This is central tower,
seventh floor multipurpose hall.
Send every hero in the facility
to this location immediately,
all of them!
( Gasps )
Garou: Taking on a bunch
of class-s heroes at once?
That might be
a bit much right now.
Well, i’m sure this pile
of bodies gets my point across.
Spectacular debut, huh?
Today was
my declaration of war.
In six months,
i’ll be even stronger.
I’ll be using the front door
when I return.
’til next time.
♪
♪ hero
( singing in Japanese )
♪ Go, go
♪ Hero
( singing in Japanese )
♪ Go, go
♪ Hero
( singing in Japanese )
♪ One punch
( footsteps shuffling )
Blizzard:
Are my orders understood?
Men: Yes!
Blizzard: And what
will you do if the target
shows the slightest bit
of resistance?
Wild monkey: We will physically
punish him without mercy
so he’ll never resist again.
Blizzard: Excellent.
Men: Thank you very much,
miss blizzard!
Genos: We have moved
up the ranks, master saitama.
You are now class b, rank 7,
and I am class s, rank 14.
Saitama: All I really did
was just defeat
whatever monsters I bumped into.
That’s a big boost.
Genos: It is because nowadays
monsters appear almost daily.
You defeat them, but you
do not report those victories
to the association.
Since your rank is increasing
despite that fact,
it would appear that multiple
eyewitnesses to those deeds
are reporting your work for you.
In other words,
the citizenry is watching you.
Your identity as a hero
is becoming well known, master.
I believe that,
in a very short time,
you might even have
fan clubs pop up.
Saitama: What? No way.
You don’t even have a fan club,
and you’re class s.
Genos: Actually,
I do have a fan club.
- ( Game music stops )
- Saitama: Seriously?
( Genos gasps )
High-speed object detected.
It is too fast for a human.
A monster?
Saitama: Oh, an item.
Genos: Master appears
to be preoccupied,
so I will go.
This will serve as a chance
to test my new upgrades.
Show yourself.
A human?
What do you want?
Sonic: Where’s saitama?
I obtained information
saying that he lives here.
Genos: So are you
a friend of his or something?
Sonic: We’ve met
somewhere before.
My name’s speed-o’-sound Sonic.
I’m saitama’s rival,
and i’m here
to settle the score.
Now out of my way.
Genos: Speed-o’-sound Sonic!
I recall now.
You are the pervert.
You have the audacity
to call yourself master’s rival?
How shameless.
One more step,
and you will be eliminated.
( Sonic chuckles )
Quite bold, aren’t you?
Okay, then. Just try to stop me.
- ( Game music playing )
- Saitama: There.
Wait. Oh, crap.
I overwrote king’s save.
After I may have
borrowed this without asking.
Way to go.
He’s gonna be pissed...
Big time.
( Pounding on door )
Huh?
Eyelashes: Class b, rank 7,
saitama, step outside!
Class b, rank one,
hellish blizzard
would like to have
a word with you.
Saitama: Uh, i’ve already
got a vacuum cleaner.
Eyelashes: What?
We are not salesmen!
Each of us
are heroes who outrank you!
Blizzard: How do you do,
class-b hero saitama?
My hero name
is hellish blizzard.
Perhaps you’ve heard of me
saitama: Nope,
not even once. Sorry.
Eyelashes: You’re looking
at the class b, rank one hero.
Saitama: Ah, okay, then.
Keep up the good work.
We good?
( Wild monkey gasps )
Bastard sure is cocky
eyelashes: You don’t seem like
the type who can take a hint,
so let me make
this crystal clear.
Every hero
who ascends to class b
must first properly introduce
themselves to hellish blizzard.
Saitama: Like, formally?
( Door creaks )
Fine. Hello.
My name is saitama.
What’s shakin’?
( Blizzard sighs )
I guess that’ll do.
Now, then, are you aware
of the various factions
in the hero business?
Saitama: Factions?
Blizzard: Precisely.
In this industry,
if you aren’t part of a group,
you don’t survive.
Saitama: I don’t get
what you mean.
Blizzard: I’m saying
it’s impossible
- to raise your rank alone.
- Saitama: Why?
- Blizzard: There are obstacles.
- Saitama: Like what?
Blizzard: Like rivals.
Saitama: I’m not
getting this at all,
and i’m kinda busy here, so--
blizzard: I’m not done
talking to you!
Saitama: Hmm?
Blizzard: I want you
to join our little group.
If you do, i’ll ensure you
remain in the top of class b.
Saitama: Uh...
Huh?
I get it!
So what you’re saying is,
if I refuse
to align myself with you,
you’ll stand in my way!
Do you make threats like this
to every new hero in class b,
like a gang leader?
Blizzard: No. I only make offers
to those who catch my eye.
Saitama: Are you afraid that I
might take your rank-one spot?
Look, don’t worry about it.
I’ll make class a pretty soon.
Speaking of, why haven’t you
moved on to class a?
Blizzard: I’m still waiting
for your answer.
Saitama: Obviously
the answer is no.
There shouldn’t be a cliquey
pecking order between heroes.
Blizzard:
Time to teach him a lesson!
Men: Yes!
Blizzard: Rough him up so bad
he never works as a hero again!
Wipe that smirk off his face!
( Both roar )
- ( SWAT )
- ( Both scream )
( Blizzard gasps )
Saitama: You won’t survive
like that, blizzard.
Give it up.
Blizzard: What a shame.
Guess i’ll
have to handle this myself.
( Saitama gasps )
Is this...
Telekinesis?
Blizzard: Yes, exactly.
You don’t seem surprised.
Saitama: So are you gonna fight
by flinging
rocks and stuff at me? Bad idea.
Blizzard: I will make you regret
ever choosing to mock me, fool.
I’ll kill you so bad,
you’ll beg for death.
Hellstorm!
Flesh peels away.
Bones crack.
The brutality of it all
breaks your will in an instant.
You did this to yourself.
You deserve it
for thinking you can surpass me.
No one is better than me!
All my enemies tremble befor--
saitama: You know,
for a top-ranker,
you’re kinda sensitive.
Blizzard: I’ll crush you!
Saitama: You don’t get
what it means to be a hero.
The world is chock-full
of super-strong
and pretty awful people.
Standing up to them
is what heroes do,
even if that means
doing it alone.
This whole act is pathetic.
You surround yourself
with weaklings and kiss-asses
just so you can feel
like you might be strong.
These factions,
crushing the noobs,
that ranking stuff,
none of it matters.
Show heroes some respect, poser!
Blizzard: Shut up!
You don’t know me!
You don’t know
anything about me!
( Rumbling )
♪
( Grunts )
( Yells )
Saitama: Huh?
( Steam hissing )
( Rubble clattering )
( Blizzard groans )
What happ--
genos: Hmm, how curious.
My hunt for a rat
seems to have led me
back to master’s apartment.
( Blizzard gasps )
That’s genos, a class-s.
What’s he doing here?
Genos:
Master saitama, apologies.
I kicked up some dust
around your home.
Saitama: This is a little more
than some dust, genos!
Blizzard: Uh...
Saitama: I caught a glimpse
of Sonic in the chaos.
What were the two of you doing?
Blizzard: You have connections
with class-s heroes?
Saitama: Huh?
Oh, you mean genos?
Genos: I am
master saitama’s disciple.
Blizzard: His disciple?
But you outrank him.
Genos: You are a hero, class b,
rank one, hellish blizzard.
I see what is happening.
You have targeted master saitama
as your latest
newcomer hero to crush.
But he is stronger
than anticipated,
and now you are near death
from fighting him, correct?
Saitama: Nah.
She just got caught up
in all that "dust kicking"
you were doing.
Genos: My deepest apologies
if I was the cause
- of any--
- Sonic: Exploding shuriken!
( Blizzard gasps ) A monster?
Saitama: Eh, not really.
This is gonna take a minute,
so you can go home if you want.
Genos: Hmph! You could throw
100 more of those things.
You would not harm me.
Sonic: Maybe,
but you haven’t even hit me...
Puppet-man.
Watch, saitama!
Bear witness!
After I turn your disciple
into scrap, you’re next!
Blizzard: Such intense hatred.
Even just standing there,
I can sense his extraordinary
combat ability.
He’s dangerous.
Genos: Master, this stalker’s
presence is an affront.
I will do the world a favor
and rid it of his existence.
( Sonic scoffs ) A slug like you
could never get rid of me.
You sure you still want to fight
when you’ve already shown me
all you’ve got?
Genos: When did I show you
all that I have got?
You lose, wretched fool.
Sonic: Huh? ( Gasps )
♪
Genos: Accelerate.
Saitama: Wow.
Looks like he’s
gotten a little faster
since the last
time we sparred. Huh.
Maybe it’s an upgrade.
Blizzard: I can’t see a thing.
( Punches clanking )
Sonic: Why does he
keep going behind me?
Does this cocky child
think he’s faster than me?
Genos: You had
some lint in your hair,
but I picked it out.
Sonic: You little bastard!
Genos: As predicted,
you dropped your guard.
Machine gun blows!
He dodged it?
- Wait!
- ( Sonic laughs )
What a hopeless buffoon.
You sure talk a lot
for someone
who only manages to punch air.
This master technique
uses special footwork
and my super-fast movement
to create afterimages.
It’s called fourfold funeral!
Now die. Scatter flash slash!
Genos: I cannot follow
his movement,
so I will lay waste
to this entire area.
Incineration cannons,
maximum intensity!
Blizzard: It’s done!
( Sonic gasps ) I won?
No, he dropped
before I slashed him.
What happened?
Saitama.
Trying to save your disciple?
You’re too soft.
Saitama: I’d just rather
my entire neighborhood
didn’t get blown to hell.
And, besides, the two of you
have no reason to fight.
- Hey, genos...
- ( Genos groaning )
Saitama: Were you built for
petty street fights like this?
And, Sonic,
I thought you were after me.
So, just this once,
i’m gonna
take you seriously, okay?
♪
Come at me, bro.
Sonic: I’ve been waiting
for this moment,
and, to kill you, i’ve perfected
the ultimate technique!
Prepare yourself!
Saitama: Nice. I’m hyped.
Sonic:
Ultimate master technique!
Tenfold funeral!
Genos: Ten clone afterimages?
Though a joke,
he must have trained hard.
Blizzard:
That maniac’s combat skills
are equivalent to a class-s.
A hero at saitama’s level
stands no chance against him.
Even so...
Sonic: Why do I feel
like i’m destined to lose
every single time I face you?
Until I can break that mentality
by beating you,
I will never reach
the next level.
Saitama: Killer move:
Serious series.
Serious sideways jumps!
( Sonic gags )
♪
What was that?
Saitama: I just
did some sideways jumps,
but I guess I went too far.
Sonic: He beat me
with shock waves?
My technique was meaningless.
He was faster.
I swear, next time we...
Genos: Is he dead?
Saitama: I wasn’t
trying to kill him.
Blizzard: Such power.
He’s not normal.
♪
I could never
make it to number one.
I had intelligence,
stamina, street smarts,
and I was fortunate enough
to be born an esper.
With those attributes,
I should be standing at the top.
If only it weren’t for her...
My older sister
and the world’s
most powerful esper, tornado.
Because of her,
I would never be number one
in anything my entire life.
There was no beating my sister.
So when I became class b,
rank one, I got to thinking.
If I remain in this position,
I could control
all the heroes below me
and, with them, gather
enough strength to surpass her.
Genos: That little runt--
terrible tornado
is class s, though.
Why not simply aim
for class a, rank one?
Blizzard:
That’s out of the question.
While i’d have no problem
climbing the ranks of class a,
i’d never be rank one,
not ever.
Class a, rank 4--bushi drill.
Class a, rank 3--okama itachi.
Class a, rank 2--iairon.
Even these three swordsmen,
disciples of the class-s hero
atomic samurai,
cannot progress any further.
Why can’t
these worthy heroes advance?
One hero stands in their way,
class a, rank one--amai mask.
- ( Group screaming )
- Amai mask: There you are.
The primitive savage
who was found frozen in ice
and revived
by a miracle of science.
Suppon, right?
You escaped
from the research facility
and attacked those
who tried to help you.
You are evil and a menace.
The association asked me
to bring you in alive.
However, i’m simply
not that merciful.
( Suppon growls )
( Gags )
Amai mask: Enough, already!
( Crowd cheering )
Woman: Amai mask! ( Squeals )
♪
Blizzard: The world
is a dangerous place.
It’s plagued
with unimaginable monsters.
You’re quite
the monster yourself,
but not to the level
of amai mask or my sister.
There’s king,
who they call the strongest man,
and, blast, who stands
atop the hero world.
They’re monsters
even among monsters.
When that’s our competition,
how can we advance
on our own abilities?
What’s wrong
with banding together?
Saitama:
I mean, nothing, really.
Still, I think i’ll pass
on your generous offer.
Blizzard: You think
you’re too strong for us?
Hmph! You’ll never
move up the rankings.
Just remember that I
offered you this opportunity.
( Doorbell rings )
King: Yo. Saitama here?
( Blizzard gasps )
King: Hey, dude.
Did you take my game
home with you?
Blizzard: K-k-k-k-k-king?!
Saitama: Oh. Yeah. My bad.
King: I knew it. Hand it over.
Saitama: Uh, sorry, but...
King: It’s no biggie.
Just give it back.
- Saitama: I erased your save.
- King: Wait. What?
Blizzard: Why are they talking
like they’re just friends?
Genos: Master does
not team up with others,
does not antagonize anyone,
- ignores rankings.
- Saitama: ...It was under here.
- Sorry.
- King: Nah,
don’t worry about it.
Oh, the button’s all smushed in.
Genos: Yet powerful heroes
are drawn to him.
Blizzard: If only
I were one of them.
Genos: It is because...
He is strong.
( Singing in Japanese )
♪
Man: Class s, rank 14, genos
and class b, rank 7, saitama.
So then, are we in full
agreement on their hero names?
Group: Aye!
Man: For slaying
numerous monsters
with steadfast resolve
and dauntless courage,
genos’ hero name
will be demon cyborg.
And, based on his appearance,
saitama’s name
will be caped baldy.
Man #2: Every aspiring hero
dreams of having a hero name.
I’m sure they’ll be elated
to hear theirs. ( Chuckles )
Man #3: Demon cyborg
and caped baldy.
I’m confident those two
will work even harder now.
- ( Sitch growling )
- ( Council laughing )
( Sitch scoffs )
Two hours of chitchat
about some useless nicknames,
while the discussion
on how to deal with garou
ended in 15 minutes.
Damn them
and their Rose-colored glasses.
Man #1: Are you referring
to that crazy fellow
who calls himself a monster?
No need to panic, sitch.
Man #2: Class s,
rank 3, silverfang
is already in pursuit.
I’m confident in his abilities
on matters like this.
Man #3: Yes, I think
we can trust in him.
Man #4: If need be,
tornado and blast can assist.
Man #1: He’s just a man,
sitch, nothing more.
He likely has nothing to do
with the prophecy.
Sitch: Damn it all!
Will they really be enough
to deal with garou?
- ( Whack )
- ( Hero groans )
What the hell?
Who--who the hell are you?
I’m a class-a hero,
not a criminal.
Why did you attack me?
Garou: Class a, rank 9,
tank-top vegetarian.
Because you just happened
to cross my path.
But i’m stunned
by the lack of challenge.
Tank-top vegetarian: Then I
suggest you brace yourself.
This is what happens
when you tangle with a hero.
- ( Blows lands )
- ( Groans )
Garou: Gotta say,
i’m not impressed.
I look forward to finding one
who can battle
a monster-class hero.