( Garou panting )
¶
death gatling: This will be your
last chance to surrender, garou,
- so take it.
- ( Garou scoffs )
Death gatling: Not how
you saw this ending, is it?
Well, that's just too bad,
hero hunter.
Everyone assembled here
is a veteran
who's faced death
countless times.
I personally picked
and brought in
the heroes I know are the best
just to hunt your ass down.
Garou: So they're
"the best," huh? ( Laughs )
I'm sure you're proud
of your little squad,
but I call bullshit.
I'm not even seeing
one class s here.
Doesn't the hero association
understand how dangerous I am?
These bargain-basement
do-gooders
in their Halloween costumes
are nothing but a joke.
Death gatling:
So even a criminal like you
cares only about class s.
Garou: Huh?
The class-s heroes
are worshipped.
They get paid the big bucks
by the hero association,
and they get let in
on classified information
that the rest of us
would never be privy to.
We're all heroes,
but we're not equals.
The rankings to decide
who's on top are so subjective.
So many heroes never even
get a chance to be recognized.
They may not be class s,
but this crew
is still tough as hell.
You've managed
to get all this attention
for taking out class-s heroes.
That makes you the perfect
target for proving my point!
( Garou sighs )
That explains
the lack of class s.
You guys are itching
to take all the credit.
Any kid who heard you
would be so let down.
( Gasps )
It's hard to breathe.
I feel dizzy, too.
The poison? ( Chuckles )
I heard there's
some monster association
that's kicking
your hero teeth in.
You sure a guy like me
should be your priority?
If you didn't know,
there's a hostage out there
that needs rescuing.
Death gatling:
Once we've brought you in,
we'll deal with all that.
Wherever there's
an upstart monster,
we'll be there to face it
head-on and take it out.
Garou: These guys are a test...
Each one a step
on my long and winding path
to becoming a true monster.
I'm not backing down.
Stinger:
The poison's kicking in.
Death gatling: He can't
take much more of this.
( Garou panting )
It takes one step at a time,
just one step.
¶
¶ hero
( singing in Japanese )
¶ go, go
¶ hero
( singing in Japanese )
¶ go, go
¶ hero
( singing in Japanese )
¶ one punch
boy: Did you watch
"justice man" yesterday?
Boy 2: Yeah! He finally used
a new attack, justice fire kick!
Boy 3: It was so cool!
Boy 1: Totally!
But know the best part?
Boy 2: The way crab demon died!
Boy 3: I know, right!
Remember his face
when justice man saw the egg
he was trying to hide?
( Boys laugh )
Garou: Yeah, but crab demon
almost had him.
When mach woman
and little justice joined in,
it was three on one,
but, even against those odds,
crab demon never, ever gave up!
¶
- boys: Huh?!
- Boy 1: What? For real?
You were rooting for crab demon?
Garou: He was only trying
to protect his home,
to stop pollution in the ocean.
He was standing up to
the whole world all by himself.
If he'd just been
a little stronger,
I'm sure he would have won.
I feel so sorry for him.
( Garou panting )
( Inhales )
Chain toad: Now!
Ankle noose!
Smile man:
Earth rotation of doom!
Chain toad: What's he doing?
Ribbit!
Smile man: Chain toad, no!
He's down.
Blam-blam: Be careful, y'all!
The snake's
got a blade or something!
Garou: You mean
I'm not allowed to have one?
Doesn't seem very fair.
( Inhales )
- ( Blam-blam groans )
- ( Megane gasps )
He's been hit in the leg
and poisoned,
but he's still fighting hard!
Smile man: Look out!
Wildhorn: He's mine.
Bison pile driver!
( Groans )
Megane: Keep your distance!
Wildhorn: What?! How did he...
- ( Screams )
- Shooter: Damn it!
Megane: He may have
figured out our timing,
but he's still wide open
from the front!
( Garou chuckles )
Megane: No.
Wildhorn: Put me down!
Stinger: Roar! Bamboo shoot!
- ( Gasps )
- ( Garou chuckles )
Looks like I'm halfway there.
( Megane gasps )
Smile man: Hey, death gatling,
I think he might
take us all down at this rate.
Let's forget
about taking him alive.
Death gatling: Agreed.
The hero hunter
has made his choice.
Megane: He can still move
at that speed?
He should be
completely worn out by now,
but somehow he just
keeps fighting and winning!
It's unnatural.
It definitely doesn't feel
like we're fighting a human!
Garou: Hey, stinger!
Fight me one-on-one,
you coward!
Stinger: You asked for it!
Leave this guy to me!
Smile man: No chance!
We'll face him together!
Death gatling: I'll turn him
into bone fragments.
Smile man: What the...
Garou: I honestly didn't think
- you'd be as dumb as they say.
- Stinger: You tricked me.
- Death gatling: Out of the way!
- Stinger: Huh?
Death gatling: I'll finish him.
He's too worn out
to dodge this.
( Megane gasps )
Death gatling:
You're in my line of fire!
Garou: Hey,
what's the matter, buddy?
We were so close a second ago.
It's not neighborly
to run away from me now.
I'm gonna be all lonely.
Megane: I can't shake him!
Death gatling:
Get away from him, megane!
I can't get a shot!
Megane: Our formation's
completely busted.
Does that mean
I'm just holding them back now?
( Panting )
( Eyelashes groans ) The new
guy's just holding us back.
Wild monkey: I don't want
to share the credit
for anything with him.
He sucks, miss blizzard.
Megane: I don't need credit.
You guys take it.
¶
this is it.
I'm gonna be killed.
( Gasps )
I'll never be a hero.
I'm just an ordinary guy,
and I've reached my damn limit!
Saitama: Your limit?
Who decides what your limit is?
¶
instead of overthinking
your setbacks,
just focus on moving forward.
Megane: That was the moment
I decided to remake myself,
to be like him.
I won't be used as a cover!
I'd rather fight to my last--
garou: Yeah! That's the spirit!
You got lots of stamina,
don't you?
- Stinger: No!
- Death gatling: Don't do it!
- It's a trap!
- Stinger: Maybe so,
but I can't ignore it!
Eat this!
Gigantic drill stinger!
¶
( Megane gags )
( Garou panting )
Death gatling: You took out all
your human shields, dumb-ass.
Now the friendly-fire problem
is no longer an issue.
You're dead, garou the monster!
Garou: There's a kid
inside that shack.
( Tareo gasping )
Garou: He'll get hit
if you open fire on me.
Death gatling:
Trying to talk your way out
with what is
so very obviously a lie?
( Garou inhales )
Watch this, turd!
This is the moment
the monster wins!
( Tareo gasps )
Death gatling:
The winner will be justice.
Time to die.
Death shower!
Impossible.
How could he survive that?
( Tareo shuddering )
M-Mister...
( Garou chuckles ) Only an idiot
would let loose like that.
( Death gatling grunts )
Garou: Don't bother
with the act.
I know.
That was death shower,
where you use up all your ammo.
Death gatling: He goaded me,
just like all the others.
"It turns monsters
into mincemeat
and obliterates them."
But not every monster, huh?
( Laughs )
I'm grateful. Heh.
You helped me prove that I can't
be defeated by guns or bullets.
( Death gatling gasps )
Garou: Not how you
saw this ending, is it?
( Laughs ) Too bad.
That's not how foils work.
You should've called in
some class-s heroes
like good little class as.
If even one of them
had joined you,
things might have
turned out differently.
Death gatling:
Class s can screw themselves.
You think the rest of the heroes
are just second string?
Class-s heroes are incredible,
but the rest of us fight through
blood, sweat, and death,
same as them!
Look at me!
I cornered the hero hunter,
class-a hero, death gatling!
Garou: Boy, you've got issues.
Death gatling: I will be
the one to put you down!
I'll prove that we
deserve our place!
Garou: Seems the one
most obsessed with rankings...
- ( Death gatling groans )
- Garou: Is you!
( Wind blowing )
You disgust me.
Bunch of idiots.
Tareo: M-mister...
Garou: Huh?
Oh.
You're still alive.
( Tareo gasping )
( Wailing )
Garou: Hey!
Tareo: Somebody help!
( Garou grunting )
( Panting )
Water.
Huh?
Genos: I received
a call for assistance.
From the look of things,
you are that hero hunter.
( Garou gasps )
¶
genos: You will be eliminated.
( Wind blowing )
¶
Genos: Machine gun blows!
( Garou hisses )
Fist of flowing water
crushing rock!
( Yells )
( Grunts )
Bastard. He let me bury him
to lure me in.
¶
genos: I see.
He defended himself using fist
of flowing water crushing rock.
It adds up.
This is why
the other heroes struggled.
Saitama: Boom!
Take a look at that!
You've got, like,
a millimeter of health left!
I did it! You're going down
this time for sure! ( Laughs )
Oh? Still got
some fight left, huh?
Take it easy, saitama.
Stay calm.
One more hit, and you win.
It'd take a miracle
for him to come back
at this poi--
announcer: K.O.!
( Saitama screams )
King: Nice.
I set up for a last-gasp,
come-from-behind victory.
Hope you had fun, at least.
I'm not gonna let you win,
but I will let you
get pretty close, though.
I mean, your moves
are always the same, dude.
I gave you a chance,
but all you do is button-mash.
I could beat you
with my eyes closed.
This puts us at, eh, 81 and o.
I'll loan you the console so
you can practice for next time.
( Saitama gasps )
Games stress me the hell out!
I am gonna pop!
King: If you ever win,
that'll go away.
Just keep it together.
( Buzzer vibrating )
Saitama:
Your buzzer's going off.
King: Huh?
Looks like you're right.
Saitama: Is it monsters?!
- ( Music playing )
- Let's go!
I'm ready to crack some skulls!
King: It says other class-s
heroes are already on-site.
- ( Music slowing )
- By the time we get there,
it'll probably be over.
( Saitama sighs )
King: But since we're
talking about monsters,
all the dead ones near my house
kinda freak me out.
It seems pretty unsanitary,
you know?
Saitama: Gross, but fair.
I'll have genos
incinerate them later.
I wonder, why do so many
monsters appear around here?
King: I don't know.
They're why no one lives
in this area anymore.
If monsters
start showing up everywhere
like they did yesterday,
there might end up being
more neighborhoods like mine.
So where is genos, anyway?
Saitama: I don't know. He hasn't
been home since yesterday.
King: What? You sure he's okay?
Dude, the monster association
is kind of a thing.
What if they
took him back to their lair
or something like that?
Saitama: He's probably fine.
It's genos.
Hmm.
Maybe I'll have a look around.
( Megane groaning )
A class-s showed up.
Thank goodness.
Garou: This one's strong.
His speed is insane, and he's
got tank top master's power.
He fires those incineration
cannons without hesitation.
Busted up like this,
it'll take a lot to beat him.
Damn it.
Genos: Surrender.
There is no way
that you can escape.
Garou: That's what I need.
Have to remember
the way he moved!
Genos: He has changed his style.
He is moving on all fours.
Garou: Gotcha.
You see, I've always had a knack
for taking apart
precision machinery!
Too bad for you!
( Gags )
Genos: Meaningless.
( Garou chuckles )
One hero after another.
I must have really
gotten your attention.
Was there a memo or something?
I'm stoked to be this popular.
Genos: The recent appearance
of an evil organization
has thrown the world
as we know it into chaos.
The hero association
must focus its efforts
and work as one
to deal with that threat.
We cannot waste time
on insignificant nobodies
like you.
( Garou grunts )
You think I'm a nobody?!
Then help me change that,
demon cyborg!
Once I've beaten you,
the world will know my name,
and they will fear me!
¶
I want everyone to know.
No hero is a match for me.
A monster stands before you,
stronger than anyone!
Such a creature does not exist.
Monster: Now!
- Rescue the hero hunter!
- ( Monsters growl )
Garou: What the...
Monster: The monster
association, at your service.
We're here to bring you back
with us, Mr. Garou.
You're in a pinch, right?
We can help you.
Garou: You guys again, huh?
Monster: Our superiors
say they'll offer you
an executive position.
Isn't that wonderful?
Garou: Don't want it.
Now piss off.
Monster: I'm afraid
we can't this time.
We're here
under specific orders.
( Monsters groan )
Monster: Impossible! Whaah!
Genos: I see.
So the hero hunter
is in league
with the monster association.
- Garou: Huh?
- Genos: Yesterday, I lost,
but I learned there are monsters
more powerful
than I could imagine.
Now, no matter what may come,
my guard will never
be down again.
( Garou scoffs )
Genos: Plus,
compared to yesterday,
I am much stronger.
( Garou grunts )
Genos: Master saitama
gave me guidance
and said that I should aim
for a higher level
and train my spirit.
I believe I am beginning
to understand what he meant.
I will not be
so easily defeated.
Garou: Master saitama?
Genos: My master is a warrior
who no monster
could ever hope to match.
He is a true hero.
( Garou grunts )
Genos: Incinerate.
Bang: Genos.
Genos: Bang, why?
Bang: Would you mind letting us
handle things from here?
( Genos gasps )
( Monster yells )
Bomb: Fist of whirling wind
slashing steel!
( Monster gags )
¶
( monsters gasp )
Bomb: Let me deal
with the monsters, bang.
You take garou.
Bang: My thanks, big brother.
( Knuckles crack )
Garou...
Face to face once again.
- It's been a while.
- ( Wind blows )
Garou: I know that voice.
So the world's most annoying
geezer finally made it.
Bang: I'm not sure what the hell
happened to you, garou,
but I will end it here.
Get up on your feet.
¶
garou: Are you strong, old man?
Bang: Hmm?
Sourface: Who's the kid?
Kind of rude, isn't he?
( Garou breathing heavily )
Sourface: What the hell?
Should I toss him out, master?
( Bang chuckles )
No.
When he wakes up,
give him something to eat,
as much as he likes.
¶
( garou growls )
( Roars )
Bang: Fist of flowing water
crushing rock!
¶
( singing in Japanese )