Saitama: You really think
you're hot stuff, don't you?
But today, I end you.
( Video game music playing )
Ora-ora-ora-ora-ora-ora!
Consecutive low kicks!
It's a cheese attack combo
I discovered!
- Ora-ora-ora-ora-ora!
- King: Good grief, man.
You just don't get it, do you?
Here. Let me show you...
Real cheese power.
Lovit rabbit: Hah!
( Both characters grunting )
Lovit rabbit: Take that! Yaah!
Announcer: K.O.!
Lovit rabbit:
Bunny-bunny hop hop!
- Saitama: I demand a rematch.
- ( King scoffs )
- Announcer: K.O.!
- ( Saitama stammers )
Announcer: K.O.!
- K.o.!
- ( Saitama stammers )
Lovit rabbit: Take that!
Mwah!
- Yaah!
- Announcer: K.O.!
Lovit rabbit:
Bunny-bunny hop hop!
Saitama: Crap game!
What a crap-ass game!
Huh? What's this thing?
King: Oh, that?
They gave those out
to a bunch of heroes recently.
It's still a prototype
or something.
It requests backup
and sends your location
at the touch of button.
Saitama: Why didn't I get one?
King: Huh? I don't know.
Maybe they figured
you'd have trouble using it,
you know, since it's
got buttons and everything.
Saitama: What?
We're going again.
This time, my low kicks
will be so fast,
I'll beat you for sure!
¶
¶ hero
( singing in japanese )
¶ go, go
¶ hero
( singing in japanese )
¶ go, go
¶ hero
( singing in japanese )
¶ one punch
monster:
We've received a message
from the monster assoc--
( Screams )
I said we've received a message
from the monster association.
( Man screams )
Man 2: He's been
taken over by something!
Man 3: Call in
the heroes on security!
Man 4: Emergency! This is west
building, conference room seven!
- Man 5: Should I fire?
- Man 3: Shoot it! Shoot it!
Sitch: Wait!
Let's hear the message.
Gyoro-gyoro:
Ladies and gentlemen
of the hero association,
greetings.
I am director gyoro-gyoro
of the monster association.
As I'm sure you're aware,
we have the son of one of your
high-ranking executive with us.
Sitch: What is it that you want?
Gyoro-gyoro:
We have but one demand.
We are sick and tired
of being oppressed
because we are monsters.
From this day on,
we wish to be left alone.
Right now, we eke out
a meager existence,
hiding in an abandoned area
of city z.
We seek nothing audacious.
We don't expect to lead lives
in the outside world.
Our offer is simply
to halt our conflict
with heroes and ordinary humans
and to cease entering areas
where they live.
In exchange for this gesture,
we want you to guarantee us
a safe place
to live out our lives.
All we hope for
is the birth of a society
where humans and monsters
can coexist in harmony.
Sitch: Then, why instigate
this destructive rampage?
Gyoro-gyoro: A tragic,
but necessary decision.
By demonstrating our strength,
we hoped you'd understand
the merit behind our proposal.
I'm sure we'd both like
to avoid any further losses.
Man 5: A cease-fire, huh?
That's about what we expected.
Very well.
We pledge that henceforth
the monster association
will not be targeted.
( Sitch gasps )
Man 5: Now release
the hostage immediately.
Enjoy this brief
moment of security,
you bloodsucking vermin.
As soon as that boy is safe,
you will all be extermin--
monster: Oops.
Guess my finger slipped.
Gyoro-gyoro:
Now, now, destrochloridium.
We're still negotiating here.
Destrochloridium:
I am a very, very bad boy.
Man 6: H-he's dead!
You killed him!
Sitch: Bastard! What kind of
negotiation tactic was that?!
( Gyoro-gyoro laughs )
Tricking you humans is so fun!
Humans and monsters coexisting?
What a bunch
of gullible morons!
You believed every word.
You're stupider than I thought,
and that's saying something!
Sitch: What will you do
with the hostage?
( Gasps ) Wait a minute.
You haven't--
gyoro-gyoro: I assure you
he's still alive.
The only reason
we took the hostage
was to ensure you cowards
couldn't back out.
We'll give you three days
to retrieve him.
In that time, assemble
the best the hero association
has to offer
to make up the rescue team.
My lord orochi and the members
of the monster association
eagerly await you. ( Laughing )
- Woman: It self-destructed?
- Man 3: But there's still
one left to deal with.
What's keeping the heroes?
Destrochloridium: If we're
all done talking, then...
I think it's time
to get a little freaky!
( Groans )
Blackluster: Hmm? Wait.
Was that guy the emergency?
Man 3: Oh!
Thank you, blackluster.
I'm damn glad we have someone
of your strength defending hq.
Sitch: Wait. Look there!
The other one was just a husk!
The parasite's at your feet!
Destrochloridium:
Slow-witted meat bags!
Now this class-s body
is mine for the taking!
Huh?! My feeler drills
are hard as steel!
Why aren't they cutting
straight through you?!
Damn it!
This is living tissue, right?!
( Squish )
Blackluster: What kind
of question is that?
Everyone knows steel
is no match for a hardened body.
Hmm?
Man 4:
This monster association
is certainly making
some bold moves.
- Man 2: What now?
- Man 7: It's obvious, isn't it?
Rescuing the hostage
is our top priority.
Man 8: But can we
send in s-class heroes
knowing it's a trap?
Blackluster: This is bad.
The monsters' actions
have thrown the executives
into a panic.
They can't think straight.
Better step up.
( Clears throat )
Check out this action!
( Grunts )
Well?
Man 2: Uh, "well?"
What, exactly?
Need something?
Blackluster: Did seeing
these sculpted muscles
calm everyone down a little bit?
Man 2: Oh, uh, sure.
Blackluster: We're full
of boldness, just like them!
Finally the time has come
for me to start shining!
Our enemies
will tremble in fear.
I just hope they're tough enough
for me to go all-out!
Monster: Do you think
the heroes will come?
Monster 2: Let 'em come!
We all saw it today.
We're way stronger!
Monster 3:
Taking hostages is pointless.
If we go all-in,
they're good as dead.
Gyoro-gyoro:
Audacity is a virtue,
but rushing in headlong
is a strategy filled with flaws.
There are freakishly strong ones
among their ranks as well.
If we allow them to get away,
it'll mean trouble later,
so we must lure them all in
and then crush them
with our full force.
Our young hostage
serves as the bait.
Once we've slain
their strongest fighters,
the remainder
will be exterminated with ease.
With no one of power
left to resist us,
nothing will prevent
our victory.
Human civilization will fall.
And, when that day comes,
lord orochi will reign supreme,
and a new world ruled
by monsters shall be born!
No applause? What's the matter?
Does the idea
of swearing loyalty
to lord orochi upset you?
Monster 4:
I thought we were here
to destroy
the hero association.
Who said anything about loyalty?
Orochi: Hold. Do I sense
weaklings among us?
( Monsters gasp )
( Roach awakening groans )
No! I'm not a weakling!
Gyoro-gyoro:
Is that you, roach awakening?
You have the gall to return here
after your utter failure?
Roach awakening:
Whoa! Wait a second!
All I lost was my legs, okay?!
I can still fight!
Next time--( Whimpers )
I thought we were
on the same team!
Come on! No! Stop it!
Don't do this! Please, stop it!
Stop--
monsters: He ate him.
Gyoro-gyoro:
And what of you, super s?
( Super s whimpers )
I'm fine, really.
I'm mostly unscathed.
See? I didn't lose!
Gyoro-gyoro:
Well, she does have
a unique and
useful set of skills.
It might be worth
allowing her to live.
Orochi: Next time, you die.
( Super s panting )
Thank you.
Gyoro-gyoro:
Ah, now where was I?
Anyone who's got a problem
can take it up with lord orochi
once the battle is over.
If you manage to defeat him,
you'll even be the new boss.
No hard feelings.
Monster 4: Seems fair.
Orochi: Gyoro-gyoro,
I do not see
goketsu among my beasts.
Gyoro-gyoro: Huh.
Now that you mention it,
he hasn't come back.
( Wings buzzing )
I will check on him immediately.
( Gasps )
¶
goketsu. He's dead.
Who could have done this?
It seems my plans won't
come to fruition so easily.
( Garou gasps )
Where am I?
Did I lose a fight or something?
( Groans )
Better get back
to the hideout for now.
Huh? Is that...
There's no doubt about it.
It's class-a death gatling.
( Groans )
Damn it.
King roughed me up pretty bad.
My body's at its limit.
I think I'm gonna
have to call it a day.
Everything seems
to be working correctly.
How does it feel, genos?
Genos: It feels great, perfect.
Thank you very much, Dr. Kuseno.
Sorry for the rush.
Dr. Kuseno:
Don't worry about it.
I mean, you did want to get back
to the front lines as soon
as possible, now, didn't you?
I made some simple modifications
and upgrades,
nothing revolutionary,
but they should
certainly make you stronger.
Genos: Understood.
I will not lose again.
Dr. Kuseno:
There's no need to overdo it.
It's okay to lose at times,
as long as you stay alive,
that is.
Seeing the state
you were in yesterday
reminded me of my younger days,
a time when I burned
with a passion for justice
and dove in headfirst
without fear of anything.
Listen, genos.
Don't do anything rash.
You understand?
( Footsteps receding )
Vendor: Monster association
declares war!
Man: Monster association?
Man 2: Is it true
they infiltrated hero hq?
Woman: They killed an executive?
Man 3: What were
the heroes doing?
Reporter: Early this morning,
a group called
the monster association
claimed that they had taken
a young citizen hostage.
They also claimed the captive...
- Zenko: Are we gonna be okay?
- ( Metal bat scoffs )
Zakkos: Seems the hero
and monster associations
are headed for an all-out war.
Sourface: Those damn beasts!
Well, if it's a war they want,
that's what they're gonna get.
Ring-ring: What happens to us
if the heroes lose?
Zakkos: It hurts to admit,
but we would be powerless.
Sourface: Damn it.
Ring-ring:
The heroes can win, right?
They just have to.
Child emperor: What do you mean
that doesn't affect
our strategy?
Are you sure you understand
the situation here,
metal knight?
Metal knight: If they
goad us into storming in,
it will only increase
our casualties.
Sacrificing our resources
recklessly makes no sense.
Child emperor: This is no time
to be crunching numbers.
They've taken
a little kid hostage!
Metal knight: All I'm saying
is that that kind of thinking
will only make matters worse.
Once we locate the enemy lair,
we should abandon any plans
to rescue the hostage
and immediately
commence bombing while we can.
I proposed that plan
to the council,
but they rejected it.
It seems they have
decided to prioritize
their own interests
in this matter,
and, if that's the case,
I want no part
of the current suicide mission.
Child emperor: He just really
wants to have everything
his own way.
Woman: The citizens
are keeping a close eye on us
to see what
our next move will be.
Man: The press
are having a field day.
How did this get leaked?
Man 2: Now that the public
has been made aware
of our failures, it's time
we take a hard-line approach.
Monster: The monster
association, huh?
It didn't say
where to find them,
but I've got an idea.
They're in city z,
and they're planning
a revolution.
Monster 2:
That message in their demands
wasn't meant for humans only.
Monster 1:
They're talking to us, too.
Monster 3: Let's join
the monster association...
Monsters: And wipe
those bastard heroes
off the face of the planet!
Saitama: Lots of monsters
today, too, huh
were they out looking for me,
or was it just bad luck?
But, more importantly,
if I don't hurry,
I'll miss the garbage truck!
Boy: What? Somebody's
in our secret base?
Are you for real?
Boy 2: Yeah.
Some white-haired dude
- is in there sleeping.
- Boy 3: Seriously?
Hey, go check things out
for us, tareo.
- Tareo: Uh...
- Boy 1: Wake him up,
- and get rid of him!
- Tareo: Um...
I don't know if I can do that.
Boy 1: Quit whining about it,
and get going!
Tareo: That hurt.
( Garou panting )
I can't shake this fever.
I might be out of commission
for a few days.
I don't have time for this.
- ( Creak )
- Who's there?!
( Tareo whimpers )
Garou: What are you
sneaking around for?
Tareo: Uh, listen.
This shack is--
i-it's our--
it's our secret base, so...
Garou: Hey, wait.
You're that kid
with the hero almanac.
Tareo: Huh? Uh...
Oh! It's you, mister!
Garou: I thought I told you
to stop calling me mister.
Why are you here?
Tareo: Uh, well...
I-I was hoping that...
You could maybe leave our base?
- Garou: What?
- ( Tareo gasps )
Garou: Why are you
telling me to leave?
I'm trying to rest up here.
Tareo: Um, well,
everybody told me
to tell that
to whoever was in here.
Garou: What, like your friends?
Just tell them to buzz off.
Tareo: B-but I...
Garou: Stop your crying.
It's annoying.
All right, fine.
I'll move to another place
soon, okay?
If they have
a problem with that,
bring 'em here,
and I'll tell 'em myself.
You got that, you little turd?
( Tareo grunts )
Garou: And let me give you
a piece of advice, kid.
It's about
getting respect from others.
Tareo: Huh?
( Grunts ) What is it?
( Boy sighs )
What's taking him so long?
Boy 2: Maybe something
happened to him.
Death gatling:
Stand back, boys.
Boy 1: Whoa! It's death gatling!
Death gatling:
It's dangerous here.
Boy 2: It's smile man
and stinger, too!
Boy 3: Wow! Look!
A bunch of heroes are here!
Smile man:
The hero hunter is wounded
and hiding out
in that shack, huh?
Death gatling: That's right.
This is it,
garou the hero hunter.
Today, it's your turn
to be hunted.
Boy 2: Sir,
is something bad in there?
Hero: There's an evil monster
inside that shack.
Get clear of here right now.
- ( Boys gasp )
- Boy 1: Uh, yes, sir.
Boy 2: Oh, no. We made tareo
go in there all by himself.
Boy 1: The heroes are here now.
Uh, he'll be okay.
- Boy 2: Right.
- Boy 3: Yeah.
Garou: If you want respect,
if you don't
wanna be bossed around...
Then you gotta get strong.
- Tareo: What?
- Garou: That's it.
Some pretty good advice, huh?
Tareo: No. I mean,
that's pretty obvious.
( Whimpers )
Garou: Yeah, it is obvious,
so obvious that you
understood it perfectly!
( Laughs )
( Groans )
Damn, even laughing hurts.
Tareo: Are you
all right, mister?
Garou: Don't worry about me.
Listen. You should go on home.
Tareo: Oh. Okay.
( Smile man gasps )
The door's sliding open.
Death gatling: Get ready.
As soon as that bastard
shows his face,
we light the place up.
Garou: They're all around us.
- Wait!
- Tareo: Huh?
Garou: In exchange
for that advice I gave you,
let me see the hero almanac,
just a quick peek.
Tareo: Huh?
The hero almanac? But why?
Garou: I just need
to look at something.
Tareo: I guess so.
Here.
Garou: Thanks.
This thing has a bunch
of comprehensive information
on the heroes, right?
Tareo: Yup. But it doesn't
cover all of them, so, uh...
Garou: I see.
Out front, four.
In back, two.
And one at each side.
Eight in all.
Ordinarily, taking them out
would be a cinch,
but, with these injuries...
Luckily, this almanac
has some useful information.
- ( Gatling gun fires )
- ( Tareo gasps )
- ( Garou grunts )
- Tareo: Hey, mister,
there's someone outside!
Garou: Stop talking.
( Scoffs ) I'm out of time.
( Gatling gun fires )
Death gatling: There's no point
in hiding, hero hunter!
We know you're in there.
Garou: Turd...
Get down on the floor.
All right, I'm coming out!
Hold your fire!
Listen.
Don't shoot up the place.
Stinger:
Aren't you a sweetheart?
You giving up?
Garou: Don't be stupid.
I just need somewhere
to catch up on some sleep
once I'm done
hunting you bastards down.
Wildhorn:
After you hunt us down?
Death gatling: Don't fall
for his taunting, wildhorn.
He's obviously in bad shape.
We'll take him alive
and bring him back to hq.
We'll get him
to tell us about his motives
and give up any accomplices.
Garou: Typical hero playbook.
Very kind of you to capture me
instead of going for the kill.
Tareo: Wow! Heroes!
And they're
really tough ones, too!
Death gatling:
Oh, you won't get off easy.
You'll have to pay.
Wildhorn: We're going
to make you regret
ever calling yourself a monster.
Garou: You've got it backwards.
You'll pay
for calling yourselves heroes.
¶
( inhales )
Time to hunt!
You dipshits are gonna
put me over 100 kills!
Blam-blam: This is
the end of the line for you!
Garou: I don't think so.
You're going down first!
Stinger:
He did that airborne? Amazing.
Garou: That was pretty close.
I don't think
he was trying to take me alive.
Arrow rain!
Shooter: Arrow rain
is my secret technique.
How'd he know?
Garou: Those are poison arrows.
Good thing I read the almanac.
Tareo: I don't get it.
What'd you do?
Why are heroes
after you, mister?
Chain toad: Despite the odds,
he's not backing down.
Is this hero hunter
just a damned fool?
Megane: No, chain toad.
Both tank top master
and metal bat were badly beaten.
I assure you, garou's no fool.
Remember what we
discussed about him.
Chain toad:
"Never underestimate him."
I'll keep that in mind.
Now let's see how he likes this!
¶
( garou winces )
- ( Chain clinks )
- ( Winces )
Smile man: Those skills.
He was silverfang's
top disciple.
Chain toad: And he's no fool.
His senses
are frighteningly sharp.
Garou: At middle distance,
chain toad and smile man
launch a ceaseless
barrage of attacks
shooter: Got him! Two hits!
Garou: But if I
back off too far,
I'm in shooter
and blam-blam's field of fire,
with death gatling on cleanup.
So what's that guy
in the track suit
been up to all this time?
- Megane: Shooter!
- Shooter: Thanks!
Garou: He's here as support.
That explains why he's
keeping his distance from me.
In that case...
You're gonna be my meat shield!
- Get back here!
- ( Pistol fires )
Damn.
I can't let my guard down
for a second.
They're relentless.
Little shit.
Megane: Just in case
you were wondering,
it's my job to chase you down
if you try to run.
In terms of stamina and
persistence, you won't beat me.
You're wounded and poisoned.
You won't hold out much longer.
But the close-up fighting
is a job for the other heroes.
Garou:
They've got me surrounded,
and I don't have the legs
to break through 'em.
And, with the shape I'm in,
there's no way
I can even hope to avoid
all their bullets, arrows,
and other weapons.
Death gatling:
This is the final chance
you're going to get
to surrender, garou!
( Garou panting )
¶
( singing in japanese )