Announcer:
Congratulations on winning
the championship, suiryu.
There was a little weirdness
in that final match,
but, in the end,
you still won unscathed!
Suiryu: "Unscathed"?
If he hadn't
stopped short, then...
Announcer: And now
an announcement
for stadium attendees.
We've been informed
that monsters
have appeared
outside the arena.
- Woman: Monsters?
- Man: This is getting old.
Man 2: We'll be okay
if we stay in here, right?
- Man 3: Probably.
- Suiryu: Whatever.
No use dwelling on it.
I'll just avoid him
from here on out.
( Sighs ) Hmm?
Aren't you the cutest thing.
Ring girl: Huh? ( Giggles )
Suiryu: Just forget about him.
- Man 4: What are those?!
- Suiryu: Huh?
Woman 2: Look! Up there! Ahh!
( Crowd clamoring )
Announcer: Monsters!
Zakkos: It's logy, Dave,
and bazuzu! They've got them.
Announcer: The competitors
that were taken to the hospital!
Benpats: Screw a bunch of this!
You guys can take care
of those things.
I'm out of here! Later!
Sourface: Hey, get back here!
- ( Thump )
- ( Gasps )
( All gasp )
( Benpats groaning )
Goketsu: So, have we got
all the tournament fighters?
- ( Lightning Max growls )
- ( Goketsu sighs )
Nothing but scrubs here.
How the martial arts
have fallen.
Whatever.
All of you will become monsters.
¶
¶ hero
( singing in Japanese )
¶ go, go
¶ hero
( singing in Japanese )
¶ go, go
¶ hero
( singing in Japanese )
¶ one punch
( crowd screaming )
Goketsu: Even the refuse of
the martial arts world like you
could be useful as monsters.
Lightning Max: As monsters, huh?
Snek: You'll have to go
through us heroes first!
Man: You heroes are the best!
Get him!
( Heroes scream )
Man: Run for it! We're screwed!
Goketsu: Is that
the end of them?
Sourface: Just one kick?
Goketsu: I am goketsu
of the monster association.
I have not come here
to take your lives today.
Zakkos: Goketsu?! No way!
Announcer: The champion
of the first super fight?!
Goketsu: You recognizing me
simplifies things.
You know resistance is futile.
Announcer: That's impossible!
Goketsu was killed
by a monster years ago!
You can't be him!
Goketsu: I was once beaten
by a monster, but not killed.
I ended up being taken
to their lair.
They made me an offer.
In exchange for my cooperation,
the monsters would give me
all I ever wanted
in order
to satisfy my ambitions!
Becoming a monster allowed me
to break through the limitations
I could never overcome
as a human.
Understand?!
The man I was is nothing
in comparison to the fighter
I am as a monster!
Be thankful, for I have
brought the same gift for you.
You will eat
these monster cells.
( All gasp )
Goketsu: Then you'll
become monsters yourselves.
Refuse, and you will die.
( All gasp )
Metal knight:
Monster association,
what are
your group's intentions?
Are you simply bent
on destruction and slaughter?
Gyoro-gyoro: There's no question
that monsters crave violence.
That goes without saying.
But violence is not
our sole objective.
There is a new phase that
we're advancing toward, you see.
Ah, but for now, just watch.
Observe the inherent frailty
of the human biology and spirit.
Goketsu: Become monsters or die.
Time to choose.
- ( Logy panting )
- Sourface: Eh?
No! Don't do it!
( Logy gasps )
( Wailing )
( Panting )
This is incredible!
The power, the violence
flooding through me.
Hey, fat boy, remember when you
mocked me during our match?
( Grunts )
Sourface: He wasn't
near that strong before.
( Logy laughs )
( Gags )
Choze: If they have
that much effect on the weak,
what will one do to me?
My genetics reign supreme
across all of human history.
My ultimate strength
is about to awaken.
Zakkos: Choze, please don't!
( Squelch )
¶
- ( fighters gasp )
- Choze: Hmm.
It not only served
to improve my physical function,
but my vast mental capacity
is unfettered as well.
So this is a monster.
- Let's see.
- ( Jakumen gasps )
- ( Bones crack )
- Sourface: Jakumen!
( Choze chuckles ) Interesting.
I could kill that peon
with ease now.
He made the mistake
of humiliating me.
He shall rue that decision
'til death.
Goketsu: Looks like
this one turned out well.
Sometimes the flesh
is too weak to survive.
- ( Sourface stammering )
- Goketsu: Now, then,
you insects eat up, too!
Benpats: Uhh! I don't wanna die!
- ( Grunting )
- Zakkos: Benpats!
Hamukichi: It's to survive.
Ring-ring: Hamukichi!
Boltane: I want this strength.
Sourface: Boltane, no!
( Monsters groaning )
( Benpats laughs )
I feel like I could do anything!
( Hamukichi roars )
( Boltane laughs ) The energy!
( Laughing )
Ring-ring: They're all
turning into monsters!
Sourface: There's no way
we can fight 'em all.
- Suiryu: Hey, what's up?
- Ring girl: Huh?
Suiryu: If I chase
these monsters off,
would you go out with me?
( Ring girl grunts )
Suiryu: That's a deal.
This'll give me
a chance to work off
the stress
from that final match.
Goketsu: One of you
still dares to defy me?
Enough talk, then.
Any potential enemy
of the monster association
must die.
Destroy him!
Benpats: Dumb-ass playboy!
So now you wanna fight
for truth and justice?
- Suiryu: Not at all.
- ( Hamukichi roars )
Suiryu: See, all I
live for is pleasure.
And guys like you...
Just get in my way.
Bakuzan: Hmm.
( Suiryu grunts )
- ( Horns stab )
- ( Fighters gasp )
( Choze chuckles ) Eh?
( Suiryu growls )
( Yells )
¶
( Chuckles ) You know what?
You're not bad.
Choze: Not bad?
Your vacuous mentality
is an affront.
( Ring-ring gasps )
What's he doing?!
Choze: I've decided.
Only those who meet my standards
shall repopulate this world.
You worms do not.
That means
you shall be eliminated.
- ( All gasp )
- ( Suiryu grunts )
( All screaming )
( Suiryu growls )
That all you got?!
Choze: Impossible!
( Gags )
¶
suiryu: That didn't
meet my standards,
but I'll give you
one more chance.
Try to make it
a little more fun.
Choze: Insufferable fool!
Zakkos: They're moving
too fast to see!
Suiryu: Dark body
quake tiger fist!
( Choze gagging )
Suiryu: Dark body
phoenix rising fist!
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Armor clatters )
Zakkos: Yeah! Nicely done!
Suiryu: Is that blood?
Can't remember
the last time I got cut.
Wow. Almost got me.
That monster-fication thing
they went through
made them really tough.
Goketsu: Impressive.
Killing you would be a waste.
You sure you won't change sides?
From now on, the world
will belong to the monsters.
The strong will be truly free,
killing as they please,
a world of bloodlust
and violence.
As a monster,
you'd find your fun.
Not a bad deal, if you ask me.
- ( Zakkos gasps )
- Sourface: He wouldn't!
Suiryu: You make a good point.
You're saying, human or monster,
as long as life is fun,
then it's all good, right?
Nah, I refuse.
I'd rather die
than look as balls-out fugly
as you, freako!
Dark body flying dragon fist!
- ( Fighters laugh, gasp )
- Sourface: Yeah!
( Suiryu gags )
Goketsu: Then, you die.
Screaming )
Woman: Watchdog man!
Man: Way to go!
Woman: Thank you so much!
Man: You're city q's
guardian angel!
Garou: I see why he's a hero
worthy of class s.
Monsters attacked just as I
was about to fight him.
His speed and strength
were surprisingly high,
but, in the end,
that's all he's really got.
Those are two things
I can easily handle.
Look out, watchdog man.
Now it's your turn to be hunted!
( Watchdog man sniffs )
Are you human
or some kind of monster?
- ( Crowd clamoring )
- ( Garou scoffs )
Fist of flowing water
crushing rock!
That's a bad doggie!
This guy is definitely nothing
but speed and power,
but the freak's got way more of
both than I originally thought.
Goketsu: What's the matter?
You done already?
You've got three seconds
to get up.
3, 2, 1...
( Suiryu yells )
Goketsu: That's it.
Fight like your life
depends on it.
( Suiryu gasps )
¶
suiryu: Damn. He's not
even flinching. What can I do?
Goketsu: You all
can have your fun, too.
Goketsu: Huh?
- ( Sourface yells )
- ( Zakkos screams )
( Ring-ring screams )
( Gatling groans )
( Mentai whimpers )
( Both yell )
Suiryu: This went downhill fast.
Goketsu: Don't get distracted.
Eyes on the prize!
( Suiryu winces )
Is it broken?
Goketsu: Come now.
What's the matter?
Get up.
I'll give you three seconds.
- 3, 2, 1...
- ( Suiryu grunting )
( Yells )
Dark body quake tiger fist!
( Gasps )
I put everything into that.
( Groaning )
He's strong,
stronger than me
in every regard.
So this is the power...
Of a monster.
( Gags )
( Goketsu grunts )
( Suiryu shuddering )
Goketsu: Eat up, boys!
That meat is a real delicacy.
- Pick him clean!
- ( Monsters growl )
Goketsu: Believe it or not,
they were once my disciples,
but they were weak
and lost themselves
when they become monsters.
Suiryu: Damn it!
( Monsters growl )
Suiryu: If I don't
do something, I'm dead!
( Gasps )
Bakuzan, we're all in trouble!
Please, I need your help!
( Bakuzan chuckles )
Suiryu, watching the finals,
it was clear.
You're stronger than me.
There's simply no way
that I can beat you.
I accept that fact,
but right now
you're the one
who's about to be killed.
Ironic, isn't it?
Your strength and skill
led you to the top
of the human world,
yet, against these monsters,
you're nothing.
Suiryu: Yes! That's exactly
why we should team up!
Bakuzan: Team up?
¶
I am going to become a monster!
Consider this
your final resting place!
Becoming the strongest human
seems kind of pointless now.
My new goal is...
To be the strongest
creature alive!
Goketsu: Shameful.
Looks like he ate them all.
Greedy bastard.
Bakuzan: Keep barking!
In a second,
I'm gonna shut
that big mouth of your--
( groans )
( Goketsu chuckles )
Looks like your body
can't keep up.
The monster-fication failed.
What a pity.
That just leaves you.
( Crowd screaming )
( Mumen rider groans )
There are patients
back there in the I.C.U.
That can't be moved.
At times like these,
heroes don't back down!
Monster: In the end,
heroes are only human.
Your kind only exist
to be dominated by monsters.
( Mumen rider screaming )
Goketsu: Everyone else
either ran off or was defeated.
Aren't you lucky?
Your cries of pain
won't embarrass you.
Now, then,
time to hear you scream.
Snek: Coiling defense!
( Suiryu gasps )
Lightning Max: Lightning kick!
Suiryu: Wait, snek and Max.
You're both okay?
( Monster squawks )
Suiryu: But why?
Why'd you come back?
Both: To save you.
( Suiryu gasps )
Snek: In our hero outfits,
we're different fighters.
My jacket and slacks protect me
against monster claws,
fangs, even beaks.
My battle suit!
Lightning Max: And I put on
my lightning shoes.
Now let's show this nimrod
what we can really do!
Snek: We're up against
three of these beasts.
Lightning Max:
Can we leave one to you?
Suiryu: Yeah!
( Monsters growl )
Suiryu: You did save me.
Thanks, you guys.
Tank top master:
Tank top tackle!
( Monster gags )
( Screams )
Mumen rider:
That was a great tackle.
Tank top master:
You're pretty brave
for a guy with no tank top.
Easy, now. Can you stand?
Mumen rider: Yeah.
You bet I can.
( Suiryu grunts )
Seems like my legs
are still good to go.
Let's get out of here.
¶
why are you guys
getting ready to fight?
Snek: We're gonna
buy you some time.
Lightning Max:
By holding this guy off.
Suiryu: Don't be stupid!
You'll die!
You don't stand a chance!
Think about it.
Neither of you could beat me!
( Footsteps rumbling )
They can't be serious.
Aren't they afraid?
( Panting )
( Blows thumping )
I won't get another chance.
Gotta go. I gotta go.
I gotta go!
I can--( Gasps )
Bakuzan: Where do you
think you're going?
The fun's all right here!
Goketsu: I hit the jackpot
with this one.
Looks like you
turned out the same as me,
a threat level dragon!
( Bakuzan laughs )
Damn right, I did!
Oh? He's still
got some fight in him?
( Laughing )
( Laughing continues )
Gyoro-gyoro:
An update on our progress.
Objective number one--
create terror
amongst the humans
via rampage and chaos.
We've been
quite successful at this.
No safe harbor remains.
The humans exist in a cloak
of uncertainty and fear.
Objective number two--
identify and secure a hostage
from the hero association.
Also a success.
The son of an important
executive is in our hands.
And objective number three--
turn noteworthy humans
into monsters.
This is also proceeding well.
Nyaan infiltrated a prison,
monster-fied those inmates
who were inherently evil,
and is now leading
our recruits to this location.
Goketsu has also turned
several martial artists.
They'll surely make
valuable additions to our ranks.
Hmm? Goketsu's still at work?
Odd.
Attention!
Goketsu, come back immediately.
If any class-s heroes arrive,
even you may not be able
to handle them.
( Goketsu growls )
Don't be so sure.
Either way, I'm done here.
- Hey, new guy.
- Bakuzan: What?
Goketsu: I'm taking you
to our lair. Follow!
( Bakuzan growls )
You don't give me orders!
I'm bakuzan!
( Rubble falling )
Goketsu: Now listen.
Many in the monster association
are stronger than you,
including me,
so don't get carried away.
The monsters will be returning
to the lair now.
That means that the heroes,
including class s,
will be coming
for those who remain.
They're too much
for you to handle alone.
Consider yourself warned.
I'm going.
The lair's in the ruins
outside city z.
Find us there.
Bakuzan: Hear that, suiryu?
There are monsters everywhere,
it seems.
Unbelievable.
I felt his power now,
and I'm scared.
( Sighs ) That's it.
No more trying
to be the strongest.
( Suiryu weakly )
Hey, bakuzan.
I don't wanna fight anymore.
Come on. Just let me live, okay?
Bakuzan: Look, suiryu,
in case you didn't know...
Suiryu: Please, stop.
Bakuzan: I'm the type of guy
who loves beating
on anyone weaker than me!
That's the only reason
I ever wanted to become strong!
Now that I've surpassed
my limits,
I've never felt better!
- ( Suiryu groans )
- ( Bones crack )
Bakuzan: How about
the other one?!
( Suiryu screams )
Bakuzan: Look at that,
the great suiryu
screaming in pain.
Too bad there's no audience
around to hear it!
( Suiryu gasping )
Bakuzan: You had youth,
ability, popularity.
You had money,
women, and freedom.
Looking back on it, do you think
you took too much for granted?
( Chuckles )
Before you die,
you'll experience a hell
that wipes all that away.
Lookin' pretty pathetic, champ.
Suiryu: Help me!
Somebody, please!
There's a monster here!
It's trying to kill me!
Is anyone out there?
It won't stop until I'm dead!
Please! I need a hero!
Can any heroes hear me?!
Just follow my voice!
Heroes, I beg you, help!
There's a monster.
Heroes, help me.
Bakuzan: Either no one hears you
or no one cares.
No heroes are coming,
so get ready to die.
Suiryu: There's nobody out there
who can match him.
Even the strongest hero
couldn't save me.
But I'm begging you.
Someone, please.
When a person is thrust into
the darkest depths of despair,
they seek a ray of light.
It doesn't matter
how small it is
or how faint it may be.
Just the fact that it's there
gives hope.
Bakuzan: Give up.
There is no hope for you.
( Suiryu gasps )
( Bakuzan laughs )
- ( Suiryu gasps )
- Bakuzan: Huh?
Who the hell are you?
Saitama: Me? Just a hero.
I heard you
calling out for help, suiryu.
You fought hard on your own.
Let me take care of the rest.
¶
( singing in Japanese )