Ng: Fist of flowing water
crushing rock!
( Blows pounding )
¶
( garou yells )
Genos: Offense and defense
in perfect harmony.
It is the same fighting style,
but bang's form is flawless.
The Victor is already clear.
( Garou groans ) What the hell?
The old s.O.B. Doesn't usually
just whale on an opponent
like this.
Damn it. I'm blacking out.
I'm about to die.
( Bang gasps )
What is that preposterous style?
Where did you pick it up?
It's like you're
a damned animal.
Garou: I'm not done.
I'll grab him
and carve out an advantage.
Bomb: No, you don't.
I took care of the monsters,
as I said I would.
And now your turn.
Take out garou.
¶
Phoenix Man: We sent in a team
to bring garou back alive,
but we had no idea demon cyborg
was such a strong adversary.
And then there's silverfang
and the other one.
I see no way
of retrieving garou,
but, if I return empty-handed,
orochi may devour me
like the others.
I need garou to somehow
get through this alive...
But it's starting
to look hopeless.
Bang: Bomb, look at the wounds
covering him.
If you'd received as many,
would you still be standing?
Bomb: If I were
60 years younger,
I'm confident I could hang in
there without a problem, maybe.
Now just a little more.
Let's finish this, bang!
Bang: Hah!
( Blows pounding )
Garou: Bang, you bastard.
Attacking your former student
when I'm already
beaten all to hell.
And, worse,
the other old fart is bomb,
master of fist of whirling wind
slashing steel.
Have they no shame,
ganging up on me like this?
Even if I put on a sob act
and begged for my life,
demon cyborg
would never let me go.
I don't see
any other way out of this.
The only thing I can do
is kill all three of them.
But that's impossible.
Bang: I will repay you
for every ounce of pain
you gave to charanko!
- Suffer!
- ( Blows pounding )
Boy: Let's play
heroes and monsters.
You're gonna play, too,
right, garou?
Boy 2: Come on, man!
Garou: Uh, okay.
( Boy 1 hums fanfare )
Justice man is here!
Whaah!
Justice kick!
( Boy 2 groans )
Garou: Be more careful
boy 1: Huh?
Garou: That must have hurt.
¶
( chuckles ) Okay, then.
- Why don't you be the monster?
- Garou: What?
Boys: Why don't you
be the monster?
- Young garou: Uh...
- Garou: What's this?
My life flashing before my eyes?
Everything about this sucks.
What was his name?
Boy 1: You're the monster now.
Got it?
Garou: That's right.
It was tatsu,
the most popular kid in class.
Girl: What's going on?
What happened?
Girl 2: Garou was fighting.
Boy: We were playing.
Then, out of nowhere,
garou got mad.
Boy 2: He went totally crazy!
We were just playing!
Boy 3: What the heck?
What's wrong with him?
Boy 4: Why'd you
hurt tatsu like that!
Man: Now tell me, garou,
why did you get into that fight?
Garou: I don't know.
Man: Is it true
you became violent
over heroes and monsters?
Garou: Tatsu's always--
I mean, he's--
man: Can you not
tell the difference
between reality and fantasy?
Garou: No, that's not it at all!
I'm always the monster, and--
man: You're the one
who lost his temper,
so you're the one
who will be punished!
Garou: It's not like I didn't
want to be the monster.
Did I hate that tatsu
was always the hero?
No, that wasn't it, either.
It's because the game itself
just felt so incredibly
one-sided and unfair.
Heroes and monsters
is just a game of pretend
based on kids' TV shows.
Everyone's free to choose
what role they play.
Tatsu was the most popular kid
in class.
But me, I was friendless,
always with a dark cloud above.
Everyone knew who the hero
was going to be.
I didn't stand a chance in hell.
Tatsu: Justice cross chop!
( Grunts )
Hey, why'd you dodge?
Garou: Huh?
Tatsu: Guys...
Hold garou still.
- ( Boys laugh ) Okay.
- Young garou: Wait!
Garou: Naturally,
there was no scenario
where the monster
would ever win.
I was always the loser.
Tatsu: Justice kick!
Garou the poop monster is dead!
Garou: The popular kid
always beats up
the little guy
that no one likes.
That's just the way
the world works.
Young garou: I've had enough!
Come on! Fight me, tatsu!
Tatsu: Huh?
What are you talking about?
Garou: I don't want
to be the monster
in your games anymore!
If I win, that's it!
You have to promise
to leave me alone forever!
( Tatsu chuckles ) Guys...
Hold garou for a second.
( Garou gasps )
Hey, that's cheating!
Let go! I wanna fight
tatsu one-on-one!
Man: The other kids
say you were all playing games
and then you got
violent out of nowhere.
Garou: That's not what happened.
Tatsu is just super popular,
so everyone's
making me the bad guy.
Man: Wrong! You did
something you shouldn't have,
so now you have to apologize!
( Young garou crying )
Garou: Screw justice,
and screw evil, too.
I'm gonna be killed
simply because that's what
everyone else wants?
It's not fair. I can't stand it.
It pisses me off!
All I want
is to make them understand.
¶
I'm here to fight
for underdogs everywhere.
Good? Evil?
I reject them both!
Bang: This is the end, garou!
Garou:
That's where you're wrong!
- ( Both gasp )
- Garou: Nothing's ended!
- Bang: What the...
- ( Garou roaring )
Bang: Garou.
( Genos gasps ) Look out!
Above you!
Phoenix Man: Yaah!
( Heroes groan )
( Garou yells )
( Groans )
Bomb: That monster.
Bang: Genos, wait!
Genos: No, bang!
Garou is a monster now!
I will shoot them both down
and end this!
Phoenix Man:
Listen up down there!
I've got garou with me!
The others, I leave to you...
Genos:
Spiral incineration cannon!
Phoenix Man: Centichoro!
( Chorus vocalizing )
Bomb: Dear god, what's that?
Is that a living creature?!
( Bang grunts ) Down there,
the other heroes!
- ( Genos grunts )
- ( Bang grunts )
¶
it took the full brunt of geno''
attack like it was nothing,
not even a scratch.
Whatever this creature is,
it will no doubt
be a fearsome adversary.
¶
( garou gasps )
What's the big idea?
Nobody asked you to butt in.
Phoenix Man: Never you mind.
Centichoro will handle the rest.
He's a living catastrophe,
destroying all in his path.
I admire
such indiscriminate destruction.
( Garou groans )
Phoenix Man: As usual,
you didn't kill your opponents,
hero hunter.
Once they're down, you have
to keep hammering away at them
until they're truly done.
Those heroes lying on the ground
could live to fight another day.
( Garou sighs )
Phoenix Man: Well, not to worry.
Centichoro will see to it
that they don't.
( Garou grunts )
You all can piss off. Got it?!
Those are my prey!
Phoenix Man: Enough of that.
Stop squirming.
Garou: Eat shit! Put me down!
I won't let you do this to me!
Phoenix Man: Why are you upset?
It's your own fault
for not finishing them.
The elimination
of two class-s heroes
makes everything that happened
here very worthwhile for us.
They are our greatest enemies,
after all.
You experienced that firsthand.
Fights, you see,
are all about matchups.
According to our strategist,
gyoro-gyoro,
the only heroes
who are powerful enough
to resist centichoro
are the psychic with abilities
beyond any other,
terrible tornado,
the loner with an arsenal
of military technology,
metal knight,
the hero known
as the strongest human, king,
and the top-ranked hero
who nearly killed centichoro
two years ago, blast.
Centichoro is working
with the monster association
just to have a chance
for vengeance against blast.
He's quite desperate
to do whatever he can
to lure the number one hero
to the battlefield.
From a matchup perspective,
those class-s heroes
lack the means to escape
their present circumstance.
Silverfang boasts
peerless technique, no doubt,
but it's only effective against
opponents of a certain size.
Demon cyborg's capabilities
are outstanding,
but his strength cannot exceed
the firepower of his components.
Those three
face only certain slaughter.
( Centichoro roars )
Genos: Here it comes!
- Bang: All right, genos.
- Bomb: You're up!
- Genos: Understood!
- ( Centichoro roars )
¶
bomb: Whirling wind.
Bang: Flowing water.
Both: Roaring qi
rending sky fist!
¶
Genos: What an amazing move.
Against such a hard exterior,
it serves
as the perfect counter!
Both: Again! Again!
Again! Again!
Again! Again! Again!
- Again!
- ( Centichoro groaning )
( Both groan )
( Centichoro screams )
Bomb: We should have
seen that coming.
Bang: Yes, that's true,
but we only had one shot
with that technique.
Thank you for the assist, genos.
Genos: It was no trouble.
Bomb: That was
a devastating attack.
The shock will travel
throughout its body.
May you shatter
into a million pieces, demon.
( Bang grunts )
We're done here.
Hmm?
( Centichoro grunting )
( Snarls )
Bang: Damn it.
The cursed beast just molted!
Bomb: That's all we did?
If we can't beat it,
then what do we do now?
Bang: The city's close by.
If it makes it over there,
it will be a massacre.
- Genos: Bang.
- Bang: Hmm?
Genos: Go. I will face it.
I will hold the monster here
for as long as I can
while you two make a run for it.
Bang: Damn fool. You know
we'd never agree to that.
Bomb: You shouldn't
make rash decisions
simply because you cannot win.
The future needs
young heroes like you.
Dr. Kuseno: Listen, genos.
Don't do anything rash.
You understand?
( Genos sighs )
Is caution truly
the path I should choose?
( Sighs )
No. I do not accept that!
( Both gasp )
¶
bang: It's suicide!
Your cannons
won't work on that beast!
( Centichoro roars )
Genos: Centichoro,
goketsu, even garou,
they are all
with the monster association.
There is simply
no avoiding this fight!
Dual blade rush!
Fighting one of them is
the same as fighting them all!
( Centichoro roars )
I will smash you apart!
Genos: If battling them
is rash...
( Centichoro chuckles )
- ( Bomb gasps )
- Bang: No! Genos!
Genos: ...Then being rash is
all I am worth in a fight!
¶
( centichoro gasps )
Genos: Jet drive arrow!
Centichoro: Insignificant flea!
( Genos yelling )
( Centichoro roars )
Bang: He went into its mouth!
Centichoro: Die!
Genos: This is stomach acid.
Centichoro: I'll melt
your body down to nothing.
Genos: You are mistaken.
You are the one who will melt!
Ultra spiral
incineration cannon!
( Centichoro gags )
( Screams )
Bomb: Ohh!
Bang: He actually pulled it off!
( Centichoro crackling )
( Genos groans )
¶
( centichoro laughing )
Genos: It happened again.
I...
I could not win.
I could not save them.
Bang: We're going
to have to run for it!
Centichoro: Futile.
Phoenix Man:
What's the matter, hero hunter?
You're awfully quiet.
Are you seeing things
our way now?
Garou: This is not
how all that I fought for
was supposed to end.
The heroes,
I wanted to defeat them
using my own strength,
and, by doing so,
become the symbol that
strikes fear in their hearts.
Why else even be
the hero hunter?
Phoenix Man: "The symbol that
strikes fear in their hearts"?
( Laughs )
Your power
doesn't even come close
to centichoro
or the association's leaders.
( Garou scoffs )
Maybe as I am now,
but just you wait.
( Centichoro roars )
Genos: What is it
that I am lacking?
There are many more
like this monster.
Am I destined to be
a mere spectator
when the heroes face
an enemy such as this?
Bomb: I hate to say this,
but we've got a problem.
It's driving us toward the city.
We cannot put civilians at risk.
Genos: What are you doing?
Bang: My brother...
It's time I go all in.
( Bullhorn squeals )
( Bang inhales )
( Exhales )
I offer all that remains
of my life to face it.
- ( Bullhorn whines )
- ( King shuddering )
¶
Courage.
Centichoro!
Listen up, bug!
I brought blast out here
to kick your ugly ass!
Bang: Wait.
Isn't that king's voice?
Genos: And blast is with him?
Bomb: Look!
I guess it heard him!
It's turning toward the voice!
Centichoro: Blast!
- ( Heart pounding )
- King: That's right!
The hero
who once beat you so badly,
you ran away crying
and soaked in your own piss!
Class s, rank 1, blast!
You want a rematch, bug boy?!
What's the problem? You scared?
Uh, coward!
If you're gonna shit yourself
in fear, do it at home.
A lowly bug like you
has got no business here!
Go back to your hidey-hole,
and suck on your mommy's milk!
Man: Looks like king
made it in time.
Woman: Yes, it seems so.
He asked for information
that he could use
to provoke centichoro.
Man: He's planning
to draw the monster in
for a head-to-head clash.
Woman: I know it's classified,
but I told him about blast,
their last fight.
Man: And his response?
Woman: All he said was,
"understood."
( Heart pounding )
But I also heard
the roar of the king engine.
¶
kin: "To set up the final blow,
"lure him in for me.
Keep him away from the city
and the civilians."
That should do it.
( Centichoro yelling )
King: Saitama?
Saitama!
¶
( king gasps )
Saitama: Oh.
That you, genos?
Huh. Guess he was here.
King: Yeah. Good thing we came.
Huh. Look at you! You seem
so relaxed all of a sudden.
Saitama: Punching that bug
in the face kinda refreshed me.
I must have been stressed out
from you handing me my ass
at all those games.
King: Was he really
still pissed about that?
- Genos: Master saitama...
- Saitama: Huh?
- I must ask you something.
- Saitama: What's up?
Genos: What do you think it is
that I am lacking, master?
Saitama: Uh, it's power, right?
Genos: Thank you
very much, master!
King: Oh, man!
Don't tell him that!
You can't use saitama
as a baseline!
Don't do it, genos!
Genos: Master's battles and
wisdom show me the true path.
He is a symbol of strength,
of what I strive to be.
I will get there, too...
Someday.
Saitama: Wanna head home?
¶
( Singing in Japanese )
¶ monsters
( singing in Japanese )
- ¶ we know
- ¶ we are
- ¶ heroes!
( Singing in Japanese )
¶ hero
( singing in Japanese )
¶ go, go
¶ hero
( singing in Japanese )
¶ go, go
¶ hero
( singing in Japanese )
¶ one punch
¶
Phoenix Man: Garou?
Did you pass out?
Good. Rest easy.
Soon you will meet lord orochi.
¶