Man: Here he comes.
Man 2: It's the man himself.
Sourface: The crowd's energy
seems to have shifted.
Saitama: I wonder why.
Announcer: No one expected
to see this man compete again,
and the crowd
is buzzing with excitement
at their chance
to see him in his element!
Suiryu has entered the ring!
His opponent is Max!
Lightning Max:
Look at Mr. Popular.
Could he really be
that much better than me?
No. No way.
I just don't see it.
And don't forget,
this guy isn't
the one you're after.
Compared to that monster,
this clown's
nothing but a scrub.
Suiryu,
I entered this tournament,
because I have
to get stronger.
If I fail,
I can't call myself a hero.
I'm sorry to do this to you,
but I consider you a competent
and capable opponent.
That's why I'm going
to use our match
to test my new
monster-fighting technique!
Suiryu: So you're
a professional hero, then.
I see. That means you train
with lofty ideals in mind.
I guess everyone's got some
reason for seeking strength.
( Lightning Max growls )
( Suiryu chuckles )
Referee: Fighters, ready.
Begin!
Lightning Max: Lightning...
Bigwheel double axe kick!
Suiryu: Personally,
the reason I sought strength...
¶
( crowd cheering )
Suiryu: ...Was so I
could live the easy life
without a care in the world.
Sorry to shut you down,
but I was stronger.
¶
¶ hero
( singing in Japanese )
¶ go, go
¶ hero
( singing in Japanese )
¶ go, go
¶ hero
( singing in Japanese )
¶ one punch
( crowd cheering )
Sourface:
Did you see that, charanko,
suiryu's crazy kick?
- Saitama: Yeah. Why?
- Sourface: Wait.
How are you so calm
after witnessing that?
Oh, I get it.
Because he's such a newb.
Genos: A class-a hero
defeated by a single kick.
There are more people
who are stronger than heroes
than I realized.
Well, it makes sense.
Master saitama used to be
under everyone's radar.
It is to be expected
that there would be
more out there like him.
That man there
might satisfy master's wish
to experience martial arts,
though I doubt anyone here
could rise to master's level.
( Cell phone buzzing )
( Gasps ) This is bad.
Announcer: Ladies and gentlemen,
it sounds like
you're still riled up
for our next match,
benpats of the way of the cruel
versus snakebite snek!
The winner of this match
will face suiryu
in the second round!
Benpats: A class-a hero, huh?
( Chuckles )
You don't look so tough to me.
Snek: If I can beat suiryu,
who defeated Lightning Max,
might have a positive impact
on my ranking.
Here goes.
Snakebite fist!
Benpats: None of your tricks are
going to work on me, old man!
Eat knuckles,
you bottom-ranked bastard!
Snek: I'm not bottom-ranked.
I'm the bottom of class a!
Man: Bad news!
There's a group
of violent monsters
- near the arena!
- Announcer: Huh?!
Man: We have
to evacuate everyone now!
Announcer: Holy crap!
I'll announce it right away--
- bakuzan: That won't be needed.
- Announcer: Huh?!
Bakuzan?!
Bakuzan: An evacuation
would cause panic.
Man: Maybe, but if the monsters
attack the venue, then--
bakuzan: This venue is filled
with martial arts masters.
It's the safest place
people could be.
Man: Good point.
Bakuzan: No need to worry.
If the monsters manage
to get inside the arena,
I will slay every last one.
Genos: There are more monsters?
There have been so many lately.
And now they have
come here to city c.
Should I tell master the news?
( Saitama yawns )
Genos: No.
I can handle this on my own.
The tournament must go on.
No matter how many there are,
I will exterminate them.
( Benpats groans )
( Coughs )
W-Wasn't expecting that.
This guy's not weak at all.
Referee: Match over! Snek wins!
- ( Crowd cheering )
- Snek: I want to believe
that I rank among
the strongest fighters around,
but I find
the harsh reality repugnant.
The top heroes
are out there in the cities,
up to their necks in monsters.
Genos: Incinerate.
Man: It's demon cyborg!
Man 2: That was so awesome!
Man 3: He saved us!
Genos: I am currently in city c,
near the stadium.
Give me an update.
Man 4: We have reports
of monsters appearing
simultaneously in multiple
cities and locations.
There are five confirmed
in city c alone.
Woman: Mr. Demon cyborg, sir,
there's another scary monster
down that way!
Man 5: And there's
a super-creepy one over there!
Genos: I destroyed one.
Where are the other four?
Man 4: We will direct you
to their locations.
( Crowd cheering )
Announcer: Using a combined
electric shock and strike,
boltane takes the victory!
- ( Rapid striking )
- Gatling's superfast punches
were like
a bombardment of fists!
Hamukichi is down,
and he's not getting up!
And Dave puts this match to rest
with a thunderous body press!
Logy is out of the tournament!
Mentai: Wait! No, please!
Announcer: The referee
stops the fight!
Choze's a tough one!
Mentai was simply outclassed!
Genos: Rocket stomp.
¶
( monster gasps )
Genos: There is
another monster nearby.
Tell me where it is,
or you will suffer
excruciating pain
until your demise.
Your choice.
Announcer: Next on the card
is jakumen
from giga-pro wrestling!
He's up against sourface
and his sourfacekempo!
It's a battle between newcomers!
Saitama: Do your best, sourface!
Sourface: Shut up, you!
I used to be master bang's
number-two disciple!
( Groans )
He's pretty huge.
Easy, now.
I'm stronger, probably.
Remember
all that strenuous training.
Jakumen: This guy's face is...
( Shudders ) Scary.
( Man screams )
Monster: How about
you give me your face? Cool?
( Man wailing )
Genos: I have located it.
You will be eliminated.
Monster: Looky here!
It's somebody famous.
Would you mind if I
carve off your face, too?
( Laughs )
( Screams )
Well, what do you think?
Like my fancy blade-work?
Eh?! ( Gags )
Genos: I baited you
into hitting my armored skull.
High-voltage fist.
Begone.
Woman: He took care of it
in no time.
Genos is incredible.
He really does have demon power.
Man: Demon cyborg,
the last monster...
Is approximately two klicks
to your northwest.
Several heroes
have already engaged it.
( Genos grunts )
Are you able to speak?
( Hero gasping )
Wh-when you fight him,
don't take your eyes
off that bastard.
He was always behind us.
- Monster: A class-s hero.
- ( Genos grunts )
Monster: You got something
against cockroaches, too?
Genos: You could say that.
I have something
against bug monsters in general.
This is the last one.
If I can take him out quickly,
it might be possible
to still catch master's fight.
Monster: Getting rid of me,
no easy task.
- ( Crowd gasps )
- Announcer: Jakumen taps out!
It's all over!
Sourface wins
with a beautiful chokehold!
The two fighters
congratulate one another!
- Such beautiful sportsmanship!
- ( Both weeping )
Saitama: How'd it go?
Did you win?
Sourface: What the hell?!
Are you saying
you didn't watch the match?!
I had a valiant victory!
Saitama: I was in the bathroom.
Sourface: You're hopeless.
Hey, hold up.
Your opponent in the next match,
be careful with that one.
I've seen bakuzan
in action many times...
Saitama: Oh, dang it.
I undid my belt in the bathroom,
and I forgot
how to tie it again.
Sourface: Charanko,
did you hear me?!
Announcer: On to the next match!
Charanko, the newcomer,
who advanced by beating zakkos,
is going up against two-time
consecutive champion bakuzan.
His lethal
dark hell killing jutsu
has turned many of his matches
into pure blood baths!
Will this bout also end with
his opponent utterly demolished?
We've got medical personnel
standing by just in case!
( Bakuzan scoffs )
All I do is teach lessons
to those who don't belong here.
Listen up.
When martial artists
trade blows,
it's not some friendly sport.
It's kill or be killed,
life and death.
It--hey!
Saitama: There we go. Boom.
Bakuzan: You're dead.
Referee: Begin!
Announcer: And, with that,
the match is under way!
The question is,
how will charanko fare
against the likes of bakuzan?
Bakuzan: Hmm?
His guard's wide open.
What's with this fool?
Does he want to fight, or what?
Announcer:
Bakuzan boldly moves forward
to close in on charanko!
Bakuzan: Hey, you,
are you an amateur?
Saitama: Yeah.
It's my first time
at one of these things.
How 'bout a little taste
of your martial arts style?
- ( Knuckles cracking )
- Bakuzan: Fine by me.
One full-service execution
coming up,
starting with the legs.
I'll use
my demon sweeper low kick
to shatter your bones
so you never walk again.
Next, your body, starting with
- my bear killer mid-kick...
- Saitama: Oh.
Bakuzan: Followed
by my carnage punch.
Both your arms will break,
and your major organs
will explode.
- Finally, your head.
- Saitama: Uh...
Bakuzan:
My hell-bringing hand chop
will split open
that skull of yours.
You'll go straight--
( Screams )
Saitama:
Don't touch my head, dude!
Announcer:
H-he's outside the ring.
Saitama: Double darn it.
I forgot
to have the match again.
Referee: The fight is over!
Call the doctor!
Bring the stretcher!
Announcer: In all my years,
I've never seen
such a bracket buster!
Bakuzan, a contender
for the championship,
was beaten
by first-time fighter charanko!
Suiryu:
Another single-hit knockout.
All right, then.
I'll do the same thing.
Reporter: We've invited
Mr. Saynuthin to talk to us
about the monster emergencies
occurring in various areas.
Mr. Saynuthin,
what are your thoughts
on the simultaneous monster
attacks going on right now?
At a loss for words, I take it?
( Boy swallows )
Reporter: Wait a minute.
I've been told
we have some breaking news.
The class-a hero
known as lightning genji
was found collapsed
with severe injuries.
Any comment
on this new development?
It seems we're all searching
for the right words.
Man: Hey!
Hey! Pull yourself together!
( Mohican groans ) Ow!
Man: Are you okay, mohican?
This man's son
should be here with him.
They were together.
What happened to the child?
- Where is he?!
- Mohican: Uh...
Woman: Mr. Narinki's son,
waganma,
was kidnapped by monsters.
Man 2: What?! Why?
For what purpose?
Woman: Unknown. But let me
remind you that Mr. Narinki
represents 7%
of the association's funding.
Losing his trust
would be devastating to us.
Man 3: Indeed.
The rescue of waganma
is of the utmost priority.
Put every class-a hero
in the city on it.
Let's find that boy!
- Man 4: But, sir, please.
- Woman: We can't allow
the other monsters
to continue their rampage.
Man 5: Class-s hero metal bat
was just found unconscious.
He's in critical condition.
( Monster laughs )
Come on! What's the matter?
You'll never be able
to hit me like that.
( Genos grunts )
I cannot track his movements.
Monster: So sorry.
Were you looking for me?
Genos: It is not just his speed.
On top of his unique movements
throwing me off,
he is attacking from
the buildings's blind spots.
One last option.
I was hoping
I would not have to use this.
Monster: Oh? You've got
some special ability
you've been squirreling away,
do you?
Are you gonna shoot laser beams
from your eyes or something?
Genos: Originally, I was opposed
to installing this component,
but Dr. Kuseno was right.
Monster: Hunter-killer missiles?
Poison gas?
Genos: In situations where
I face a superior adversary,
I must acknowledge reality
if I am to grow.
Monster: Oh, what could it be?
I sure hope
it's not roach repellent!
( Gags )
What is this?! Huh?
My legs! What have you done?!
Genos: It is
an ultra-strong adhesive.
I am prepared to stop
anything in its tracks,
even an ultra-fast ninja,
but, by using this weapon,
I'd be acknowledging
that his speed poses a problem.
Monster: What are you
talking about?
Genos: Nothing that is
any concern of yours.
Incinerate.
( Monster wails )
Genos: He sacrificed
his legs to escape.
No matter. It is still fatal.
Better return to the stadium.
I might still be able
to watch master's fight.
High-speed object approaching.
The roach?
No. This is something different.
( Gasps )
( Heroes moaning )
Blizzard: Guys, wait.
What are you doing?
Don't fall for
the enemy's tricks so easily!
Super s: You look so cute
when you're panicking.
Unfortunately, these fools
you brought are my pets now.
- ( Blizzard gasps )
- ( Heroes growl )
( Super s laughs )
How does it feel
to have your lackeys taken?
Come on! Resist me more!
Or are you holding back?
( Laughs )
What if I let you join
mistress super s's
harem of slaves?
( Blizzard gasps )
( Heroes snarling )
Saitama: You won't survive
like that, blizzard.
Blizzard: Shut up!
Super s: Even after
taking on so many,
you're still holding your own.
But just how much more
can you take?
( Blizzard gasps )
( Moans )
Super s: Yes!
Time for some real punishment!
( Laughs )
That did the trick.
Now you're mine, body and soul.
And you're one of those
esper sisters. Isn't that right?
Your younger sibling
is the class-s hero
known as terrible tornado,
which means you'll be
just the bait I need
to tempt her
to come and play with me!
She'll make a far better toy.
( Yelps )
Even after all that,
she won't give in.
Such strength of will
I hate girls like her.
( Gasps )
( Screams )
That hurt, you bitch!
I thought I could use you
to snag your little sister,
but forget it!
I'm killing you now!
Blizzard:
Oh, my big sister will come,
even without bait.
( Rumbling )
Super s: What's causing
these tremors?!
Blizzard: Looks like
she was closer than I thought.
She felt the pain
you put me through,
and she's pissed off.
There.
- ( Booming )
- Super s: What the--
something is approaching...
Something terrifying.
- Blizzard: Now you'll meet her.
- ( Super s gasps )
Blizzard: My sister,
terrible tornado.
- ( Squelch )
- ( Monster gasps )
Super s! I'm sorry,
but the heroes
had a monster of their own!
Super s: This is more serious
than I imagined.
We need to retreat and regroup.
Blizzard: That's her.
¶
tornado!
I know it looks bad,
but I'm still fighting this--
tornado:
Oh, don't worry about it.
You can go on home now,
blizzard.
I'll take care
of cleaning up everything.
Super s: Stop her, slaves!
Delay her while I escape!
( Heroes moaning )
Blizzard: Tornado, wait!
Those men are my team!
Don't attack them!
I told you not to attack them.
- ( All moaning )
- Tornado: Come on.
That was barely an attack.
Blizzard: No, that counts.
Tornado: And I wouldn't call
this bunch of nobodies a team.
Those buffoons
are just dead weight.
I don't know
why you waste your time
hanging around
with that class-b club.
( Sighs ) Now look.
The monster got away!
Why'd I stop fighting
to chitchat with you?
There's a ton of monsters
I need to destroy.
Oh, and would you
let the nobodies know,
in real emergencies,
if they don't evacuate the area,
then they're just in the way.
( Blizzard sighs )
( Crowd cheering )
( Snek panting )
I mustn't doubt myself,
so I've tried to keep it
completely out of my mind,
but I can't.
I can never shake it.
( Monster roars )
Wanna eat humans!
Wanna eat human flesh!
Snek: That's far enough!
Now that I,
snakebite snek, have arrived,
I won't let you
lay a finger on anyone!
( Thinking ) Looking back,
I once shone brighter
than anybody.
I felt the pride of being
one of the few real heroes.
I had the power
to protect people,
and it filled my spirit
with purpose.
But slowly,
over time, reality set in.
Try as I might,
there were others
who I could never defeat.
Even among the nameless masses,
there were those out there who
were far stronger than myself.
Are professional heroes
even necessary?
Lately, I haven't been so sure.
If I didn't exist,
if the hero association
didn't exist,
would there be
someone who would step up
and defeat the monsters
in our place?
At the very least,
there seems no need
to protect a man like this.
( Suiryu chuckles )
I liked Max from earlier,
nice and aggressive.
Snek: Hard to believe
from the guy
who's been on his heels
and won't fight back.
Suiryu: You misunderstand me.
I was just checking out
how skilled you are.
Class-a heroes
make a lot of money, I hear.
If your level is all it takes,
then it might be
worth my while.
- ( Snek gasps )
- Suiryu: Just kidding.
Why should I work for money?
( Laughs )
Snek: How'd you
get to be so strong?
Why does a guy like you,
who has no real sense
of purpose, have such power?
Suiryu: Hmm.
Maybe I was just born talented.
Snek: Everything about you
disgusts me.
Suiryu: Back when I trained,
all I did was
keep my master company.
I haven't even
practiced in years.
But I'm curious.
How'd you get to be a hero?
With that level of ability,
I mean.
( Snek sputters )
What was that?
Suiryu: More strong monsters
are appearing every day.
Even performing at your best,
you won't make any difference.
With or without heroes,
those who are going to survive
will survive.
Survival of the fittest
means the weak get weeded out.
It's just
the natural order of things.
Snek: Natural order?
Are you actually suggesting
we ignore the people
being attacked by monsters?
- ( Crowd yelling )
- Woman: What's going on?
Woman 2: Is this
part of the show?
Man: How'd they get
in the hospital?!
Mumen rider: Don't worry!
We'll hold them off here!
Everyone head to the roof!
Suiryu: Whatever happens,
I know that we'll survive.
Man: What the hell's
a monster doing at a prison?
If you came for the boss,
he broke out
to bash you bastards!
Monster: Puri-puri prisoner
is not here?
Doesn't matter.
Snek: And just
who do you mean by "we"?
Suiryu: The strong, of course.
Snek: Wait. You're not--
suiryu: I am. Understand now?
( Crowd yelling )
Saitama: Huh.
They sound excited.
¶
( singing in Japanese )
Monster: Report, gyoro-gyoro.
Tell me.
Have my monsters created chaos?
Gyoro-gyoro: Indeed.
Some casualties were incurred,
but overall
the advantage belongs to us.
The hero association
is in a panic.
Monster: Good.
And what of goketsu?
Gyoro-gyoro:
He's on his way to the venue
where the martial artists
have gathered.
Our confirmed major victories
include the heroes demon cyborg,
metal bat,
and metal knight.
Yet our greatest weapons
still await their turn
to participate.
The monster association's
overwhelming victory
is imminent,
o monster king orochi!
¶