¶
( man cackles )
Now I will cover
the world in darkness!
( Cackles )
- Man #2: Not so fast...
- ( Boy gasps )
- Man #2: Devil Earl!
- ( Monsters gasp )
( Fist creaks )
( Boy sighs ) Aww, man.
That lame theme song
means justice man is here.
Just when it's getting good,
the hero always butts in.
- ( Punches whacking )
- Hang in there!
Don't give up, devil Earl!
Kick justice man's butt!
Justice man: Justice punch!
Devil Earl: Nyaah!
Boy: Darn it!
He got beat again.
It's not fair!
Why doesn't any monster have
a chance against justice man?
What?
Heroes never lose? Really?
Why not? Why does good
always have to win?
That's totally not fair!
Monsters have things
they want, too.
And monsters try.
They try really hard.
So why do they always end up
losing and getting killed?
I root for them.
What about what I think?
I mean, monsters are cool, too.
Why should the popular win
- while the hated lose?
- Garou: While the hated lose?
Both: It's tragic!
Garou: If that's
how the world works,
then I will become
the strongest monster,
and I'll lose to no one.
( Birds squawking )
( Groans ) Huh?
What the hell am I doing here?
What happened last night?
It's all so fuzzy.
¶
¶ hero
( singing in Japanese )
¶ go, go
¶ hero
( singing in Japanese )
¶ go, go
¶ hero
( singing in Japanese )
¶ one punch
man: In regards to last night's
attack on director zeimeet,
it was almost
certainly the work
of the vicious hero hunter,
garou.
Man #2: Then, he's not
just targeting heroes now.
It's the entire association!
Man #3: He was able to defeat
tank top master quite easily,
and the usual protocols
will not dispel fear.
Issue a cautionary memo.
( Marker squeaking )
Man #1: Executives should
remain indoors if possible.
When going out, they must be
accompanied by a class-s hero.
Man #2: Is that realistic?
Class s has been
up to their ears
in dealing with monsters lately.
Man #3: The directors are
the conduits to our sponsors.
Their safety takes precedence.
King: Act as
an executive's bodyguard?
I refuse.
"Why not?"
Because I'm already
in the middle
of a big battle, okay?
( Video game music playing )
My opponent is down,
but I'm not finished.
I'm going to hit the boss
in his secret lair.
Ask someone else.
¶
executive: I'm counting on you
to protect us today,
Mr. Metal bat.
Metal bat: Really? This is what
they call a critical assignment?
Executive: It seems
association executives
are targets, too,
now apparently,
but my boy here simply insisted
on going out
and trying peasant food.
( Boy gasps ) Look, papa!
A plate of pudding's coming by!
Executive: How droll.
Our tab won't even
be 10,000 yen.
What an amusing experience
this is,
trying to make their inferior
cuisine more fun to eat.
Metal bat:
What is this? Am I in hell?!
( Gasps ) Whoa, whoa!
Don't put that back on the belt!
- Boy: Why shouldn't I?
- ( Metal bat growls )
They need these plates
to tally your bill.
Executive: Come, now.
It's only good manners
to return one's plate.
Metal bat: Pretty sure I just
told you not to put them back.
Executive: Is this sea urchin?
The color is off-putting.
Perhaps they have caviar.
Boy: Medium fatty tuna?
Is any kind other than
extra fatty tuna even edible?
Metal bat: Stop doing that!
( Thinking ) One more time,
and this bat tastes blood.
- ( Cell phone buzzing )
- Hmm?
( Gasps )
Executive: Something important?
Metal bat:
It's my little sister!
Uh, hang tight for a sec.
I'll be right back.
¶
I didn't have a choice.
An important assignment
came up out of nowhere.
I'll take you shopping
another time. I promise.
Huh? Where am I now?
Nezumi Sushi.
( Gasps ) No, that's not it!
This really is an assignment.
Oh, come on. Please don't cry.
I'll explain everything later.
( Gasps ) Gotta go.
I'll call back soon.
I'm the one
who should be crying.
Last time I do a favor
for some executive douche bags.
( Rumbling )
Oh, crap! Is it garou?!
Boy: Papa!
Metal bat: Pretty sure
that bug's not him.
Executive: Save my son!
That monster has him!
Centipede: That's
the hero association
executive, all right.
Plant: Then that
must be his kid.
Perfect!
Let's take the runt and bail!
Metal bat: I don't think so.
Neither one of 'em
is going anywhere. Understand?
( Spits )
They haven't
paid their bill yet.
Saitama:
Charanko said he signed up
for this "super fight"
tournament thing on a whim.
What a knucklehead.
But this might do.
There could be some
seriously strong fighters here.
Worker: What name
did you register under?
Saitama: Oh. Uh, charanko.
Worker: All right. Please
write in your fighting style.
Saitama: Fighting style?
Huh. What was it again?
I feel like it's...
Let's see how the tournament
bracket turned out.
Oh.
Some fighters got seeded
this bakuzan guy must be tough.
In the opposite bracket,
looks like suiryu
is the top seed.
Man: What's up?
You're charanko
from the dojo, right?
Saitama: Oh, crap!
Someone who knows charanko!
Man: Hey, what's the matter?
Surely you haven't
forgotten me already, have you?
"Fist of seltzer water
on the rocks"?
Quite the jokester.
Well, I don't blame you
for being nervous.
After all, you never
could beat me, could you?
Charanko: Aww, man.
That jerk better not
be competing in my place.
Nah, he wouldn't
be that stupid.
Oh, actually,
saitama does tend
to be pretty stupid.
- Mumen rider: Saitama?
- Charanko: Huh?
Hey, do I know you, or...
Mumen rider: Tell me,
are you friends with saitama?
Man: Now, I bet you're
thinking to yourself,
"why's a guy like sourface
entering the tournament?"
( Saitama thinking )
Don't know. Don't care.
Just hurry up,
and go somewhere else.
Sourface:
I've got myself two reasons.
The first,
this super fight is ideal
for making a name for myself
as a big-time martial artist.
Master bang was the champion
once, and just look at him.
The second reason, the incident
at the last tournament.
A masked fighter named wolfman
won the championship,
but afterwards the real wolfman
was found unconscious.
The winner was a fake.
And, because of that,
registration under an alias
and use of headwear
was strictly prohibited.
Saitama: Headwear? Wait. Like...
Sourface: You've already lied
about your fighting style,
but that might be
a bit of a gray area.
Saitama: What happens
if they find out?
Sourface: At the very least,
you'd be banned for life.
Who knows?
They might even follow that up
with a heavy fine and a lawsuit,
maybe even have you arrested.
Saitama: Oh, really?
Sourface: Huh?
What's the matter?
No way.
You... ( Chuckles )
Know exactly
who the fake wolfman was, too!
Saitama: I'm safe.
Sourface: I studied his
fighting technique in a video.
There's no doubt.
The fake wolfman was...
Garou.
( Garou chuckles )
So we meet again.
Boy: Huh? Oh, hey, mister!
You out patrolling again?
Garou: I told you
not to call me "mister."
Now lend me that book.
Boy: I told you to get your own.
Garou: Huh?
Boy: Hey, I know.
Let's read it together.
( Garou sighs )
Ah...
Saitama: Garou, huh?
That name keeps popping up.
Sourface: It was six months ago,
right after it went down
and he was expelled.
It had to be him.
Saitama: What went down?
Sourface: You were
skipping classes then,
so you wouldn't know.
It was on a day
when master bang was out.
( Students grunting )
Sourface: Hmm?
- Garou: I'm finished.
- Sourface: Huh?
Garou: There's nothing left
for me to learn here.
It's a waste of time.
Let's fight for real.
Sourface: He'd hidden
his true nature
as he sharpened his fangs.
If it hadn't been for him,
we wouldn't have
had to leave the dojo.
Damn that arrogant bastard!
That's why I'm here today,
to win this tournament...
And get my mojo back.
I have to prove to myself that I
can hold my own against garou.
( Laughs ) But look at you.
I never imagined
master bang's runt
would enter
the super fight tourney.
You think a lot of yourself,
calling yourself
the top disciple.
I'd pump the brakes
if I were you.
Mumen rider: I see.
So you think saitama
might enter this competition
in your place, then?
Charanko: Yeah. An amateur
wouldn't stand a chance
in this tournament.
He'd likely
get himself killed.
Mumen rider:
There's nothing to fear.
Charanko: Huh?
Mumen rider: You're forgetting.
He's a hero.
Sourface: It's so annoying!
If I'd have known
that garou would be expelled,
then I'd never
have left the dojo.
And, if that were the case,
you know who master bang's
top disciple would be.
All sourface, baby.
What you think?
Wanna relive old times
and practice choke-holds
'til you black out again?
Saitama: You left
the dojo, right?
Sourface: So what?
Sourface: Well,
I took on garou by myself.
That's why I'm here,
to get rid of that guy for good.
And if he keeps up
his hero hunting,
we're gonna meet one day.
What I'm trying to say here
is someone who runs off
shouldn't be acting
like a big shot.
( Sourface growls )
You're gonna eat those words.
You hear me?
The super fight
is a one-day tournament.
If by some miraculous chance
you win and move up,
then we'll meet in the ring.
When we do, you're
gonna learn a hard lesson.
You'll find out what it's like
to be in a real fight.
( Door slams )
Saitama: A real fight, huh?
I honestly don't remember
what they're like.
Boy: Did you see that, papa?!
He sure showed those monsters!
Executive: Let me snap a pic,
as the kids say.
Metal bat:
Hey, it's still dangerous.
I gotta get you back.
Centipede:
Venus peopletrap and I
were no match for you,
but we knew that before
the fighting ever started.
You are truly a class-s hero,
metal bat. No doubt about it.
Yet the strong
often become delusional
and mistakenly believe
they're at the top
of the food chain.
I believed that myself once.
Metal bat: You sure do die slow.
Want me to finish you off?
Centipede:
When centisempai appeared,
I knew how wrong I was.
( Rubble crashing )
- Metal bat: Another one of you?
- ( Both whimper )
Centisempai:
Rest now, little one.
I will avenge you.
( Boy yelps )
That thing is so gross!
Metal bat: This one
won't be as easy to squash.
( Executive gasps )
What's that odor?
( Gags )
( Metal bat gasps )
¶
Looks like these things
have nothing to do with garou.
Whatever!
No use thinking about it!
Just smash 'em
and be done with it!
Mumen rider: That's right!
No matter what terror he faces,
he stands up and fights!
- Charanko: Uh...
- Mumen rider: That's why
you don't have
to worry about saitama.
Charanko: Uh...
Mumen rider: He's not like that.
He'd never use a false identity
and break the rules.
He's a hero!
Charanko: Uh, well,
I guess I'll take
your word for it.
Mumen rider: Good call!
( Saitama sneezes )
( Gasping )
( Sighs )
I hate killing time.
Boy: And this one
is watchdog man.
- Cute, isn't he?
- ( Garou chuckles )
Just looks like a guy
in a dog suit to me.
So is he tough?
Boy: Well, of course he is.
He's a class-s hero.
Garou: Class s, rank 12, huh?
Boy: He keeps watch over city q
from his lookout
in watchdog Plaza.
You can always find him
hanging out there.
Garou: Really?
( Sirens blaring )
Announcer: Warning!
Emergency evacuation! Warning!
A monster has appeared
in the shopping district
of city s,
threat level demon.
( Boy gasps )
Announcer:
The class-s hero, metal bat,
is currently
engaging the monster.
Citizens outside are requested
to move indoors quickly.
Boy: Mister, i'm--
garou: You heard what she said.
Hurry up, and get home.
Boy: Okay!
Announcer: We repeat, warning!
- Emergency evacuation! Warning!
- ( Garou chuckles )
- Lafreshidon: Huh?
- ( Metal bat yells )
( Centisempai buzzes )
Centipede parade!
( Metal bat yells )
( Panting )
¶
lafreshidon: He is obstinate.
Centisempai: No wonder
he could beat centikohai.
Metal bat: What are
you disgusting bugs after?
What could they
possibly be worth to you?
( Lafreshidon chuckles )
How about this?
Defeat us, and we may tell you.
( Metal bat gags )
Lafreshidon: No one can escape
my hypno-scent for long.
Centisempai: Excellent!
Metal bat: That was brutal
( centisempai laughs )
Gah!
Eternal rest is yours, hero!
( Metal bat babbling )
( Centisempai laughs ) Daah!
( Bat thunks )
¶
lafreshidon:
Did he just hit himself?
Centisempai: Huh?
He's out of his mind!
( Gasps )
Metal bat: There!
That cleared my head.
( Centisempai gasps )
He's become even more powerful?
Lafreshidon: How was he able
to clear
the sedative so quickly?!
It's not possible!
Metal bat:
Once my fighting spirit's up,
I can take almost anything.
( Both gasp )
Metal bat:
You know, you really
slapped the hell
out of me just now.
But I'm nice,
so I'll let you two
off the hook easy!
( Lafreshidon screams )
Metal bat: Just one whack each,
and we'll call it even!
¶
( Sighs )
It's been a while
since I had to try that hard.
( Gasps ) Ah, crap!
I forgot to find out
what they were after!
Way to space on that one.
- ( Both snoring )
- Metal bat: Doesn't look
like the nimrods were hurt.
Wake up, you two!
Maybe a good smack'll
get you moving.
Hmm?
Hero: We're here to help!
Hero #2: We'll fight
those monsters with you!
Metal bat: Sorry,
but you missed the party.
( Both gasp ) What?!
( Man sighs )
Crisis averted.
Thank you, metal bat.
The director and his son
are safe and sound. Hmm?
- What? Something wrong?
- Man #2: I don't like this.
Centisempai and centikohai
appeared so close together,
which can only mean--
man #1: No, it can't be!
Man #2: How long has it been?
Two years? Maybe less?
- If he appears again--
- man #1: Right.
A few heroes
would never stand a chance.
The entire city
will be leveled.
( Rumbling )
Pineapple: Wait. Is that--
it's the giant bug monster,
centichoro!
That thing
is threat level dragon!
Metal bat: Dragon, huh?
Mohican: I'll request
some class-s assistance.
Let's wait for backup.
Metal bat: The bastard's here
for those two.
Get them to safety
while I keep this creep busy.
Get a move on!
Mohican: You got it!
Metal bat: Now, then...
How do you wanna do this?
Pineapple: Did he see us?!
I can't really tell!
Centichoro: You won't escape!
Metal bat:
Get the hell out of here!
Mohican: Don't look back!
Just keep going!
( Metal bat spits )
- ( Centichoro roars )
- ( Metal bat yells )
- ( Bat vibrating )
- It's friggin' hard!
Centichoro: Pathetic.
¶
( Metal bat sighs )
Full-swing hit, and it
didn't even scratch him,
but the bastard protected
his face-thing when I went in.
That's where I need to bash it.
¶
Mohican: He's coming after us!
Pineapple: Wait! Look! On top!
Mohican: Hell, yeah!
¶
metal bat: Killer move!
Fighting spirit...
Dragon pummeling!
( Centichoro roars )
( Metal bat gasps )
Centichoro:
Centipede undulation!
( Heroes panting )
Mohican: Screw this!
Level dragon's insane!
Pineapple:
Mankind was never meant
to face a monster like this!
( Sirens blaring )
Announcer: Emergency evacuation!
Warning! A new monster
has appeared in city s,
threat level dragon.
( Crowd screaming )
Woman: What happened
to all the heroes?!
Man: It's the end of the world!
Let's get out of here!
Garou: Well, well.
Everyone's all excited.
Threat level dragon
gets announced,
and, boom,
suddenly it's a party.
I wonder if metal bat
will still be alive
by the time I find him.
Huh?
Metal bat?
How'd he--
oh, that's how.
( Scoffs )
So some other monster
got to beat up a class-s, huh?
- I wasted my time.
- ( Metal bat groans )
Back to the grind.
( Garou stammers )
Metal bat, hold up!
- You're not dead yet?
- Metal bat: Huh?
Garou: You being alive
changes things.
( Laughs )
My second class-s hero.
From here on, you face me.
I'm hunting you.
Metal bat: Huh?
Get real, dipshit.
Can't you see that centipede?
Get your ass--
¶
now I see. You're that guy
who's been running around,
calling himself a hero hunter.
Garou: Damn right.
This monster won't fall to you.
( Chuckles )
Metal bat: You can see
I'm busy here.
But, sure,
I can spare a little time
and crack you wide open.
( Singing in Japanese )
Woman: Whoa! City s
is at threat level dragon.
Woman #2: Think everyone'll
be okay there?
Man: Ladies, pardon me.
Got a question for you.
Headed to super fight?
If so, would you mind
if I tag along?
Woman #2: Wait. Aren't you--
woman #1: It's him!
Man: So, yeah? Cool.