Pardon me.
Excuse me... sir?
Oh, uh...
Can I help you?
Yes. Where is the entrance
to the Uffizi Gallery?
Yeah... You go right
through that archway
and through the doors.
Thanks. I appreciate your help.
Okay. Let's go.
That's the Neptune Fountain.
It was by Ammannati.
Ammannati?
Yup.
It's a marvelous
piece of work.
Nah...
Personally, I think
Ammannati was just better off
being Michelangelo's
assistant.
My name is Jean
Louis Bataille...
I sell cosmetics out of
Paris. What about you?
Oh, I'm Filippo Adani...
I work in, uh... finances.
Are you on
vacation?
Well, I'm on a
business trip and...
I figured it would
be a good idea
to bring my sister Florence
with me to see the city.
I thought she would
enjoy Firenze.
Huh... Florence,
eh? Tell me, Jean...
Was one of your parents
born here in Italy?
Well... Actually, my
mother was born here...
How did... How
did you know that?
Florence comes from
the name Firenze.
And the name Jean
can be traced
all the way back
to John the Baptist.
He's Firenze's
guardian saint.
Wow... So, did you come
to Florence on business?
Me? No. I'm on
vacation too...
I've worked solid for
the past three years
without a
day off...
so I drove from Milan to spend
a week at the galleries.
That statue there is
Giovanni da Bologna's
Rape of the
Sabine Woman.
All three of those
figures in the statue
were carved out of one
gigantic piece of marble.
As legend has it,
when Rome was being built,
the city was overflowing
with rowdy men
and there weren't enough
women to go around.
So the men would invite
people from neighboring towns
to a feast,
and in turn would steal
the women for themselves.
[Rico] They would
really steal the women?
This isn't a good story
for a young girl.
You sure do
know your art...
Not really.
Since we're both
at the gallery,
would you be interested in
spending the afternoon with us?
Oh... you don't want to
spend the day with me...
I'd like
that a lot.
[Jean] So, Filippo... You
seem well versed in art.
Did you
ever study it?
Actually, yes. I used to be an
art student here in Firenze.
[Jean] Ahh, I
figured that.
So did you ever grow
tired of this gallery?
[Filippo] No,
not at all.
I would visit
here quite often
while I was
attending art school.
The beauty of this gallery...
as for art in general,
is that your
mood for that day
can affect your
overall experience...
Making you see and feel
things you haven't before.
Florence... Are you enjoying
this? You look a little bored.
No. I'm not
bored at all.
Some of the more
difficult things
I have a hard
time understanding.
But when I look at
paintings or sculptures...
It gives me goose bumps.
I get lost in the artwork.
You're a very perceptive
little girl, Florence.
You must get ecstatic
when you hear the names
Botticelli or Lippi.
Lippi?
Well, you know who
Botticelli is, right?
His very first instructor
was named Filippo Lippi.
Filippo?
Yeah.
It's starting to
get crowded in here.
We are at the Uffizi. Would
you expect anything else?
Want to
move on?
So what do
you think?
Are those
two tourists?
Maybe. Though they could be
from the Social Welfare Agency.
Oh, you mean
that order
to keep our eye out
for little girls, huh?
Yeah.
If we're supposed to be
worried about children,
then forget walking
around outside.
They're all
over the place.
I got near her earlier.
It looked like she was trying
to hide something
in her coat.
Really? It was probably just
a stuffed animal or something.
Hmm, Maybe.
I can't see her
being a threat.
Take a look at her
hands, they're like silk.
Not what one would expect
from a trained assassin.
Should we wait until
he's alone tonight?
It can't wait
that long...
Tell the guys
to grab him
if he wanders off
somewhere by himself,
but to be
conspicuous.
Of course,
Christiano.
This is an art
gallery, Guglielmo.
Are you trying to insult
Italy's treasures on purpose?
No, I...
I didn't...
Tell them there
will be no gunfire
in any galleries
or churches...
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
Hey,
Filippo...
Yeah?
I just remembered
something and I have to go
make a phone
call for business.
While I'm gone, would you mind
keeping an eye on her for me?
Maybe show her
around some more?
Sure... I'd
be delighted.
I may be awhile, so
please take your time.
I'll meet up with
you guys at the exit.
Florence... You stay
with Filippo, okay?
'Kay.
[Guglielmo] Yes, I realize
this whole city is filled
with churches
and galleries,
but it's what he said.
Look, it was an order
straight from Christiano...
Alright...
Don't forget...
Where the hell in
this godforsaken town
are we supposed
to attack?
Don't move...
Drop the phone.
Alright.
Listen... Who are
you working for?
Bigliazzi? Or are you
with the R.F. scumbags?
Don't try
anything stupid...
Unless you want me to cut
your neck from ear to ear.
No... You wouldn't dare
do something like that.
Why's
that?
You police
have your rules.
You can't just go
around slicing necks.
I can kill you
for two reasons.
First off, I'm
no police officer.
And second... I can't
stand terrorists.
You used to study art in
school, right, Filippo?
Yep...
I sure did.
Then why didn't you
become an artist yourself?
There's quite
a few reasons
The main ones being I had no
artistic talent to begin with,
and because I had to
take on my father's work.
You see, I was born with
a knack for mathematics.
So, that's the
path that I chose.
You obviously
really love art...
so what's stopping
you from painting now?
I'm not getting
any younger,
and opportunities can be
difficult to come by at my age.
There's just
no time.
But what about you? What do you
want to be when you grow up?
Gee, I...
Think about it all
you want, Florence.
Huh?
You're young. The possibilities
before you are endless.
Your brother seems like
a really great guy.
I'm sure he'll let you
experience all sorts of things
while you're
still young.
Yeah... My brother...
He really is a great guy.
Ready to
talk now?
I'll ask
again...
Who are you
working for?
The Republican
Faction.
Why are you
following Filippo?
To recover Mr. Bigliazzi's
private ledger,
and then
take Adani out.
See, that
wasn't so hard.
Up.
[phone ringing]
[Operator] Ministry of
Tourism. Firenze Office.
It's Jean from
Section Two.
I'm currently
in the Uffizi.
There's a man taking a nap
in an off-limits bathroom
on the east
side, last stall.
Get him out
of here ASAP.
There will likely
be one more incident,
so prepare a car and
keep the police busy.
Sorry I
took so long.
No worries.
Hi, Florence.
Did you
behave yourself?
Yes.
So. Where would you
like to go next?
I'm getting a
little tired...
How about we go somewhere
quiet to relax.
Good idea.
Come.
We're dealing with the
R.F. Exterminate them all.
I understand.
[Jean] These back
alleys are nice.
It's a side of Italy tourists
don't always get to see.
Yeah.
Hello there,
Mr. Adani.
Is the ledger
inside the case?
Hand it
over quietly
and Mr. Bigliazzi will look
past this little episode.
And come back with
us to Milan...
Otherwise...
Some innocent people
will have to pay.
You wouldn't!
Filippo.
You're gonna be fine.
Damn it!
Filippo! Run!
You take that way.
Right.
Rico,
quick!
What's going on?
Who are you people?
I'll spare you the
lengthy explanation.
We're with an
intelligence agency...
And you...
You're Mr. Bigliazzi's
personal accountant.
So you knew.
[Jean] The ledger
you took...
It proves that he's
funneling money into the R.F.?
That's right.
Is there...
anything else?
I wanna know...
why they're so eager
to put a bullet
into your head.
A few days ago I
overheard them planning
a terrorist attack on Rome...
I'm sure they're trying to stop
me from going to the police.
Is that right?
Don't worry.
We'll have plenty of time
later to talk about that.
[Jean] What made you
betray your employer?
[Filippo] I'm what you'd
call a goody-two-shoes.
I've never got a
parking ticket
or even jumped on a
train without paying.
When I quit art school
and went into accounting
like my father wanted,
I got more than
I bargained for.
I soon became
aware that my father
had been evading his taxes
for the past 20 years,
and was putting that money back
into various terrorist groups.
I didn't want any part of it,
so I ran off with the ledger.
I knew Bigliazzi was in cahoots
with the police and that...
if I was going to
be assassinated...
I wanted to
see Firenze
just one more time
before it happened.
Jean.
Multiple footsteps
coming this way.
Filippo... I assume you
avoided military service?
Conscription is the
duty of all citizens...
I was with the border
patrol for 13 months.
Then you know
how to use this.
You see
him?
No.
Jose.
Where are you?
[Jose] We're standing
by near your location.
Okay... We're heading
to the Grazie Bridge...
Let's meet
up there.
[Jose]
Copy that.
Rico... You and Filippo
head through the courtyard
and make your way
to the Arno River.
Grazie Bridge will
be on your left.
Yes.
Here.
Grab my hand.
[Filippo] Florence.
Was what you said
at the Uffizi
a lie, too?
[Rico] I'm no good at lying,
so I let Jean do it for me.
That's good.
I see them.
Go.
[Jean]
Hurry.
Come on... You
have to keep up.
We can't let them get away.
Christiano will kill us!
I know!
I don't want any tourists
getting involved with this...
Let's lure them to a
deserted part of town.
No problem.
Jose... Can I have
permission to open fire?
Just a few
more seconds.
How about now?
Yeah...
Go ahead.
Hang in there... We'll have
you at a doctor in 10 minutes.
I was...
prepared for this...
I'm satisfied to die in
such a beautiful city...
I even got to say goodbye
to Botticelli and Lippi.
I've... I've grown
tired of this life.
Filippo.
I won't stop you if you
want to die that much...
but I think you dying
would be a waste.
I think Botticelli and Lippi
would want you to live...
They'd want you
to draw and paint
for the whole world
to see... And...
Besides, Firenze is
such a beautiful city.
[Filippo] Yes.
That it is.