[Doctor]
All right, Henrietta.
How have you been feeling
lately? Any trouble sleeping?
Or nausea, slight
fevers or muscle aches?
None of those,
Mr. Bianchi.
You need to be
honest, Henrietta.
It's for your own sake.
I'm telling the truth.
I've been feeling fine lately.
So then... are you confident
you can listen to your handler?
And control
your emotions?
Yes, sir.
I'll try my
very best.
Henrietta's as cute as
ever. What a darling.
You got that right.
Kinda makes me wish
I had a daughter
of my own.
If I could have my way,
I'd round up all the girls
before you men could get
your hands on them...
And start the best
ballet company
that Europe
has ever seen.
You sure they'd
enjoy that?
Of course
they would.
Hey, Amadeo. I think
I have a better idea
of what to do
with these girls.
Oh yeah? What's
that, Giorgio?
We should put 'em
on a soccer team.
That's
perfect!
You Italian men
are all the same.
Now, now... You all
know my Henrietta
is not your
play-thing.
Easy there, tiger.
We're just joking around.
Yeah, heavies like
us don't know jack
about taking care
of a little girl,
but that's
obvious, huh?
Alright... I'm done
with Henrietta...
Could you bring in Angelica
in about 10 minutes?
Yes, sir.
Of course.
Henrietta.
I'm going to ask
you one more time
since Ferro
left the room...
Are you honestly
feeling okay?
Doctor... Please don't
keep me from working.
It's all there
is for me to do.
I've only killed 4
people this month.
But the month before I
killed at least ten...
That's probably more
than Triela's got.
So you're lying? About
not feeling alright?
I'm fine!
But if... if I don't say
how many I've killed,
I'm afraid you'll think
I'm not usable anymore.
You always report to
someone about that, right?
Man, that girl
is delicate.
So please...
Listen,
Henrietta.
Steady your
emotions.
Once you can do that, you
won't need to worry anymore.
Alright.
If I could only make that
girl into a ballerina...
[Giorgio] Olga.
You're up next.
[Olga]
I win.
Come on in.
Well, good morning,
Angelica... Come and sit down.
Do you
remember me?
You're Doctor...
Bianchi.
That's my name, but it says
it right here on my ID card.
You look like you're
doing pretty well lately.
Oh, I finally
made it!
Aww. Don't tell me my sweet
Henrietta is already done!
Don't even bother
asking, Priscilla.
Jose. You'll have to lend
me Henrietta sometime.
I found a great boutique
that she would adore.
[Doctor]
Angelica...
How many people do you
recognize in these pictures?
Number 6 and
number 9...
Number 13...
and number 20.
Doctor. How many
have I forgotten?
Have I lost any... important
people in my head?
It's just a little test.
Nothing to worry about.
Do you remember
this story?
Once upon a time, there was
a kingdom made of pasta.
In this kingdom there lived
a prince who loved pasta,
and would eat it for
every meal of every day.
[Priscilla] That
brings back memories.
Well then...
That ring a bell?
[Angelica] Doctor. Can I
start working again soon?
I'm not the one who
decides that, Angelica.
You'll have
to ask Marco.
Okay.
Jose, are you a little
more satisfied now
that you know what
she's thinking?
The only reason I allowed you
to watch Henrietta's interview
was because you
requested it...
Don't waste your time
looking for more knowledge.
What you need
is faith.
And Marco...
The reason I forced you
to sit through this
was to hopefully
renew your interest
in being
Angelica's handler.
What happened to
your enthusiasm?
Come on,
Bianchi...
You of all
people should know
how I ended up
feeling this way.
We went through
it together!
I worked long and hard to
teach her everything I could,
but it was those damn
cyborg engineers.
The conditioning
process wiped her mind!
Everything I
taught was useless!
Look, maybe you can
rationalize it in your head
because you're
a doctor,
but can you honestly say you'd
have no problems with this
if you were a
Handler yourself?
I understand
how painful it is.
They're studying the effects
of the implants as we speak...
Soon the side effects
will be avoidable
and possibly
even reversible.
Perhaps Angelica could
hold out until they're done.
But abandoning all
hope for her is wrong.
[Angelica]
Marco!
They finally
released me today...
Now we can be
together again.
The doctor gave me this book
to read. It's pretty good.
But... when can
I start work?
Your unsteadiness is a
handicap you can't afford.
It's much too
early for work.
Go change clothes and
start running laps.
[Marco] All of the girls from
the Social Welfare Agency
are far
from happy,
but they're not
necessarily unhappy,
if they even know
the difference.
A few
years ago,
there was an unfortunate
little girl named Angelina.
Hi, Pero.
[Marco] Her own parents
tried to kill her.
Apparently right before her
father's business went bankrupt
he took out a large
insurance policy on Angelina
and was looking
to cash in.
Around that same
time, I was...
[Patricia] So they
dismissed you because
your eyesight
got worse?
But I thought it was
a workplace injury.
I don't care
about the job,
I'm just happy that
I can still see.
Even if I my eyesight is bad,
I can still see your eyes.
Oh, Patricia...
They're the most beautiful
things I've ever seen.
I must say, you have quite an
impressive resume here, Marco.
Consider
yourself hired.
Thank you, sir. This
is a great honor.
Oh, and by the way,
do you like children?
Uh, yeah. Children
are wonderful.
So, who is this new
organization working under?
The State
Department?
Doctor Bianchi highly
recommended you, Marco...
Did... he not tell you
anything about this job?
He just said I'd like the job
and he couldn't talk about it.
Sounds like you have a lot
of trust in his judgment.
Come over here. I'll
explain your job to you.
Daddy...
Mommy... Pero.
Why am I
in this bed?
And who are you?
You are in a
hospital right now
that's part of the
Social Welfare Agency.
A hospital?
That's strange...
I remember going on
an errand with Pero...
then this car
came after me...
Next thing I knew
I couldn't move.
The doctors used their
magic to help you get better.
Where's my
daddy? And Pero?
Your parents had
to do something,
so they'll be
back later.
And Pero is
with them too.
Are you gonna
stick me with that?
Why? Do you not
like getting shots?
Of course not. No kid
likes getting shots.
How about if I
tell you a story
so you won't even
know it's happening...
Now let's see
what we've got...
Do you
like pasta?
I love it.
I'll tell you... about
the Prince of Pasta.
A long,
long time ago,
there was a great
kingdom made of pasta.
In this kingdom there lived
a prince who loved pasta
and he would eat it
every single day.
This was great for him,
but there was a problem.
There was only one fork
in the entire land,
so the prince always had to
eat his pasta all by himself.
Well, even the most delicious
pasta has no flavor
when you're forced
to eat it alone.
It still hurt anyway.
Yeah, I should
have figured that.
Well, keep going.
What happens with
the pasta man?
I'll wait to tell you more when
it's time for your next shot.
Now you behave
yourself, okay?
[Marco] The nearly dead
Angelina was reborn
as a cybernetic
test subject.
I decided to rename
her Angelica...
Her parents were the
scum of the earth
for what they
did to her,
but I felt they were right
in calling her an angel.
And who's the little cutey,
Marco? Is she your daughter?
She is the most adorable
thing I've ever seen.
You two both know
she's not my daughter.
Angelica is our
newest employee.
Oh,
okay.
They call me the missionary
of love, Amadeo... It's a...
Well, I'm the fallen
angel of love, Priscilla.
[Marco] Back then, Section 2
was in its infancy.
We had under ten
people on staff.
We never got any real work,
so we had plenty of spare time.
So how
is she?
Almost too good. Those
implants are incredible.
Does she ever ask you any
questions about her family?
Yeah,
sometimes.
But whenever
she brings it up
I pull out the
Pasta Prince story.
Once she hears that,
she forgets all about it...
It's kind of
funny because
I keep making up the
story as I go along.
Oh, you mean you made up that
story about the pasta guy?
I just always
assumed it was from
one of Patricia's
children's books.
Have you told her
about your new job yet?
No. I'll get around
to it next week.
Welfare? I thought you were
with the military police.
Well, remember that old
friend of mine, Bianchi?
He's the one
who got me in.
So what is it exactly
that you do for them?
How should I put it? I kind
of take care of children.
That's great news. We can see
each other more often now...
It's the perfect
job for you, Marco.
[Marco] Every time
I saw Angelica,
she would pester me about
the rest of the story.
I had completely
run out of ideas,
so I had some of my colleagues
help me thicken up the plot.
We really had nothing
else to do at the time.
All the fairy tales
I've ever heard
have had a
princess at least.
And maybe the princess could
be kidnapped by a dragon.
A dragon, huh? I don't know...
Seems kind of ordinary.
[Priscilla] Well we're not
professionals, you know,
and it's not like the
story has to be complex.
[Giorgio] What are former
military and intelligence
agents doing
yapping about this?
Ah, who the hell cares?
Nothing better to do.
I wish they'd get that
girl into combat shape
so we can get back
into the field.
I'm sick of
waiting around.
This storytelling is
easier than I thought.
Just as Giorgio
was hoping,
Angelica's implants were
finished a short time later.
By the time Prince Pasta
had met Princess Pizza,
Section 2 was finally
strong enough
to be used in
anti-terrorist operations.
Why did you name
the prince Pasta?
Because only the prince of the
pasta kingdom can eat pasta...
There's only one fork available
in the whole kingdom...
so only one person
can be named Pasta.
In all this time that
you've been away at work,
the last thing
I expected you
to be doing was writing a
fairy tale for a little girl.
So, uh... what are
you writing down?
This all sounds very
interesting to me
so I wanted
to take notes...
Marco... Can't you
tell me where you work?
I'd really
like to know.
The Social
Welfare Agency...
It's your typical
government job.
Is that...
Is that so?
Yep.
Spread your feet apart
about shoulder's width...
and be sure your arms are
firmly locked in place.
Don't touch the trigger
until you're ready to shoot.
Now, go ahead
and take a shot.
Don't let the sound or
recoil startle you.
Wow! That's an impressive
first shot for a girl your age.
Those cybernetic implants
really are amazing.
Hey, Priscilla. Just riding
around wasting time again?
What's with the
stealthy sunglasses?
Hey, give me
some credit here...
I just finished hand
to hand combat training.
You mean you train just
like me, Priscilla?
Normally, I'm just a boring
intelligence analyst,
but I figure if I'm going to be
hanging around with you guys,
I should toughen
myself up a little bit.
Strength brings
possibilities.
Possibilities?
That's right...
Possibilities that can be used
for good or
bad things.
I wanted to help you just
like the Pasta Prince
saved Princess Pizza,
but from the looks of it,
you should be protecting me.
So tell me,
Angelica...
Did you find it scary shooting
a gun for the very first time?
No. It was something I had to
do, so I really enjoyed it.
This conditioning creeps
me out sometimes.
Man... What the
hell's your problem?
We do nothing but
baby sit all day
and I'm sick
and tired of it.
So? Take a look
at your paycheck.
It's not a
bad day's work.
You know, I get the
feeling you're just here
to hit on chicks,
you marine trash!
Tell me, Giorgio, are all
ex-army as pinheaded as you?
Do you really love
murder that much?
Shut up!
Looks like the little baby
wants to pick a fight.
Come on!
[Jean] If I could have it
my way I'd fire you both,
but the Agency doesn't
see it that way.
I'll make you
suffer instead...
I'm sending you to
army operations
for the next
3 months...
If you both want to
act like macho thugs
you can do
it there.
[Both]
Yes, sir!
I guess I tested
the possibilities
that Priscilla was
talking about...
Do you think
I failed?
Not at all. You did
great, Angelica,
and I am so
proud of you.
[Marco] Ironically, this
incident convinced the Agency
to put the
cybernetic implants
into a real life test, and soon
enough Section 2 was in action.
It was after that test that
we first started learning
of some of the
negative side effects
to the cybernetic
transformations.
They're so pretty.
Yeah.
Angelica.
Amadeo! Giorgio!
Hey, you're finally back.
Those 3 months seemed
like an eternity.
You guys brought
it on yourselves.
Yeah, we know...
Angelica. Here.
Come on...
Apologize.
Yeah, thanks,
I know...
I'm really sorry
about what happened.
And what happened?
I must have missed it.
I have to admit
I'm shocked.
I thought you two would
be together forever.
Doctor Bianchi...
What is it that Marco
actually does
for his job?
I'm not
at...
You're not at
liberty to tell me?
He said the same
thing to me...
And the whole while
I could still smell
the gunpowder
on him.
I can't live my
life with someone
who may or may not
come home alive...
All I want is a simple
man with a normal job.
Oh!
What ever happened to
that story he made up?
The one about
the Pasta Prince.
Right... He finished it and
it turned out really well...
We actually all pitched
it and helped him out.
You know, I never got
the chance to hear
the finished story.
Would you mind telling it
to me? If that's alright...
I'd... really love to
turn it into a book.
[Marco] I stopped telling
Angelica the story
a while back.
I don't want to think that
everything I did for her
back then was in vain.
Poor girl. She no longer
remembers the story.
Do one more lap and then
we'll call it a day.
Yes, sir.