[Jose] Don't make a move
until I've determined
that the mark is inside.
[Henrietta]
Yes, Jose.
If I don't ID this guy, then
we walk out of here, quietly.
Okay.
Good morning, sir.
I apologize for intruding like
this. Do you have a minute?
No. What do you want?
Just a few moments
of your time.
I am a reporter
from Libero Italia.
What is it you're reporting?
I heard that Mr. Scallo of
the Costelo Company was here.
I would love to
get an exclusive.
Yeah, well, there ain't
nobody here by that name.
So, good luck finding
your interview.
Wait...
I'm positive that
he's in this building.
And I told you that you
got the wrong room, chief.
You hard of hearing?
No...
Then maybe it's a learning
disorder. Your guy ain't here!
Sorry, I...
Now, get lost before
I pop your eyes out
and make your
sister watch!
[Head Baddie] Louie,
what's going on--
Hey--
Throw your grenade!
Take him.
Let's pack up
and go home.
[Jose] Now
you've done it.
[Jose] Ferro... The
mission has failed.
I repeat: Mission
has failed.
[Ferro] Roger.
We're on our way.
Yeah.
Henrietta, why did
you lose control?
Uh...
This isn't
like you...
I've never seen you
lose it like that.
Your arm's been hit.
Are you okay?
Yes...
[Jose] Let's go.
Right.
[Henrietta]
Jose...
[Jose] Is your
arm hurting?
I only--
I just wanted to
help you, Jose.
[Jose] We'll have a doctor
take a look at that arm
as soon as
we get back.
[Jose] Officially, the Social
Welfare Agency is a
government-sponsored
corporation that's
in the business
of saving lives.
At least
that's the ruse.
In reality, it's an agency
on the fringe of technology.
They give terminal patients
another shot at life
using cybernetic
implants.
This conditioning process
then shapes the patient
into an efficient
machine for handling
all of the government's
dirty work.
How's she
coming along?
Do you think you'll be
able to fix her, doctor?
[Doctor] The damage
was minimal.
The bullet shaved off some skin
and artificial muscle tissue.
We won't need to
replace the arm.
That's good to hear.
Don't
misunderstand...
She'll need surgery every
time she sustains injuries.
The conditioning process takes
a huge toll on their bodies.
If she continues to
suffer damage, she,
or any of the units
for that matter,
could grow dependant on
the reconstruction process
or suffer from severe
memory dysfunction.
So, you're saying...
Any of our implants are
replaced with little effort.
They're designed
that way.
But their impact
on the brain
and other living
tissue is substantial.
What happened out
there today, anyway?
People are saying
that she lost it,
ignored her orders
and spun out of control.
[Jose] I don't know.
She claims she killed those
people to protect me.
That's a little disturbing.
Sounds like a lost
cause if you ask me.
[Doctor] Jose, I know you're
fond of this girl.
You think she's
special somehow.
So, don't you think
you should increase
her level of
conditioning?
[Doctor] I mean, treating
a cyborg assassin
like a normal
little girl?
Come on, that just
doesn't seem natural.
[Jose] Children brought into
the agency undergo
what they call 'conditioning'
in addition to
their physical modifications.
Fortunately, for her,
the conditioning erased any
and all memories of her past.
Good and bad.
Henrietta, let's go.
Coming.
[Ferro] It's nothing. Just
fill out the location
and the reason
for the trip.
And, just sign here...
[Jose] Okay.
A day pass?
Yeah.
Where's your field
trip headed?
Oh... Just around...
Anything else?
The pomodoro
there is superb.
Today you learn
that not only
must you study and
train for work,
but you also have to
learn how to act properly
in the outside world.
To blend in.
Yes...
When you drink tea, hold
the saucer close to the cup
so it doesn't rattle
Yes...
Henrietta!!!
[Jose] Let go of him and
take your seat.
Yes sir.
Are you all right?
I'm terribly sorry.
I Hope this helps.
Uh, thanks.
Now, if you
don't mind,
cancel the Grappa and
bring out dessert.
Yes sir. Yes sir.
Did I do
something wrong again?
Let's just continue
with our meal, shall we?
Okay.
[Jose] As
time passed,
I began to put in more
effort with Henrietta.
[Jose] Now pay attention.
To do a job, any job,
you have to learn many
different things.
Every successful job is
just the completion
of many smaller,
simpler tasks...
I'm going to start giving
you notes to study each day.
[Henrietta] Okay.
Make sure the muzzle doesn't
stick out over the edge...
stay down as low
as you can...
And if your rifle
doesn't have a bipod,
then you'll have to grip
that barrel tight
with your
bracing hand.
Anything closer than
six hundred meters,
you aim for the head.
Anything past six hundred,
aim for the center
of the body.
What?
Take a look at the sky.
See the little
dot by that cloud?
Can you tell me
what that is?
No, sir. Sorry.
How about a guess?
Come on, anything will do.
Who knows? Maybe
it's a magic pixie.
Is it an airplane?
That's a good answer...
In wars past,
plenty of people mistook
that light for a plane...
But what if it were
night right now?
What would you
think then?
A star?
Close. It's the planet Venus,
not far from Earth's orbit.
Make sure you don't
look directly at the sun
with that thing.
Of course, we'd probably
need something
a bit more powerful if
we were going to shoot
a Venusian in the head.
Jose...
You know everything,
don't you?
[Doctor] Are we awake?
[Doctor]
No baths.
No baths until that skin
on your arm takes hold.
What's the matter? You
have bad dream?
I don't think
I know.
The tears just started
pouring out of nowhere.
[Triela]
Henrietta!
Rico just
told me...
You flipped your lid
out there today.
I couldn't control
it. I just snapped.
Triela...
I don't know
what to do.
Don't sweat it.
Hey, I know! We can go have
a drink in Claes' room.
A drink?
Yeah. She's got
the best tea,
and I swear she puts
magic in her cakes.
[Triela] You just wanted
to make him proud of you.
That's all.
Yeah... I guess so.
[Claes]
But Triela,
isn't that the only
thing any of us can do?
We all seek approval.
And if I were him
that kind of devotion
would make me feel
uncomfortable.
Hey, but it's okay...
'Have fun while
you're still young,'
that's what I always say.
Is that so? I thought
that was from TV.
No, those are
my own words.
[Jose] Henrietta,
are you in there?
Yes--
Come in, please.
So... How's that arm
of yours doing?
Fine... It still feels kind of
heavy and I'm not used to it,
but it's going
to work.
I'd like you to join me on the
roof of the main building.
Okay, I
will.
It's cold out,
so put this on.
Are you sure that I'm
allowed to accept this?
I'll be waiting for
you on the roof.
Glad you could
make it.
Come check
this out.
What's that?
A telescope?
[Jose] Isn't
she beautiful?
I wanted to be able to
show you the stars...
and not through
a rifle scope.
This is... This is the first
time I've seen stars...
[Henrietta] What
made you do this?
I haven't seen a better
night for stargazing
in a long
very time.
And it's your reward for
all of your hard work today.
You're not angry?
About today?
Do you want me to be?
Take a look...
Orion's bright tonight.
[Jose] In Greek mythology,
Orion was mistakenly killed
by his love,
the goddess Artemis...
Stricken with grief over
her love's death...
She carried Orion's
body high into the sky
on her silver
Moon-chariot,
and she left him in
the darkest place
in the heavens where he
would shine the brightest.
[Jose] Such a sad story.
[Henrietta]
Jose...
You know everything,
don't you?
[Jose] Yeah. Yeah, I do.