Henrietta?
Would you mind if...
Can I watch as we leave.
Better hurry, We depart
in five minutes... Come on.
We should arrive in
Sicily by in the morning.
Um, Jose?
What is it?
I don't understand
why we're going away
like this on such
short notice?
You haven't had a
break in a long time.
We all need time away
from work now and again.
but This is the first time
I've gone away on a vacation
that wasn't planned
well in advance.
I'm sure the chief just
wanted to be on the safe side.
Why, has
something happened?
Elsa has been murdered.
She was murdered...
Her body was discovered
early yesterday.
She and Lauro were attacked
outside a small town.
They haven't found
who did it yet,
but it's just a
matter of time.
What about Lauro?
He was killed, too.
Lauro's dead-
Henrietta...
It's good...
At least Elsa and
Lauro are together...
That way she
won't be lonely.
They were found in a park,
together, yesterday morning.
Damn, that's
disgusting.
Looks like they were probably
murdered late last night.
The male runs an
import firm in Rome,
the female's
his daughter.
It doesn't appear to
be motivated by theft,
his wallet's
full of cash.
It's odd... Why would the
killer leave his gun behind?
Good question,
you don't see expensive
pistols like that everyday.
Inspector Baracchi!
What'cha
got?!
There's a couple
of agents here
from Intelligence
to investigate.
Intelligence Agents?
Well, well... This is
getting better every minute.
Who's the officer
in charge here?
I'm Inspector Baracchi...
So tell me, What did we do
to get Intelligence
all the way out here?
We have reason to believe
this may be related
to an ongoing
investigation.
We'll take over all
contingencies from here.
You'll find all the necessary
paperwork's been handled.
Fine- it's
all yours.
Don't you think it's odd for
them to show up like that?
How would Intelligence
even know find out?
A little bird?
If they want to clean
up the mess, fine by me.
Although, they do strike
me as a little odd.
Those guys seem way too
organized to be regular Intel.
But, they got the papers
signed by the right people.
Let's just let
sleeping dogs lie.
Is that one
of our cyborgs?
Yes sir, It's
definitely Elsa.
Shot in
the head...
execution-style.
Were they working out
on an assignment...
or were they just in the
wrong place at the wrong time?
The log says they went
out for personal reasons.
At this time, there's no
way of knowing who did it.
If they were hit because
of their affiliation
with the agency, it could
be R.F. or Southern Mafia.
Or, another agency.
I want the killers
found immediately.
Yes, sir.
What about the press?
Don't worry, it
won't get covered.
Ferro's already taken
care of the media.
Get the bodies out of here
as soon as the
evidence is gathered.
I have to get back and
report this to the director.
Understood.
You needed to see me?
Ahh.
Have you heard about what
happened this morning?
I heard something
about a puppet
from Section 2
being attacked.
One of our men was
killed as well...
They still don't know
who's responsible.
That's what happens when you
go out for a Sunday drive.
I want you to look
into the situation.
This is might be a good chance
to put pressure on Section 2.
Section 1 will hold
it's own investigation.
Uh... So, What do
you want me to do?
I don't like the
idea of cyborgs
running around
killing people.
They say its the way of
the future, I disagree.
Your report could recommend
the termination of Section 2.
I understand.
I want you to check
out these cyborgs...
Find out what they're
really up to.
Yes...?
Yes, sir.
Yeah... Right.
Section One's investigating?
No, I understand. I'll
cooperate fully. Of course.
They're here now.
This is Elenora Gabrielli,
I'm Pietro Fermi.
I've been expecting you.
Good to meet you.
And who's this?
Rico.
My cyborg.
Rico...? Isn't that
a boy's name?
Each cyborg is named
by her Handler.
We can give them
whatever name we want.
She have a last name?
No.
So, what exactly have
you guys come up with
as far as
possible suspects.
We're still
running it down...
But, in our
particular business
we tend to have
enemies everywhere.
And you insist on
having cyborgs
do all the
killing for you?
They're more efficient killers
than any human I've known.
They don't think, or feel,
they just do. They just kill.
You make it sound as if
these cyborgs you developed
were the perfect
killing machines.
Effective but not perfect.
Their eyes are the weak spots.
Hit them in the brain and
they die like anyone.
But that's the
rare instance.
The problem with
what you see here
is that no fratello has been
eliminated like this one.
Fratello...?
Ah, like siblings.
So, are you saying
these cyborgs
just follow the
orders they're given?
They're never free to
exercise their own judgment
when they go out
on a mission?
Every Handler is free to train
his cyborg as he sees fit
but strict discipline and
conditioning are used to ensure
that every one of them
does their job right.
But they do think
for themselves,
especially when their
Handler is in danger.
They would die
protecting him.
Interesting...
So they're not
just puppets.
Was there anything unusual
or out of the ordinary
that happened during any
of their recent missions?
Nothing was
reported.
Okay, what about
them as a team?
Did they work
well together?
They were
very effective.
Rico, put
the gun away.
Fermi... I understand your
curiosity about the cyborgs
but if you weren't
with the Agency,
you'd be dead
right now.
So, now you know what
makes the cyborgs tick.
Well then... Elsa died but
failed to protect her Handler.
It appears Elsa fired two
rounds at the assailant.
Have you found
the slugs?
Our people are combing
the entire area.
If she
hit anyone,
there could be traces of
blood we can analyze...
You know, Triela got
another stuffed bear
for her collection
the other day.
Now she has nine
bears altogether.
She was
so excited,
she stayed up all night
deciding a name for it.
Henrietta, you could have
any those things, too.
No... I'm happy
to do my job well
and make you proud of me...
That's enough for me.
You know, it's okay to want
something for yourself.
Here, that reminds me I've got
something I want you to have.
For all your hard work.
Open it now?
Of course.
Wow... you're sure
careful with it.
I want to save the box, the
wrapping paper and everything.
Thank you.
Now you can take pictures of
your friends or teddy bears...
...or anything you
want to remember.
I'll... take really
good care of it.
I should hold
your gun for now.
I want you to show them
around the cyborg ward.
So, this is kinda
like a dormitory, huh?
Uh-huh.
Rico, I wanted to
ask you something...
What?
Well... does it make you
sad that Elsa's dead.
It has nothing
to do with me,
We never even talked.
But, she was a
cyborg just like you.
It makes no
difference to me.
This was
Elsa's room.
It's empty...
Most of us share rooms, but
Elsa liked to live alone.
This place
is gloomy,
I hope all the rooms
aren't this depressing.
Henrietta and Triela
have lots of stuff
decorating
their rooms.
I think their Handlers give
them lots of presents...
But, I don't know
that for sure.
Was there anyone here
that Elsa confided in?
Um, maybe you should
ask Triela about that.
Triela?
Rico, you
back already.
Can we
come in?
Who are you?
Books, stuffed animals-
they're like regular kids.
This is Ms. Gabrielli and
Mr. Fermi from Section 1.
They want to talk
to you about Elsa.
Claes where
are you?.
You don't
need me here.
Why don't you tell me
what Elsa was like.
Just like most of the
girls around here,
she was totally infatuated
with her Handler
Does that go
for you, too?
Oh... I wouldn't
say that...
But, I'm I certainly
am devoted to him.
The Conditioning?
Conditioning and devotion
are two different things.
One comes from hard,
constant, training,
the other one comes
from the heart.
Sounds like it has a lot
less to do with discipline
or loyalty and a lot
more to do with love.
That's how
Elsa was.
How does it make
you feel to know
that one of your peers
has been murdered?
Well I feel... You see Elsa
pretty much kept to herself.
And, judging by the way she
acted most of the time...
I figure, she was
probably more than happy
to go to her death
protecting Lauro.
All right, then.
Thank you very much for
talking with us, Triela.
Next time you come
could you bring me a teddy
bear or some flowers?
What do you make of the
Section 1 investigator?
He appeared to me to
be a very capable man.
Well then.
Take this... it's the
ballistics report
on the bullets that killed
Lauro and Elsa. Look over it.
This is bad.
This could turn out to
be a problem for us.
Yeah I know, the
Director of Section 1
would never keep
this quiet.
He may become an obstacle
to our cybernetic testing.
Any ideas?
Well, I suppose we could try
to bury the ballistics report
and then blame it on some
simple clerical error;
that might take the heat
off for a little while.
I think they'd buy that,
and It wouldn't be a
mistake they could pin on us.
Elsa De Sica fought
and died bravely
trying to protect
her Handler.
Right.
And I want you to send
Jose and his cyborg away...
and I don't want to
see them back here
until this business
with Elsa cools off.
You're always trying to
protect Jose, you know that?
Guys like Jose have to be
protected by people like us.
We have to protect him from
that which is most deadly,
the truth.
Jose!
Jean.
I find it difficult
to believe
Elsa could be brought
down so easily.
Whoever it
did this,
they knew exactly how
to both of them out.
They shot her in the eye
and Lauro in the head.
Well, They were
good at their job.
That's right...
So, the Republican
Faction was responsible?
Yes, there's no
doubt about that.
Blood samples found
at the murder scene
match those of two
known R.F. operatives.
Their activities have been
known to target people
within various
government agencies.
I guess the cyborgs still
need a little more work.
I guess this concludes
Section One's investigation
into this matter.
We still don't know
how the R.F. was able
to track Lauro's team.
But, they obviously
marked them
and successfully terminated
them that night.
Elsa de Sica fought
and died bravely
trying to protect
her handler.
We'll, be working on impact
resistant optics right away.
So, she was happy to die
for her handler, huh...
Hey, Rico... Would
you be happy to die
if doing so meant that
Jean wouldn't have to?
I don't think I really
want to die... But-
The cyborgs serve
their Handlers.
For them there is
no other option.
Rico?
If Jean, my Handler, says
so then it must be true.
What? Sicily? Why
would they go there?
How should
I know?
They finished
their mission,
came back to headquarters
for a couple of days
and then left for a
vacation in Sicily.
Oh and just for
your information,
you know this
phone line
has probably been
tapped by the Agency.
So? We're not doing
anything wrong.
Okay,
thanks.
Um, Pietro? Did You get the
report done for the Director?
Of course.
Was he okay with it?
Yeah, But... we have a couple
of things left to check out.
Let's go.
Henrietta-
Yes, Jose?
Good morning.
Oh, good morning.
Take a look outside.
It's beautiful!
Welcome to Sicily...