[Triela] Hurry up
before he leaves.
[Henrietta]
But...
You want to
ask him, right?
Yeah... It's just...
Come on.
[Henrietta]
Jose?
Yes... What is
it, Henrietta?
Umm, uhh.
It's okay.
Well, Christmas is
coming up soon, and...
Yes?
So, I was thinking...
How's a drive sound to you?
As long as we get to
spend time together
it'll be a
perfect Christmas.
Go back to your room.
Good night, Jose.
Good night, Henrietta.
Jose said yes. We'll be
spending Christmas together.
See? What'd I say?
It's as simple as asking.
You were right.
It really wasn't that
hard... Thanks Triela.
[Hilshire]
Giacomotti...
Relax. I just want to ask
you a couple of questions
about your
organization.
Triela, I wanted to get
information from him,
not kill him.
I determined that he was
an imminent threat to you.
Maybe so, but you could've
been more gentle about it.
Listen, from now on
no more shooting
without my permission.
If that's the case...
then what's stopping you
from increasing the
level of my conditioning?
Take our friend here
and put him in the car.
Yes, sir.
[Jose] You do know
she's correct, right?
[Hilshire] I'm not going to
give her excess conditioning.
If you truly
feel that way,
then it's your responsibility
to train her correctly.
Though to be perfectly honest,
I'm not really one to talk.
Seems we both got
stuck with a job
that we're not
very good at.
Then what do you
recommend I do
to get along
with Triela?
Well, it's your
job to condition her,
not be her best friend...
However, she's a smart girl.
All she needs is to be
treated with respect.
[Henrietta] One,
two, three, four,
and five...
and that makes six!
You're one away from seven...
You know, seven
is a lucky number.
Hurray for me.
[Henrietta] I wish
I had some too.
Why don't you ask your
nice brother for some?
It's almost Christmas.
He'd buy them all for you.
No thanks... Spending
Christmas with him
is enough of a
present for me.
Do Hilshire's presents not
make you happy anymore?
He doesn't even
care what I like.
He just gets me the
same thing every year.
Sometimes I wonder if
he gives me these gifts
to please me or to
please himself.
You don't look too
good... Are you okay?
Not really. It's
that time of the month.
It's irregular
and the cramps
have been killing
me since yesterday.
It's too bad they won't
let us take any medicine.
I shouldn't have
said anything.
Just thinking about it
makes it feels worse...
But this pain reminds
me that I'm alive so,
I'll endure it.
That's the spirit.
I'll never know what
that feels like.
They took out my uterus
during conditioning.
Right, I forgot.
Sorry about that.
Triela. Hilshire's
looking for you.
Rico... Did you know
that you're bleeding?
It's nothing.
Jean scolded me during
conditioning, that's all.
Here. Let me help you.
Triela. He said to wait
in the Section One office.
Jose sees Henrietta
as his little sister...
and Jean sees Rico as
his little work dog...
Which makes me... What
does he want me to be?
If the conditioning
decided it all,
it would sure
be easier on me.
Hey, check it out.
We got ourselves a
princess from Section Two
gracing our office. What do
you think she's doing here?
She must be waiting
for a prince.
That's funny...
I thought we were all
frogs, here in section one.
He's not in
Section One.
Did Giacomotti talk?
I guess so.
Where to today?
The airport.
We'll be looking for
a retired Mafia boss.
Affirmative.
What is it?
Nothing.
I'm sorry for
the inconvience sir.
We didn't realize you
were with the government.
[Hilshire] We're searching
for a man named Mario Bossi.
He's been seen
wandering around Europe
after leaving the
Mafia several years ago,
but word has it
he's back in Naples.
[Triela] Are we killing
Mario Bossi once we find him?
[Hilshire]
No Triela,
We're taking him back
with us for protection.
[Triela]
Protection?
He holds
information we need
if we want to prosecute
his organization's Don.
Once he's safe,
we're going to have Mario
testify under an escape clause.
Naturally, the Mafia's
willing to go to any lengths
to stop that
from happening.
[Triela] So what
you're saying is
they're going to kill him
if we don't step in.
Precisely. We're to protect
him until the trial.
Why can't Section One
do this instead of us?
Because Mario and I
are old associates.
I know several places in
town that he used to frequent
and with any luck, we'll be
home in time for Christmas.
So keep your
eyes peeled.
Wishful thinking
usually leads to nothing,
especially when you're
depending on luck.
Triela.
Is something wrong?
Huh?
I don't know. You've looked
a little pale recently.
Stop it.
You don't have to
worry about me...
I see.
[Hilshire]
Who is it?
An old friend.
Mario from Vesuvio.
Hilshire!
Nice to see you
again... Mario.
So why didn't
you go to the DA?
You know there are countless
Mafia hitmen and dirty cops
eager for a handout and all
of them are looking for you.
I'll go to your
precious trial...
but I still have unfinished
business here in Naples.
Sorry, but I have
strict orders
to bring you back
to the Agency.
You've still got
a cold heart...
And by the way Hilshire...
What the hell am I doing
attached to this little girl?
I'm sure you've heard all
about our cyborg units...
I wouldn't bother bother
trying to run away
while attached to her.
So she's one of them.
That explains things.
What? You can't be serious!
Why do I have to go in too?
I'll be watching the door.
Nobody's gonna bother you.
Come on, unless you want me to
piss my pants right heres.
Don't let your guard down.
Hurry it up.
Don't rush me. Why does
everyone at your agency
have a chip on
their shoulder?
Did you learn about the
agency from Hilshire?
I suppose.
Hilshire doesn't seem
like the type of guy
to have friends with
Mafia connections.
Many years ago a rookie
Europol investigator
caught a Mafia boss
in Amsterdam.
What did
he do?
Their black market
tobacco business
wasn't bringing
in enough cash
so they turned to
exporting children,
also known as 'lambs',
through Amsterdam.
And that investigator
was Hilshire...
Around
that time,
I was seriously considering
leaving the Mafia
for a career elsewhere.
He helped me escape in return
for some insider information.
The organization's been
after me ever since,
and Hilshire was was fired when
they found out he was involved.
Lucky for him, he got
picked up by the agency.
As for me, I've been
running ever since.
Did you two correspond even
after he joined the agency?
For just a short while.
It was a give and take thing.
Did he ever happen to
mention anything about me
before we caught
up with you?
No... Tell me, do
you two get along well?
Look Mario. Just
because we're a fratello
doesn't mean
we're best friends.
Mario!
Damn!
What's going on?!
I'll get him!
Sorry, little girl.
You know it's a lot
easier to find a traitor
when they return to the
city they left behind.
I'm sick and tired of
running from you guys.
I want this to end.
You can talk all you want
later for all I care...
The boss is waiting for us.
See Naples and die.
Huh? What did
you just say?
Just an old saying...
It means that
before you die
you must experience the
beauty and elegance of Naples.
Well, in that case it means
you can die in peace old man.
If you're gonna
take me to your boss,
you'd better
hurry it up.
Huh?
Someone you don't want
to play around with
is about
to show up.
[Triela] Did you get hit?
[Mario]
Huh? No.
If you try to run again I
won't hesitate to shoot.
What's with the
attitude, little girl?
Female stuff...
Someone forced me to run
all over town to catch him.
Are you alright?
Actually, no,
I'm not. It's painful.
Tell me...
Why did you risk
coming back to Naples
with all this
heat... on you?
To see my...
my only daughter.
Daughter?
The first time I ever seriously
thought about leaving the Mafia
was when my
daughter was born...
Having her made me realize
that I despised everything
I had done
with my life.
Every year I've sent
her a Christmas present...
But since I've
left the Mafia...
I haven't laid eyes on her
once... I promised myself...
that I'd deliver a present
to her in person this year.
A girl needs a father,
or so I'm told... right?
I'll tell Hilshire
that you got away.
Triela... Do you have
any idea what happened
to your real parents?
Afraid not...
All I've been told is
that the agency found me
somewhere in Amsterdam.
After listening
to your story,
I guess I might have
been a 'lamb' myself.
I couldn't possibly ask
for... your forgiveness.
There's no need for that.
Who's to say it was
your fault anyway?
I'm sorry.
Just go see your daughter and
treat her like a princess.
And you try to get
along with Hilshire.
Now hold on...
Believe it or not, Mario,
he and I get along quite
well most of the time.
I don't hate him
specifically...
It's the rest of
you selfish adults
that I hold a
grudge against.
Mario got away?
Sorry.
It's no big deal. It was
just a favor for Section One.
Triela.
Uh, yeah.
What is it?
We still have some time
until our flight leaves...
What do you say we get
in some shopping first?
I just realized that
I've only ever given you
boring dolls for presents.
How 'bout a...
a nice dress
or a...
pair of shoes?
What I like is...
I like the
way it feels
when I tighten my
bow around my neck
or the clicking sound
of my leather boots
when I walk on
cobblestone...
or my jacket...
Okay. I've always... had a
tough time trying to figure out
what kids would like
for presents...
So, I don't know. I just
assumed they like teddy bears.
But if you'd like
something else this year,
don't hesitate to ask.
You know now that
I think of it,
just get me a teddy bear
like you always do...
Henrietta says that the
number seven is good luck.
I already have six,
so please, one more.
If that's
what you want.
Triela.
Coming!
That tree looks great.
Thanks. Hey,
welcome back.
Are you
feeling any better?
Not yet.
I give in.
Maybe once a year
it's okay to have
a day like this.
[Henrietta] Huh?
Just talking to myself.
Incidentally, on
Christmas morning,
I found two gifts waiting
for me under the tree.
One from Hilshire and
one from Mario Bossi.
As it turned out I ended
up with one extra teddy bear,
which was fine with me...
Just another sibling
to spend Christmas with.