A toy?
Yeah. But can you
really call it that
when it's sole purpose is
to explode and kill people?
This one's a lot weaker.
Not at all like the others.
The timer, the connections,
the explosive used.
It's all way too
amateur to be the same.
I'd be surprised if the
thing even detonated.
So what are you saying?
That this was a diversion?
That this wasn't
the real objective?
Okay, so what about the planned
attack on the National Museum?
We've come across bits and
pieces of intelligence,
but nothing solid.
It's fleeting
information like this
that tickles the
analysts instincts,
sometimes making
their imaginations work
harder than
we'd like...
They think the
militant factionists
are chomping
at the bit.
I see... But your people
don't believe that, do they?
What's really starting to bug
me is this amateur subway bomb
and how it
all fits in.
It doesn't make
much sense.
The factionists are incapable
of making their own bomb.
So they'd have to hire
someone to build it...
Perhaps they made this
shoddy bomb to...
make it look like
the professionals
they can't hire
have lost their edge.
You know, you'd make a
good mystery writer.
Luckily, no injuries
were reported
and officials aren't
even certain that
the bomb
was made...
--What do you
think, Franco?
...by an established
terrorist group.
We knew from the start that
they couldn't make a bomb
to save their
own hide.
I'm talking about how they
thought they could lure us out
with a stupid
stunt like this.
The fools underestimated
us, that's for sure.
They'll get no
help from us.
Yeah... It's not
even worth our time.
That man in the corner with his
back to us is Enrico Perdini.
He's an ultra
left wing terrorist
within the
Republican Faction...
and responsible for last years
bombing in Republic Square.
As well as four other
bombings in recent years.
Busy guy.
So tell me, Henrietta? Do you
hear anything of interest?
Mostly politics.
It's complicated.
He's going on and on
about the southern plant.
Keeps criticizing their
development work.
He said that... he
won't allow any more
of the northern
plant's tax funds
to be fed to the
southern plant...
And if their
plan succeeds,
the government will
be forced to rethink
its economic approach
for the 3rd quarter.
Changing his stripes
just to get more money.
You know when he first started
out he was an anarchist,
believe
it or not.
What made him change
his way of thinking?
Nothing... See, this guy
will work for any cause
to get funds for
his own movement.
The R.F.'s Lombardian Plains
Freedom Movement is supported
by northern capitalists
who have followed the flow
of European
right-wingers
and anti-globalism
activists for years.
Much different than these
left-wingers who rob banks
to finance
their agenda.
Alright. Let's see if we
can persuade them to go
in the wrong
direction with this.
They've lost sight of
the ultimate goal.
If we make them
relearn the meaning
of a just cause
they'll have...
No other
choice.
Right... I'll get the committee
moving on this right away...
I'll also make sure the
package gets delivered
no later than
two tonight.
When that time comes,
give them a lesson
they'll never forget...
Got that,
Henrietta?
Enzo.
Would it be all right with you
if we stopped watching Enrico?
That'd be fine. I've
assigned an auxiliary team
to trail him
from here on out.
We'll make our
move to capture him
once he's met with
the bomb makers.
Until then, continue
preparing for the assault
at the
branch office.
Speaking of, will one
fratello be enough?
I'd prefer to take the
bomb makers into custody
while they're
still alive.
That will complicate
things on our end,
but I'll call
headquarters
and see about getting a couple
more fratellos by this evening.
Thanks, Jose. You know
Rome Branch would help
if they could,
but they're running
thin on personnel.
All of their special ops are
already en route to the museum,
and those that are
left are better off
sitting behind
their desks.
[Jose] So what is
Enrico's plan?
To blow something up. That's
all we can be sure about...
This guy's willing to go
to any lengths necessary
to get what
he wants.
What's wrong,
sport?
Don't look so
disappointed.
Jose and
I love ya...
We just know we're gonna need
some extra hands for this job.
And if you and the
backup from HQ
take care of
things smoothly,
you'll be getting
a very nice reward.
What is this?
Perfume?
I suppose I'm guilty
of buying her too much,
though the things I buy for her
make up her salary. Trust me.
She more than deserves
everything she gets.
Well, kids are the most
adorable when they're her age.
I can understand
buying her stuff.
After all, incentives to
do better can never hurt.
My own daughter
is old enough now
that she can go out
and party all night.
She rarely comes by the house
anymore to see her folks.
Tommaso.
I've brought the support
from headquarters.
Fine.
Excuse me. This is where
they print the newspaper.
It's government property,
not a place for children.
It's alright,
Pietro.
She's the one I
told you about.
We already have a
room waiting for you.
You should take her
inside immediately.
Right.
Sorry about that, guys.
One of the biggest headaches
about acquiring
outside help...
is having to take their
snotty attitude with a smile.
I'm used
to it.
Well, you two can relax
here until this evening.
Is there anything else I
can get you while I'm out?
Yeah... Some spare
ammo for Henrietta...
Oh, and I could
use an FN57...
Jean, it's me...
Pattern B.
[Jose]
Right.
Yeah? That's right.
Understood.
Bad news.
He gave your
team the slip.
Yeah... And how
did you know that?
One of our teams caught up with
him when he got on the train.
They're on
him now.
Great.
He actually just
got off the subway.
Where?
At Cavour
Station. B line.
All right.
I'll follow him.
Okay.
Wait. Hold on...
If I'm not mistaken,
that's one stop
before the museum.
If he's at the museum do
you know his real target?
No.
At any rate... It won't matter
after we finish tonight.
I'll contact
our guys there.
The backup?
The backup is already
here, isn't it?
Yes. I called for
Rico and Triela...
We've planned for multiple
contingencies, just to be safe.
You know, it's going to
be at least a few hours
until we find out where
they're hiding...
Why don't you try to
get in a quick nap
while you decide what you
want for your reward?
Actually...
I already know
what I want.
[Enzo] He's not heading
for the museum anymore.
He's going in the
opposite direction...
just kind of
wandering around Rome...
What could his target be?
Enrico is back.
[Walkie-Talkie]
Copy.
Enrico... What are
you still doing in Rome?
You're supposed
to be gone.
I'd feel much more comfortable
making the deal in Ostia.
[Enrico]
Sorry, Flanca.
I wanted to scope out the
location first before I commit.
The longer you
stay in Rome,
the better the chances
you'll get nabbed
by this agency I've been
hearing so much about.
It's way too dangerous
to stay here.
Some guys were following me
earlier this afternoon...
but I was able to
shake them off.
I'm certain they have their
hands full right now...
the diversion at the museum
is working perfectly.
Anyway, I'd rather
do this tomorrow.
Just remember to
deliver it tonight
by the time we
already agreed on.
[Enrico] The bomb
arrangements are set.
Did we really have to use them?
I don't trust outsiders.
Yes, we did... Flanca and
Franco's bombs are nearly
impossible
to dismantle.
They're simply
the best in Italy.
That guy is
a lost cause.
You're right. There's
no cure for a fool.
Since it's an
order from above,
we'll help him
out on this one...
though to be honest I'd
prefer to have people
like him
just disappear.
Where are they
planting it?
If you
knew that,
you probably wouldn't
want to give it to them.
Should we go
through with this?
I don't know.
If they really are serious
about doing it there...
Then maybe it wouldn't be such
a bad idea to give them a fake.
I'm gonna
get ready.
It's time, but the bomb
makers have yet to show up...
Remain on
standby.
Roger.
You positive these
two are gonna show up?
They'll
be here.
Enrico.
Something's going on... All
the traffic beyond the bridge.
It's just stopped.
There's nothing.
What?
Maybe there was an
accident or something.
It's too hard to
tell from here.
There's been an
accident reported.
The police have diverted
all traffic on this block
because of a three-car
pile-up east of here.
Damn it.
Hey, Simon.
You there?
Yeah.
Go ahead.
Can you see what's going
on across the river?
No, but I can hear police
sirens in the distance.
Go check
it out.
Yes, sir.
[Jose] Enzo...
It's started.
That's fine
with me...
If the bomb makers were
planning on showing,
they would have
been here by now.
Take Enrico alive...
and grill the bastard.
Is camouflage really necessary
for a simple car accident?
Guess so.
Cut the lights! Everyone
stay away from the windows!
Lights out on
the third floor.
Southwest side of
the fourth building.
Enrico must be in
there. Can you see him?
No, sir. Not
from this position.
Understood... Hilshire...
What's going on down there?
I've just
ordered Triela
to climb the wall
on the west side.
Good. I'm sending Henrietta
in now so we can surround him.
[Henrietta] Please...
Don't shoot me.
Please...
Please help me.
There's scary people
downstairs... with guns.
And they...
What the hell? How did this
little kid get inside here?
Perfect timing... We can
use her as a hostage.
Don't worry. Come to us.
We'll keep you safe.
Hurry.
Hurry up before the bad
guys come after you.
Now be a
good girl...
Damn!
[Flanca]
Officers!
Did something happen here?
Why is the bridge closed?
There was an arrest
here last night.
This area's off
limits now.
Looks like Place D'Espagne
was able to avoid the bombing
without
her help.
Are you sure a
simple ice cream
is all you want
for your reward?
Especially in the
middle of winter.
I'm sure...
Didn't you know there's
a meaning behind ice cream
in Place D'Espagne?
Oh, my!
Are you okay?
Sorry... I'm really sorry.
Well, I'm glad your
ice cream is all right.
You are in Place
D'Espagne after all.
Yeah.
What is it?
That girl... She was wearing
an expensive perfume.
So what?
Designer perfume...
and an Amati violin...
She must be the daughter
of a well-to-do family.
At the end of the day,
it's girls like her
that we Republican Factionists
are out to protect.