[AINS] I have gathered you
here to discuss our future.
Albedo, Overseer of the
Guardians, and Demiurge,
our greatest strategist.
I would hear your opinions.
[BOTH]
Lord.
[AINS] Now that we have put
my initial plans into motion,
tell us what doctrine
you believe Nazarick
should follow, moving forward.
If anyone else has an opinion,
you may raise your
hand to speak.
In order to facilitate
our discussion,
I ask that Demiurge explain
our current situation
in a way that
all can understand.
Begin with our latest operation.
As you wish.
[MOMONGA sighs] I may be their
leader, but I don't have
much experience in this
whole conquering thing.
At least this way, I can
pretend I understood the plan.
What I do know is that
Nazarick's survival
is our first priority.
Second, would be spreading
the name of Ains Ooal Gown
throughout the world.
Actually, that's
just my priority,
since I wanna find out
if any of my old friends
are trapped here like me.
But that might have
to take a backseat,
especially when we still know
so little about this world.
[DEMIURGE] As you've likely
heard, thanks to the efforts
of Mare's group,
we've subjugated
all the leaders
of Eight Fingers.
As a result, Nazarick now
has complete control
of the Re-Estize underworld.
[AINS]
Hm?
This brings us closer
to Ains' ultimate goal.
Which you all know
is world domination.
[AINS]
Mm?
Or I should hope you know
if you're not a fool.
[AINS]
Huh?
[MOMONGA]
Wait, so is that where we're at?
World domination?
Okay, okay, don't freak out!
You've gotta act like it
was your idea, after all!
[gasps]
[MOMONGA]
Actually, world domination
might be a good way to
get our name out there.
Even if we have
a bad reputation,
at least people will
know who we are.
My friends might be a little
surprised with the direction
I'm taking the guild,
but whatever.
There will be plenty of time
to explain things later
and that's if I find them.
[AINS]
Hm?
You remembered.
Of course, my lord.
I remember every last word
you relay to me.
You said taking over the
world might be enjoyable.
[AINS]
Yes, I recall the conversation.
I'm pleased to hear it.
[AINS]
From that one time.
None other, my lord.
[MOMONGA]
What time?!
[AINS] I see. Your impeccable
memory pleases me.
Your praise is too much.
[AINS] But world domination
is a complicated affair.
I must agree, my lord.
[AINS] How do you suppose
we begin our conquest?
I humbly suggest we announce
Nazarick to the public.
[AINS]
Hm?
Since the ones who
controlled Shalltear
are still moving
behind the scenes,
I fear that staying
in the shadows any further
will only encumber us.
[ALBEDO]
That's my opinion as well.
We can hunt them more
effectively in the open.
Right now, we're
wasting resources
trying to maintain secrecy.
[AINS]
Mm. An appealing proposal.
There is merit in
controlling the kingdom
from the shadows and striking
fear into the hearts
of their leaders, but in
doing so, we may force ourselves
to answer to the whims
of their throne.
That's not a pleasant prospect.
Frankly, I find their
leadership quite lacking.
Save for one individual.
There are other
concerns as well.
For example, being tied to one
kingdom limits our movements.
If the ones who targeted
Shalltear have more flexibility
than us, we would be
at a disadvantage again.
Therefore, Lord Ains,
I propose that the
Great Tomb of Nazarick
enter the stage of the world
as an independent nation.
[GUARDIANS murmur]
It appears this
came as a surprise.
But I assure you
Lord Ains has been
thinking of doing this
for a long time.
[GUARDIANS]
Oh!
[MOMONGA]
What?!
In the end,
I fear my intellect's rather
trifling compared to your own.
I won't pretend to grasp
the depth of your wisdom,
though I do hope my explanation
skims the surface accurately.
[AINS]
No, on the contrary,
you ascertained
my plans perfectly.
I'd expect no less
of my lead strategist.
[GUARDIANS]
Ah!
Merely observing your actions
made it crystal clear.
Anyone could have reached
the same conclusion.
[AINS]
Yes, I recall my... actions.
I am pleased to hear it.
[AINS]
From that one time.
None other, my lord.
[MOMONGA]
What time, damn it?!
[AINS] Well, of the
many actions I've taken,
which do you deem
the most relevant
to our current discussion?
Your accomplishments in
Carne Village come to mind.
[GUARDIANS gasp]
[AINS] I suppose that did
go rather well, didn't it?
At the risk of
sounding sarcastic,
you did subjugate the
village personally, my lord.
There's no way
it wouldn't go well.
I didn't know that
was you, Lord.
That's the human village, right?
Helpless humans our lord could
have eradicated with ease,
and yet he decided to rule
over them peacefully instead.
You see?
Lord Ains considered
that village
a sort of testing ground.
He's had conquest on his
mind long before today.
[GUARDIANS gasp]
[AINS]
Ah--
[KAIJALI] I haven't seen
Nphirea yet, boss.
Ya figure he's still sleeping?
[ENRI]
Yeah, maybe.
He was up late working on
his potion last night.
He's missing out on
this nice weather!
So what's for
breakfast today, boss?
[laughs] Well, Kaijali,
thanks to your hard work,
we've got plenty of meat.
So I'll be whipping up
a nice and hearty stew!
Nice arms!
No!
I'm still scrawny
compared to you.
Sure, but you've
got great definition!
I mean it!
[VILLAGE CHIEF 2A]
Good morning, Enri!
[ENRI]
Good morning, chief!
Nice weather, huh?
Mr. Goblin!
Another hard day at work?
You bet!
Can't leave all that farming to
you and your husband, now can I?
What would we do without you?
I know I've said this before,
but we really can't
thank you goblins enough.
If you weren't here
to lend a hand,
we'd have been forced to
abandon the village long ago.
I see. So we're short
on people, even now?
[VILLAGE CHIEF 2A]
Mm-hm. I'm afraid so.
Thankfully, the survivors
stuck around,
but we haven't been able
to bolster our numbers.
We've got a long way to go.
And the only person that
moved here from the city
is that ex-adventurer,
Miss Britta, right?
Can't blame them,
but there aren't many people
crazy enough to move to
a dangerous place like this.
What have I told you
about being negative?
Things will work out eventually.
You say that, but...
You remember what the
government official said.
We'll have lower taxes and
exemption from civil service
until the village can pull
itself together again.
It's not going to happen
overnight, and that's fine.
She's right. Give it
some time and I'm sure
that people will
want to move here.
We'll keep working hard
in the meantime!
Fair enough.
Lord Gown did go to the
trouble of saving our lives.
The least we can
do is keep living,
no matter how lean
the times may be.
Agreed! Someday,
I hope to pay him back
for the kindness he showed us.
[KAIJALI]
Wow, that's some smell.
[ENRI]
Sure is.
Nphirea, we're having
breakfast soon.
Bring your grandmother!
Oh, morning, Enri!
You're not going
to believe this!
[ENRI] You're really
worked up! What happened?
A miracle!
Finally, finally I made
a brand new potion
and it's all my own!
This is going to
be revolutionary!
You know all those
solutions and herbs
I've been gathering lately?
Well, I finally got
the right proportions
and the potion turned purple!
Okay!
That's enough of that,
thank you very much.
[NPHIREA, ENRI]
Huh?
You're clearly high off
your own fumes, kiddo.
Don't worry.
You get breakfast going and
we'll catch up with you soon.
'Kay? I'll splash some
cold water over his head
and he'll snap out of it
in no time flat.
Are you sure?
Trust me on this.
All right, good luck, then!
[NPHIREA giggles]
You've got to pull
it together, brother.
[sighs] Let's be frank.
You're in love with
the boss, right?
Uh--
Mm-hm.
Then show her!
You're givin' all of your
love to those potions!
It's weird.
All right then. I'll try.
Trying ain't gonna
cut it, brother!
Listen, show off your strength
and she'll fall for you.
I'm afraid "strength"
isn't my strong point.
You got strength up here,
so work with that!
Tell you what,
when the time comes
for you to make
your move, I'll pose!
Like this.
That'll be your cue
to talk smart
n' show her those pearly whites.
This pose, don't forget it.
And if it looks like you
should press your advantage.
I'll hit'cha with this one.
Uh, okay.
[KAIJALI]
Then I'll do this pose!
If that works, this one.
And then this one!
And after that, this!
I'm tellin' you,
add some more salt!
I ain't givin' up till
Miss Enri marries me!
Lay off!
We took a vow not to make
any moves on the boss,
don't you remember?
That's right!
She's gotta make the first move!
Too bad for you, then.
I'm the leader, so she's gonna
take a fancy to me
before you punks.
You shut your mouth, Jugem!
Who cares if you're strong?
[GOBLIN 2A]
Punch him and see what happens!
[UNLAI laughs]
[ENRI] They certainly
are worked up today.
[NPHIREA] Ruby powder...
Wings of magic...
[ENRI]
Uh. Hey.
And then, stir it up...
Um, Nphi, you all right?
Uh-huh. In fact,
I've never been better.
Grandma is still too
busy working, though.
Soup time.
Sorry, but the
battle's already won.
And I got the proof
right here on my spoon.
Look!
This handsome goblin got
an extra piece of meat!
[GOBLINS gasp]
[KUUNEL]
That's right. I ate my meat
and at the bottom of the bowl,
there was more meat
waiting for me!
And as you all know,
that's one more piece
than the allotted amount!
In other words,
it must be love!
It's a lie!
You probably broke
one big piece in two!
Also, did anyone here
witness the first piece?
Perhaps it was actually
just a bite of potato
and you were mistaken.
Enri thinks you're a creep.
You know this deep
in your heart.
Our god asked us to
ensure Enri's happiness.
"Dear lord, please tell
this creep how wrong he is!"
I thought your god was evil.
--Why do they care?
--[splat]
[GOBLINS gasp]
[ENRI gasps]
[ENRI]
Nphi?!
I think I'd better
take him to bed now.
[NEMU] Isn't the guy
supposed to carry the girl?
[KAIJALI] Some things
are better left unsaid.
--[ENRI growls]
--[GOBLINS, NEMO gasp]
[GOBLINS, NEMU laugh nervously]
[ENRI] Jugem and his friends
do more than just
protect the village from danger.
They've brought smiles
back to our faces.
And for those who
lost everything,
they're like another family.
After all they've done,
there has to be some way
I can repay their kindness.
All right, everyone.
Are you ready to do this?
[JUGEM]
Aim.
Fire!
[SHURINGAN]
All right, lookin' good!
A fine row of arrows
like that will send
any intruders
packing in no time!
[VILLAGERS laugh, murmur]
Right. Next wave. Line up!
[NEMU]
Hey! Enri, let me help, too!
I'm fine in here, but if
you could take care of that
job I gave you yesterday,
then that would be great.
Aw. Okay.
[ENRI]
Not a single complaint.
She used to be so spoiled,
but she's been such
a good girl since then.
--[thud]
--[KAIJALI] Hm?
[ENRI panting]
Heard a bang. Are you okay?
Yes, it's nothing.
It seems I was a little
rough on the knife, though.
You gotta be careful
with stuff like that.
Since there's no
blacksmith way out here,
no one can fix it
if it gets dinged up.
Ah.
We can't get maintenance done
on any of our weapons, either.
That must be inconvenient.
Yeah, but we manage
somehow! Hah!
[NEMU grunting]
[ENRI] Working hard!
Got it all ground up?
Uh-huh! Did a bunch! All this!
Oh, wow. I'm so proud of you!
That smell...
Pretty intense stuff.
It's like Nphi's potions.
It's bad, but not
that bad. Right?
[NEMU]
Mm-hm! Mm-hm!
What she's making is
something called "Enkaeshi."
It's a specialty of our village.
These herbs can only be
gathered this time of year.
They're potent medicine.
Sounds like this stuff must
be big business for you.
My apologies, Miss Nemu.
[NEMU] Hm! But look. I'm
almost out of the herbs!
I'll be done with these
by the end of the day.
But I think we've
already covered
all the gathering spots
that I know of.
Aw!
[ENRI]
Kyumei.
Hey.
You got a message for us?
[KYUMEI] Yeah. It seems
like something weird
is happening in Tob Forest.
What do you mean?
It can't be.
Are the people who attacked
the village back?
No.
It's like a disturbance coming
from deep in the forest.
That's bad timing,
because we need to gather
those herbs before
it's too late.
Sorry boss, but that's
way too dangerous.
[KYUMEI] I'd like to send
out a scouting party,
but it might take a while.
We've got our hands full just
watching over the village.
I need to go out there
in the next few days.
The herbs aren't in season long
and we'll be in a bad spot
if we can't sell more.
Let's bring this to Jugem
and see what he says.
Good. Thank you.
[JUGEM]
All right, here's the plan.
While Miss Enri and her group
are lookin' for herbs,
the rest of us will spread
out and scout the area,
moving deeper into the forest.
[JUGEM] Report back if
you see anything strange.
As for Miss Enri's bodyguards,
let me see here.
--Gokou.
--[GOKOU] Sir!
--Kaijali.
--[KAIJALI] Sir!
--Unlai.
--[UNLAI] Sir!
[JUGEM]
You ready?
[GOKOU, KAIJALI, UNLAI]
Yeah!
I shouldn't need
to tell you this,
but her safety is top priority!
[UNLAI, KAIJALI, GOKOU]
Yes, sir!
Nphi. We're counting
on you, too.
Show the boss what you're
made of out there.
[NPHIREA yelps]
So now's the time, huh?
[clears throat] Leave it to me!
I'll take good care
of you, I promise!
How kind of you. Thanks, Nphi.
Huh? That's not enough?
I've prepared various
alchemical, uh, concoctions.
So don't worry!
Sure. Sounds great.
Not worried at all!
[NPHIREA]
It's Bebeyamok moss.
If you mix a clump or two
of that in healing potions,
it increases their
effectiveness a bit.
I never had a clue, wow.
So is it worth a lot of money?
Uh, a little.
Although in this case,
the herb Enri
is looking for
is worth a lot more.
I can come back here
for some moss any time.
[UNLAI]
Roger that!
[KAIJALI] Wow, Nphi's really
something, huh, Enri?
[GOKOU] I can't tell any
of these plants apart.
All just green to me!
Does that issue apply
to all goblins?
Like your people just
aren't cut out for botany?
Hell if I know, but I
never met a goblin
who was any good with plants.
We're not much for gathering,
but when it comes to hunting
and skinning, we do just fine!
Lots of shade here.
The humidity is
high enough, too.
This is exactly
the kind of place
that those herbs like to grow.
Let's spread out
and look around.
I found some! You were right!
I'm glad we brought you along!
Call it good luck.
Something wrong?
[ENRI] Mm-mm! I'm just
impressed, that's all!
You found the herbs
right away and you know
how to pick them so
much faster than me.
Well, I am a pharmacist.
I'd better be good
at this stuff.
I guess so.
Thanks anyway, though.
[ALL gasp]
Shh!
[rustling]
It sounds like there's
something coming our way.
Better pull back
and hide for now.
Right.
[panting]
[gasps]
[AGU panting]
It's a child.
Just watch and wait.
[panting]
[BARGHEST 2A growling]
[gasps] It's a barghest!
[growls]
[NPHIREA]
It didn't notice us.
I think the smell of the herbs
must be masking our scent.
Keeping you safe
is our first priority.
If the kid gets attacked,
don't run out there to help him.
It may seem cruel,
but that's how it goes.
He's scared.
[sighs] It's okay.
We'll save him.
[ENRI]
Nphi!
All right, let's think.
Why'd he run all the way here?
If he knows what's
happening in the forest,
then he can warn us before
it affects the village.
Assuming we don't all die!
There's no guarantee we can
win against that thing.
I can't fight, so maybe
I have no right to say this,
but if there's a chance
we can help, we should.
If someone is dying and
we turn our backs on them,
in a way, that's no different
than siding with their killer.
I was saved, so I
have to do the same
for those who are
weaker than me.
I'm sorry.
[AGU screams]
[KAIJALI]
You heard the lady, let's go!
[UNLAI]
Hey, over here, little puppy!
If you wanna take a bite outta
someone, we got more meat!
Come and get some!
[growls]
[AGU grunting]
All right, give it all you got!
[GOBLINS grunt]
[BARGHEST 2A roars]
[GOBLINS yell]
Now, Reinforce Armor!
[roars]
[GOKOU]
Nice one, brother! He's stuck!
Not completely, and
probably not for long
if it keeps
struggling like that.
Strike hard and strike now!
[GOBLINS yell]
[roars]
The chain!
Get down!
[GOBLINS yell]
[GOKOU yells]
[UNLAI yells]
[KAIJALI]
Take that!
[BARGHEST 2A growls]
[ALL sigh]
[AGU] You saved me.
What tribe are you from?
Let's save the
questions for later.
We have to do something about
those injuries of yours.
Any way you can help?
You're bleeding all over
the place, aren't you?
Don't poison me!
What a pity.
I was looking forward to
giving this to Lord Gown.
Whoa.
And done!
This wasn't ideal,
but at least I can tell
Lord Gown it works, right?
And here I thought you
jerks were gonna kill me!
Uh. I mean, thank you
for saving my life.
That's better! Show a
little gratitude, brat.
I'm not a brat!
My name's Agu and I am
the fourth son of Ah,
the leader of the Gigu Tribe!
[ENRI]
Nice to meet you, Agu.
So what happened?
Where'd you get all those cuts
and what are you
doing in the woods?
[AGU] I got attacked,
so I ran. That's all.
We need more details.
Wasn't just the barghest
that attacked you.
Uh! The Giant of the
East sent his minions.
The Giant of the East?
And the Demon Snake of the West.
He joined up with him.
War is coming.
[AINS] Carne Village would've
been wiped from the map
by the Slane Theocracy
had I not intervened.
It's population has decreased,
but with the help of the
summoned goblins I gave Enri,
it may yet recover.
After discovering unsettling
changes within the Great Forest,
Enri makes her way to E-Rantel
in order to run errands
and request the assistance
of the Adverturer's Guild.
Chapter 3: "Enri's Upheaval
and Hectic Days."
Your life was once saved.
How will you use it?