[AGU]
What is this place?
[ENRI]
Our village.
Why, is something the matter?
Kinda looks like
the Monument of Ruin.
Sounds like a scary place.
Sure is!
If you ask me,
it's the scariest part
of the whole Great Forest.
It's a big building made of wood
that's completely surrounded
by undead warriors.
Yeah, and whereabouts is it?
[ENRI] Let's talk more once
we're inside the village, Gokou.
Smart idea!
Huh?
[yelps] Hey!
[LUPISREGINA]
Good old Enny.
You still make the cutest little
scream when you're scared.
Oh, Miss Lupis!
[LUPISREGINA]
So, spill.
How'd this goblin kid
end up with you?
Well... I was just...
No! Wait, don't tell me!
Ooh! You stole Nphy's girl
from right under his nose?
Well, isn't this a tragedy--
the hopes and dreams of
such a pure-hearted boy
crushed into the dirt!
This is so hilarious!
[laughing]
Just kidding.
So...
Why'd you bring this
thing back with you?
Calm down, I'm not
gonna eat you.
I found her.
What's up?
Oh. Miss Britta.
We let a hobgoblin
inside our walls?
[gasps]
Hey, my bad.
The thing is, I used
to be an adventurer.
Kinda hard to get
outta that mindset.
An adventurer?
[BRITTA]
That's behind me now.
These days I'm
an apprentice ranger
that lives here in the village.
You'll be okay, Agu.
Carne Village is a place
where goblins and humans
live side by side.
That's what it looks like,
but I still can't believe it.
Okay, all of us are here,
so let's see what the
little guy has to say.
Well, Agu? Tell us about
this Giant of the East.
Sure. Originally,
the forest was controlled
by the Great Beast of
the South and two others.
The Giant of the East,
and also the Demon
Snake of the West.
The Great Beast of
the South might be
what we called the
Wise King of the Forest.
But then the Great Beast
disappeared without a trace.
Which left the forest
out of balance.
And not too long after that,
something else took its place.
That's the Monument of Ruin?
It is.
The master of that place
controls the undead.
We call him the Small Shadow
which Burrows in the Darkness.
And what does
all that have to do
with you getting attacked?
The Giant of the East
and the Demon Snake
of the West are gathering
their forces for an attack
on the King of Ruin.
They seemed to wanna
use all of us goblins
as foot-soldiers.
Or as emergency rations.
So most of us decided
we'd just hide from them.
But then...
They must be tough to send
your whole tribe into hiding.
If a monster that
powerful shows up,
there's no point in
trying to fight it.
We may as well just run
with the non-combatants.
[LUPISREGINA]
If you're in a bind,
I could always ask
Lord Ains to help you out.
This is our village.
So let's protect it ourselves.
We won't always be able
to rely on his charity.
Well, then, maybe we
should start by reporting
this to the village chief.
I'll pay a visit to the
Adventurer's Guild in E-Rantel
tomorrow and post our
situation as a job.
Hey. Could I come with you?
I've got some herbs to sell.
Oh. Sure.
I'll go get the other
militia members up to speed.
Yeah, I'm out, too.
Probably gonna go wander
around the village
a bit more before I head home.
[NPHIREA]
Oh, Miss Beta.
Could I take a bit of your time?
If it's not a bother,
I was hoping
you could take
this to Lord Gown.
We haven't replicated
a fully red potion yet.
But I think this is a step
in the right direction.
I'm delighted to hear that.
I'm sure Lord Ains
will be equally pleased.
[LUPISREGINA] Wow! I was
right to come visit today.
Also, feel free to
call me Lupisregina.
I'll allow it just for you.
So, have women always
been the leaders
here in the Carne Tribe?
Huh?
Why does Miss Enri
have so much power?
It's 'cause she can kick
our butts in a fight.
[gasps]
I've seen Miss Enri
beat down a barghest
and break its neck
with just one hand!
After that, she drained its
blood into a cup and drank it!
Seriously?
Are you tryin' to
scare the kid, Gokou?
Hey, Agu.
That Lupisregina girl
is dangerous.
So keep your distance.
What makes her so dangerous?
Trust me on this.
Best thing you can do
is avoid her attention.
Look, I'm tellin' you this
for your own good, okay?
Uh. Yeah. I get it.
I gotta say though,
this is one crazy tribe.
Yeah... Like, um... too...
[knocking]
[ENRI]
Oh, hello, Jugem.
[JUGEM]
I'm sorry for waking you.
That's fine. Did
something happen?
Well, we searched
through the forest,
and we managed to find a few
members of Agu's tribe.
I'm relieved to hear it.
You did great.
But there's more.
See, we captured the five ogres
who were chasing them.
Ogres?
That's right. And, well...
We told 'em about the
village and they said
they wouldn't mind joining us.
Huh?
So, I have a request
for you, Miss Enri.
[gasps]
[OGRES growling]
Listen up, ogres.
This is our boss, Miss Enri.
Your lives are in her hands.
So you'd better show
respect and hope
she's in a good mood.
[OGRES growling]
[gasps]
[OGRES grumbling]
Lower your heads at once!
You scary. Please,
little master.
Did not mean to make you mad.
We attack your tribe.
But now, we sorry.
You are forgiven.
On the condition that you
work hard for my tribe.
Oh, wow.
Now I can see why Miss Enri
is the leader of Carne Village.
That was scary.
I couldn't tell it from
looking at you though.
You know it's not everyone
who can get ogres
to accept them as their master.
I'm still just an
ordinary village girl.
I only did that because
Jugem asked me to.
Honestly, I spent
the entire time scared
that they would eat me.
I understand, but
even though they say
all ogres are man-eaters.
I think that just means
they're carnivores.
Since the goblins hunt,
I'm sure we'll have
plenty of meat for them.
So there shouldn't be much risk
of them attacking anyone.
Besides, at the moment,
we need all the help
that we can get.
Maybe we should've had them
pledge themselves to you.
I think I'm best
suited to supporting
the frontline fighters,
but you can hang back
and base your orders on
what you see happening.
Yeah, I guess. That makes sense.
And, by the way, about
us going to E-Rantel.
Oh, yeah!
I'm nervous about
going to the city,
but I'll try not
to embarrass you.
--Sorry.
--[ENRI] Why?
I have to heal the goblins
we rescued from Agu's tribe.
So I won't be able to join you.
I really wish I could though.
[ENRI]
Wait. I have to go by myself?
The goblins will escort you
all the way to
the gate, of course.
[ENRI] But, they're not allowed
to enter the city, are they?
I'll tell you what.
I bet I'm the only person
in the world in this bind.
It's so weird, suddenly
having to act like
I'm above other people.
And on top of that,
I have to go visit places
I've never been and do things
I've never done before!
So. Listen.
I was really just hoping to
sell some medicinal herbs.
First, I'll use Detect Magic.
[MAGIC CASTER grunts]
You'll not make a fool of me!
Reveal the magic item you
tried to sneak into the city!
Do you mean this thing?
--[SOLDIERS, MAGIC CASTER gasp]
--[ENRI] What?
[MAGIC CASTER]
Appraisal Magic Item.
What demonic relic is this?
It has such an
incredible power level
that my appraisal spell
couldn't measure it!
Madness! Impossible!
Tell us your true
identity, woman!
I thought you seemed
suspicious from the start!
Huh?
--Yeah, so did I!
--[ENRI] Wait, what?
Cease this frail
attempt at deception!
Tell us how you obtained
that artifact, wench!
Well, you see...
It was a present I got
from Lord Ains Ooal Gown,
a spellcaster who
saved my village.
You mean you received
such a terrifyingly
valuable item for free?
What? Are you saying that this
item would be expensive?
[MAGIC CASTER]
Don't play stupid!
That horn can summon
a horde of foul goblins.
Though I don't actually know
the exact number, persay.
--[SOLDIER 03C] Goblins?
--[MAGIC CASTER] Yes.
It is in equal parts
dangerous and valuable.
It could be sold for
at least 3,000 gold.
No way.
That much?
I could understand if she were
an experienced magic
user, or even just
a highly ranked adventurer,
but this simply makes no sense!
If her claim that
she's nothing more
than a village girl were true,
then she wouldn't
have that item!
She must be planning
something nefarious!
No, I-- I'm telling the truth.
I'm just a village girl.
Move, men, arrest her at once!
You're kidding me!
Don't try to resist!
[SOLDIER 03A]
No sudden moves!
I'm sorry, but you've
made a mistake.
I'm just a girl from
a country village!
I don't know anything
about magic, I swear!
[MOMON]
What's this about?
Huh?
Well, if it isn't Lord Momon.
It's an honor, sir.
[MOMON]
What has she done?
Well, sir, she was in possession
of a suspicious item.
[MOMON] Enri. Yes.
It's Enri Emmott, correct?
Uh. Yeah. Have we met, sir?
[MOMON]
Uh--
Oh!
You're the gentleman
who came to my village
with Nphi, aren't you?
But, how do you know my name?
[MOMON]
Mm... Hm...
Do you want to talk?
[MAGIC CASTER clears throat]
Release the girl at once.
But, why would we do that?
I have just been assured
that her intentions
are good by the Adamantite
class adventurer Lord Momon.
I understand, sir.
Emmott of Carne Village.
We grant you entry
into E-Rantel.
Oh. Thank you.
You guys have a nice day.
[ENRI]
This is worth 3,000 gold?
It's hard to believe
that Lord Gown would
give these things away
if they're that valuable.
And I've already
used up one of them.
[gasps]
Greetings. Mr. Momon
bade me to ask you
a quick question.
Beautiful.
Such flattery will get you--
[ENRI]
Just like Miss Lupisregina.
[gasps]
Oh! That was random.
But, I guess you just remind me
of another pretty person I know.
Your personalities
are different, but--
You have my thanks.
Huh?
Anyway, on behalf
of Lor--uh, Mr. Momon,
I ask this question;
please answer with haste.
Miss Emmott.
What business do you
have in E-Rantel?
Well, before I get to that.
Mr. Momon's the whole reason
I was able to get in.
So please let him know
that I'm very grateful.
[NABE]
Consider it done. Proceed.
Thank you.
So there were a few things
I needed to do here.
Let's see. First,
I'm gonna visit the temple.
I plan to see if any
of the homeless there
would like to move
to our village.
Then I need to post a job
at the Adventurer's Guild,
sell these medicinal herbs,
and purchase supplies.
I understand. Farewell.
What an interesting lady.
[ENRI] My village needs
defenders against
the Giant of the East and
Demon Snake of the West.
Both of those creatures
are incredibly powerful.
I'm afraid that only
Adamantite class adventurers
can accept your request.
Is one around?
Their services come
at a very high price.
Right, uh.
Doesn't the capital
give financial aid
for this kind of thing?
They do.
However, that subsidy
is only able to cover
a portion of the
total cost accrued.
Thank you for explaining.
Could I get an estimate
of what the cost might be?
[RECEPTIONIST 03A sighs] Give
me a moment to calculate it.
For now, you can take a seat.
[ENRI]
Thanks again.
[sighs] She seemed
really annoyed with me.
I suppose that makes sense.
A customer who can't pay
isn't a customer at all.
[ENRI]
I could always make some money
by selling this horn,
but I got it as a gift.
It would be ungrateful of me
to pawn it off like that.
[sighs]
[RECEPTIONIST 03A]
Miss Emmott? Miss Emmott!
Miss Enri Emmott
of Carne Village,
or no, Lady Emmott!
Um. Yes, ma'am?
[RECEPTIONIST 03A]
About your village's request.
May I ask for some
additional information please?
Yeah, no problem.
If you find the idea agreeable,
we could discuss the
details over a drink
in the reception room.
I'm begging you!
Tell me every last detail!
I shudder at the
thought of missing
any shred of information!
Okay?
That was exhausting.
[KAIJALI]
Miss Enri!
[laughs]
[ENRI] The guild lady
had so many questions.
Which is weird, because I felt
like she blew me off at first.
[KAIJALI] Sounds like
you had a rough time.
On the plus side,
the medicinal herbs
sold for a great price.
It warms my heart to hear that.
Let us join in prayer
and thank our god
for blessing you on this day.
Then let's join
as husband and wife.
We heard that last part, Cona!
You know, I still
feel like I should've
accompanied Miss Enri
into the city.
Don't be stupid!
If one of us goblins
tried to enter the city,
he'd be killed by the
guards immediately!
Heh! I'd like to see them try.
Don't worry, Miss Enri.
I, the mighty Gokou,
will always protect you.
And so will the rest of us!
Oh. That's right.
I was planning to wait
until we got back home,
but actually, I think this
might be the perfect time.
Kaijali.
It's for me?
[ENRI]
Gokou.
Unlai.
Nosuli.
Suigyo.
Cona.
I don't know much about weapons,
so I got someone from
the Adventurer's Guild
to help me pick them.
Finest sword I've had.
Got a nice heft to it.
This can do some damage.
This is a big help.
My last sword had just chipped.
Glad to help.
Wow. Miss Enri.
You picked these
out just for us?
I hope they're to your liking.
These are great gifts,
but I don't really feel
like we deserve them.
[ENRI] Not only did you risk
your lives to keep me safe,
you helped me rebuild
my home village.
I could never do enough
to fully repay you for that.
I know this isn't much, but,
I hope you'll accept it.
I'll always be grateful
for every last one of you.
You're so kind.
[ENRI]
What?!
Well, I hope you'll
at least consider it.
I will.
[KAIJALI]
What happened?
I'm sorry, but I
need a little time
to think things over
right now, Kaijali.
Hey-yoh!
Miss Lupisregina! Hi!
I'm so glad you're
here right now!
Whoa there, take it easy!
Someone help!
Save me! I'm being assaulted!
Oh, no...
[ENRI] What? No--
Calm down, I was just--
Aw, I didn't mean to upset'cha.
I was just makin'
a cute little joke.
It's fine. Could I
ask for some advice?
I'm kind of at
my wit's end here.
Is something stressing you out?
Well, your big sis Lupisregina's
got your back, okay?
C'mon, ask the question.
[laughs]
Long story short,
the village chief
wants me to take over for him.
A year ago, I was doing
chores for my parents.
I'd be an awful chief.
I'd run the village
straight into the ground.
The worst part is the whole
village got together without me.
And every last one of them
agreed that I should do it.
It's so ridiculous. So, uh...
I should just turn
them down, shouldn't I?
That's a toughie. I don't know.
I never promised I'd have
an answer for you, Enri,
just that I'd hear the question.
[chuckles] I really
can't help you out.
I can only say this much.
Whoever the village
chief may be,
they're going to make mistakes.
There have only
ever been 41 people
who could make the
perfect choice every time,
and none of us can hold
a candle to them.
There's no need to worry about
whether you'll make mistakes
because you're bound to.
That said,
out of all the denizens of this
village, logically speaking,
you're obviously the
most qualified candidate
for such a position.
Wait. Do you
really think that?
[LUPISREGINA]
I do.
Why don't'cha ask that
young man what he thinks?
[chuckles]
[ENRI]
What's that?
[NPHIREA]
It's the ogre's new home.
The goblins got together
and built it for them.
In just one day?
Yeah, Lord Gown
came by and lent us
a few stone golems to help out.
That's one more way
this village owes him.
So about you becoming chief.
I think... I really
think you should do it.
And why is that? I'm just a--
[NPHIREA] No. You're more
than "just a village girl."
You lead all the goblins.
And you're good at it, too.
Yeah, but--
[NPHIREA] When I talked to
Mr. Jugem and the others
about protecting the village,
they told me that,
push come to shove,
they would kidnap
you and escape.
What?
He also wanted me to help
them find and protect
Nemu so that we could
all run away together.
Oh.
But look, if you were
to become village chief,
that would make
this your village.
Knowing that, the goblins
would fight for it.
It might not seem like
much of a difference,
but to them, it really would be.
That magic horn really
makes the goblins
value their summoner.
If you ask me, that's 'cause
of who their summoner is.
Huh?
After all, you value
each and every one of them
as a unique individual.
Of course they treasure you.
Instead of using them as slaves,
you treat them as partners.
It's just that simple.
But, it's not like I'm the
only person in the village
who treats them nicely.
The others aren't rude,
but have you ever
heard them call
a goblin by his name?
I know I haven't.
[gasps]
Me neither.
That's how it is.
If my opinion matters to you,
I think you would be good
at this kind of thing.
And if you become chief,
you'll unite humans and
goblins under one leader.
Well, I suppose everybody
would help me, right?
[NPHIREA]
Of course.
All right then.
Thanks for the advice.
I'm on my way to talk
to the village chief.
Once a choice has been made,
there's no point delaying.
'Kay. I'm rooting for you, Enri.
[LUPISREGINA]
Just as I thought.
She really is doing it.
This is so exciting.
[giggles]
[YURI] Lupis? Lord Ains
has called for you.
Oh, well, if it isn't
my big sis Yuri.
And what is it that has you
in such a pleasant mood?
Just now,
a new leader has been
born in this village.
One with great potential.
Why, she could change history.
Unless, something wicked
was to come along
and snuff out her spark just
as it was about to kindle.
I wonder what
kind of expressions
those villagers would make.
Just the thought of
them screaming out
as they're crushed
underfoot like insects
makes me tremble
with excitement.
[YURI] My, my. You are
a sadistic creature.
Yeah, I guess I am.
I just really hope
this village burns.
[AINS] After we built
our Nazarick decoy
in the Great Forest,
the Giant of the East
and Demon Snake of
the West united
and began gathering
forces to oppose us.
The names of these new monsters
have piqued my interest,
so I will journey forth
into the forest
to seek their layer
with Aura at my side.
Meanwhile, I have also devised
a test for Lupisregina.
Chapter 4: "Giant of the East,
Demon Snake of the West."
If you value your life,
submit yourself to me.