[BOTH gasp]
[AINS]
Are you certain?
[GAZEF]
Of course.
[AINS]
You will die.
Fortunately, I came
here prepared to die.
[AINS] Then what are you
hoping to accomplish?
All that stands before you on
this path is your destruction.
What stands before me now
is the commander of my enemies.
Therefore, my course is clear.
[AINS]
I may be close in proximity,
but my power is far
beyond your reach.
[AINS] You can't even
react in time to dodge.
That is but a fraction
of what I'm capable of.
Knowing that, do you
really think you have
any hope of winning?
[GAZEF]
It's possible, Master Gown.
[AINS] Do you think
yourself invincible because
I have no desire to kill you?
I assure you, the thought
never crossed my mind.
I merely wish to fulfill
my duty as Chief Warrior
of the Kingdom. Surely
that's not a surprise.
[AINS] If you face me, know
that I will strike you down
without hesitation.
And I assure you, your
demise will be absolute.
I expect so.
[AINS]
A shame.
I'm something of a
collector, so it pains me
to kill someone so
rare and valuable.
In the name of my Kingdom,
as Chief Warrior,
I challenge the Sorcerer King,
Ains Ooal Gown to a duel!
I harbor no regrets!
Come! Let us end this!
[CLIMB]
No.
[BRAIN]
Gazef.
Before we formally begin,
one last thing.
Why don't we have these two
serve as witnesses to our duel?
[BOTH gasp]
[AINS]
Hm.
[BRAIN]
No, please wait!
I beg of you, Lord Gown.
Although I know this
is a selfish request,
let me fight beside him!
Even with us both, we can
hardly match your strength.
So surely, you will allow it?
I won't have you do this.
Do you wish to drag my resolve
as a warrior through the mud?
[gasps]
[AINS] It's irrelevant.
I'll fight any number of you.
They need not enter this fight.
And you need not lay
a finger on them.
[AINS] Those eyes.
I know that look well.
It's the gaze of a man
who has prepared himself
for death, yet steps
forward all the same.
Something I admire.
Fine. I accept your conditions.
[AINS] Do you know what I
call this, Master Stronoff?
"PVP"!
[GAZEF]
Thank you.
[AINS] I will be certain
to return your corpse
in perfect condition.
With resurrection
magic you may--
No need.
If this battle ends me,
then so be it.
Leave my corpse to lie
amongst my fallen comrades.
Lord Stronoff, why?
Let's begin, shall we?
My friends. This will
be my final battle.
Watch closely.
[GAZEF] Brain. You'll do
that for me, won't you?
This is his dying wish, Brain.
Then I got no choice.
It's an honor, Gazef.
I'm proud to bear witness
to your courage.
I feel the same.
[AINS]
One last thing, Master Stronoff.
May I have a look at
that sword of yours?
[BOTH gasp]
[GAZEF]
Certainly.
[BOTH gasp]
[AINS]
Impressive! A fine blade!
Master Stronoff,
how much do you know
about the power of this weapon?
Everything, I believe.
Specifically, the edge of this
blade is uncannily sharp.
It's able to cut through
metal as if it were paper.
[AINS]
How unfortunate.
That is a mere fraction of
this sword's true capacity.
[GAZEF]
What?
[AINS] The data level,
meaning the level of magic
the sword possesses,
is equivalent to this dagger.
[AINS] As you can see,
a weapon of such weak
magical caliber cannot even
leave a scratch on my body.
However, despite your
ignorance, it is possible
to harm me with that sword.
More than that, under the
right circumstances,
one might even kill me with it.
That means we've at least
fulfilled the most
basic requirements of a duel.
Now, if I win, may I claim
that sword as a prize?
This is the Kingdom's blade.
I'd die a disgrace
if someone took it.
[AINS] Hm. I suppose I've
had PVP matches where
both players retained
their items.
I'll allow it.
I'm grateful, Sorcerer King.
[AINS]
This seems a proper distance.
Now, you there,
in the shining armor.
Can you give us
a signal to begin?
Uh--
Do it, Climb. Don't worry.
Yes, of course!
I have some magic
handbells here with me.
Will ringing them be adequate?
[AINS]
Mm.
[GAZEF grunts]
You okay?
A bit nervous, of course.
But I'll be all right.
Good luck, Master Stronoff.
[bells chime]
[GAZEF yells]
[AINS]
One note.
You should always
prepare countermeasures
against time spells.
[AINS]
Delay Magic. True Death.
Farewell, Gazef Stronoff.
I'm sorry it had
to end this way.
Wait, what?
What did he just do?
I couldn't see.
Gazef! Hey! Get up!
[AINS]
He's already dead.
[BOTH gasp]
No, it can't be!
[AINS] Seeing him challenge me
to a battle he couldn't win
reminds me of our first meeting.
In honor of your
Chief Warrior's courage,
I will cease the pursuit
of your forces and withdraw.
His body will be returned to you
once it's been purified.
[BRAIN]
No, he wouldn't want that.
We'll take Gazef
home on our own.
We don't need help from you.
[AINS]
If you wish.
But be warned that to reverse
the instant death spell I used,
low-level resurrection
magic won't be enough.
[AINS] Also, I have a
message for the people
of your kingdom.
I am not unreasonable.
I offer mercy to all
those who bow to me.
[AINS] If you relinquish
E-Rantel to me
within the next few days,
I will prevent these creatures
from running rampant
in your capital.
Inform your king.
If you don't mind,
I'd like to carry Gazef's
body back, myself.
[CLIMB]
Of course.
And although I don't
deserve such an honor.
I'll bring his sword.
[JIRCNIV]
Seventy thousand?
[sighs] Absurd. So many
men with one blow...
And at the spell's end,
five giant beasts
were summoned to
the battlefield,
causing massive casualties.
Then, Lord Gown
engaged in a duel
with the Kingdom's Chief
Warrior, Gazef Stronoff,
and bested him.
[BAZIWOOD gasps]
While we did take losses,
it wasn't from battle.
--The cause was mass panic.
--[JIRCNIV laughing]
[NOBLE 13A]
We need to return to the capital
before anything else.
Where is Marquis Raeven?
[NOBLE 13C] If he fled, he
should have been here by now!
We were fools to think
we could fight that monster.
You're saying we should just
turn E-Rantel over to him?
[NOBLE 10C] It's a small price
to pay if it saves our Kingdom!
Why, Gazef?
You chose death.
And you left me with
this weight in my heart.
It's not fair.
You should have let
me die at your side.
[BRAIN]
Fourfold Slash of Light!
[pants]
I learned that move just
because I admired you.
[BRAIN] But you still didn't
let me fight alongside you.
I wasn't even good
enough to die!
They say you become
a lot weaker to tears
as you get older.
Seems it's true.
There's no need for you
to blame your grief on age.
Not when you've lost
someone so dear to you.
Sorry I left all that to you.
I wasn't feeling
up to a meeting.
So, do you mind filling
me in on the details?
Sure. Since Prince Barbro
has yet to return,
they're hiring some adventurers
to find out what's keeping him.
They'll form a search party
and head out tomorrow.
Huh.
Then they discussed
the fate of E-Rantel.
The nobles and the
king both agreed.
Seems we're handing it over.
I feel sorry for the king.
This won't go well for him.
True.
The noble faction will gain
influence because of this.
And the king will grow weak.
There something else?
[CLIMB]
I survived.
But the fear is still
fresh in my mind.
I was completely
helpless back there.
That was true despair I felt.
[BRAIN]
Hey. Let me ask you.
Why do you think Gazef
requested that duel?
Huh?
Uh. I mean...
[CLIMB] Maybe I'm being
arrogant, but I think I know.
[BRAIN]
Go ahead.
I believe he wanted
to show us the truth.
[BRAIN]
About what?
The power that Ains
Ooal Gown can command.
[gasps]
He saved us so that we
might find a path forward
for this kingdom.
You think?
Yeah.
He wanted us to return
here with information
so we could plan
a defense someday.
[gasps]
Maybe so. We can try.
I mean, he did put
his faith in us.
[BRAIN] I had hoped I
could fight him someday.
Last time, he defeated me.
But I was always
dreaming of a rematch.
Well... Guess I'll
be a loser forever.
That's not what you are.
What should I do, huh?
I mean, with these unanswered
feelings he's left us with?
Wait, no. It's all right. Yeah.
I'll win in my own way.
[BRAIN] Hah! You hear that,
Gazef? Screw your wishes!
I think you took
the easy way out!
You threw your life away
instead of facing me!
Our battle will continue,
even if you're not here with me!
I'm still gonna surpass you!
I think he'd want that.
Hey, Climb. Time we had a drink.
A drink. You mean now?
Uh-huh. After the
fight, as promised.
And one for Gazef, too.
Father, why don't you
take a walk in the garden?
The spring flowers
have come to bloom.
Earlier, as agreed upon,
we officially ceded control
of E-Rantel to the Sorceror
King, Ains Ooal Gown.
No need to fear the nobles.
I'll deal with them.
And as for the duties assigned
to my missing brother...
I'll carry them out
in his stead.
[RENNER]
Say, Climb.
[CLIMB]
My Lady?
Well, I...
I have a request for you.
I am always at your service.
It's nothing formal.
I've simply heard that
an altar has been made
for those who lost their lives
in our battle with the Empire.
I'd like you to deliver
these flowers there for me.
Although I feel rather ashamed
that I can't do more for them.
[gasps] Your kindness is our
Kingdom's greatest treasure.
They would be grateful.
You're too kind!
Oh. Excuse my outburst.
Um. I'll get to
that. Immediately.
[CLIMB] I don't know
what the future holds
for this world anymore.
But no matter what happens,
I'll protect Princess Renner.
[bell tolls]
Give me back my dad!
Give me back my dad,
you monsters!
Please. He's just
a child, I'm sorry!
He didn't know
what he was doing!
Forgive us!
Please have mercy on my son!
I'm begging!
Lord Ains will not
be disrespected.
It's a crime
punishable by death.
The ignorant must
learn that Lord Ains
is the Supreme Being
of this world.
You'll serve as an
example to the rest.
Who's there?
[AINS]
Ha!
[MOTHER 13A]
Please, help us!
[AINS] You turn to violence
over a tiny pebble?
You'll never land a beau
with that attitude.
Even though this is a farce,
that's a low blow.
[clears throat]
All who disrespect Lord Ains,
regardless of age,
must submit to a
suitable punishment.
Which in this case,
of course, is death.
[AINS] And if I said that I
refuse to allow it? What then?
I would see it as treason
against the ruler
of this land and crush you!
[AINS]
I see.
But if you think you can
take my life so easily,
you're mistaken, evildoer!
Greetings, my lord.
I understand, Lord Ains.
As you desire.
I have not asked your
name, armored stranger.
Let it be known.
[AINS]
Momon.
Well then, Momon.
Lord Ains has an extremely
generous proposal for you.
He'll grant you the
honor of joining
the ranks of Nazarick.
[AINS]
That's absurd.
How uncouth.
Lord Ains rules this city,
but he does not wish to control
its people through
bloodshed and despair.
This is true.
Although I doubt most
commoners would believe it.
[AINS]
What would you have me do?
When someone here
steps out of line,
throwing a rock for example,
you track them down
and give them what they deserve.
We can't encourage
lawlessness after all.
If you do this,
you'll personally
ensure that his rule
brings no harm to any innocents.
Not that Lord Ains wants that.
[AINS] You'd make me into
your watch dog, would you?
I wouldn't put it that way.
You'd be helping the people,
both as a representative
of the city and as
an enforcer of the law.
[AINS]
I will not follow an unjust law.
That's perfectly fine,
as he has no intention
of imposing any.
That said, if you refuse
and raise your sword
against the ruler of this city.
Then you'll leave me
with no choice.
I'll slay you right here.
And some bystanders may
be collateral damage.
[MOTHER 13A, BOY 13A gasp]
[AINS]
Fine!
I'll accept your offer.
But know this, if you
lay so much as a finger
on an innocent citizen
of this city,
you will face this blade.
And it will not relent until
all your heads are taken.
[DEMIURGE]
So the subjugation of E-Rantel
went smoothly, I trust?
Everything is proceeding
according to Lord Ains' plan.
Turns out humans are
surprisingly adaptable.
I suppose it's merely
their instinct to survive,
but the weak do tend
to follow the strong.
Either way, it was only
possible because of Momon.
Indeed.
Their faith in this fabricated
character shall keep
their fears at bay,
it would seem.
And even better, if they
collect information
for Momon and unite beneath him,
we won't have to worry
about outside enemies
gaining ground.
Our supreme leader was
certainly thinking ahead!
For all my scheming,
I'm afraid such thorough
machinations are still
beyond my comprehension.
Yes.
Though I don't lament my
comparably meager intellect.
Rather, I am pleased
to devote it to him
with every fiber of my being.
For he is the ruler of
life and death alike.
The highest existence.
And the man who I hope
to call my lover someday.
[AINS]
You may raise your heads.
[AINS] Your efforts have
done me a great honor.
My lord! My Sorcerer King.
We are unworthy of such praise!
It is our pleasure to come
running at your call!
Serving you is the greatest
gift we could ever ask for!
I second those
sentiments wholeheartedly.
My lord, I await
your next order.
I offer you my strength,
my life, and my body,
to do with however you see fit,
o' noble Sorcerer King.
[COCYTUS] No matter the trial
and no matter the order,
I shall not hesitate.
So long as we fight for the
glory of the Sorcerer King,
nothing will stop us!
I will give it my best!
And I'll work hard every day!
Great and mighty Sorcerer King,
as the representatives of all
those who serve under you,
we sincerely congratulate you
for the stride you've made
in taking this city.
[AINS]
Thank you for your kind words.
But we are as close as family.
Indeed, I consider you the
children of my dearest friends.
Therefore, you need
not hide your hearts
in such stifling formality.
No matter my title,
"Ains" will suffice.
As you wish, my lord.
My darling Ains.
[AINS] Nazarick shall hide
in the shadows no longer.
[AINS] This day shall be
known as the founding date
of the Sorcerer Kingdom
of Ains Ooal Gown!