There!
[AURA]
'Kay! Massacre is now complete.
Normally, we'd kill everyone
in the castle, too.
But, we don't know which
one of you is the emperor,
so I guess we'd better hold off.
That said, if the emperor
doesn't apologize
to our lord, we'll destroy
your whole country.
Emperor! Step up or
we'll kill you all!
[JIRCNIV]
Ains Ooal Gown... Who is he?
No. I don't have
time to analyze.
Don't attack!
I'm Emperor Jircniv
Rune Farlord El Nix.
I wish to talk.
This guy's kinda gutsy.
Yeah. I'm surprised
he didn't run.
Well... It seems I've
underestimated our foe.
I suppose I'll have to visit
the Great Tomb
of Nazarick myself
if we're to make peace
with its ruler.
[LOUNE]
Majesty. Please.
Apologies, but we
need you to wake.
[yawns]
I've not taken an
afternoon nap in years.
Not since I was a child.
Perhaps I owe
Lord Gown my thanks.
Yeah. You needed a break.
You're always workin'
on one thing or another.
What's that about?
Personally, I think that
Bloody Emperor's to blame.
That's a shame.
I thought you were close.
He's fine, but he pushed
through so many new reforms
that now I can barely
keep up with the man.
Right, Vermillion?
True.
And with all the fat nobles
we've purged from office,
the bureaucracy's been
stretched a bit thin.
[FLUDER, BAZIWOOD chuckle]
What a profoundly
stupid man he is.
[sighs]
However,
if I continue to make laws
at such a hectic pace,
the next emperor will
surely despise me.
[BAZIWOOD]
What do you mean "next emperor"?
Do you plan to take
a lady of Baharuth
as your empress, or will
you seek one from outside?
I would prefer someone
from another country.
There's Princess Renner.
Your thoughts?
Her actions have certainly
been praiseworthy,
but there's something
off about her.
I get the unpleasant
feeling that she makes
mistakes deliberately.
Then have you
considered the Queen
of the Dragon Kingdom?
She carries the blood of
the Brightness Dragon Lord.
And the Dragon Lords have
access to Wild magic.
Imagine casting resurrection
without the loss of life force.
Give me a break, old man.
She's a crone who hides
her age with magic.
Those two are both
the type of women
I despise the most.
[knocking]
[LEINAS]
Your Majesty. It's Leinas.
Door.
[gasps]
Your Majesty. Excuse me.
[JIRCNIV]
What is it? Come in.
Right.
We're close.
Our scouts have already sighted
the Great Tomb of Nazarick.
Assuming that the report
they gave me is accurate,
maids are stationed outside.
Presumably to welcome
us upon arrival.
Really? Maids at a tomb.
The place we're about
to see is a world
that is completely
unknown to us.
If the worst should happen,
please come to my side
immediately, Your Majesty.
Ah, I see.
If needed, we'll escape with
your teleportation magic.
Well, if it comes
to that, your knights
will buy you as much
time as we can.
[LEINAS]
As always.
I will prioritize my own
safety first and foremost.
Right. I understand.
You informed me of this when
you first became my knight.
Yes. It's the deal we struck.
[JIRCNIV]
Now...
Let's find out what kind of man
this Ains Ooal Gown really is.
Greetings, Emperor
Jircniv Rune Farlord
El Nix of Baharuth. we've
been awaiting your arrival.
We bid you and your
retinue welcome
on behalf of Lord Ains.
I am Yuri Alpha.
And my name's Lupisregina Beta!
Lord Ains has proved himself
a gracious host already
by sending such beauties.
You're a most welcome sight.
Now then.
First, let us correct
this unacceptable weather.
What?
It can't be!
No more clouds. It's
already much warmer.
Speak.
What magic did they just use?
The most basic Control Weather
is a sixth tier spell.
But I believe this magic
to be of an even higher level!
It's simply amazing!
You all must be tired
after your journey.
[FLUDER sputters]
[HOODED STUDENT 06B]
No. This is impossible!
[HOODED STUDENT 06C]
Th-They're using Death Knights?
[JIRCNIV] Death Knights?
What are these things?
Are they the same as the
undead you're keeping
below the Ministry
of Magic? Answer me!
Yes, but it's
unimaginable that anyone
could control so
many mighty undead!
Majesty. Look.
Uh. Even with all
four of us here,
I have my doubts that we
can beat one of those things.
Stay back. You're in danger.
You said it's fine
for me to run?
If you think that's for
the best, then feel free.
However, if you do run,
you'll cease to be
one of my knights.
Which would make you uninvited,
much like the Workers
who came here before.
[gasps]
[YURI]
No need to be nervous.
The Death Knights you
see here were created
by the hand of
Lord Ains himself.
Created, you say?
Yes. As such, they
are absolutely loyal
to any order he might give them.
You can rest assured
that they'll do
nothing to harm you.
[laughs]
Such mastery! It's incredible!
Master Paradyne?
What would you like to do,
Your Majesty? Ha!
[FLUDER laughs]
Shall I teleport the
both of us out of here?
I believe it might be possible
for us to escape in that manner.
Of course, that's
assuming the master
of this place allows us to.
That's an interesting
expression, old man.
Let me ask you something.
Did you truly think I'd run?
Of course not--
I should know better.
My Jircniv is much
braver than that.
We've finished
preparing your table.
Please relax and
enjoy yourselves.
Would anyone care for
some ice-cold refreshment?
Tasty!
I've never had
anything like this.
It strikes a perfect balance
between sourness and sweetness.
It's soothing to the heart.
[sighs]
I'd say the journey was
worth it just for this.
We thank you for your patience.
Lord Ains has finished
preparing and will see you now.
If you'll please step this way.
[JIRCNIV]
Gold. Status. Power.
Both military and magical.
Beautiful women, too.
[JIRCNIV] There is absolutely
nothing I could offer
this Ains Ooal Gown that
he doesn't already have.
There are many who would
equate him to a god.
I'm amazed that
no one's tried to run.
A "victory" for us
would be to make it home alive,
with the Empire intact.
Excuse me, Lord Ains,
but the Emperor of Baharuth,
Jircniv Rune Farlord
El Nix is here.
He's come in response
to your summons.
[AINS]
Emperor of Baharuth.
Thank you for coming.
I am the master of the
Great Tomb of Nazarick,
Ains Ooal Gown.
I'm pleased to meet
you, Master Ains.
You've been a most
generous host.
Pardon, Lord.
I cannot abide this blasphemy.
These humans stand here
as if they're your equals.
I must correct this.
Prostrate yourselves!
[GROUP gasps]
[AINS]
Enough, Demiurge.
[DEMIURGE]
Uh--
You're free to stand.
[AINS] It was not my
intention to insult you,
but through my inability
to control my subordinate,
I've done just that.
Please forgive me.
I will bow my head if you wish.
[gasps]
There is nothing
to forgive. Worry not.
This is a common occurrence.
Sometimes our vassals
misinterpret us.
One of my subordinates
has committed
precisely this offense.
I am most embarrassed.
Allow me to present you with
the head of the foolish noble
who sent intruders to your home.
Will you accept it?
[AINS]
I shall.
I'm not one for trophies, but I
won't put this gift to waste.
Amazing.
[AINS]
Go. Join the line.
[AINS] Now, Emperor Jircniv
Rune Farlord El Nix.
[JIRCNIV]
Jircniv will suffice.
[AINS]
I see. Emperor Jircniv, then.
Since my subordinate has acted
so rudely towards you,
I in turn will disregard
the trouble your noble
has caused to Nazarick.
[gasps]
[AINS] There is no longer
a need for apology.
You may go home in peace.
[JIRCNIV gasps]
[AINS] We're about to be
rather busy here in Nazarick.
[GROUP gasps]
[AINS] Thanks to your noble,
we now realize that trouble
will come to us even
if we keep to ourselves.
Armed with that knowledge,
we shall pre-empt any
aggression that may come.
What exactly is your meaning?
[AINS] I will defeat any
who would dare attempt
to bring harm to
the Tomb of Nazarick.
They'll be made to pay
for their arrogance.
This world shall feel my wrath
until the quiet
I love has returned.
An admirable goal!
Why don't we form an alliance?
As if your pathetic country
could ever be more--
Watch your mouth.
[AINS] Cease this racket.
I demand silence.
Rise up.
Found a country and
rule it as a king.
I can think of no
title more worthy
for the illustrious
Ains Ooal Gown.
My empire will do
all in its power
to assist you in
this great endeavor.
[AINS] What merit do
you see for yourself
in this, Emperor Jircniv?
I wish only to establish
friendly ties with you,
and the great country
you will someday create.
Let us prosper, together.
[AINS] I see. Then I
look forward to it.
[JIRCNIV]
What is he thinking?
He's at an
overwhelming advantage.
If he demanded my subservience,
I'd have no choice
but to accept.
I see. This is wonderful.
In that case,
if there is anything
we can provide you now,
ask and it will be yours.
[AINS]
Excellent.
I cannot think of
anything at present.
Though it would be
convenient if I had a way
to contact you quickly.
My secretary can
assist with that.
Meet Loune Vermillion.
[AINS] And for my part,
I'll send Demiurge to you.
[AINS]
Since you were so gracious
as to forgive his rude display,
I would like to leave
this matter to him.
Demiurge is one of my
most trusted aides.
I'm sure he can resolve
any issue that might arise.
[JIRCNIV]
He's already moved against us.
Sending a demon that can
control men with its voice.
[AINS] This is the birth
date of a new alliance.
Perhaps we'll make it a holiday.
I quite agree. Let's make it so.
Nothing would please me more.
[AINS] Well, the emperor
acted just as expected.
[SHALLTEAR]
Pardon, Lord Ains.
but might I ask
a humble question?
[AINS]
Go on.
[SHALLTEAR] Why are we
treating that human emperor
as an ally when he's clearly
so much weaker than us?
All of our actions
must be justified.
But why can't we simply
take what we want?
[AINS] We could destroy
Baharuth with ease,
but we would be condemned
for our aggression.
I'll not have the name of
Ains Ooal Gown sullied so.
[COCYTUS]
I see.
Oh, wow, you were really
thinking ahead, Lord Ains!
[laughs] Do all of you truly
believe that the thinking
behind the Supreme One's
plan is that simple? Huh?
[AINS]
Huh?
--[AURA, MARE] Huh?
--[COCYTUS] What?
Is there something we missed?
[laughs]
Oh, goodness. Lord Ains.
I think it would be
beneficial to tell Shalltear
and the others
your true intentions.
They affect our
future plans, after all.
[AINS]
As expected of you, Demiurge.
Along with my overseer of
the floor guardians, Albedo.
You've recognized
my true thinking.
[MOMONGA]
The hell is he talking about?
It's amazing to think how
long you've been planning.
I finally see why
you created Momon.
It's brilliant.
Your political acumen
knows no bounds.
[MOMONGA]
Really?
What does Momon
have to do with it?
I still don't grasp
your meaning.
[AINS]
Demiurge.
I permit you to explain my plan
as I believe you understand it.
[DEMIURGE]
Yes, My Lord.
[JIRCNIV]
Damn.
That was the castle
of a Demon King.
Death was sitting
on that throne.
[JIRCNIV]
But no. I'm not done yet.
We still have a
chance of victory.
This Ains Ooal Gown is a
monster among monsters
who can make Death
Knights with ease.
Should he become our enemy,
Baharuth will fall.
Even if we seek to appease him,
such a being might kill
the living for amusement.
He's undead, after all.
We're agreed?
Completely.
[HOODED STUDENT 06B]
The situation is just
as you've described.
[BAZIWOOD]
I feel the same.
I've got my doubts
that this is an enemy
mankind can win against.
[JIRCNIV]
From what I've seen,
he rules as an
absolute overlord.
And disregarding his appearance,
he has a king's charisma.
And on top of that,
this fiend is intelligent.
I saw meaning behind every
movement he chose to make.
I've no idea where he
obtained such knowledge,
but he appeared to know a
great deal about our empire.
[gasps]
[JIRCNIV] Ains Ooal Gown
clearly surpasses the old man
as a magic caster.
Fluder's obsessed with magic,
yet he left without protest.
Normally he would've
begged to stay behind
so he could glean
new information,
regardless of the risk.
[JIRCNIV]
He barely seemed curious at all.
[gasps]
[JIRCNIV]
He knew.
[JIRCNIV] He wasn't curious
because he'd seen it before.
Sorry, but are you
all right, Your Majesty?
You look a little pale.
[JIRCNIV]
How long?
From the beginning? Of course.
Yes, I believe he's
the one who suggested
we send Workers to that
tomb in the first place.
He's a traitor.
[ALL gasp]
Fluder Paradyne has betrayed me.
That's impossible.
Surely this is but a jest.
It's no jest. Just how
reliant upon him are we?
If I strip him of power,
how much damage
will it cause us?
The damage would
be unimaginable.
Fluder represents much
of our strength.
No country has a caster
that can match him.
Fluder's power is a
great negotiating tool.
If they learn of his demotion,
our neighbors will
feel emboldened.
There is much we must accomplish
if we're to
overcome this threat.
Our only hope is to gather
together the Empire,
the Kingdom, the Theocracy,
the Council State,
and the Holy Kingdom.
We will have to create
a grand alliance,
to fight against Nazarick.
Ostensibly, the Empire will
act as a faithful ally
while we form a resistance.
It's risky.
In the event that our
plan is discovered,
our country will be
the first to fall.
Roles reversed,
I would make an example of
our Empire by destroying it.
Oh, yeah.
That does sound like
somethin' you'd do.
I'll take that as a compliment.
Because of this, the
Empire can't be the first
to suggest an alliance.
The other countries must
band together on their own.
And as we await this.
We must seek out an
individual with the power
to threaten Ains himself.
[BAZIWOOD]
You think they exist?
I know it.
I've seen them
standing by his throne.
Yes. That's how he'll think.
We can proceed with confidence
that this is the emperor's plan.
Men of some intelligence,
like himself,
are often easier
to read than fools.
So the emperor's plan
is to turn one of us
against the others while
creating an alliance
of human kingdoms
behind Lord Ains' back?
Then it's doomed to fail,
'cause none of us
would ever betray Lord Ains!
If the Empire's already
planning to betray us
then maybe we should go ahead
and destroy it right now.
No need for that.
Everything that has transpired
has played directly
into our master's great plan.
Isn't that right, my lord?
[AINS]
Yes. Exactly so.
[GUARDIANS gasp]
[DEMIURGE]
Lord Ains' gaze
is always set to
the distant future.
If not for the hero Momon,
we would've been forced
to rule E-Rantel
through fear and oppression.
The Golden Princess
may have been
of assistance there,
but such a valuable card
is best kept in reserve.
She was just as I imagined
from Sebas' description.
No. She surpassed
my expectations.
I like her.
If that's the case, I'd like
to meet her myself someday.
I think you'll get
the opportunity soon.
Now then. Supreme One.
In accordance with the plan
that you set into motion,
the stage is now set
for our country
to rise and dominate this world.
[AINS]
Yes. Quite.
I think this leaves us
with one final matter
to be decided at present.
A mere king would
be no different
from any of the worms
we're about to conquer.
I humbly suggest
that we come up with
a more befitting title.
[AINS]
Very well. Do as you wish.
Would anybody here care
to make a suggestion?
Why, yes, I have an idea.
In honor of Lord Ains'
perfect form,
I believe we should call
him the King of Beauty!
[AINS]
Huh?
[AURA]
I've got one!
There's no one who's
stronger than Lord Ains,
so why don't we call
him the Muscle King?
[MARE]
Um, m-may I suggest one?
Lord Ains is very kind, so um...
What if we called him--
I don't know.
The King of Love, maybe?
[DEMIURGE]
Personally,
I believe we should
call him the Wise King.
In honor of his sound judgement.
[MOMONGA]
"Wise King?" So dorky.
[ALBEDO]
Sebas?
[SEBAS] I for one
believe that "King Ains"
would be sufficient.
[ALBEDO]
And as for my opinion.
Since he's the one
who stands above
all other Supreme Beings,
why not the Supreme King?
[GUARDIANS]
Ooh!
[ALBEDO]
What are your thoughts, Cocytus?
[COCYTUS] Hm. Lord Ains
is unrivaled in magic.
The people he rules
should know that.
Therefore, I believe
"the Sorcerer King"
would be a fitting
title for him.
[AINS]
Yes. A fine suggestion, Cocytus.
Once our country is established,
I shall be known as Ains Ooal
Gown, the Sorcerer King.
[EMPIRE KNIGHT 06A]
My Lord Fluder. I have news.
A pair of Adamantite
class adventurers
wish to meet with you.
They're a team that
calls themselves "Darkness."
You're a-a god.
You're truly an entity
of the tenth tier!
I am undeserving. I know this.
But I beg of you, oh great one.
Make me your student!
I want to see the
chasm of magic.
To tug upon the threads
of creation! Show me, please!
[AINS] And in exchange?
What will you give me?
[FLUDER]
Everything!
All that I have is at
your disposal, my lord.
I kneel before you, O' Deep One.
Wise Master of the Chasm!
Your Grace--
It's fine.
[JIRCNIV] We have to be
both clever and swift.
This is no petty border dispute,
but a battle to defend mankind.
To protect our future.
[AINS] The Baharuth Empire
formally recognizes Nazarick
as a sovereign country
lead by the Sorcerer
King Ains Ool Gown.
Jirkniv also demands that
E-Rantel and the lands around it
be returned to Nazarick.
When the leaders of the
Re-Estize Kingdom meet
to discuss thier options,
Gazef advises them
to appease me.
Chapter 10:
"Preparation for War."
It's difficult to lead
when those that serve
you are incompetent.