[AINS]
Raise your heads.
[SERVANTS]
Lord.
[AINS] You all fulfilled
your roles splendidly
during our operation in
the kingdom of Re-Estize.
[AINS]
Sebas. Solution. Come forward.
[AINS] I'm certain the
information you gathered
will prove invaluable.
Therefore, I have
decided to honor
your diligent efforts
with a reward.
Sebas.
Lord.
[AINS] You asked that
I spare Tuare's life,
and indeed I shall,
but I do so to repay a debt
to a prior associate,
not in response to your efforts.
Therefore I shall grant
you something else
that you desire, as well.
[SEBAS] Lord Ains, my only
wish is to devote myself--
[AINS]
If you hope to please me,
then I highly suggest you
accept my generosity.
[SEBAS]
My apologies. In that case,
I would ask for clothes
and other daily
necessities for Tuare.
[AINS] Granted. I shall
provide the necessary gold.
Perhaps she can accompany you
on a bit of a shopping date.
[SEBAS]
You jest, my lord.
[AINS]
Not at all.
Then you have my gratitude.
[AINS] Now, Solution,
tell me what you desire
so that I may grant it.
I would like to request
a small selection
of humans, Lord.
If possible, I would
prefer them to be alive.
And if those humans
were innocent as well,
that would give me
the utmost pleasure.
[AINS]
Living humans, you say? Granted.
However, I will not
allow innocent ones.
Forgive me, but I fear
I cannot grant your wish
exactly to your specifications.
[SOLUTION]
It's more than enough, my lord!
[AINS]
Next. Entoma.
[ENTOMA]
Lord.
[AINS] It seems that your
voice has yet to return.
[ENTOMA] Do you find
me repulsive, my lord?
[AINS]
Certainly not.
Your efforts are all
that matter to me,
and they have earned
you a reward.
[ENTOMA]
In that case, Lord Ains.
I would have the voice
of the woman who stole mine.
Should the need to
kill her ever arise,
I ask that you give me
the order to do it.
[AINS]
Ah, the girl with the mask.
She remains a mystery
to me. But very well.
I will call for you
if such a time arises.
[ENTOMA] You have my
gratitude, Lord Ains.
From the depths of my heart.
[AINS]
Mm.
Ah.
Mm. That's the stuff!
[AINS]
I had to get a bit creative,
but I finally found a way
to clean these bones of mine.
[AINS] Who knew a slime bath
would be so refreshing?
It didn't sound very
appealing at first,
but I wish I'd tried
this ages ago.
I can feel my gooey friend
slithering its way
into every nook and cranny.
[AINS sighs]
[MOMONGA] This might be
the most Japanese thing
I've done since I
came to this world.
Hot baths are a
national pastime!
I may be all bones,
but a love for bathing
is in my blood for sure!
Well, not that I had
the time or money to enjoy
anything this fancy back home.
[MOMONGA] I wonder if I
embarrassed Sebas back there.
Tuare does dote on him, though.
Demiurge said they seem close.
If they go on that
date in E-Rantel,
maybe I'll wear a
disguise and tail them.
Just kidding.
[AINS]
Still, as their supervisor,
it's my job to ensure
that my employees--
or subordinates--
enjoy their time off!
[ECLAIR]
Do not leave a single speck
of dust behind, understand?
--[MANSERVANTS] Yee!
--[MAIDS] Yes.
[ECLAIR] Heh! For, surely,
this Great Tomb of Nazarick
shall be mine to command soon!
[MANSERVANTS]
Yee!
[ECLAIR]
Mm-hm!
[ECLAIR] Why, I didn't
notice you standing there!
Lovely weather we're having.
A fine morning!
[ECLAIR]
Hm?
[FOIRE]
Looks like you're in top form
this morning, Cixous!
That's because I'm taking
care of Lord Ains today.
[LUPISREGINA] Oh! So you need
the extra calories, huh?
Whoa. Miss Lupisregina!
You just had to sneak up
on us, didn't you?
Goodness, you nearly
made my heart
leap out of my chest!
[giggles] Can you blame me?
That look on all your
faces was priceless!
I'll have to try this
back in the village.
[FOIRE]
What village?
These days, I've been working
at a human settlement
called Carne Village.
[LUMIERE] Humans, huh?
That must be taxing.
More like a total bore!
I was hoping for a gig
with a little more
excitement, you know?
[ECLAIR] Unhand me!
Unhand me this instant!
I have highly important
cleaning to do!
--[MAIDS shriek]
--[MAID 1D] It's CZ!
[MAID 1E]
Hey, CZ!
[CZ]
So there you are.
[ECLAIR] My insides! They're
about to become outsides!
[CZ] I wish you would stop
misusing Complete Invisibility.
I know, sorry!
[CZ] On top of that,
you started without me.
You said we'd have
breakfast together.
[LUPISREGINA]
Shoot, I forgot!
That sure did surprise me!
I'm just happy we got
to see Miss Lupisregina.
[MAIDS chuckle]
[gasps]
[CIXOUS]
Gotta refocus.
I'm taking care of
Lord Ains today!
Okay! It's time to go!
[CIXOUS]
Good morning to you, Lord Ains.
[AINS]
Mm.
[AINS] Ah, always here
well ahead of schedule.
You are permitted to enjoy your
breakfast at the very least.
To be frank,
serving you is my joy,
and the greatest
honor in my life.
That goes for the
rest of the maids
and the eight-edge
assassins, as well.
[CIXOUS] We only come
early because, with you,
we treasure every moment.
[AINS] It was not my
intent to reprimand you.
But did you rest well yesterday?
I did!
In order to serve
the Supreme One
with every fiber of my being,
I ensured that I rested
most thoroughly.
[AINS]
I see.
[MOMONGA] It's like we're
running a sweatshop here.
[knocking]
[MOMONGA]
If I don't order them to rest,
they'll work
themselves to death!
Loyalty is nice,
but there's a limit!
And they're alive, so I
can't just reprogram them
like when they were NPCs.
[CIXOUS]
Lord Ains.
Lord Demiurge is here
to meet with you.
[AINS] If you're looking
for Albedo, she's off.
My lord. She's "off"?
[AINS] I requested that she
spend the day in leisure
with the other female
floor guardians.
And this
is something I put together
for the male floor guardians.
I had hoped to include Sebas,
but he's occupied
with Tuare today.
I'll invite him next time.
What is it?
[AINS]
An information circular.
Come to me, my cavalry beast!
Whoa!
That's way more fancy
than a regular bicorn!
Look his horns. And his
muscles are so taut!
Indeed so!
He's truly worthy of the
title "War Bicorn Lord."
Although, technically,
any level 100 Bicorn
would look like this.
[AURA] I see. So what
do you call him, then?
A bicorn. I just said.
I don't mean its
species! Its name!
[ALBEDO]
Does he need one?
That's up to you
since he's your pet.
He's more of a weapon
than a pet, actually.
Also, I'm not quite certain
that I'm summoning
the same bicorn each time.
Well, you could
always ask Kyouhukou,
since he's so good
at summoning things.
I don't know if that expertise
applies to anything
other than cockroaches, though.
[ALBEDO]
Kyouhukou?
I know he's loyal to
Nazarick, so I feel bad
for disliking him,
but his appearance
is rather distressing.
Yeah. No kidding.
His family can never behave!
They skitter up in your clothes
and it's just the worst!
I can feel their
little legs now!
[SHALLTEAR]
That's enough!
You're making me positively
itchy! How vile!
I'm relieved to see that
everyone is on the same page.
[AURA]
Back to the bicorn.
Are you gonna name him or not?
[ALBEDO] If I did, I would want
it to have a dignified name.
Something that
embodies my passion
and dedication for Lord Ains!
How about "Top of the World?"
[SHALLTEAR sighs]
Lord Ains certainly is
the top of the world, but is it
appropriate to ride on him?
[ALBEDO chuckles]
[growls]
Let's forget the name.
Hey, why don't you take him
for a quick test ride?
[BICORN whinnies]
[ALBEDO]
Am I doing something wrong?
[AURA] Get off for now.
We'll figure it out.
Yes. Right.
I see! You must be too
heavy for the thing!
I am not!
Even taking my armor and
muscle mass into account,
I'm well under the
recommended weight limit!
[BICORN whinnies]
[AURA]
He's acting strange.
[ALBEDO]
What could it be?
[SHALLTEAR laughs]
I'll look it up for you.
You might drown in your own
ignorance at this rate.
An encyclopedia
by Lord Peroroncino!
This was a gift from
Lord Ains, by the way!
Let's see.
Bicorn.
B... i...
She shouldn't brag.
Lord Ains gave me this
wristband as a gift.
Just like my ring.
Although,
I wish I could receive
something a little more
personal from Lord Ains.
Something special
that's ours alone.
[SHALLTEAR]
I found it!
What's it say?
Give me a moment.
According to this entry, bicorns
are a symbol of impurity.
In terms of who is
capable of riding them,
they are the
opposite of unicorns.
While unicorns can only
be ridden by pure maidens,
bicorns can only be
ridden by impure ones.
Huh?
[BOTH]
Huh?!
[SHALTEAR] Is there something
you want to tell us, Albedo?
What do you mean?
But you're supposed
to be a succubus.
How does that make sense?
'Kay.
[ALBEDO]
Not "supposed to be," I am one!
I'm sorry, but I don't have
any experience with men!
I've been too focused on
my job as a floor guardian,
waiting in the throne
room, day after day!
I hardly even talk to people.
Who am I supposed
to have sex with?
I'm ashamed to admit
it, but Lord Ains
hasn't summoned me
to his bed even once.
What about you Shalltear,
how is your love life?
[SHALLTEAR yelps]
I've only been
with girls, really.
[AURA]
Whoa!
Well, you know what it's like.
It's impossible
to find a good man.
Or more like the only
good one is a dead one,
but not if they're decomposing.
Right? Right?
I know I should just
smile and agree,
but this is absolutely twisted.
[ALBEDO] At any rate,
at least we know why I can't
ride the bicorn, as humiliating
and ridiculous as it is!
Actually.
Lord Ains might sleep with me
if I tell him it's for work!
[SHALLTEAR]
That's cheating!
Hah! This is all for
the sake of Nazarick!
Surely you wouldn't
let your jealousy
get in the way of our success!
Ha! Why would I be
jealous of a woman
who resorts to that?
It's not even love.
Just business!
[BOTH growling]
Hey, you two.
I doubt this is how Lord Ains
wants us to spend our day off.
But this is all new to me.
I'm not used to relaxation.
When you're not working,
what do you enjoy?
Admittedly, I spend
most of my time
patrolling the first
to third floors.
If I have a moment left over,
I might take a bath
or fix up my clothes.
A bath. Yes.
Now that I think about it,
we have a nice spa on
the ninth floor, don't we?
[HAMUSUKE grunting]
Growing strong, Hamusuke is!
That's great, Hamusuke!
Keep it up!
[HAMUSUKE] Becoming a master
of martial arts, I am!
Well, that's not exactly
an easy feat to pull off.
Martial Arts require
an innate talent.
Give it my best effort, I shall!
Refuse to accept defeat, I do!
[HAMUSUKE]
Submit, you will!
[MARE]
Uh, sorry if I kept you waiting!
[PULCINELLA] Well, if it
isn't Lord Mare. Greetings!
Good to see you,
as always, Pulcinella.
Might I ask what business
brings you here today?
[PULCINELLA] Nothing
complicated, I assure you.
As you know, I'm currently
under the employ
of Lord Demiurge, and he's
sent me here on his behalf
to make a small delivery.
I entrust it to you, young lord.
[MARE]
Uh, thanks for bringing it by.
Um, so, uh, what kind of
work has Lord Demiurge
been focusing on these days?
[PULCINELLA]
Breeding experiments.
Breeding between humans
and non-human species
is impossible, so they say!
A tragic limitation
this world has.
Even with the beauty of true
love binding two species,
their union cannot bear fruit.
My master is diligently
striving to rectify
this mistake of nature.
To give two poor
lovers a chance
to conceive a child!
Sorry. Those were more
details than you asked for.
And since you've received
the information circular,
I best be on my way.
To create such happiness
is a demanding job.
Okay. Well, thanks and
good luck with work!
[PULCINELLA]
Mm-hm.
"This is for male
floor guardians, only.
As such, take heed. Do not
distribute this circular
amongst the female
staff, please."
[giggles]
[gasps]
Whoa. Okay!
I better deliver this
to Cocytus right away!
Yeah.
[AINS] Such infernal discord!
I demand silence!
[AINS]
Silence. Hm.
Is this a good pose?
Might look cooler if I bent
my forearm inwards some.
[AINS]
Such infernal discord!
I demand silence!
[AINS] All right, I can scratch
that pose off the list.
Guess I should practice the
lines I use to buy time.
[MOMONGA sighs]
I'm just a normal
nine-to-five office drone.
How am I supposed to pull off
this supreme overlord routine
day in and day out?
[MOMONGA sighs]
[MOMONGA]
What do I do?
I need to present myself
with the admirable air
worthy of a Nazarick overlord.
But I gotta do it without
destroying the image
everybody has of Ains Ooal Gown.
Ah. I need a nap.
Get up, you sloth! Keep working!
[knocking]
[CIXOUS]
Lord Ains? It's time.
[AINS] Well, I suppose
that settles that.
[AINS] Guess I'll put
my practice to the test!
[MOMONGA]
Hell, yes!
Now that is how
a ruler takes a seat!
I mean, not that I know
how a ruler would sit,
but it felt right.
[AINS]
Now, then. Mare.
What've you brought me?
Uh, right!
I, um, well, it's a...
valuable document!
[AINS]
Why are you staring?
Is there something interesting
I'm unaware of on my face?
Wha-- Not at all, my lord!
Honestly, I was just admiring
how cool you are, Lord Ains.
[AINS]
I am? [laughs]
Well aren't you
adept at flattery!
I'm not trying to flatter you!
Uh. I...
I'm sorry, Lord Ains, excuse me.
It's just that...
I genuinely do
think you're cool!
I mean, right now,
that way you sat down,
your movement was so graceful
and yet so commanding!
[AINS]
I see. Thank you, Mare.
I'm truly happy to hear that.
Your words always
seem to have a way
of filling me with joy.
[AINS] And not only that,
but it fills me with gratitude
for my comrades.
Your comrades? Y'mean
the other supreme beings?
[AINS]
That's right.
I'm thankful that we created
the Great Tomb of Nazarick
together, and equally grateful
they carried onward
with their endeavor
until they created all of you.
And, of course, that includes
the two of you as well,
Albedo and Cixous.
You actually know my lowly name?
[AINS] I consider you all
to be my treasures.
[AINS]
I wouldn't even give you up
to Bukubuku Chagama herself.
[ALBEDO panting]
[CIXOUS]
Lord Ains. I can't stay silent.
And know I speak
for all of Nazarick
when I say this.
But of all the creators
who lived in this world,
we're so thankful you're
the one who stayed behind.
[CIXOUS gasps, grunts]
Forgive my tone.
I don't mean to
offend our creators,
nor do I mean to
speak so freely.
But. Please accept
our continued fealty!
Please, my lord!
[AINS]
I shall.
For I am the one ruler of
the Great Tomb of Nazarick,
your exalted master.
The fearsome yet fair,
Ains Ooal Gown!
[ALBEDO gasps]
[AINS] Now then, Mare.
Go wash your face.
[AINS yelps]
Oh, Lord Ains!
I've tried so hard, but I
can't hold back any longer!
You are to blame, my lord!
[AINS]
What the-- Wait.
...after hearing your words!
And I'll be done long
before your assassins
--can try to pry me off of you!
--[AINS] Hang on! Huh?
[AINS] What in blazes
is wrong with you?
Get off me, Albedo! Hey, stop!
Leave my clothes alone and
quit gyrating like that!
[ASSASSINS]
Gone mad!
[ASSASSINS scream]
[ALBEDO moans]
Oh, Lord Ains!
[ASSASSIN 1B] What'd you
expect from the overseer
of the guardians?
[ASSASSIN 1C] Lord Mare,
we could use some help!
[ASSASSINS]
Hey, Lord Mare!
Uh, sure.
[ALBEDO] Give me but
a drop of your mercy!
Beautiful.
[ALBEDO]
Let it flow within me!
--Lord Ains! Lord Ains!
--[AINS] Will you calm down?!
[AINS] So you even look
like that when you bathe?
Well, being naked is his
normal state of being.
[COCYTUS]
Come now.
I'd appreciate it if you
didn't make me sound like
some sort of pervert.
[AINS]
Forgive me, Cocytus.
Your exoskeleton is very regal.
[COCYTUS]
You honor me, my lord.
[AINS]
Thank you, Mare.
I'll wash your back
next, if you'd like.
No! That's far too kind!
[AURA] Quite a mane you've
got down there, Albedo.
[ALBEDO]
You know, Aura,
you don't have to be
so crass about it.
[AURA laughs]
[ALBEDO]
Lord Ains is bathing
just on the other
side of this wall.
I wonder if there's
a peephole around here?
[AURA]
Don't the guys do the peeping?
[SHALLTEAR] That doesn't
exactly apply to our situation.
After all, if Lord Ains
wants to see us nude,
he need only command
us to strip.
[AINS]
Uh...
[DEMIURGE]
My deepest apologies, Lord Ains!
The overseer of the guardians...
How dare she speak
in such a manner.
I'll tell her to stop at once!
[AINS]
No! Well. I mean.
Albedo already
has enough stress.
This is her time to
cut loose and relax.
[DEMIURGE]
Of course, understood.
[rumbling]
[AURA]
Whoa, hey, what're you doing?
You can't just jump in
without rinsing off!
[AURA] What the...?
Is that stone lion moving?
[LUCIFER] Those who lack
bathing manners have no right
to enter the baths!
[LADIES scream]
[LUCIFER]
Suffer your divine punishment!
[COCYTUS]
A guardian of the baths?
I had no idea such
a creature existed.
[AINS] They don't.
That's Lucifer's voice!
It's his doing!
[DEMIURGE]
The supreme being?
[SHALLTEAR]
I can't even crack it!
This is no normal golem! Albedo!
[ALBEDO] Get out of here,
you golem-craft, pervert scum!
[AINS]
Don your armor and weapons.
We shall enter the women's bath!
I assume this is one
of Lucifer's pranks,
but we must rush to
their aid all the same!
[GROUP]
Lord!
[MOMONGA] So much for
our day off, I guess.
[ALBEDO]
Perish!
[AINS] The floor guardians
and servants gather
in the throne room
so that Demiurge and
Albedo can announce
the future plans of Nazarick.
I've no doubt such a capable
pair will convey our goals
with style and grace.
As a great ruler, my only
duty is to nod benevolently.
Hm? Hold on.
How did they come
to that conclusion?!
Chapter 2: "Carne
Village Once More."
Yes, it will be fine.
Everything will
proceed as planned.