[STUDENTS gasp]
[FLUDER]
Death Knight.
Summon Undead Sixth.
[FLUDER]
Submit to me.
[FLUDER] Still, the
monster will not yield.
If I could control this fiend.
I would surpass even
Rigrit Bers Caurau,
and become the most accomplished
magic caster in this world.
I believe you've surpassed
the power of the
Thirteen Heroes, sir.
Anything to report?
Nothing as of yet, sir. Sorry.
That's a shame.
We are still unable to simulate
a natural transformation.
Correct.
We're currently testing
to see whether proximity
to the undead is enough to
turn a corpse into a zombie.
[FLUDER grunts]
[EMPIRE KNIGHT 06A]
My Lord Fluder. I have news.
A pair of Adamantite
class adventurers
wish to meet with you.
[FLUDER] Are they from
Silver Thread Bird?
Or if not, perhaps they're
members of Eight Ripples.
[EMPIRE KNIGHT 06A]
No, sir.
They're a team that calls
themselves "Darkness."
[FLUDER]
Hm.
[AINS] These are happy
times for the Empire.
[NARBERAL]
Oh? And why do you say that?
[AINS] The eyes of those
walking past are bright.
They're the eyes of
a people that believe
the future holds
promise for them.
I've quite enjoyed
the view so far.
[AINS]
Emperor El Nix rules here.
Though, by all accounts,
he earned his title
as the Bloody Emperor,
his reforms have
greatly improved
the people's lives.
According to Fluder,
he removed all incapable
nobles from power
and chose their replacements
based on merit alone.
The country is avidly
researching magic
and improving their military.
[AINS]
Take a look at those knights.
[HORSE whinnies]
[AINS] These professional
soldiers are the backbone
of the Empire's military.
[EMPIRE KNIGHT 06B]
Hey, look.
[EMPIRE KNIGHT 06C]
Adamantite adventurers?
[NARBERAL] I must say,
they still seem rather weak.
[AINS]
Indeed they are, to our eyes.
But they're far stronger
than any force comprised
of peasant levies and
self-equipped nobility.
[AINS]
Now, then.
We came all this way,
so we may as well
visit the local
Adventurer's Guild.
I'd like to do a simple
job to get my name out.
Though I hear the guild
is less active here.
I heard the same.
The second-rate sell-swords
common around here
are known as "Workers."
[AINS] They're not
necessarily inferior.
They just take quests
outside of the guild.
They aren't protected
by the guild,
but nor are they bound
by its rules.
I imagine there's some merit
in making such a choice.
[MOMONGA sighs]
Man, this is gonna be a hassle.
[DEMIURGE] This plan will
allow us to declare
the Great Tomb of Nazarick
a sovereign nation.
And to spread word of
the great and mighty
Ains Ooal Gown
throughout this world.
[AINS]
Yes.
I believe this will help
achieve our noble purpose.
You honor me.
My lord, with your blessing,
I'd like to begin at once.
[AINS]
Mm.
[MOMONGA]
Demiurge really did come up
with a kickass plan.
I'd be hard-pressed to come
up with something better.
And, regardless...
[AINS]
The die has already been cast.
[LOUNE] The "incident"
in the Re-Estize Kingdom
caused significant damage
and casualties there.
Our reports indicate
the demon Jaldabaoth
was eventually defeated
by an Adamantite class
adventurer known as
Momon of Darkness.
I see. And Momon
slayed this demon?
[LOUNE]
No, it escaped him.
The kingdom has
tightened security
and is searching for it.
But, despite their efforts,
there've been no sightings of
the demon in the days since.
Then the Re-Estize
Kingdom is already
in a state of exhaustion.
If so, then there may be
no need for us to wage
our annual war this year.
Through their
incompetent nobles,
we've learned key information.
The great Baharuth Empire
will never follow
in the footsteps of
that kingdom of fools.
I, Emperor Jircniv Rune
Farlord El Nix,
have an order for you.
Imperial Court Wizard
Fluder Paradyne.
Are you prepared to serve me?
[FLUDER]
Yes.
Begin to investigate the demon
Jaldabaoth will all haste.
Yes, Your Majesty.
This Momon of Darkness
piques my interest as well.
So, too, does Ains Ooal Gown,
the man who saved
the king's Chief Warrior.
Some powerful figures
are emerging.
Heroes and demons alike.
Makes me wonder.
It's been 200 years
since the war against
the Demon Gods was fought.
Perhaps we're overdue
for another war like it.
How do you suppose the
Four Imperial Knights
would perform in such a battle?
I dunno. Could get a bit dicey.
But with all four
of us together,
I bet we could make a
good account of ourselves.
If there's a chance
of victory, I'll fight.
But if defeat is
guaranteed, I'll retreat.
The emperor is here.
Do try to show
a bit more respect.
Worry not. You can
be as you are here.
Listen, old man.
Continue your
investigations both
on Momon of Darkness
and Ains Ooal Gown.
In regards to one, at least,
I have some news that
you may find interesting.
Do you?
[ZANAC] Unfortunately,
it will be some time before
the streets and buildings
are fully repaired.
Jaldabaoth did quite
a bit of damage.
[RENNER]
Tell me, brother.
Do we have any idea what
happened to the people
the demons took as prisoners?
We're looking into the matter.
All we're certain of now
is that almost 100,000 people
were somehow taken
without a trace.
How terrible.
Father. Do not be discouraged.
Across the land, the people
are praising your leadership,
and working hard
on the restoration.
All thanks to the plans created
and implemented
by you and Renner.
Jaldabaoth was overheard saying
that he was after
a magical item.
The magician's guild
is looking into this.
Finding what he wants
may help us find him.
[MAID 06A]
Please wait!
Huh?
Father, it's good to see you!
Prince Barbro.
Though you're his son,
you cannot enter
the king's presence unannounced.
Be silent, you upstart commoner.
Cheeky peasant.
I ought to have you
thrown in the dungeon.
You'll do no such thing.
Sir Gazef is my Chief Warrior
and trusted bodyguard.
He spoke only as his
duty requires of him.
Only nobles may become
knights of this kingdom.
It's dangerous to
keep a lowborn man
like him at your side.
What business do you have here?
We've come to ask why you've
left E-Rantel undefended!
That's because the Empire
is not attacking us, brother.
All we know is that
the Empire doesn't plan
to attack us around harvest
as they have in the past.
They must be shifting
the time of their attack
so as to catch us off guard.
Right!
Send me to crush the Empire
and the demon
Jaldabaoth after that.
Put your faith in me.
My younger brother can
scarcely swing a sword.
[RAMPOSA sighs]
--[BRAIN, GAZEF grunting]
--[clanging]
[yells]
[grunts]
You've come a long way, Brain.
That sounds a little
patronizing from down here.
[CLIMB]
Brain. Are you hurt?
C'mon, I'm not that fragile.
Well fought. That was amazing.
It was an honor just
to see that match!
It's closer every time.
[CLIMB]
I have duties to attend to.
So I'll excuse myself.
Until next time.
What about you, Brain?
I've got the day off actually.
This job has its perks.
I'm glad Princess Renner
hired you, but I'm surprised
you agreed.
Yeah, I surprised myself
with that one, too.
Whelp. I'm headed out as well.
Take care.
[GAZEF] I feel like he's
bound to disappear again.
It'd be great if he'd
replace me when I retire.
But something tells me
that won't happen.
[HEKKERAN]
It's the truth, Rober!
He was in full-plate armor,
black as night,
and he had two greatswords.
This guy was the real deal,
I'm tellin' ya.
Think he was a mercenary?
Either that, or he's
a foreign adventurer.
I know all the famous ones
that work in the Empire,
but I've never heard
of someone like him.
So he's not a worker?
[HEKKERAN sighs]
No way.
He had a completely
different air to him.
Oh, yeah!
Did I mention he had a
beautiful dame by his side?
She had gorgeous black hair,
and don't even get me
started on her eyes.
So that's what you
wanted to talk about.
Surely you don't think
she's as good looking
as Ms. Imina.
Well, to be honest,
she was even more beautiful.
And to think,
it was only yesterday
that you were swearing you
had eyes for no one else.
Please don't tell
her I said that.
I'll buy you a drink, okay?
Hey, old man, can you
get this guy a--
Water.
Come on. He went out
shopping, didn't he?
Ugh.
Oh, hello, Imina.
What's up?
[HEKKERAN] Nothin', you're
just a little early is all.
Huh?
--[ARCHE grunts]
--Oh, excuse me, Arche.
It's fine.
[HEKKERAN]
Well, members of Foresight,
it's time to talk business.
This job'll take us to
the Re-Estize Kingdom.
They're looking for people
to explore an ancient tomb.
In short,
the job is to sneak
into another country
and rob an ancient gravesite.
That's right.
It's a dirty job, which makes
it suited for us Workers.
Tell me, Arche.
You manage to get any
details on our client?
I did. The client's well known.
Name's Count Femel.
He's a noble who's said
to be losing favor
with the Bloody Emperor.
However, he's yet
to have any privileges
stripped from him,
so he's still wealthy.
So we know he can pay, then.
He's offering 200 gold
up front and 150 after.
[ROBERDYCK, IMINA gasp]
It's one of those
contracts that pays high
up front and on completion.
These don't come up too often.
And on top of that,
we get bonus pay
depending on what we find.
Word is, we're not the
only team he's hiring.
Here's the really exciting part.
This ruin's never been
explored before.
Well, that's
certainly a surprise.
I didn't think such a
place could still exist.
And can your source be trusted?
[ARCHE] It's true that there's
no evidence of a ruin there
on any maps of the area.
Nor could I find any
historical references
to a tomb or city.
There's a village
fairly close to it.
We can ask there.
I wish.
I'm sure the client wants us
to be as discreet as possible.
Of course. If we do
something careless,
that's it. We'll surely invoke
the wrath of the kingdom.
So it's a dirty kinda job,
like I said before.
All right.
So do we take the money
or turn it down?
Roberdyck?
I'm willing to try it.
Well, vice leader?
Sure, let's do it.
We haven't had a proper job
like this in a while.
At least it's not hunting undead
in the Katze Plains. Arche?
If you're doing
all this to help me,
I'd like you to stop.
We can turn this job down.
I'll be okay.
It's not for you.
It's for all of us.
We get 350 gold even if
nothing's down there.
S'good. Right, Rober?
My thoughts exactly.
Though an untouched tomb's
bound to have treasure.
Don't you think, Hekkeran?
Whaddaya say, Arche?
Thank you all.
You know, it is too bad.
But I doubt even this
reward'll be enough
to pay off your parents' debt.
[ARCHE]
That's all right.
As long as I can pay some of it,
the creditors will wait.
Lemme know if you want me
to talk with your father.
I would be happy to offer
the word of God to him.
Although, he'll need to
learn God's anger first.
We might have to poke
a few holes in his ears
before he can hear us.
Uh--
This isn't right.
It's their debt.
They should pay it themselves.
I'll just take my sisters.
[bell rings]
If Ms. Arche takes
in her sisters,
she won't be able to do
dangerous work anymore.
She'll most likely
have to retire.
Then what'll she do for cash?
She oughtta be just fine.
I mean she's a
third tier magic caster.
There's plenty'a
work in the city
for somebody at her level.
That's a good point.
We're the ones who're
outta luck here.
[ROBERDYCK] True. Third tier
magic casters are rare enough.
I doubt we'll ever find another
with that special
talent of hers.
It's a valuable skill.
Just by observing
another magic caster,
she's able to tell exactly what
tier of spell they can cast.
I hear Fluder Paradyne
has that particular
gift as well.
[sighs]
I guess we could always recruit
a second tier magic caster
and train 'em up.
That sounds like it should
be our last resort.
Yeah, but workin' as a team
of three would be risky.
Unless you two wanna
rejoin the guild.
I fight to save life.
And that goal is ill-aligned
with the rules of the temple.
If it comes to that point,
I expect I would retire myself.
[HEKKERAN]
Retire to do what?
[ROBERDYCK]
Oh, I'd be fine with any job
that involved helping people.
I could work the fields
in new villages,
and spread the word
of God to them.
Huh, I wonder what I should do.
Should you really be making
that decision on your own?
Ah-- Hey, watch yourself.
[ROBERDYCK chuckles]
Aw, there's no need
to be jealous
of what we've got goin' on.
I'm sure you'll find
love eventually, too.
How the hell did you get
through all those bottles?
It's okay! Just tell
us how you feel.
Or I'll bite'cha.
[door opens]
[ARCHE'S FATHER]
Arche. Welcome home.
[ARCHE'S MOTHER]
Welcome home, dear.
[ARCHE]
What's that?
This fine lamp was created
by the artist Jean Sharlu.
[ARCHE]
We didn't own that before.
So how did it get here?
That's simple.
I purchased it from his
gallery this very morning.
[gasps]
[ARCHE'S FATHER] And would you
believe it was only 15 gold!
Ha!
Why did you buy it?
[ARCHE'S FATHER]
We're nobles.
We're supposed to spend
money on such thi--
We aren't nobles anymore!
No!
Once that wretched Emperor dies,
our prestigious family shall
retake our rightful place!
We are not yet vanquished!
As long as we
continue to demonstrate
our power and nobility,
those fools who doubt us
will know that our proud
house has not given up!
As I've told you many times,
we can't waste any money.
We should only be buying things
that are necessary for survival.
[ARCHE'S FATHER]
This is necessary!
I won't waste more
money on this house!
My sisters and I are leaving!
Where's your sense of gratitude
for the years of care that your
mother and I provided you?
[ARCHE]
I've paid my debt.
[ARCHE'S FATHER growls]
[sighs]
[UREIRIKA giggles]
You're back!
Where's Kuude?
[UREIRIKA]
Our room.
I see.
I want to sit down with
you two and have a talk.
Shall we go?
[UREIRIKA]
Sure!
I've never felt hands
as hard as yours, sis.
But, I love them.
Why, thank you.
[HEKKERAN]
Well...
This may be Foresight's
final adventure.
[HEKKERAN]
I'll be damned.
Never seen this
many famous Workers
in the same place at once.
This client really does
have deep pockets.
Stop running your mouth.
The leaders are all
gathering, so get in there.
Fine, I'm on it.
I was expecting your group
to make an appearance here.
'Course we did.
Nice to meet you guys in person.
[ERYA] I've heard
many interesting things
about Foresight.
[HEKKERAN]
Same, Heavenly Warrior.
I look forward to seeing
the one swordsman
they say can equal
Gazef Stronoff in action.
Your words do me honor.
That said, I doubt
he's my true equal.
Before too long, it'll be him
who's compared
to me, Erya Uzruth.
Those are some bold words.
Are those all the members
of Foresight behind you?
Oh, my. An elf? No, a half elf.
You take it easy.
No hands on my companion.
I wouldn't dream
of such a thing.
A comrade in arms should
be treated with respect.
Now that we've
completed our greetings,
I'll excuse myself.
That one's a bit on
the dangerous side,
if you ask me.
I was thinkin' the same thing.
Do you think he's actually
as skilled as they say?
I saw the man in action
at the colosseum recently.
It's true he's as strong
as the Kingdom's
Chief Warrior was
a few years ago.
[SLAVE 06A screams]
Heartless bastard.
It looks like swordsmanship
is the only thing
him and Stronoff have in common.
Your attention.
First, please allow me to thank
each and every one of you
for accepting my
count's request.
Please, come this way.
[GUILD ADVENTURER 06A]
Hey, grab this, will ya?
[HEKKERAN]
Sleipnir?
Even grand nobles rarely
have those steeds.
We've prepared carriages
for your mission.
And we've hired guild
adventurers to protect
the campgrounds
until you return.
I'm willing to entrust
gold-plated adventurers
with the task of carrying
my things for me.
But when it comes to
the protection of them,
I'm a little less confident
in their abilities.
Then I'm pleased to inform you
that we've hired some extra
protection. Mister Momon.
Let me introduce you to
the Adamantite Adventurer
Momon of Darkness.
As well as his
teammate, Miss Nabe.
[WORKER 06A]
Whoa, I've heard of him.
[WORKER 06B]
He's the highest rank there is.
I take it you find this
protection sufficient.
[AINS]
I would like to ask something.
Why have you chosen
to go to these ruins?
[ALL]
Huh?
[AINS] For most adventurers,
there's a moral imperative
to accept each job
request they receive.
I'd like to know why
you Workers decided
to take this request.
What drives you?
The amount of money.
[AINS] So it comes down
to that: you've been offered
enough money to put
your lives on the line?
That's correct.
We've been offered
a sum of money
we would risk death to gain.
[AINS] Very well. It's your
right to make that choice.
[AINS] I see now. I asked
a truly worthless question.
Forgive me.
[AINS] The mercenaries invading
the Great Tomb of Nazarick
cannot possibly comprehend
the danger they face.
They shall find the
riches they seek,
but they will have
little use for them...
...in death.
Their eyes blinded
by a few baubles,
they journey deeper into
the bowels of Nazarick.
They are no better than
maggots looking to feed.
Chapter 7: "Butterfly Entangled
in a Spider's Web."
No trespasser shall
escape my grasp.