[music playing]
SHIZUKA: My dear, Zero.
I hope you grow up quickly
by feeding off your hatred.
You do want to
kill me, don't you?
I hope to always
keep you in my sight.
Your eyes-- so filled with
hate-- are mine and mine alone.
You see, Zero, you and
I are now bound together
by an unbreakable bond.
[gasping]
KANAME: That woman.
Seems she's still alive.
[theme music]
[girls giggling and talking]
GIRL: Yeah?
Well, Aido is my choice.
GIRL: If I could dance with
Aido, I'd be in Heaven.
GIRL: Don't you think
Takuma would be nice, too?
He seems like he
would lead so gently.
YUKI: Zero hunts vampires.
YUKI: He said that he could
never forgive himself.
So how did Zero feel when
he pulled the trigger?
-Hey.
Snap out of it, will ya?
-Sorry.
[girls screaming and talking]
-Everyone get back!
Is it me, or are they more
excitable than usual today?
-It's that stupid event
that's got them like this.
When that gate opens,
make sure you're ready.
YUKI: Huh?
[girls screaming]
YUKI: Don't push!
Please!
Don't push!
-Just a little closer.
ZERO: One more step,
and I'll make you cry.
Got it?
[screaming]
-Don't worry about him.
Just go for it!
-Yeah, Zero isn't
as scary nowadays.
-She's right, it's true.
-Hey!
You shouldn't give
me so much trouble.
[girls talking loudly]
HANABUSA: You need
help holding them back?
-Huh?
-Just kidding.
[door slamming]
-Sorry, everyone.
GIRL: It's just Yuki!
-(LAUGHING) They're
really jealous of you.
It's so-- cute.
-Um, would you let
go of me, please?
I need to get back.
-That's how you
show your gratitude?
After I came to rescue just now?
KANAME: You're bothering
the disciplinary committee,
Hanabusa.
-Yuki, don't take
these duties of yours
so seriously that you only
end up getting yourself hurt.
-OK, sure.
I'll be more careful.
ZERO: Don't let
yourself be carried out.
Come on.
-Hey!
Zero!
[foot steps]
[door closing]
-It's awfully noisy today.
-Well, you know the
ball is coming up soon.
[groaning]
-I, myself, cannot
wait for the ball.
-Sounds exhausting.
[horses running]
KAIEN: Yuki, are
you upset that I
let Zero go on that
assignment the other day?
Zero was born a hunter, Yuki,
which means sooner or later,
a job was bound to come to him.
-You're saying
that it's his duty?
-In order for Zero to
live as a human, yes.
Regardless, I have a request.
We have a transfer student.
I'd like you to show her around.
-A transfer student?
-Yes.
She was scheduled to
start much earlier,
but she has a weak
constitution, so she's
been recuperating at
her villa somewhere
deep in the mountains.
[knocking]
KAIEN: Oh, well, I
guess she's here now.
Come in.
-Um, good evening.
YUKI: Huh?
She's a night class student?
-Please meet Maria Kurenai.
Good evening, Maria.
I would like you to
meet my daughter, Yuki.
YUKI: Nice to meet you.
-She looks so tasty
and so healthy.
-You listen here!
That's taboo at this Academy!
-Aw.
I'm sorry.
Nice to meet you, Yuki.
-Uh.
-So the library is this way.
And just up there is
the room the night
class will be using today.
Do you want to take a look?
What's wrong?
-You see, Yuki, transferring to
this Academy scares me a bit.
I know that's hard
to believe, but I'm
afraid the other
vampires aren't going
to accept someone
as frail as I am.
See!
I knew you wouldn't believe me!
-No.
I was just surprised.
Listen, I really
don't think there's
anything to worry about.
Both the Dorm President and
Vice President are really nice.
And also-- you've got me, and
the Headmaster on your side
as well.
We'll be glad to help.
So you see, Maria,
you're gonna be fine!
-Thank you, Yuki.
-Yuki.
I really do love being
with girls like you.
HANABUSA: A late arrival?
A transfer student.
It's quite mysterious.
Something's
definitely wrong here.
-Is this about that book
you were reading yesterday?
-No, what he's saying is true.
We've got a new student.
-Hey!
Those are my Choco Biscuits!
I was going to share
them with Lord Kaname!
(SIGHING) Jeez, today really
isn't going well at all.
[giggling]
MARIA: This class
looks like fun.
Say, shouldn't have this
class started already?
-Who the hell are you?
-The hell?
-Excuse me, boy.
You think you-- can
talk that way to me?
[gasping]
-I believe it's the
new student's duty
to introduce one's
self to the class.
Right, Marie Kurenai?
-Oh.
-If I've upset you,
please forgive me.
I'm sorry, Lord Kaname.
-I can't believe I finally
get to meet a Purebred.
This makes me so happy!
[gasping]
-A pleasure to meet you.
-Oh.
I'm sorry.
I think I've made everyone
a little uncomfortable.
(GIGGLING) Perhaps it's best
if I come back another time.
[door slamming]
-What's with her?
-Just relax, will ya?
Frowning like that will
only give you wrinkles.
-You know what, mind
your own business!
[foot steps]
-Hey-- Hanabusa.
[door slamming]
-Zero.
-Stop standing around!
You're still on duty!
-Hey, what is your--
YUKI: By the way, the Headmaster
gave me some good news.
Remember that girl
you saved yesterday?
Well, they were able to erase
the whole event from memory,
and she's doing just fine now.
Isn't that a huge relief?
-Not really.
I didn't agree to go out
and hunt down that Level
E just so that I could
save somebody else.
What I wanted had absolutely
nothing to do with it.
It was just work.
-A duty of a hunter.
-Well, if that's the
way you feel, Zero,
than I guess that's how it is.
But it seems to me you're only
interested in doing whatever it
is you want to do. .
I mean, that's how you
act toward your studies.
And that's why you went to do
that job by yourself, isn't it?
Hunting a vampire is
a pretty big deal.
So when you suddenly
leave campus
to do something like that
without telling anyone,
who do you think
worries the most?
For a second there, I
thought you'd run away.
It's just that--
I'm afraid someday
you'll decide to take your
revenge on that vampire who
killed your family and not
tell me anything when you do.
-If I wanted to do that,
I have no obligation
to tell you about it.
YUKI: Yes, you do.
If you lose control, it's my
job to kill you, isn't it?
You gave me a gun for
that very purpose.
It's in my desk drawer right
now, ready and waiting,
to remind me of the
promise I made to you.
-That's true.
I guess you'll have trouble
keeping your promise if I
go and disappear
without telling you.
But this means you're assuming
I'll be beaten at my own game,
doesn't it?
That's kind of rude.
-Don't you accuse
me of being rude!
But I do believe in you, K?
-That hurt.
(COUGHING) Huh?
-Oh, hey Maria.
Something wrong?
-I think I may have taken
my little prank too far.
Everyone hates me now.
-Zero?
What are you--
[chain rattling]
YUKI: No!
-You pulled that gun
on her for no reason.
Why would you do that?
-No!
ZERO: Who-- are you?
-How do you do?
I'm Maria Kurenai.
-I' sorry if he
scared you, Maria.
He's a guardian here at
the Academy like I am.
His name is Zero.
He's my partner.
But he generally doesn't
take things this far.
Well, not usually.
-Yes, but I shouldn't be
wandering the grounds so late
at night.
I apologize.
And-- thank you so much
for protecting me, Yuki.
You're nice.
I like girls like you.
You see, good girls
like you happens
to taste especially
delicious, Yuki.
(LAUGHING) Now, don't fight!
[girls talking loudly]
YUKI: It's time for
the day class students
to return to their dorms!
-Oh no.
This is worse than
Saint Chocolatal's Day.
-What's this?
"Will you please ask me
to be your dance partner?
Thank you."
-Well, I'll pass.
You can have it, Rima.
-Huh?
-I heard from that others
that you're a model, Senri.
(GIGGLING) You're quite popular.
-Hey.
-Oh, sorry.
[giggling]
[door opening and closing]
TEACHER: Why aren't
you all in your seats?
Class has already begun.
This isn't a day care, you know.
-Now, let's begin.
[music playing]
[knocking]
TAKUMA: Kaname?
-Come in.
-Sorry.
But Maria here says that she
can't sleep well in our dorms
because she's too nervous.
MARIA: If I could, I'd like
to leave the dorm for a while.
To keep things peaceful
in the night class.
I heard there was
a building used
as a temporary dorm for the
night class in the beginning.
If possible, I'd
like to stay there.
-Very well.
I will speak to the
Headmaster about it.
-Huh?
You're allowing it?
-I'm so happy!
Thank you so much!
-It seems Maria Kurenai
transferred here officially
and took the same vows we did.
Other than that, it says she was
born with a weak constitution,
and she's never
attended a soiree.
That's about it.
There's nothing particularly
strange about her.
Well, other than the
fact that she's fearless.
-Hey, Akatsuki-- did you happen
to meet that woman before?
-What woman?
-The Pureblood
vampire whose lineage
is on par with the Kuran family.
She disappeared
after going crazy.
Her name is Shizuka Hio.
-She went missing after the
incident involving the Kiryus.
Some say she died after that.
But, no, I've never met her.
Is there a reason you're asking?
-No.
It's nothing.
All right, let's stop.
Talking about that
woman is unlucky.
[wind blowing]
GIRL: You seem tired, Yuki.
YUKI: Well, it's getting
harder to control the fan
girls outside.
Right, Zero?
-Huh?
Yeah.
-That's because it's
almost time for the ball.
YUKI: Yes, but I'm more worried
about the upcoming school
exams than the ball.
BOY: And you're the
problem, Yuki Cross!
The ball is a Cross
Academy tradition.
And the class which scores
the lowest on the exams
is the class who has to
work the ball that year!
YUKI: Huh?
-I am very worried, Yuki.
You alone are the one
responsible for bringing down
our class average
every single year.
-You realize that's a rather
mean way to put it, class rep.
-The ball is a
precious official event
in which both the day class
and the night class attend.
And if I don't get a chance
to dance with Ruka this year--
(GROANING) I'll hold a
grudge against you for life!
-Oh no!
It looks like I'll have to study
as if my life depends on it.
If not, then I'm going
to fail for sure!
-Yuki, you can always
ask your father
to get a good tutor for you.
Hey, what's wrong?
TAKUMA: You can't go that way!
The day class is
still in session!
Oh no.
This could get dangerous.
Maria!
-Don't worry!
I just want to look
at the cafe terrace.
(GIGGLING) This is fun.
-Hey!
That's far enough!
-What are night class
students doing out here?
-Stay away from that
transfer student.
The Vice Dorm President can
handle her on his own, K?
-Zero?
OK.
-Yuki.
Good afternoon.
This is the second time
we've met during the day.
GIRL: Aido is here!
-Aido!
What are you doing?
[girls screaming]
GIRL: No!
Now he's hugging her!
-The jealous girls
will go mad with envy,
and bully you from
now on, Yuki Cross.
-Huh?
ZERO: Hanabusa.
If you have a moment, I'd
like to have a word with you.
-Oh, all right.
I actually wanted
to talk to you, too.
-Huh?
Hey, Zero?
-Yuki, be careful
around Maria Kurenai.
-And don't you two go
getting into a fight either!
-I'm worried.
-Oh, he'll be OK.
I think.
-No, I'm worried about you.
[girls yelling]
-GIRL: All right,
disciplinary committee,
you need to explain yourself.
[girls running and yelling]
-It looks like you're having
a hard time being chased, too.
-Ichijo.
Where's Maria?
Did you ever catch her?
-Well, it seems that while the
day class girls were chasing
me, she managed to slip away.
And I haven't seen her since.
-You have a hard job being
the Vice Dorm President,
having to deal with
things like this.
-(LAUGHING) Well,
I, uh-- you see,
I think if Kaname were to ask
everyone in the night class
to bear the same
responsibilities as me,
then they would
probably do it, too.
A Pureblood vampire
has countless powers.
One of those abilities is
to make other vampires who
aren't pureblood obey them.
But even though Kaname
may seem a little pompous,
he refuses to use his
power in that way.
So that's why when
it's needed, I
offer to take on
tasks of this nature.
-That's so nice of you.
-Hm.
It seems that when
you're with me,
the girls are all too scared
to come any closer than this.
That's rather convenient.
But a bit lonely.
So?
-I want to know something.
Is Maria Kurenai somehow
related to that woman?
-That woman?
-Shizuka Hio.
-Such insolence.
You do realize you just
referred to a Pureblood
without using the
proper honorific.
But I understand.
After all, she is the one
who butchered your family.
All right.
The Kurenai and Hio lines
had a shared ancestry a long,
long time ago.
But that's it.
-One more question .
No one has been able to track
that woman down for four years.
And that's because her
appearance has changed,
hasn't it?
-I don't know
anything about that.
Only Purebloods themselves know
all the powers they possess.
But what's more important
is what you sense about her.
And I want to hear
that from you.
-Why is that?
-So as to keep peace
in the night class?
-Don't joke.
-You are the only
one who would know.
Because you have a
blood bond with her.
TAKUMA: Kaname, what's to
be done with that transfer
student?
-Well, I suppose you can
take care of her, Takuma.
-Huh?
-It'd be a problem if I
were to do anything openly.
This Academy has all the pieces
that she desires in one place.
-Pieces?
Well, I suppose that is
a good way of putting it.
But, is it a coincidence
they are all here?
-No.
I arranged things this way.
MARIA: Looking at me
with those sad eyes.
Zero is so cute.
-You realize jealousy
doesn't suit you at all.
-(LAUGHING) This is so much fun.
[music playing]