[music playing]
SHIZUKA (VOICEOVER):
He's just like me.
This child has no
place of his own.
ICHIRU: Shizuka!
Shizuka!
SHIZUKA (VOICEOVER): No.
He is no longer a child.
Before I had realized it,
the other twin had grown up.
-Purebloods don't die easily.
ICHIRU: Shizuka!
I'll give you my blood.
Just please don't die!
-No.
I won't turn you into a vampire.
Besides, it's too late.
-It can't be!
No!
(CRYING) No!
Shizuka!
SHIZUKA (VOICEOVER):
In just a small way,
Ichiru and I share the
same circumstances.
[theme music]
SHIZUKA (VOICEOVER): Since
we both had no place to go,
I hoped we'd find a place
within each other to belong.
It was a sincere wish.
ICHIRU: So you
really will take me
with you, Miss
Pureblood Vampire?
[wind blowing]
SHIZUKA (VOICEOVER):
Four years have passed.
SHIZUKA: Ichiru.
Did you come here to
look at my body again?
What's the matter, Ichiru?
Are you still upset
I'm in this body?
-I understand that you
had to do it in order
to hide your identity.
It's just--
-Just what?
What is it?
ICHIRU: The way you look
and sound are so unlike you.
It's unsettling.
-Such honesty.
I admit I'm enjoying this.
You don't like it?
ICHIRU: No.
-It's the perfect time.
Here.
Ichiru, why don't
you drink my blood?
-I've already had
plenty of your blood.
And it has made
me much healthier.
-You should still drink it.
After all, you're my
bodyguard, aren't you?
[drinking]
-If I were, a
vampire, I would be
able to savor the
taste of this blood.
Why won't you just
turn me into a vampire?
-Because, if I
did that, then you
would just end up
becoming my servant.
And you would stop
being so insolent.
Where's the fun in that?
-What about Zero?
You turned him into a vampire.
-Zero wouldn't yield and
become my servant so easily.
And it keeps me
from getting bored.
Don't look like that.
Why would you want
to be a vampire?
We're such fleeting beings.
SHIZUKA (VOICEOVER):
Just like that man.
SHIZUKA: So easily shattered.
ICHIRU: Are you talking
about your vampire servant?
The one who was hunted
down by my parents?
SHIZUKA: Why, yes.
You want to know about him?
I thought you wouldn't want
to, so I've avoid the subject.
-You needn't force yourself
if you don't want to tell me.
SHIZUKA: Oh.
Are you jealous of him?
-I'm not!
I just thought remembering
those old memories would
make you suffer!
-Well, if that's the
case, I might as well
tell you the truth.
He and I would never
have ended up together.
I was a rare beast,
so I was locked up
and kept in a luxurious cage.
And he was the human they
threw into the cage as bait.
But this man was unlike
any of my other prey,
and he glared at
me in silent rage.
So I thought rather than devour
him, I'd make him a companion.
And for the first time,
I felt attachment.
I didn't hesitate.
I turned him into a vampire.
I think he never forgave me
for that until the very end.
However, when I
asked him to run away
with me to some faraway
place, he didn't refuse.
But after that, what was
waiting for him was--
SHIZUKA: I sought revenge.
And I couldn't stop myself
from killing your parents.
You must really
hate me, don't you?
-I don't.
-Hm.
Is that right?
If that's true, you
really are sinful.
-What a complicated look.
Did you hate it?
-I know you don't feel
that way about me.
So please don't
tease me like that.
-I like you.
Especially the way you always
wear your heart on your sleeve.
SHIZUKA (VOICEOVER):
I will pretend
not to notice your
feelings for me.
And this way, I will maintain
a subtle distance between us.
For every time a Pureblood
develops an attachment
to someone, destruction
always follows.
[crying]
-What's the matter?
Why are you crying like a child?
Could it be?
Is it possible you
really do love me?
-Don't say such things.
You know how I feel you.
[clock chiming]
-If you're afraid of being all
alone, shall I remain with you?
[breathing heavily]
-What is this?
[gasping]
-Is that-- No!
What are you devouring?
[groaning]
-The Level E is
raging inside you.
You are craving Shizuka's blood.
Aren't you, Zero?
Unfortunately for
you, it is too late.
ICHIRU: I offered myself,
but she didn't want me.
Not even in the very end.
She didn't want my blood.
I was nothing to her.
After all I did, she
only thought of me as a--
-No.
You're wrong.
She wanted you to
stay the way you are.
A human.
Not a vampire. (GROANING)
-I won't turn you
into a vampire.
Why would you want
to be a vampire?
We're fleeting beings.
-Shut up!
What do you know?
You weren't by her
side this entire time.
What right do you
have to say that?
ZERO: I know.
Even I-- someone like
me-- has a person
I don't want to see
turned into a vampire.
(GROANING)
-That's why I understand
better than you know.
-Give it a rest.
You're pitiful.
The Zero you've become
is no longer the same
Zero I once envied and hated.
Just look at you.
You've already become a Level E.
-Ichiru.
-Yuki.
[groaning]
-Don't look at me, please.
[screaming]
ZERO: Yuki.
Don't look at me!
YUKI: Akatsuki!
Please!
Wait!
Akatsuki!
Akat--
-Hey.
Headmaster?
-What are you doing
here, Headmaster?
Where's Zero?
Where did he go?
-Uh, well, I'm
afraid he got hurt.
I asked Yagari to take him to
the association medical clinic.
YUKI: Was he hurt that badly?
-Don't worry.
It's just a precaution.
[music playing]
-The game we were playing
is finally over, Shizuka.
SHIZUKA (VOICEOVER):
You poor thing.
How sad.
-You must be
Princess Shizuka Hio.
-You've become the next
leader of the Kuran family.
I pity you.
A
[chess piece breaking]
KANAME: And I, you.
[tapping sound]
GIRL: You're taking
ample notes today.
Wait, come to
think of it, you've
been awfully studious
since the ball.
-Huh?
-Learn your lesson?
-Uh.
Yeah.
I guess I did.
That, and-- well,
Zero's absent, so I
thought I'd take
extra notes for him.
YUKI: When will
Zero be coming back?
-Oh, I don't think he
will be gone for too long.
It's just Zero's so eager to
be back that he's not getting
enough rest.
So I'm thinking they should
keep him there for a little bit
longer.
How about we go pay
him a visit later?
-All right.
I was wondering.
Did you know about--
-Hm?
-About Maria?
I mean, Shizuka Hio.
-I didn't.
I'm ashamed of myself.
A precious student of
mine was in danger,
and I wasn't able to
do a thing about it.
-That's not true.
-The disintegrated
body of Shizuka Hio
was all that remained.
And the Headmaster told
us he taken care of Zero.
That's it.
That's what I witnessed.
-I see.
[inaudible] had enough
reasons to kill that woman,
but I don't think he would
do something so rash.
However, it can't be
helped if it appears
that he had, in
fact, killed her.
What's wrong, Aido?
-No.
Nothing.
-In any case, I must report
all this to the Senate.
[ticking clock]
-It's a fact that someone has
committed the greatest taboo.
They have dared to
do the unspeakable
by killing a Pureblood.
It's tragic.
People gave her cruel
nickname of Kuruizaki-hime.
I wonder if anyone
truly understood her.
-No one's here.
We're alone.
Not even the eye
patch is coming.
-Hm.
-Want some candy?
-No.
Thank you.
I have heartburn now.
-Hm.
-Something's wrong.
I've got a bad feeling.
-Hm.
[wind blowing]
-Can you smell that?
-Yes.
Even the sweetest
of smells can be
nauseating if it's
far too strong.
Like flowers that
are out of season.
Or blooming all at once.
-It's cold tonight.
-Hm.
-I can tell by the way
you're acting Hanabusa,
that something is bothering you.
-Hey.
-Hm?
-Akatsuki, how much do you
know about Shizuka Hio?
-She was out of control.
She was dangerous to
both vampires and humans.
She attacked the Kiryu
family after going berserk,
then she disappeared
and showed up here.
That's all I know.
-She was regarded as a
nuisance and ostracized,
but still, she was
a rare Pureblood.
-I wonder if anyone
understood her.
-I know that she had
a Pureblood fiance.
And then, for some
unknown reason,
she started keeping a
human male by her side.
To be exact, he was a
vampire who used to be human.
A servant.
And Shizuka loved him.
But-- he was put on the Vampire
Hunter's execution list.
And so the Kiryus
hunted him down.
But I've also heard that
the servant had not yet
fallen to Level E status.
AKATSUKI: Then there's
no way his name
could have been on
the execution list.
HANABUSA: Yes, I know.
But it was.
Shizuka attached the
Kiryu family for revenge.
AKATSUKI: No matter what
the reason, a Pureblood
shouldn't have gone
after the hunters.
Most aristocrats want
peace, not conflict.
Her actions were the same
as the one who'd gone crazy.
HANABUSA: Shizuka
Hio had proven to be
a high risk to the Senate.
They must have been searching
for her relentlessly.
And Shizuka was probably on the
run, fleeing from the Senate.
So why would she risk it?
Why would she come
to Cross Academy?
She knew she wouldn't
be welcome here!
-Another act of madness.
-No.
You're wrong.
There is something
she wanted here.
KANAME: The blood of
a Pureblood vampire.
The power.
I promise to find the very
thing that you hated most,
and I will destroy
it once and for all.
Those who twisted the
fate of the Purebloods.
-And I don't think she's
the only one who wanted it.
Someone else is
after it is as well.
[glass breaking]
-This new power is quite strong.
I will need to learn
how to control it.
[glass shattering]
-But I expect I'll get
used to it quickly.
One game is over.
And the next one's begun.
-Zero.
I wonder how he's
doing right now.
KANAME: Thank you for
patrolling the grounds.
-Kaname!
-Were you taking a break?
KANAME: I heard that
Zero was injured.
How is his recovery going?
-Oh.
Well.
The Headmaster said
there's nothing
to worry about, so I guess--
-That incident was
something the night
class should have taken care of.
I'm very sorry that you
got dragged into it.
But-- No matter what I do,
you won't let me protect you.
-Well, it's just that--
-Now.
For Zero, the task
would be rather
difficult to do, especially
in his condition.
-Zero.
He saved me.
I made a promise.
I swore I'd protect him.
But in the end, I
was the one who--
-I see.
-Kaname.
Are you--
-You mustn't blame
yourself, Yuki.
He owes you.
It is the least
that he could do.
Very least.
-No.
That's not true.
You don't understand.
You're wrong, Kaname.
Zero is suffering.
No, it's not just Zero.
SHIZUKA (VOICEOVER): He wants
to destroy himself with me.
ICHIRU (VOICEOVER): But she--
she didn't want my blood!
She never once
desired it at all!
-Everyone suffered.
Because of their entwined
destinies, and all I could do
was watch.
ZERO (VOICEOVER): It's true.
I did used to wish that I could
die along with that woman.
But that's not what I want now.
-I believe in you.
I really do.
Zero.
[foot steps]
-How's Zero?
-It's no use.
I've even administered medicine.
[yelling]
ZERO: That's enough.
-Zero.
ZERO: Please.
Kill me.
[gasping for breath]
-No, don't.
Listen, Zero.
Yuki is waiting for you.
-Yu-
[crashing]
-What was that sound?
-Could The Senate have learned
about Shizuka's death already?
KANAME: It's such a shame.
You didn't have the
opportunity to drink
the blood that would
have saved you.
I left her remains
there for you, Zero.
-Yuki is very sad right you.
-Yuki.
Yuki!
[screaming]
KANAME: I'm surprised.
You haven't completely
lost yourself yet.
[yelling]
-That thirst's more
painful than death,
and still, you insist on
continuing to fight it.
The purest blood that
courses through my body
will prolong your life, and
force the shadows of madness
to recede.
Understand one thing.
I am not doing this for you.
It is for Yuki.
-Now.
Take my blood.
[gasping]
-Lord Kaname.
[DRINKING]
-Yuki.
[credit music playing]