♪
( Kakyoin gasps )
( Polnareff gasps )
( Hol horse chuckles )
For such a tough guy,
he sure was easy to finish off.
( Both gasp )
Hol horse: But I guess
if you think about it,
the end is usually a pretty
sudden curtain call, you know.
Most folks
don’t get to say goodbye,
especially when a bullet
to the brain’s involved.
It may seem like i’m talking as
though I know everything, but...
( Polnareff growls )
Kakyoin: Polnareff!
Don’t let him get to you!
You’re much stronger than that!
You still don’t get it, do you?
Mr. Avdol told you,
he begged you
not to fight alone...
( Polnareff gasps )
Kakyoin: But you
completely ignored him.
Even if it meant
dying with your enemy,
you were hellbent
on getting revenge.
He followed you,
because that worried him,
and this is what happened
as a result!
Polnareff: Then tell me,
what am I supposed to do?
Kakyoin: We need
to fall back for now.
( Polnareff gasps )
Avdol was stabbed in the back
and didn’t have a chance.
My sister couldn’t
defend herself and was killed.
You want me to hold these
regrets inside and run away?
Kakyoin: How can we fight them
when we don’t even know
what their stands can do?
Don’t fight a battle
that’ll only end in your death!
That’s what Mr. Avdol
was trying to tell you.
Hol horse: Hey, come on.
Do it, li’l pol pol.
Polnareff: Why, you...
Kakyoin: Polnareff, calm down,
and slowly retreat
toward me, got it?
That truck’s
our way out of here.
Polnareff:
You want me to hold it in?
How?
( Gasping )
A-all right.
( Centerfold laughs )
- ( Polnareff gasps )
- Centerfold: Hey, polnareff.
♪
( Hanged man laughing )
( Polnareff gasping )
Hanged man: It’s your fault
avdol died, you know?
I think that means you owe him.
It only seems fair.
Your friend bit the dust
because of you.
( Laughs )
Polnareff: Damn you,
you bastard.
Where’s your real body?!
Kakyoin: Polnareff, calm down!
Hanged man: But there’s
no need to be sad.
Actually, you should be happy.
You’re about to see
your dear friend again.
You’ll soon be dead,
and then you can enjoy
the afterlife
with those two fools.
You’re welcome. ( Chuckles )
I have to say
your sister was so very sweet.
Once you’re reunited
with your sister,
be sure to ask her
exactly how I killed her.
We had such a ball.
( Polnareff yells )
Kakyoin: Polnareff,
don’t fall for his tricks!
He wants you to attack!
Polnareff: Bastard!
♪
( Hanged man chuckles )
Oh, didn’t you know?
Your chariot
cannot cut my hanged man.
( Polnareff gasps )
Hanged man: I’m in the mirror,
where your stand can’t go.
That’s why!
( Laughs )
So close and yet so far away.
Hol horse, fire away.
Let’s put an end to this idiot.
Hol horse: Aye, aye, sir.
( Chuckles )
( Polnareff gasps )
Hanged man: Die!
Kakyoin: Emerald splash!
- Hanged man: Huh?
- Hol horse: What?!
♪
Hol horse: What the--
wait. He shot polnareff!
Hanged man: Huh?
Hol horse: Kakyoin, was it?
Not bad, partner.
( Groans )
That’s out of my stand’s range.
Even if I got him from here,
the bullet wouldn’t hit him
with very much force.
Hmm?
( Spurs jingle )
He went after them, eh?
Well, i’ll be.
He must really have it in
for polnareff.
Polnareff:
I’m so sorry, kakyoin.
I-it’s just that...
I thought so long
as I could avenge my sister,
I wouldn’t care
if I lived or died.
But I understand now.
I know avdol
was fighting for me.
His sacrifice
won’t be for naught.
I’ll fight to keep on living.
( Kakyoin gasps )
You sure that you
really mean that, polnareff?
Polnareff: Mm, oui.
Kakyoin: That’s all
i’m giving you
as proof that we’ve made up,
polnareff.
Polnareff: Right.
M-merci, kakyoin. ( Groans )
Kakyoin: When those bastards
come after us again,
I swear
we’ll defeat them together.
( Overlapping chatter )
Joseph: Avdol, my old friend.
♪
( Jotaro gasps )
Polnareff: You know,
I was so sure
that I stabbed him
with my sword,
but my strike never hit him.
It was like he wasn’t there.
Even breaking the mirror
into pieces didn’t stop him.
The hanged man just attacked
from the shards.
How in the hell am I supposed
to fight against that?
He attacks your reflection,
but his knife sinks
into your real flesh,
and my stand
can’t go inside mirrors.
How are we
supposed to attack him
if he’s in some kind
of mirror world? Damn it!
Kakyoin: Polnareff,
you keep talking about
"inside the mirror"
and "the mirror world,"
but there’s no such thing
as a world in a mirror.
Remember, this is reality,
not fantasy.
( Polnareff gasps )
What are you talking about?
You saw it, too, didn’t you?
You can only see him
in a mirror,
and when you turn around,
he’s gone.
Kakyoin: Yes, but anything
that you see in a mirror
is just a reflection
created by light.
Polnareff: I’m not an idiot!
You don’t have to tell me that!
Listen, I mean this case.
I’m talking about
what’s going on now.
If stands can exist
in this world,
there could be
a mirror world, too.
Kakyoin: There isn’t.
Polnareff: Come on, man!
Kakyoin: I think that fact
is what’s going to help us
solve the mystery of hanged man.
Look, stands are able
to destroy other stands,
so there still
has to be something
we don’t know about his--hmm?
( Gasps )
Polnareff! The chrome
of the steering wheel!
Polnareff: What?!
Kakyoin: The bastard’s
caught up to us!
Polnareff: Look out!
( Both grunting )
Polnareff: Hey, are you okay?
Talk to me.
Kakyoin: I--i slammed my chest,
but i’ll be fine.
Polnareff: What?
( Yells ) Chariot!
Kakyoin, avoid the reflection!
( Both panting )
Polnareff: Damn. I got it.
- I just saw him do it.
- Kakyoin: Huh?
Polnareff: He’s going
from mirror to mirror.
This guy moves
by jumping around,
one reflection to another.
He traveled all this way
by reflecting over and over.
It’s the only explanation
for how he caught up to us.
Kakyoin: Reflecting?
That means he’s actually light.
Are you saying that the true
nature of his stand is light?
Polnareff: I am. I just saw him
in the car’s bumper.
He’s going to reflect
off that surface
and onto something else.
Stay clear of reflective stuff.
Take anything shiny
off your body
and your uniform buttons!
Boy: Hey, mister,
are you guys okay?
Want me to bring you
some medicine?
Polnareff: We’re fine.
Look, it’s dangerous!
Get out of here!
Boy: Whoa, you guys
totally messed up your car.
- Hey, you’re bleeding, mister.
- ( Polnareff gasps )
Boy: Are you sure you’re okay?
Polnareff: That asshole!
Kakyoin: He’s reflected
in the kid’s eye!
( Hanged man laughs )
Polnareff: Listen, kid.
- Don’t look at us.
- Boy: Huh?
Polnareff: I told you,
don’t look at us!
Don’t follow me with your eyes!
Boy: Huh? But you’re hurt.
Polnareff: I’m fine, see?
Perfectly fine, got it?
So go look over there!
Boy: But--but you’re bleeding.
Polnareff: You brat,
I said look over there!
Boy: Huh?
( Hanged man laughs )
Polnareff: Damn you, centerfold!
Hanged man:
What are you going to do?
You wouldn’t poke out
this cute little kid’s eye
with that sword of yours,
would you, polnareff?
- ( Polnareff gasps )
- Kakyoin: Polnareff!
Hanged man: And now
I finally got you.
You can’t run anymore,
not unless
you gouge the kid’s eyes out.
( Laughs )
Kakyoin: You disgusting,
cruel son of a bitch.
You’re dead!
( Polnareff gasping )
( Hanged man laughs )
- Hmm?
- ( Polnareff laughing )
Don’t worry, kakyoin.
Mon frere, that’s not what you
say at a time like this.
Listen, in times like these,
you’ve got to say
something fitting.
Before you get your revenge,
say something like this here.
My name is
Jean Pierre polnareff.
For the honor
of my dearest sister’s soul
and so my good friend avdol can
rest peacefully in heaven above,
i’m going to hurl you
into the depths of despair!
Prepare yourself, centerfold!
Sorry about this, kid.
I’ll buy you
whatever candy you want, okay?
( Boy yells )
You got sand in my eye!
( Polnareff chuckles )
Kakyoin: What the--
polnareff, he’s in your eye!
Polnareff: I don’t
really understand how,
but he essentially moves
at the speed of light.
No one can normally see
speed like that.
But then, I knew that
if the kid closed his eyes,
the next move
would be to my eye.
There was no other place
for him to go,
and that’s how we’ll beat him.
Kakyoin: Oh, I see.
Narrator: Hanged man
can only exist
within the world of reflection.
When one world
is about to be destroyed,
he must migrate
to another reflective object.
Polnareff: So, as long
as I can read his trajectory,
I can slice
through him like butter.
( Centerfold screams )
Polnareff: His real body
is over there.
♪
You bastard. Finally.
Finally!
( Man panting )
Polnareff: At last we meet...
Centerfold!
( Man growls )
Polnareff: My name is
Jean Pierre polnareff,
and i’ve seen through your
stand’s clever little trick.
It’s a stand of light that moves
at extraordinary speed.
I know there’s no way
that I can catch it,
but if I can predict where
your stand’s going to jump next
and I slash its trajectory
in that moment,
I can cut you!
If kakyoin and avdol
hadn’t shown up,
I probably wouldn’t
have figured that out,
- and you would have killed me.
- Kakyoin: Huh?
No, polnareff!
This isn’t the man
with a pair of right hands!
That’s not centerfold!
( Polnareff gasps )
♪
What the hell?!
Kakyoin: Polnareff!
( Polnareff gags )
( Centerfold laughs )
Over here!
I’m centerfold,
insignificant fools!
Polnareff: At last.
Centerfold: That man
is some beggar
who was in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
I just carved
a small wound in him,
the same wound you were
so gracious to give me.
( Man gasps )
Centerfold:
You totally fell for it.
Getting close to him
without knowing what I look like
was a grave mistake, one you’ll
pay for with your lives!
( Laughs )
Kakyoin: You bastard.
Take this! Emerald--
centerfold: Whoa! Wait now.
Take a good look around you.
( Laughs )
Hey, gather round!
( Overlapping chatter )
See these two gentleman?
They say they’ve got
a boatload of cash to share!
( Overlapping chatter )
Kakyoin: What?!
Man #2: They’ll give us
money for nothing, huh?
Man #3: Such generosity!
Man #4: You have
such big hearts! Thank you!
Man #5: Bless you, kind sirs.
( Overlapping chatter )
Centerfold: Have you figured out
what’s going on yet?
( Laughs )
Hanged man: You say
you’ve figured out my stand?
You fool!
You think I don’t know
my own weakness?
( Polnareff gags )
Hanged man: I have no weakness!
You can never know
where i’ll jump to next.
Polnareff: Don’t look.
Don’t stare at us.
Please, just look away!
( Hanged man laughs )
You can’t run anymore!
What are you going to do,
blow everyone up?
( Polnareff screams )
Centerfold: You sacrificed
your entire youth
just to hunt me down,
and just when you’re close,
you’re going to fail
to avenge your sister?
How pathetic and sad.
Meanwhile, I, centerfold,
will continue a life
surrounded by young beauties
like your sister.
I can see it now.
Oh, the pleasures.
( Chuckles )
Come to think of it,
that sweet sister of yours
was really good at sobbing.
- ( Laughs )
- ( Polnareff growling )
( Men murmuring )
Centerfold: Farewell.
Polnareff: Wh-why, you...
Kakyoin: Polnareff,
you could do better than that.
Polnareff: Eh?
Kakyoin: "Why, you,"
isn’t what you say.
When taking revenge,
you have to be more refined.
This is what you say.
My name is noriaki kakyoin.
In order to avenge
my dear friend avdol
and so that the soul
of my friend polnareff’s sister
may rest in peace
for all eternity...
I will have you pay
with your life.
Men: Whoa!
Kakyoin: I’ll give
this gold coin
to whoever picks it up.
Behold, a coin so perfect
it shines like a mirror.
Polnareff: Yeah, now I see.
( Men yelling )
Kakyoin: Looks like
all of their eyes
are focused on one point now.
Polnareff: Yeah.
Kakyoin: We know the trajectory
that hanged man
will have to take.
Polnareff: Merci, kakyoin!
Man #6: Huh?
( Centerfold gasping )
( Man #6 yells )
( Hanged man groans )
Polnareff: Now!
( Centerfold screams )
( Men murmuring )
Kakyoin: Hold it!
( Centerfold gasps )
It won’t open!
Polnareff: Looks like
you’re the one
who’s really good
at sobbing, centerfold!
And you’re about
to plummet into hell,
begging and crying
the whole way down.
But there’s one thing
I can’t rely
on the guardians of hell to do,
and that’s...
To turn your body
into a pincushion!
( Centerfold screams )
Polnareff: I’ve been waiting
years for this moment!
♪
I’ll leave the rest
to the devil.
Rot in hell.
Kakyoin: So this is
the true hanged man, huh?
He was rotten
all the way to the core.
( Polnareff scoffs )
I got my revenge.
Hol horse: Hold it!
♪
Finally caught up with you.
( Chuckles )
Why are you walking so slow?
If you’re gonna run, run like
your lives depend on it.
It’s way more fun.
Isn’t that right,
Mr. Centerfold?
Better say your prayers, boys.
This is where your lives
come to an end.
Come at us with everything
you’ve got. Understand?!
It’s so boring if you
just stand there and die.
Right, Mr. Centerfold?
Hey, Mr. Centerfold,
aren’t you gonna play?
Polnareff: I don’t think
he’s listening anymore, cowboy.
Hol horse: Huh?
Polnareff: He’s quite busy
at the moment
carrying out
his sentence in hell.
Hol horse: Hmm?
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey.
Don’t try to pull that nonsense.
Bluffing won’t work on me.
Nice try, though.
There’s no way
you could have beaten him.
Even I wouldn’t try my luck
against that mother.
You know, polnareff,
your sense of humor stinks.
( Laughs )
Polnareff:
That piece of shit’s corpse
is 2,000 or 3,000 meters that
way if you wanna take a look.
Hol horse: Huh?
Okay, I will!
Polnareff: Huh?
You’re running away?!
Hol horse:
I don’t stand a chance.
I’m at a total disadvantage
by myself.
I’m high-tailing it out of here,
waiting for a better chance.
Or better yet,
waiting ’til I find myself
another partner in crime.
It’s all about being number two.
That’s the motto
I like to live by.
Got a problem with it?
What?!
Kakyoin: Mr. Joestar! Jotaro!
Joseph: We already know
about avdol. What a tragedy.
We didn’t have a lot of time
to do much for him,
but we gave him
a proper funeral.
( Kakyoin and polnareff grunt)
( Hol horse whimpers )
Kakyoin: The one who stabbed
Mr. Avdol in the back
was the man
with two right hands,
but the cause of death
was hol horse’s bullet.
What should we do with him?
Polnareff:
I’ll give him his sentence.
( Hol horse whimpers )
♪
Polnareff: Death!
( Grunts )
( Hol horse gasps )
Woman: Please run,
sir hol horse!
I’ll hold them off for you!
Polnareff: The hell?!
Get off me!
Woman: I don’t know
what exactly is going on here,
but I do know
I will always protect you!
You are my everything, darling!
Please run! Hurry!
Polnareff: Let go of me,
stupid bitch!
Come on! What are you doing?!
Jotaro, kakyoin,
don’t let hol horse get away!
Jotaro: It’s too late.
Polnareff: Huh? Eh?
( Horse neighs )
Hol horse: Very well said,
my little sweetheart!
I’ll gladly accept your feelings
and keep on living!
Remember, i’m only running away
because I love you, baby,
forever and ever!
( Polnareff growls )
Why, you--
come back here!
( Woman groaning )
Aah!
Polnareff: Oh,
don’t you dare, "aah," at me!
( Scoffs )
Joseph: Polnareff, that woman
is just another one
of his victims,
and he no longer had any
intention of fighting with us.
We have no time
to deal with him.
Avdol is gone now,
but we have to forge ahead.
( Polnareff sighs )
Joseph: It’s already
been 15 days.
We don’t have time to waste.
( Polnareff inhales )
Damn it.
Guess it can’t be helped.
♪
All right,
we continue onward to Egypt.
Listen up!
In order to defeat dio,
we have to fight as one.
We can’t go off on our own,
or we’ll play
right into the enemy’s hands.
Got it?
( Jotaro chuckles )
Polnareff: Let’s get a move on!
- ( Kakyoin groans )
- Jotaro: Good grief.
♪
( Sore babbles )
♪ All the old paintings
on the tomb ♪
♪ they do the sand dance,
don’t you know ♪
♪ if they move too quick
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re falling down
like a domino ♪
♪ all the bazaar men
by the nile ♪
♪ they got the money on a bet
♪ gold crocodiles
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they snap their teeth
on your cigarette ♪
♪ foreign types
with the hookah pipes say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian
♪ The blond waitresses
take their trays ♪
♪ they spin around,
and they cross the floor ♪
♪ they’ve got the moves
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ you drop your drink
♪ then they bring you more
♪ all the school kids
so sick of books ♪
♪ they like the punk
and the metal band ♪
♪ when the buzzer rings
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re walking
like an Egyptian ♪
♪ all the kids
in the marketplace say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian