( Baby crying )
Kakyoin: That piercing noise...
( Crying continues )
( Machinery humming )
( Groaning )
( Crying continues )
Huh
♪
What is this place?
An amusement park?
I’ve never been here before.
W-why in the world
am I riding on a Ferris wheel
in my pajamas?
How’d I get here?
The desert.
I remember being in the desert,
riding through Saudi Arabia
on camelback.
But where are the others?
( Crying continues )
Did they abandon me?
- ( Dog whimpers )
- ( Gasps )
( Crying baby continues )
This isn’t making any sense.
There’s not a soul
anywhere in the amusement park,
so why do I hear
the cries of a baby?
And for that matter,
where is it?
♪
( Gasps )
Hmm?
( Gasps ) Th-this card is...
Death 13.
( Spurting )
Oh, no! The card is moving!
( Card laughs )
( Kakyoin screams )
( Screams )
Polnareff: Kakyoin. Kakyoin!
Hey, take it easy.
Stop screaming
and shaking the bed
like that creepy girl
from "the exorcist."
You’re weirding me out.
Kakyoin: Where are we?
Polnareff: Don’t ask
stupid questions.
Now come on,
and get up already, would you?
- ( Kakyoin groans )
- ( Birds chirping )
Polnareff: After breakfast,
we’re gonna take to the skies.
Looks like
another scorcher today.
( Kakyoin sighs )
I had a terrible nightmare.
It was truly horrifying.
Polnareff: You don’t say?
Lay on the details.
I wanna hear all about it.
Kakyoin: Well, the thing is,
I can’t remember.
- I’ve forgotten it all.
- Polnareff: Reviens?
Kakyoin: Regardless,
it was petrifying,
but when you woke me up,
you pulled me out of it.
Polnareff: Wish we
could talk more about it,
but we’ve gotta get a move on.
Let’s go.
Hurry up, and get ready.
( Kakyoin sighs )
( Gasps )
There’s a cut on my hand.
But how’d it get there?
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Polnareff: Jotaro
and Mr. Joestar
are already headed to the plane,
so we’ll meet them there,
and the way I hear it,
we’re traveling
500 kilometers today.
- ( Boy screams ) No!
- Both: Huh?
Boy: This can’t be happening!
Please, not my poor dog!
My dog is dead!
Who would do such a thing?!
Kakyoin: A dog? Dog?
I could have sworn...
That I saw a dead dog
not too long ago.
Polnareff:
Whoever did this is sick,
but there’s nothing
we can do about it.
Let’s go.
( Boy sobbing )
Joseph: Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey! Hold on
a dang second there, mister!
What exactly do you mean,
you can’t sell us the plane now?
I seem to recall you
taking my money last night
and saying it was a done deal.
Man: You’ll get a full refund,
but first we need to see
to a baby with a fever.
- It’s 39 degrees celsius.
- Joseph: Huh?
Man: There’s no doctor
in this town,
so we have no choice
but to take the baby
somewhere else to get help.
( Joseph groans )
Okay, then, what do you say
to us taking
that plane over there?
Man: I’m sorry to say
that one’s broken,
and the others are out...
- Polnareff: What’s up?
- Some kind of argument?
- Jotaro: Yeah.
Kakyoin: A baby?
( Baby crying )
- A baby.
- ( Crying continues )
I remember
hearing a baby’s cries...
But where?
Man: You’ll be able
to use the plane
after it gets back
tomorrow night.
We can renegotiate
and talk prices then.
Joseph: Did you say,
"tomorrow night"?
Our group has
someone’s life on the line,
just like you guys do.
We can’t afford
to spend two days
pissing around this place.
Man: So what you’re telling me
is you’d rather let
that baby die?!
( Joseph groans )
Well, I...
Woman: Excuse me.
- I have a suggestion.
- Men: Huh?
Woman: We can kill
two birds with one stone
by having these gentlemen
take him to the doctor
on their way.
Joseph: Uh, nice idea, but--
woman: The cessna
is built to carry four,
but surely there’s
enough room for a baby.
( Kakyoin gasps )
I could have sworn
I just saw it smile
and that the child
already has teeth.
Man: You sure about this, lady?
Do you really want to leave
your baby with these guys?
Joseph: Eh, just a minute.
We can’t do that either.
It’s too dangerous
for the baby to come with us.
( Both sigh )
( Engine sputtering )
Joseph: I told them
this would be dangerous.
Polnareff: Hey, just try
and take it easy, Mr. Joestar.
There’s no way a stand
could catch a plane
flying hundreds
of kilometers an hour.
I mean, we even made sure
the plane itself wasn’t a stand.
I’d say we’re good to go.
Jotaro: I’m far more worried
about the old man’s flying
than I am an attack
from enemy stands.
( Polnareff humming a tune )
Woman: Oh, thank goodness.
What a relief.
By the way, I wonder
who that baby belonged to.
Man: Huh? Are you saying
you’re not the mother
of that child, miss?
Woman: Oh, no. I found it
by the well this morning.
Though, from the moment
I heard the baby’s crying,
I wasn’t able to help myself.
I felt I had to put him
on that plane.
- Man: Ah?
- Man #2: What could happen?
( Polnareff yawns )
( Kakyoin sighs )
Polnareff: Maybe it’s just me,
but I always get so tired
when I get on a plane.
If it’s all right
with you, Mr. Joestar,
I think i’m gonna take
a 30-minute catnap.
Joseph: Sure.
- Polnareff: Huh? Huh?!
- ( Kakyoin gasps )
Polnareff: W-what is this?
Hey, kakyoin,
where the hell are we?!
Where’d Mr. Joestar go?!
( Yells )
Kakyoin: This is the same dream
I had this morning,
but now it seems
we’re both inside the dream.
( Polnareff gasps )
What? A dream?
Kakyoin: Yes.
( Polnareff sighs )
That’s a relief.
It’s just a stupid dream.
I was worried for a second,
but if it’s only a dream,
who cares if the dog is dead?
Kakyoin: Polnareff,
you can’t be serious.
Polnareff: Dreams are only
as scary as you make ’em.
That’s kind of the way it goes.
Oh. Just try and relax.
Kakyoin: How can I relax when
we’re having the same dream?!
Polnareff: I suppose
you have a point there.
This is kinda weird.
But in a dream,
isn’t anything possible?
Oh, boy! Would you look at that?
This dreaming thing is great.
So good.
See? All you have to do
to make your dreams fun
is think they’re fun.
( Laughs )
- Kakyoin: Listen.
- ( Polnareff groans )
Kakyoin: Do you remember seeing
the dog’s carcass this morning?
Obviously, the dog and I
had the same dream,
and in that dream, that dog
was unmistakably slaughtered.
Once I was awake,
I found this cut on my hand.
Polnareff: Eh? Where from?
Kakyoin: From the enemy’s stand,
death 13.
Polnareff: The enemy stand?
Kakyoin: Mm-hmm.
Polnareff: Oh, I get it now.
You’re paranoid, ’cause you
had a dream about stands.
Hah! Man, you have
got to take it easy.
Kakyoin: You’re wrong!
It wasn’t a dream about stands.
A stand was in my dream.
Polnareff: That’s what I said.
You were having a dream
about stands.
Kakyoin: Ahh!
You still don’t get it, do you?
Child: Lali-ho! Tell me,
does it hurt being that stupid?
Both: Hmm?
( Polnareff gasps )
Child: Oh, for the love of--
let me spell it out for you!
I’m saying that you’re
slow on the uptake, polnareff!
Polnareff: I-it’s coming
from the dog’s wound.
♪
( Megaphone squeals )
Child: Lali-ho!
Allow me to welcome you
to my humble abode.
This is a dream,
and i’m the grim reaper!
Polnareff: It’s a megaphone?
♪
What the--what is that thing?!
Kakyoin: Polnareff,
stay on guard,
and watch closely.
That fiend is death 13.
( Polnareff gasping )
W-w...
( Screams )
Kakyoin: Come forth,
hierophant green!
( Polnareff gags )
Kakyoin: Hierophant, attack!
( Polnareff gags ) Chario--
kakyoin: Why can’t I
summon hierophant?
What is this?
Polnareff: Chariot is
not coming out either.
Kakyoin: Is it because we’re
in some kind of twisted dream?
Death 13: Lali-ho!
It’s romantic,
wouldn’t you agree,
being able to die in a dream?
Lali-ho.
( Polnareff groans )
( Kakyoin moans )
Joseph: Eh, jotaro,
do you sense that?
Jotaro: Yeah, clear as day.
( Polnareff gagging )
Death 13: Are you stupid?
Surely you know by now that only
a stand can defeat a stand.
It’s time for you to enter
your eternal sleep, polnareff.
Lali-ho.
Kakyoin: Polnareff!
Death 13: Die!
Huh?
- ( Polnareff gasping )
- Joseph: Polnareff.
Hey, polnareff, wake up.
It would appear our little
traveler has wet himself.
Do us all a favor,
and change his diaper.
Polnareff: Huh? ( Scoffs )
- Jotaro: Hmm?
- ( Baby mutters )
Death 13: Eh, curses.
Someone must have woken
the fool from his slumber.
He’s quite lucky.
( Kakyoin shudders )
Death 13: Lali-ho.
I suppose it’s no matter.
Even if he wakes up, he won’t
remember a single thing.
I’ll just have to finish him
the next time he falls asleep.
Which means your death
has been moved up.
Lali-ho!
Joseph: Hey, there, polnareff,
have you woken up yet?
I’d like that diaper changed
this year.
Polnareff: All right.
I’m up. I’m up.
( Sighs ) Man...
I feel like I had some
kind of terrifying nightmare,
but i--i don’t remember
what happened at all.
I’ve completely forgotten.
Joseph: After you change
the boy’s diaper,
you can head back to dreamland
to finish your business.
I won’t wake you up again.
( Kakyoin shuddering )
( Polnareff gags )
Merde! Hold on a second, guys.
What the hell is this?!
The kid took a dump
in his diaper.
Just look at the size of it.
Joseph: Well,
he is a baby, you know.
That’s why he wears diapers.
Polnareff: You’re kidding me!
That’s why?!
C’est degueulasse.
What a vile,
disgusting creature.
And he’s gotten it
all over the place!
Joseph: Would you stop yapping
and change the damn diaper
already? It stinks.
( Polnareff sighs )
How are you not embarrassed?
Do us all a favor,
and grow up already.
Does this look right to you?
Well, it looks good to me.
Jotaro, I need you
to hold on to the edge there.
I’m gonna try and pin it.
Jotaro: Okay. Like this?
Polnareff: Yeah, I think so.
Now hold on to the baby.
( Kakyoin shuddering )
( Murmuring )
Both: Hmm?
( Kakyoin groans )
Death 13: Lali-ho!
( Kakyoin screams )
Stop it! Stop it!
- Jotaro: Kakyoin, what’s wrong?
- Polnareff: Hey!
Joseph: What’s going on?
Kakyoin: Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it! Stop!
( Joseph yells )
Damn it!
I’ve lost control!
Jotaro: Wait. Are you saying
that we’re gonna crash?
- Kakyoin: Stop!
- Polnareff: Kakyoin,
what’s the matter with you?
He’s been this way
since he woke up!
Joseph: I don’t care.
Just calm him down.
Jotaro: Old man, if you don’t
regain control of this thing,
we’re all done for.
Death 13: Kakyoin, you need to
pull yourself together, pronto.
We’re about to crash
because of you.
Lali-ho.
Talk about a restless sleeper.
At this rate,
you’ll kill us both,
you and my user, that is.
Kakyoin: Y-your user
is that baby?
How in the world
is that possible?
No way.
He’s only about six months old.
Death 13: Wrong. I’m 11 months,
almost a year old.
It may also interest you
to know that i’m a genius.
I may poop in my diapers,
but I know a hell of a lot more
than you fools!
Lali-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho.
( Kakyoin screams )
( Gagging )
Death 13: And with that, you’ve
lost your ability to scream.
( Laughs )
Kakyoin: A stand within a dream.
I have to find a way to let
Mr. Joestar and jotaro know.
Death 13: Hmm?
Polnareff: What are you doing?
- Mr. Joestar!
- Jotaro: Damn it. Level us out.
Joseph: Just calm down.
Can’t you see
i’m working on that
while trying
to stay cool and collected?
Kakyoin: I’m not waking up.
Death 13: Lali-ho.
Looks to me
like no one’s going to notice
if you’re cutting your arm
with a knife
that’s smaller than my wee-wee.
Besides, you can hurt yourself
all you want in this dream,
but it won’t wake you up.
As long as you’re asleep,
I completely control
every iota
of your precious mind.
My stand, death 13,
infiltrates the minds
of its slumbering victims
when they are
at their most vulnerable.
Kakyoin: Damn it. Stop.
( Joseph screaming )
Jotaro: What’s wrong, old man?
We’re crashing.
Joseph: I’ll control it
with hermit purple.
- I did it!
- Polnareff: Whoo-hoo!
Joseph: I lifted the plane
just in the Nick of time!
Polnareff: What a close one.
( Baby sighs )
Death 13: It would seem
we managed to avoid crashing.
That was too close for comfort.
Now, then, what do you say
to me killing you
by crushing that heart of yours?
That way, joestar and the others
will think
you had a heart attack
and died of natural causes.
( Kakyoin grunting )
Death 13: Die, kakyoin.
Joseph: Did you guys see that?
How do you boys
like them apples?
- My flying’s not too shabby.
- Polnareff: Well done.
- Jotaro: Hey.
- Joseph: Hmm?
( Men yell )
Joseph: What? Why the hell
is there a palm tree
all the way out here?
Jotaro: Good grief. Damn.
I knew you’d do this.
( Kakyoin gasps )
( Insects chirping )
Joseph: Hmm.
Polnareff: Is this enough,
Mr. Joestar?
Joseph: Yeah. Thank you.
( Polnareff sighs )
We survived, but...
Kakyoin, what’s going on, man?
This is all your fault,
you know?
Kakyoin: I’m not sure.
I feel like I just endured
a horrible dream,
and when I awoke,
I was utterly exhausted.
I think there’s
something wrong with me.
Joseph: Try and cheer up.
It’s probably a case of fatigue.
It’s been about a month now
since we left Japan,
and the enemy’s
been attacking us nonstop
ever since that day.
Jotaro: Hey.
It looks like the baby’s fever
has finally gone down.
Joseph: Thank goodness
he’s safe and sound.
If anything were to happen,
to this little guy,
i’d never forgive myself.
( Laughs )
Peek-a-boo. Bleh!
( Baby laughs )
Joseph: Peek-a-boo. Bleh.
Joseph: He has
such an adorable smile,
don’t you think?
Polnareff: I really
don’t get what’s so funny.
You’re not even
making any jokes,
just faces. What an idiot.
♪
Baby: Oh, put a sock in it.
This isn’t my idea
of a perfect night, either.
Jotaro: Hey, old man,
the radio survived.
What should we do?
Should we send out an s.O.S?
That’ll mean dio
can find us, but...
Joseph: We have to.
Let’s call for a rescue,
for the baby’s sake.
( Baby coos )
( Kakyoin sighs )
Huh?
I thought I was feeling
twinges of pain.
I’m bleeding.
Wait. Did I cut it
when we crashed?
( Gasps )
♪
What’s this?
The cuts form letters.
"Baby...stand"?
But how did they--
I don’t know what it means,
even though it’s my handwriting.
I can’t remember anything.
Did I do this to myself?
There isn’t any blood
on my knife,
but it seems the cuts
were made with this blade.
How strange.
Could I have really forgotten
violently cutting my own arm?
Baby: Damn it. I was told
that they were a clever bunch,
but this one actually carved
letters into his arm
while he was cutting himself.
- ( Groans )
- Kakyoin: Hmm?
( Baby gasps )
Kakyoin: What was that look
on the baby’s face just now?
It’s as if he
deliberately looked away
the moment I met his gaze.
( Gasps )
Baby...
Stand.
- ( Gasps )
- ( Baby groans )
Baby stand.
I hate to say it, but I might
be losing my mind, because...
I’m starting to think...
( Baby yelps )
Kakyoin: That this baby
is a stand user!
( Baby crying )
Joseph: Hey, kakyoin,
what do you think you’re doing?
( Baby crying )
Joseph: Come on, now.
That is way too rough.
You could strangle the boy.
What’s wrong with you?
Kakyoin: My apologies.
Joseph: There, there.
Everything’s all right.
Joseph: Let’s have
something to eat, shall we?
He should calm down
once he has some food in him.
Polnareff: Hey, jotaro,
it looks like poor kakyoin’s
really starting
to lose it out here.
Jotaro: Hmm.
Joseph: There, there...
Polnareff: I wonder
if he’ll make it
through the rest of this trip.
♪
( Baby laughs )
♪ All the old paintings
on the tomb ♪
♪ they do the sand dance,
don’t you know ♪
♪ if they move too quick
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re falling down
like a domino ♪
♪ all the bazaar men
by the nile ♪
♪ they got the money on a bet
♪ gold crocodiles
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they snap their teeth
on your cigarette ♪
♪ foreign types
with the hookah pipes say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian
♪ The blond waitresses
take their trays ♪
♪ they spin around,
and they cross the floor ♪
♪ they’ve got the moves
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ you drop your drink
♪ then they bring you more
♪ all the school kids
so sick of books ♪
♪ they like the punk
and the metal band ♪
♪ when the buzzer rings
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re walking
like an Egyptian ♪
♪ all the kids
in the marketplace say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian