( Centerfold screams )
( Enyaba gasps )
( Staff clatters )
( Enyaba gasping )
My son, my precious boy
has been murdered!
- ( Weeping )
- ( Cat yowls )
I can sense the misfortune
that has befallen my son.
The bond between mother
and son has spoken!
( Cat yowls )
( Enyaba wails )
( Cat growls )
( Enyaba yelling )
My precious, beautiful boy,
you died covered
with wounds like this?
Those bastards.
( Gasping )
I can feel it.
I suffer the same pain you felt!
( Cat growling )
You were utterly magnificent
as you fought for lord dio,
my dear centerfold.
How? How did they do it?
To kill such a noble
and pure soul like you,
they must have done
something underhanded!
( Sobbing )
- ( Cat yowls )
- Damn them!
The bastards!
I will make sure they pay
a terrifying price
with the empress card!
They’ll regret
the day they were born!
- ( Cat yowls )
- Move!
- ( Cat groans )
- I won’t stand idle.
This is the time for action,
a time for vengeance
with the stand
that brings a slow death!
( Wails )
Oh, the anguish, the pain!
I shall kill them all!
( Cackling )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Narrator: Jojo and crew head
to the sacred city, varanasi.
Polnareff: Listen up.
I don’t usually get
on a soapbox like this,
but stupid people are just that.
You could repeat something
a million times over,
and they still won’t listen.
You know the type, don’t you?
There’s just no helping
the poor souls.
But you know, uh--
hold on.
I never got your name, did I?
Nena: Nena.
Polnareff: Nena!
That’s a great name.
Daughter of a wealthy family
in the sacred city varanasi
that we’re
passing through, right?
You’re good-looking,
and you’ve got an equally good
head on your shoulders.
- I have an eye for people...
- ( Joseph sighing )
Polnareff:
Which leads me to my point.
Hol horse is a horrible,
lying bastard, understand?
He was manipulating you.
Think how your parents
would feel.
You hear me?
You can’t end up
like this, okay?
I know it’s easy
when you’re in love,
but you can’t afford
to see the world
with such a narrow view.
Take a step back,
and look at the whole picture.
- Kakyoin: Hey.
- Polnareff: Eh?
Kakyoin: We’re almost there...
The city of varanasi.
♪
Narrator: The sacred river,
the Ganges...
A place for holy men,
the old and the sick,
where domestic animals
and food for human consumption
lie alongside human waste
and corpses for cremation.
The river embraces all.
From birth unto death,
its holy waters
form a microcosm of life.
It is said that visitors
of the sacred city of varanasi
remain transfixed,
never wanting to leave.
Perhaps the landscape
that is this sacred land
is a mirror unto the soul.
( Insect buzzing )
Joseph: Hmm?
Man...
This thing
isn’t getting any better.
♪
Jotaro: What’s wrong, old man?
You don’t look well.
Joseph: Uh-uh.
Looks like my bug bite
just got a lot worse.
This thing must be infected.
Kakyoin:
It’s definitely swollen.
It would be best
to have a doctor look at it
before it gets worse.
Polnareff: Hey, doesn’t that
sort of look
like a person’s face?
Joseph:
Stop kidding around, polnareff.
That’s creepy.
( Polnareff laughs )
Sorry about that.
Want me to go
to the hospital with you?
Joseph: No! Stop treating
me like an old man.
( Stand squeaks )
Doctor: Hmm.
I’ll just Lance this.
Joseph: Huh? What did you say?
Doctor: It’s definitely
infected now.
It’ll get worse
if we don’t drain the fluid.
Joseph: Hey, hey, hey.
Can’t we just put medicine
and a bandage on it
and call it a day?
Doctor: Don’t worry, my friend.
We’ll numb the area
so it won’t hurt.
No problem. No problem at all.
Come, now. Lie down.
( Joseph groans )
Doctor: Sir, I studied
medicine in england.
I can do appendectomies, too.
- Uh-oh. It’s a little rusty.
- Joseph: Eh?
Doctor: Well, that’s no problem.
( Joseph gasping )
Doctor: All right.
Let’s slice it open.
Joseph: Eh, come on.
I don’t wanna watch it
being cut open. Have a heart.
Doctor: It’ll be fine.
- ( Metal scrapes )
- ( Joseph winces )
( Groaning )
- ( Slicing )
- ( Fluid spurting )
Hey, are you done yet?
Can I open my eyes now?
- ( Doctor gags )
- Joseph: Huh?
- ( Doctor shrieks )
- ( Joseph yells )
What the...
- Growth: Hey, doctor...
- ( Joseph gasps )
Growth: Trying to cut me off?
That’s a pretty stupid move,
you old fart.
( Joseph gasps )
( Growth laughs )
( Joseph yells )
Growth: Chu-mi-min!
Joseph: What the--
what the hell is this?!
Empress: I am the empress,
as in the empress card,
old man Joseph, and now,
i’m gonna bloody you up good!
Joseph: When did you
get on me, damn it?!
No way! This thing’s got teeth?!
( Grunts )
Damn thing’s strong.
No! It grabbed the scalpel!
( Yells )
Oh, no!
Thank goodness
that was my artificial hand.
Empress: Bastard!
Think you can just cut me?
I’m a part of your body now,
old man Joseph.
You can’t get away
from me, honey,
no matter how hard you try.
You know, I bet I can tell you
what’s going through
that thick skull of yours.
You’re probably thinking
something like,
"only a stand
can beat another stand.
"My stand, hermit purple,
"has the power of clairvoyance
and remote viewing,
"but how am I supposed to fight
"something like this
with those powers?
"How can I destroy something
that’s growing
out of my own arm?"
So, honey, was that spot on?
Joseph: Where’s the user?!
How in the hell
could you have infected me?!
Empress: You moron,
I won’t tell.
Joseph: Disgusting freak.
( Empress laughs )
Running off to your friends?
We’ll see how that goes,
won’t we?
Nurse: Doctor,
your next patient
is waiting for you.
( Gasps )
( Screams )
Doctor!
Joseph: Uh, hey,
don’t get the wrong idea.
I didn’t--
empress: I killed him!
I’m Joseph joestar, an American.
I’m staying at hotel Clarks.
Joseph: What?
Empress: And by the way, girlie,
I have a thing for hot
young nurses like yourself.
I think I should
give you an exam.
Joseph: What?!
Nurse: M-murderer!
Joseph: Wait! It’s not true!
Oh, no.
( Siren blaring )
( Overlapping chatter )
♪
( Joseph panting )
( Empress laughs )
Now you can’t go
back to the hotel.
You’re all alone now, honey.
I can kill you
without anyone interfering.
Joseph: You little--
you’re pissing me off!
I’ll crush you to tiny bits!
What?
Empress: Hey,
this is your own arm.
Take care of it,
you shitty old man.
It grew arms.
How much more could it grow?
Eh?
( Empress laughs )
Joseph: What the hell?
Let go of it!
I mean it, freak, now!
Empress: Not a chance.
Hey, officer,
the murderer’s over here!
He’s right here!
( Officer grunts )
Joseph: It’s been a while
since it’s come to this.
( Inhales )
Officer: Hey,
what are you doing?
Joseph: Overdrive!
- Eh?
- Empress: Moron!
It’s your arm, remember?
You think your hamon would work
against your own body?
Officer: Hands up! Don’t move!
Joseph: Then how about
hermit purple?!
Empress: Y-you’re crushing me.
Joseph: I can use it
this way, too,
so how does it feel, ugly?
Officer: I told you not to move.
Now freeze!
- ( Bullets whizzing )
- Stop, criminal!
Joseph: Damn it.
Empress: What are you doing?
I can’t see.
Joseph: Shit.
Jesus, Mary, and Joseph.
♪
Polnareff: Do you get
what i’m telling you, nena?
Real men don’t
have to talk a big game
like your
six-shooting boyfriend.
That’s how you figure out
who’s a liar
and who’s the genuine article.
( Joseph panting )
Damn cops have run me
in the wrong direction.
I’m nowhere near the hotel now.
If I had known
this would happen,
I would have taken
polnareff with me.
Polnareff: Instead of
a petty guy like hol horse,
why not be with me?
Am I not your type?
Nena: Hmm.
Polnareff: Come on.
I don’t dwell on the past
like some.
I don’t care who you were
dating before, even hol horse.
What’s important is the future.
We just need to understand
each other, right?
Nena: Oh, look over there,
polnareff.
Polnareff: Hmm.
Nena: That place is a hotel
run by a nice Japanese woman
named kumiko.
Polnareff: Huh?
Nena: She manages it
with her Indian husband.
Man: Out of the way.
You’ll get run into.
Nena: We can probably
get a cheap room.
Polnareff: Oh, really? Huh.
Tell me more about this hotel.
( Chicken clucks, shrieks )
- ( Empress bites )
- ( Joseph groans )
( Empress chewing )
Joseph: Huh?
Wha...
What the hell are you doing?!
Huh?
Empress: Chu-mi-min!
I’m eating, joestar.
A growing girl needs her food.
Joseph: You stole those
at the market,
- you quick little bastard.
- ( Empress bites )
Joseph: Ahh!
Eh? Why, you--
( yells )
Empress: Chu-mi-min.
Look how big i’ve gotten.
It’s tough having another mouth
to feed, isn’t it, daddy?
Chu-mi-min.
Joseph:
You disgusting little cow!
- ( Empress spits )
- Joseph: I’ll show you
that nobody has
the experience or the smarts
to take down
the great Joseph joestar.
You don’t stand a chance,
you bastard.
Now how the hell
am I gonna do that? Damn it.
Here goes nothing.
Hermit purple!
( Empress grunts )
Oh, daddy dearest,
you’ve done a wonderful job
of raising me,
but you know, you shouldn’t
tie your children down,
or they won’t grow.
It only smothers them.
You should raise them
to be free.
If not, they might rebel.
( Joseph yells ) Oh, no!
( Crowd murmuring )
( Joseph shouting )
It’s no use.
If I had a camera,
I could use hermit purple
to get a picture
of the stand user’s location.
Damn it all!
Come on, think, Joseph. Think.
At this rate,
it won’t just be my arm.
She’ll take over
my whole body. Huh?
( Empress shouts )
- Joseph: Huh?
- ( Empress laughs )
I’ve already grown enough
that I could easily end
your pathetic life.
See? My hand can reach
your throat now, old man.
I just have to bust
your carotid artery,
and you’ll crumple over
like a sack of potatoes.
( Joseph gasping )
( Empress yells )
( Yelling )
Joseph: Oh, no!
( Crowd murmuring )
( Empress yelling )
Man: What’s he doing?
Joseph: Bastard!
- Man: He’s lost his mind.
- Man #2: Look at that.
Some very strange man has
a strange growth on his arm.
( Joseph panting )
Damn it!
Where the hell’s the stand user?
Nena: I have
to tell you something.
- Polnareff: Huh?
- Nena: I need a reliable man,
a good man like you
to take care of me,
and i--i love you, polnareff.
Such a kindhearted,
trustworthy man you are.
Polnareff: Uh, really?
But it’s all so sudden.
This is happening.
I have finally found one.
Eeh! Lucky. Eeh!
♪
- ( Siren blaring )
- Joseph: Huh?
Empress: Hey, Joseph joestar,
you idiot,
you keep getting
farther and farther
from jotaro and the others.
( Laughs )
Joseph: Do you really think
i’m just running
around town randomly?
I’m not doing this just
to wear myself out, you know.
Empress: Wha?
Joseph: I’m running
so I can kill you!
This is the end of the line!
See that?
You’re going in!
Have a nice soak!
Hah!
( Empress gurgling )
You senile, old fool!
( Joseph screams )
A nail?
Empress: Yeah,
I picked it up earlier
when you were rolling around
on the ground like an idiot.
Now I can shove it
right in your carotid,
and you’ll bleed out
like a stuck pig.
Did you actually believe
i’d suffocate
if you stuck me in here,
you fool?
Die!
I may be made of your flesh,
but i’m nothing like you.
Forget the rules already, chump?
Only a stand can
hope to defeat another stand.
Oh, yeah, didn’t you say
you were gonna show me
all that fighting experience
you have?
Was I supposed to be impressed?
Some plan.
You’re just a helpless geezer
who’s gotten too old
to help anyone, even himself.
Joseph: My prosthetic hand,
it was on the verge of breaking
from her attack earlier,
and now I can’t get
any strength into it.
Empress: Just one more push.
Your life as an invalid
is about to come to an end.
Chu-mi-min.
There’s not a single way
you can defeat me.
You might as well surrender.
- Eh?
- ( Joseph grunts )
Empress: What the hell is this?
( Grunting )
( Groans )
Joseph: Huh?
I might as well what now?
I’m sorry. My hearing
isn’t exactly what it once was.
Run that by me
one more time, will you?
( Empress gasps )
It’s coal tar!
That was your plan all along.
It wasn’t to suffocate me.
You were trying
to keep me from moving!
But how?
How did you know
there was coal tar in there?
( Joseph laughs )
With my stand’s power.
Hermit purple
told me everything.
Man: H-hey, everyone, look.
Man #2: What is this?
Man #3:
The ashes that foreigner
spilled everywhere
when he wrecked the place.
Man #4: They’ve formed into
a perfect map of the city.
( Empress gasps ) You drew
a map with hermit purple?
That’s how you found the tar,
a map out of incense ashes?
Joseph: Yeah.
Now I think even
a glorified pimple like you
should see the difference
in our fighting experience.
When your opponent starts
boasting, he’s already lost.
That, shrew,
is a line from my Wilder days.
Like a fine wine, I guess
I just get better with age.
And now...
( Empress gasps )
Joseph: A stand
will defeat another stand.
- ( Empress gasping )
- Joseph: Next you’ll say,
"please stop it. I beg you."
Empress: Please, just stop it.
I beg you! ( Screams )
Joseph: This will hurt me
as much as it hurts you,
but children can’t depend
on their parents forever.
Once you’ve grown up,
you’ve gotta learn
to live on your own!
( Empress gasping )
( Screams )
Joseph: Now then...
I wonder where that thing’s
stand user is hiding.
( Overlapping chatter )
Polnareff: Uh, so what
do you say, nena, darling?
Shall we seal our new love
with a sweet kiss?
( Nena shuddering )
( Gagging )
( Polnareff gasps )
What the hell is this?!
It’s nasty! Ugh!
What’s wrong, nena?
( Screams )
( Nena screams )
( Empress screams )
Joseph: So she was the empress’s
stand user all along.
Polnareff: Huh?
( Shudders )
Joseph: She was
an ugly old troll.
She attached her stand to me
as a tumor with a human face
and camouflaged herself
as a beautiful woman.
You were careless.
She played you like
a damn fiddle, polnareff.
( Polnareff gagging )
♪
Kakyoin: And here I thought
we’d finally be able
to sleep in a bed for once.
Jotaro: If the old man
hadn’t screwed up,
we wouldn’t be out here
hiding from the cops.
Joseph: I took care of things.
We can take this car.
Polnareff, you do the driving.
What?
Don’t tell me
you’re still in shock.
I was the one
who was attacked by the stand.
Polnareff: Sure, but I think i’d
rather have gone through that.
( Car engine starts )
♪
( Car engine roaring )
♪ All the old paintings
on the tomb ♪
♪ they do the sand dance,
don’t you know ♪
♪ if they move too quick
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re falling down
like a domino ♪
♪ all the bazaar men
by the nile ♪
♪ they got the money on a bet
♪ gold crocodiles
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they snap their teeth
on your cigarette ♪
♪ foreign types
with the hookah pipes say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian
♪ The blond waitresses
take their trays ♪
♪ they spin around,
and they cross the floor ♪
♪ they’ve got the moves
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ you drop your drink
♪ then they bring you more
♪ all the school kids
so sick of books ♪
♪ they like the punk
and the metal band ♪
♪ when the buzzer rings
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re walking
like an Egyptian ♪
♪ all the kids
in the marketplace say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian