Woman: Fear, glorious fear,
it’s a natural emotion
present in all animals.
Now i’m curious. Tell me.
What do you think causes fear?
( Chuckles )
There is the kind of fear
born of animal instincts
and the kind of fear
born of a rational mind
that terrorizes humans.
Namely when you encounter
a foe stronger than yourself
and realize you have no way
of fighting back
against the unknown,
your helplessness
begins to sink in
and evokes inside of you
a terrible and paralyzing fear.
( Chuckles )
( Woman #2 moaning )
Woman #1: When you are
faced with such fear,
you have a number of options
before you from which to choose.
You might struggle, resist,
flee, accept, or freeze.
But upon meeting lord dio,
a new,
unexpected reaction arises.
You feel joy!
Dio: How do you think
most people act
once they feel joy in fear?
It’s an interesting experience.
Woman #1: Our friend
is currently on the plane
that joestar and
the others have boarded.
He’ll greet them accordingly,
and they will find it
utterly impossible
to reach their final destination
in one piece.
( Cackles )
( Insect buzzing )
Kakyoin: Hmm?
- ( Gasps )
- Avdol: Hmm?
( Both sigh )
♪
( Buzzing continues )
Jotaro: A rhino beetle?
No. It’s a stag beetle.
Joseph: Hey, avdol,
is that a stand?
Are we already encountering
another stand user?
Avdol: It’s possible.
This could be a stand that
takes the shape of an insect.
What the--it hid
in the shadow of the seats.
Avdol: Damn.
It could be anywhere.
( Beetle chirps )
Kakyoin: Jojo,
it’s next to your head!
Look to your right!
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Kakyoin: Whoa. It’s so huge.
That thing has to be a stand.
No doubt. It’s here for us.
Jotaro: That’s disgusting.
Just sit tight.
I’ll take care of it.
Avdol: Be extremely careful.
I’ve heard that there is
a user of an insect stand
that likes
to rip out the tongues
of his victims before they die.
Jotaro: Star platinum!
( All gasp )
Avdol: It dodged you.
I-I can’t believe it.
It’s faster than star platinum,
a stand that has
the speed and precision
to grab a flying bullet.
Kakyoin: Then there’s
no doubt about it.
That bug can only be a stand.
Where is he?
Where is he hiding?
Where is the one
who’s controlling it?
We need to find him.
It’s getting ready to attack!
( Star platinum roars )
Jotaro: No, damn it.
- Joseph: Jotaro!
- Avdol: Jojo!
( Jotaro shuddering )
( Star platinum growls )
Joseph: Star platinum
stopped it with its teeth
just in the Nick of time.
Avdol: Just as I feared,
it’s going
after jotaro’s stand’s tongue.
It’s him, represented by
the tower card of the tarot,
symbolizing calamity and
the interruption of a journey.
This stand is called...
Tower of gray!
( Tower of gray chitters )
Avdol: Tower of gray
is responsible
for countless mass murders,
which he made to look
like unfortunate accidents.
The plane crash
last year in england
that caused over 300 deaths
was likely his work.
And how many more
have there been over the years?
I’d heard rumors, but to think
he’s teamed up with dio...
Jotaro: Ora!
( Yelling )
Avdol: It dodged
that attack, too?
Not just from the single hand,
but it also dodged
a two-fisted barrage of blows.
I-it’s so fast.
( Tower of gray laughs )
Even if you had 10 guns
to shoot bullets
from one centimeter away,
they would not be able
to touch my stand.
Not that you could kill a stand
with a gun, anyways.
You’re all going to die with
the rest of these weaklings.
Joseph: He has to be
on this plane with us.
Who is it? Who is the one
controlling the stand?
Which one
of the passengers is he?
If we can track him down,
we can squash him.
( Jotaro gasps )
It disappeared again.
( Buzzing )
( Kakyoin gasps )
Heads up. It’s over there now.
( Tower of gray laughs )
Jotaro: What’s it
planning to do?
Avdol: No. It can’t be.
( All gasp )
( Tower of gray laughs )
Bingo.
Got their tongues.
Now for the best part.
Narrator: Massacre--
its definition,
to kill everyone.
Kakyoin: No.
It actually did it.
Avdol: Fine.
I’ll burn that damn bug alive!
Go, magician’s red!
( Magician’s red squawks )
Kakyoin: Avdol,
just hold on a second.
Avdol: Hmm?
( Man groaning )
It’s so damn noisy
on this flight.
- What’s with all the ruckus?
- Kakyoin: Be careful!
Man: Might as well
go to the bathroom.
Why’s this wet?
What’s with
all this slimy stuff?
"M"--( Sniffs )
"A-s"--( Screams )
Blood! This is blood!
( Gasps )
Kakyoin: Atemi.
We have to defeat it
before the other passengers
start to panic.
Easier said than done, though.
Mr. Avdol...
Using an active stand
like your magician’s red
inside an airborne plane
could make it explode,
killing all of us.
Jojo, if your power were
to rip a hole in the fuselage,
- it’d be a catastrophe.
- ( Buzzing )
This calls for
a quiet and discreet stand.
My hierophant green
is most suited to defeating it.
Let me take care
of the pest control.
( Tower of gray laughs )
Noriaki kakyoin, eh?
I’ve heard all about you
from lord dio.
Don’t bother.
You think you have
silence on your side,
but your stand
cannot keep up with my speed!
Kakyoin: You sure about that?
Emerald splash!
( Tower of gray laughing )
Kakyoin: Hmm?
Emerald splash again!
( Tower of gray laughing )
You seem to think you can hit me
if you fire enough shots,
but you haven’t hit me at all.
- Kakyoin: Huh?
- Avdol: Not good.
It’s dodging
everything he throws at it.
- ( Kakyoin gags )
- Jotaro: Kakyoin.
( Tower of gray laughs )
I’m just too fast for you.
You’re way too slow
to get a bingo.
And, kakyoin...
With my next attack,
i’ll stab your stand’s tongue
with this tower needle
and rip it out.
Won’t that be fun?
Kakyoin: Emerald splash!
Tower of gray: Don’t you get it?
( Laughing )
Avdol: Damn. Impossible.
How can he win if his attacks
don’t find their Mark?
Tower of gray:
You’ll go mad from the pain
once this rips its tongue out.
( Laughs )
How exquisite.
Kakyoin: Is that right?
If its tongue’s ripped out,
i’ll go mad from the pain?
My hierophant green
will go mad, all right.
( Tower of gray screams )
What?
Kakyoin: If it rips you apart,
it’ll go mad...
From pure joy.
( Tower of gray screaming )
Kakyoin: His appendages
had already slipped
beneath the seats.
I just needed enough time
to set up my little trap.
You didn’t realize
I was using my emerald splash
to keep you in one spot?
( Man gags )
Joseph: What the...
Kakyoin: So that geezer
was the user all along, huh?
Heh. Guess I should
have expected as much.
A repulsive stand
usually has a repulsive user.
Well, that’s strange.
It doesn’t look like he had
dio’s flesh bud in his forehead.
Avdol: Tower of gray
was always evil.
He killed tourists
by the hundreds
and got paid for it.
He’d make it
look like an accident
and got away with it every time.
I’m sure dio
was able to use him,
because he was easily bought
and blinded by greed.
( Plane creaking )
Joseph: Eh?
Something’s wrong.
It could be my imagination,
but I get the feeling
this plane isn’t
flying straight anymore.
♪
It’s crooked.
No doubt about it.
Huh? It can’t be.
- Jotaro: Hmm?
- ( Kakyoin sighs )
Attendant: Sorry, sir.
You can’t be up here.
The cockpit is up ahead,
so passengers may not enter.
Joseph: I know that.
Attendant: S-sir, wait.
( Attendants gasping )
Both: Oh. He’s so handsome.
Jotaro: Move it, bitch.
Attendant #2: What a shock.
Kakyoin: Whoa, there.
Sorry, ladies.
His disrespectful behavior
towards you two is incorrigible,
but we have an emergency
on our hands.
( Both sigh )
Kakyoin:
Please forgive him, for me.
Both: Okay.
Joseph: Damn it!
This is horrible!
We’ve been had!
Jotaro: Their tongues
have been ripped out.
That rhino bastard.
He killed the pilots
before we knew he was here.
( Both gasp )
Joseph: Hmm.
We’re losing altitude fast.
The autopilot’s
been destroyed as well.
Damn it, we’re going to crash.
( User laughing )
Jotaro: What?
User: My stand is
the tower card,
which signifies
horrible accidents
and the end of journey.
I’ll keep you from lord dio
if it’s the last thing I do.
Even if you manage
to survive the crash,
you’re still
10,000 kilometers from Egypt.
Those who swore loyalty
to lord dio
will pursue you relentlessly.
You don’t stand
a chance in hell.
There are stands in this world
with powers that defy
the very limits of imagination.
Lord dio’s power is the one
that rules over all of them.
He is the master of stands,
reigning over the world
like a god among mortals.
There’s no way
you’ll reach him alive.
You bastards
won’t even see Egypt.
Your deaths
will be swift and painful!
( Laughs )
( Both gasp )
Jotaro: You’re
definitely professionals.
Good thing you didn’t scream.
That annoys me
all to freaking hell.
Now, i’ve got a request.
This heap’s gonna hit water,
and this old man’s
gonna land her there.
Joseph: Huh?
Jotaro: Go put life jackets
on the other passengers,
and make sure
they’re buckled up.
Attendant #1: Uh, yes, sir.
Jotaro: You got this?
Joseph: Mm...
I have some experience
with prop planes, but this...
Kakyoin: Prop planes?
Joseph: But, jotaro,
this’ll make
three plane crashes for me.
Have you ever heard of someone
being in a plane crash
three times,
let alone surviving each one?
( Men sigh )
Jotaro: That settles it.
I’m never riding in a plane
with you again.
Er thrumming )
Narrator: The plane landed
35 kilometers
off the coast of Hong Kong.
Jotaro and the others
had no choice
but to head to the city.
Reporter: ...South of Hong Kong,
near lamma island.
Rescue efforts
are now under way.
Narrator: Hong Kong,
Hong Kong island,
kowloon, the new territories.
With more than 235
individual islands in the area,
its breathtaking nightscape
is known the world over
as the million-dollar view.
Joseph: Yeah, no problem.
That’ll be fine.
Please make sure the only ones
aboard are us and the crew.
Right. There’s been enough
collateral damage because of us.
By the way...
Shopkeeper: Hey, big guy.
Jotaro: Hmm?
Shopkeeper: You guys aren’t
from around here, are you?
Want some rice porridge?
Can’t come to Hong Kong
and not try our rice porridge
and dim sum.
We have some hot cola, too.
Kakyoin: Rice porridge? Not bad.
Did you know, jojo,
unlike in Japan, rice porridge
is a staple food in Hong Kong.
To some, it’s quite a delicacy.
One bowl, the popular way,
with pork and century egg,
if you have it.
Shopkeeper: Coming right up.
Avdol: In that case, i’ll have--
Joseph: Hey! What?
You boys think
we have time to eat?
We’re going to my old favorite.
You can wait
to stuff your faces there.
Shopkeeper:
Hey, you dandy guy over there,
I know you’d be interested
in some Hong Kong hot cola.
Joseph: Hot cola?
That’s blasphemy.
Everyone knows
it’s supposed to be cold.
Jotaro: Old man,
who were you just callin’?
Joseph: Hmm? Oh, that.
I’ll explain
when we get to the restaurant.
Be patient.
We need to work out a plan
that’ll get us to Egypt as
safely and quickly as possible.
More users
are bound to come after us,
and that could cost lives.
Kakyoin: Right. A plan.
Avdol: I agree with you.
We can’t allow
any more innocent civilians
to be hurt
because of our failure.
The quickest way would be
by plane, but that’s out.
Joseph: Indeed.
It’s now become
completely impossible
for us to fly to Egypt.
You see, if we encounter
a stand user like the last one
on a commercial flight,
we’ll cause a disaster,
one that will harm many people
and might kill many more.
With that in mind,
we’ll have to get to Egypt
by either land or sea.
Avdol: I hear you,
but if we fail to find dio
within 50 days...
Hmm.
( Both grunt )
Kakyoin: If we could have
stayed on that plane,
we’d probably be in Cairo,
and this would be over.
( Jotaro sighs )
( Joseph sighs )
♪
I’m well aware of that.
However, it’s too soon
to worry about it.
( Men gasp )
Joseph: One hundred years ago,
Jules verne wrote
"around the world in 80 days,"
a story about a man who travels
40,000 kilometers in 11 weeks
using nothing
but trains and steamboats,
we may not have a plane,
but we still have 50 days.
We’ll be able to travel
the 10,000 kilometers to Egypt.
And as for the route
we’ll take...
♪
I say we go by sea.
We’ll charter
a suitably sized boat,
go around the malay peninsula,
and cross the Indian ocean,
"a silk road of the sea,"
as it were.
Avdol: I believe
that is best as well.
Crossing by land
could be difficult,
and we’d have to cross
the himalayas or the desert.
If we ran into trouble,
we’d lose a lot of time.
There are too many dangers.
Kakyoin: I haven’t been
to any of those places
using either route before,
so I really don’t know.
I’ll leave it
up to the two of you.
( Jotaro sighs ) Same with me.
Joseph: Then it’s decided.
Now the greatest danger
that we’ll face
will be the stand users
that dio sends against us.
We’ll have to do our best to get
to Egypt without being spotted.
♪
- ( Jotaro gasps )
- ( Kakyoin chuckles )
Don’t be so jumpy.
This is just to let them know
we want more tea.
If you do this in Hong Kong,
they’ll usually bring you more
within a few seconds.
Also...
Anytime the server pours
some tea into your cup...
Tap the table.
It’s a way of saying thank you.
( Waitress giggles )
Man: Excuse me.
Sorry to be a bother.
I’m a tourist from France.
Could you help me out?
My Chinese is a bit rusty,
and i’m having a hard time
with the characters on the menu.
Could you help me decipher it?
Jotaro: You’re annoying.
Go away.
Joseph: Come now, jotaro.
It’s fine.
Try to be nice to the man.
I’ve been to Hong Kong
many times over the years.
I can at least read
the characters on the menus.
Why don’t you join us?
So what do you want to order?
Dish with shrimp, duck,
shark fin, and mushrooms?
Hmm.
We’ll have this, this, and this,
and might as well
get some of these.
Oh, and this.
Waiter: Mm-hmm.
( Gong chimes )
Avdol: These look like dishes
with beef, fish...
Clams, and frog.
Kakyoin: Indeed, this is
quite different from our order.
Jotaro: I knew this
would happen, damn it.
( Man gasps )
( Joseph laughs )
Well, it makes no difference.
It’s all on me, boys.
Besides, it doesn’t matter
what you order.
It’s all delicious. ( Laughs )
All right, everyone. Dig in.
( Men gasp )
Kakyoin: Oh. This is...
Joseph: You see that?
And you were worried.
( Laughs )
Man: Well, they’ve certainly
taken a lot of time
to prepare this.
It’s almost artistic.
Take these carrots, for example,
cut into perfect little stars.
In fact,
it reminds me of something.
( Men gasp )
Man: I remember now.
Someone I know has a Mark,
a birthmark just like this
on the back of their neck.
Know anyone like that?
( Joseph growls )
- ( Avdol growls )
- ( Jotaro sighs )
Kakyoin: Are you another...
Enemy?
( Man chuckles )
( Joseph gasps )
Avdol: Mr. Joestar, look out!
- Joseph: It’s a stand!
- ( Metal hand clangs )
Avdol: Magician’s red,
come forth!
( Magician’s red squawks )
( Stand grunts )
Avdol: What the hell?
You were right,
another stand user.
- ( Joseph gasps )
- Kakyoin: Whoa.
He has such speed
with his sword.
Man: My stand
is the chariot card,
and his name is silver chariot.
Mohammed avdol,
it seems that I will be
disposing of you first.
I’ve carved a burning clock
into that table.
Before that clock strikes 12:00,
you will be a dead man.
♪
♪ All the old paintings
on the tomb ♪
♪ they do the sand dance,
don’t you know ♪
♪ if they move too quick
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re falling down
like a domino ♪
♪ all the bazaar men
by the nile ♪
♪ they got the money on a bet
♪ gold crocodiles
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they snap their teeth
on your cigarette ♪
♪ foreign types
with the hookah pipes say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian
♪ The blond waitresses
take their trays ♪
♪ they spin around,
and they cross the floor ♪
♪ they’ve got the moves
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ you drop your drink
♪ then they bring you more
♪ all the school kids
so sick of books ♪
♪ they like the punk
and the metal band ♪
♪ when the buzzer rings
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re walking
like an Egyptian ♪
♪ all the kids
in the marketplace say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian