>> MEOW.
>> I'M TIRED, BIG BROTHER.
>> I'M TIRED, TOO, BIG BROTHER.
>> QUIT COMPLAINING!
>> MEW.
>> MEOW.
>> CAN WE PLEASE TAKE A BREAK,
BROTHER?
>> YEAH, LET'S TAKE A BREAK,
BIG BROTHER.
>> UHH!
>> OHH!
>> OK, BUT JUST FOR A MINUTE.
>> AHH.
>> HUH?
>> [GROWLING]
[ROAR]
>> A DEMON!
>> WHY, YOU--
>> WIND SCAR!
>> AAH!
>> WELL NOW, HOW'D YOU LIKE
THAT?
IT SERVES YOU RIGHT FOR TRYING
TO EAT ME.
>> HUH?
HEY, THAT'S--
>> HEH HEH HEH.
GUESS YOU'LL KNOW BETTER
THAN TO MESS WITH ME AGAIN,
NOW, WON'T YOU?
>> HEY, WE'RE LEAVING, SHIPPO.
>> HUH?
UHH...JUST A SEC,
DON'T LEAVE ME BEHIND!
>> WAS THAT...THE GREAT HERO?
>> YES, IT'S GOT TO BE HIM,
BIG BROTHER.
>> IT'S THE GREAT HERO!
>> MEW.
>> MEOW.
>> WOW, IT'S REALLY HIM,
THE LEGENDARY GREAT HERO.
>> YEAH!
>> YOU SEE, I LOST BOTH
MY MOTHER AND MY FATHER
SOME TIME AGO.
>> OH, SHIPPO, YOU POOR GUY.
>> BUT DON'T WORRY, I'M OK,
I'VE GOT MY FRIENDS WITH ME.
>> YES, THEY SEEM LIKE
GOOD PEOPLE.
>> I'M MORE WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
THE WORLD OF HUMANS SEEMS TO BE
GOING THROUGH TROUBLED TIMES.
>> IT'S OK, I'LL BE FINE.
>> HUH?
>> ESPECIALLY NOW THAT
I'VE MET YOU.
>> I...UHH...SAME HERE, MISUKI!
>> UNBELIEVABLE.
HOW IS IT THAT SHIPPO MEETS
GIRLS AT EVERY SINGLE TOWN
WE VISIT ON OUR JOURNEY?
>> PROBABLY RUBBED OFF FROM
A CERTAIN SOMEBODY WE ALL
KNOW ONLY TOO WELL.
>> OF COURSE WE'LL GET RID
OF THIS DEMON THAT'S BEEN
PLAGUING YOUR VILLAGE, GOOD SIR.
HOWEVER, IF IT IS INDEED HIDING
UP IN THE MOUNTAINS, IT MAY TAKE
US SOME TIME TO CLEAR IT OUT.
>> OH, WE ARE VERY WELL AWARE
OF THAT.
>> GOOD.
NOW THEN, ABOUT OUR LODGING.
>> PLEASE STAY HERE AS LONG
AS YOU WISH.
>> DO YOU SUPPOSE WE COULD ASK
THE YOUNG LADIES TO TAKE CARE
OF US?
>> CERTAINLY, I'LL ASK SOME
OF THE YOUNG MAIDENS OVER
TO HELP OUT AT DINNER.
>> AND THROUGH THE NIGHT
AS WELL?
AAH!
>> LET'S NOT IMPOSE ON OUR
HOSTS, MONK.
>> NOW...NOW, EASY, SANGO.
>> COME ON, GIVE ME A BREAK.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT ALL THE FUSS
IS ABOUT.
FROM WHAT I'VE HEARD IT'S JUST
A PUNY LITTLE DEMON ANYWAY.
AND IF IT DOESN'T GET US
ANY CLOSER TO THE JEWEL SHARDS,
THEN I'M NOT INTERESTED
IN THE LEAST.
>> PLEASE, GOOD SIR,
DON'T SAY THAT.
>> HEY, WHY SHOULD I CARE?
THE SOONER WE LEAVE THIS DUMP
OF A VILLAGE THE BETTER.
>> INUYASHA...SIT, BOY!
>> AAH!
KAGOME!
WHAT DID YOU DO THAT FOR?
>> SIT, BOY.
>> KAGOME!
>> SO TELL ME, SHIPPO, ARE YOUR
FRIENDS ALWAYS SO VIOLENT?
>> THEY'RE JUST IMMATURE
I GUESS.
BUT DON'T YOU WORRY, I'M ALWAYS
HERE TO KEEP THINGS TOGETHER.
>> OH.
>> WE'LL BE BACK SOON, I HOPE.
>> I CAN'T THANK YOU ENOUGH.
>> AND YOU LOOK AFTER THINGS
HERE, OK, INUYASHA?
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> AREN'T YOU GOING, INUYASHA?
>> WELL, I DON'T THINK
THEY'LL REALLY BE NEEDING ME.
BESIDES, WHAT HAPPENS IF
THE DEMON ATTACKS THE VILLAGE
WHILE EVERYONE IS GONE?
>> WE'RE PLACING ALL OUR
HOPES ON YOU AND YOUR FRIENDS.
>> YEAH, YEAH, I KNOW.
>> WELL, IF YOU DON'T MIND,
I THINK I'LL GO TAKE
A LOOK AROUND.
>> SURE, DO WHATEVER YOU WANT.
>> THERE.
HE HE HE...I WONDER IF MISUKI
WILL LIKE IT.
OH, SHE'S GOING TO LOVE IT.
>> MASTER!
>> WHA--
>> HA HA HA!
>> 1.
>> 2.
>> 3.
>> 4.
>> 5.
>> MASTER.
>> MISTER.
>> MUSTARD.
>> MEW.
>> MEOW.
>> WHAT'S THE IDEA OF SNEAKING
UP ON ME LIKE THAT?
>> WE'RE FOX DEMONS, AND WE HAD
THE GOOD FORTUNE TO CROSS PATHS
WITH OUR HERO, MASTER SHIPPO.
>> MISTER.
>> MUSTARD.
>> MEW.
>> MEOW.
>> HUH...MASTER?
>> LATELY THE DEMON WORLD
IS IN TURMOIL, ALL BECAUSE
THE DEMON NARAKU HAS BEEN
STIRRING THINGS UP.
AS A RESULT, EVIL DEMONS
ARE RUNNING AMOK AND DOING
AS THEY PLEASE.
>> OUR OWN HAPPY LITTLE FAMILY
OF FOX DEMONS WAS ATTACKED
BY DEMONS SUCH AS THESE.
>> THE 5 OF US GOT SEPARATED
FROM OUR PARENTS, AND NOW WE'RE
LOOKING HIGH AND LOW FOR THEM.
>> MEW!
>> MEOW!
>> THROUGHOUT OUR TRAVELS
WE HAD HEARD TALES OF
THE GREAT MASTER SHIPPO.
>> WE HEARD THERE WAS A GROUP
WHO BATTLES AGAINST
THE EVIL NARAKU.
>> AND AMONG THEM, A FOX DEMON
WHO IS A GREAT HERO AND
A NATURAL BORN LEADER.
>> MEW!
>> MEOW.
>> HMM, WELL I SUPPOSE THEY MUST
BE TALKING ABOUT ME.
>> HA HA HA!
>> PLEASE, MASTER,
WE WILL WORK VERY HARD.
TRAIN US TO BE STRONG
AND COURAGEOUS LIKE YOU.
>> PLEASE MAKE US YOUR
DISCIPLES.
>> YOUR UNDERLINGS.
>> MEW.
>> MEOW.
>> BUT I DON'T KNOW HOW
TO TRAIN YOU.
>> OH, COME, COME.
THE RUMORS ABOUT YOU ARE
LEGENDARY.
YOU HAVE AMONG YOUR FOLLOWERS
A PRIESTESS...
A DEMON SLAYER...
A MONK...
A HALF DEMON.
SO TELL ME, ARE YOU NOT IN FACT
THE GREAT SHIPPO WHO LEADS THIS
BAND OF ILLUSTRIOUS WARRIORS?
>> LET'S SEE.
ME LEAD A...PRIESTESS...
A DEMON SLAYER...
A MONK...
AND A HALF DEMON?
INUYASHA IS MY SLAVE,
I USE HIM LIKE A FOOT STOOL!
>> YEAH!
>> AND THE HUMANS ARE ALL
MY PERSONAL SERVANTS.
>> MASTER SHIPPO,
PLEASE TEACH US ONE OF YOUR
DEADLY MOVES!
>> YOU HAD A TECHNIQUE WHEN YOU
FOUGHT NARAKU, DIDN'T YOU?
>> A DEADLY TECHNIQUE?
OH, YEAH, OF COURSE...
YOU MUST MEAN THIS.
FOX MAGIC SMASHING TOP!
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?
>> YOU MUST BE.
>> SERIOUSLY.
>> MEW.
>> MEOW.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> PLEASE, DON'T MAKE FUN
OF US, MASTER.
>> PLEASE, DON'T.
>> SURELY YOU HAVE ONE
INCREDIBLE MOVE?
>> INCREDIBLE MOVE?
>> A TERRIFIC ONE.
>> PERHAPS SOMETHING LIKE
FIN SWORD?
>> OR MAYBE MORE LIKE
WIND SCORE?
>> OR ELSE LIMPLARD.
>> AN UNBEATABLE MOVE.
>> UNBEATABLE!
>> WAIT A SEC...YOUR NOT TALKING
ABOUT THE WIND SCAR?
>> THAT'S THE ONE!
THAT'S IT.
>> HUH?
>> YOU MUST TEACH US THAT ONE,
MASTER.
>> PLEASE, MISTER.
>> PLEASE, MUSTARD.
>> MEW.
>> MEOW.
>> BUT, YOU SEE, THE WIND SCAR
IS ACTUALLY...
>> PLEASE, MASTER,
YOU MUST TEACH US!
>> ALL RIGHT, I'LL DO IT.
THE 5 OF YOU WAIT RIGHT HERE.
I NEED TO GO GET SOMETHING.
>> HURRAY!
>> INUYASHA, INUYASHA!
>> HEY, WHAT IS IT, SHIPPO?
HAS THE DEMON FINALLY SHOWN UP?
>> GIVE ME THE TETSUSAIGA!
I NEED TO DO THE WIND SCAR.
>> HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> WIND SCAR.
WIND SCAR.
WIND...SCAR!
WIND....OHH!
>> WHAT THE HECK ARE YOU UP TO?
>> INUYASHA, HOW DO YOU DO
THE WIND SCAR?
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> I WANT TO DO THE WIND SCAR,
TOO.
>> WHAT?
>> HOW DO YOU MAKE THIS THING
WORK?
>> YOU'RE DOING IT ALL WRONG.
YOU DON'T JUST SWING A
TETSUSAIGA AROUND LIKE THAT.
LISTEN, SHIPPO, IT'S ALL
IN HOW YOU SENSE THE FLOW
OF THE ENERGY,
AND WHAT YOU DO AND SAY.
WHEN I RAISE IT, I MAKE A SOUND
LIKE...GA GA GA!
TO INVOKE THE SWORD'S POWER.
AND THEN I FOLLOW WITH A SOUND
LIKE...ZU BA BA!
>> GA GA GA AND ZU BA BA?
>> MORE LIKE...GA GA GA
AND ZU BA BA.
TRY IT.
>> IT SERVES YOU RIGHT FOR
TRYING TO EAT--
>> LISTEN, IF YOU DON'T DO
THE GA GA GA AND ZU BA BA PARTS
YOU'LL NEVER GET IT.
WATCH ME, IT'S LIKE THIS.
FIRST YOU SAY: GA GA GA!
AND ZU BA BA!
AND THEN, WIND SCAR!
SEE, IT'S LIKE THAT.
UH-OH, THIS DOESN'T LOOK GOOD.
SHIPPO, WE'VE GOT TO...
HEY, WHERE'D HE GO?
OH, I SHOULD OF JUST STAYED
ASLEEP.
>> I GUESS I WAS KIND OF FOOLISH
TO THINK THAT INUYASHA COULD
TEACH IT TO ME.
>> SHIPPO!
WAIT!
>> MISUKI!
>> HEY, SHIPPO, WHERE WERE YOU?
>> UMM...I WAS...UHH...
I WAS JUST SCOUTING AROUND
FOR THAT NASTY OLD DEMON.
OH, I JUST REMEMBERED,
I WANTED TO GIVE THIS TO YOU.
>> OH, THANK YOU.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL, I LOVE IT.
>> WELL, I THINK YOU BETTER
GO BACK TO THE VILLAGE WHERE
IT'S SAFE NOW, OK?
>> HMM, YOU BE CAREFUL.
>> SURE.
>> THANK YOU!
>> HMM.
>> MASTER!
>> AAH!
>> H-HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN
STANDING THERE?
>> LONG ENOUGH.
>> LISTEN, YOU GUYS,
ABOUT THE WIND SCAR,
YOU SEE I COULDN'T GET MY SWORD
TO WORK, AND SO...
>> THAT WAS GREAT, MASTER.
>> TRICKING THAT HUMAN GIRL
WITH SUCH GRACE AND SKILL.
>> I WASN'T EXACTLY TRICKING
HER...
>> YOU SET A FINE EXAMPLE
OF THE FOX DEMON TRADITION
OF ENCHANTING OTHERS.
WE CAN'T LET THE RACCOON DEMONS
OUTDO US.
>> NEVER!
>> SO, MASTER, TELL US PLEASE,
ARE YOU GOING TO DO SOMETHING
DELIGHTFULLY AWFUL TO THIS GIRL?
>> WELL ACTUALLY,
QUITE THE OPPOSITE.
>> I'M SURE MR. SHIPPO HAS
A TERRIFIC TECHNIQUE,
WHATEVER IT IS.
>> I'M SO EXCITED.
>> LET'S SEE IT, LET'S SEE IT!
>> GEEZ, WHAT DO THESE FOX
DEMONS WANT?
>> OUT OF MY WAY, YOU LITTLE
FOX BRATS.
YAH!
>> AAH!
>> STUPID DEMON, WHAT DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING?
>> HEH HEH HEH!
>> UHH...
THIS MUST BE THE DEMON THAT'S
TERRORIZING THE VILLAGE!
I HAVE TO TELL INUYASHA
RIGHT AWAY.
>> HEY, BUDDY, DO YOU KNOW
JUST WHO IT IS YOU'RE DEALING
WITH HERE?
>> WHO?
>> THIS IS THE FOX FAMOUS
THROUGHOUT THE FOX DEMON WORLD.
THE ONE AND ONLY MR. SHIPPO!
>> YOU'RE THE ONE WHO SHOULD
GET OUT OF HIS WAY.
>> YOU KNOW IT!
>> I WOULDN'T GET IN HIS WAY
IF I WERE YOU.
>> BETTER WATCH YOUR STEP,
BIG GUY.
>> COME ON!
>> HE'S PRETTY TOUGH!
>> UMM, COULD YOU LET GO
OF MY TAIL, PLEASE?
>> WELL, WELL.
I GUESS I'VE GOT TO FIGHT HIM,
THEN.
>> OK, GO GET HIM, MASTER!
>> GET HIM!
>> MEOW!
>> LOOKS LIKE I'VE GOT
NO CHOICE.
>> COME ON, LETS SEE WHAT
YOU'VE GOT.
>> TRY THIS ON FOR SIZE!
AAH!
RUN AWAY!
>> YOU LITTLE SQUIRTS, ARE YOU
TRYING TO MAKE A FOOL OF ME?
>> WHOA!
>> AAH!
>> MASTER!
>> HEH, LITTLE TWERPS.
>> OH, BOY...THAT WAS
A CLOSE ONE.
JUST A SEC...I SENSE SOMETHING.
>> HI, MASTER!
>> HI, MISTER.
>> HI, MUSTARD.
>> MEOW.
>> TELL US THE TRUTH,
ARE YOU REALLY THE GREAT SHIPPO,
HERO OF THE FOX DEMONS?
>> YES, I AM SHIPPO.
NO TWO WAYS ABOUT THAT.
ALWAYS HAVE BEEN.
>> [CONVERSING]
>> AND YOU REALLY ARE
A POWERFUL DEMON, RIGHT?
>> YES.
YES, I AM.
>> AND YOU HAVE A DEADLY
TECHNIQUE, RIGHT?
>> YEAH, I GUESS.
>> SO, THEN WHY DID YOU RUN OFF?
>> WELL, YOU SEE...
>> TELL US!
>> UHH, THE THING IS...
>> MASTER, LOOK THERE!
>> MISUKI...
>> SO TELL ME, ARE YOU--
>> GO PLAY A TRICK ON HER!
>> PLEASE SHOW US YOUR SKILLS
OF ENCHANTMENT.
>> WE WANT TO SEE!
>> WHAT'S WRONG, MASTER?
DO IT!
>> I DUNNO, SHE HARDLY SEEMS
WORTH THE EFFORT.
AND BESIDES--
>> AND BESIDES NOTHING!
>> ARE YOU POSITIVE YOU'RE THE
GREAT HERO OF THE FOX DEMONS?
'CAUSE I'M STARTING TO HAVE
MY DOUBTS.
>> ERR...
>> WELL, ARE YOU?
>> YES!
I AM THE GREAT MASTER SHIPPO,
AND I'M GOING TO PROVE IT, OK?
>> THIS SMELLS LOVELY.
HUH?
>> HOLD IT RIGHT THERE, HUMAN.
THE JOKE'S ON YOU!
>> THE JOKE'S ON YOU!
>> READY, TAKE AIM...
LET HER HAVE IT!
>> STOP IT!
PLEASE, OW, THAT HURTS!
>> HEY, QUIT JUMPING AROUND.
>> AAH!
>> MISUKI?
MISUKI!
SPEAK TO ME, MISUKI.
ARE YOU OK?
TELL ME.
HUH?
>> SO THEN, SHIPPO.
IT WAS YOU.
>> UHH...UHH...
>> HE DID IT!
>> HURRAY!
HURRAY!
>> WOW, SHE'S SOAKING WET.
>> THANKS TO THE GREAT
MR. SHIPPO.
>> HOPE THAT TEACHES YOU
A LESSON.
>> OH...
I...UH...
>> DON'T SPEAK TO ME,
I HATE YOU!
>> HURRAY!
>> UH...UHH...MIZUKI?
>> HEY, MASTER.
>> HEY, MISTER.
>> HEY, MUSTARD.
>> MEOW.
>> YOU WERE SO TERRIFIC.
>> YAY!
>> OH, WELL, YOU HAVEN'T SEEN
ANYTHING YET.
>> [CRYING]
>> IT'S ALL OVER.
MY FIRST LOVE HAS ENDED AGAIN.
>> HURRAY FOR THE GREAT SHIPPO!
TAKE THAT, LITTLE GIRL!
>> HEH HEH HEH.
>> AAH!
HE'S BACK!
>> YOU TRIED TO MAKE A FOOL OUT
OF ME WITH THAT CHEAP TRICK OF
YOURS, BUT THIS TIME WE'RE GOING
TO SETTLE THINGS PROPERLY,
MASTER SHIPPO.
>> SAVE US, MASTER!
>> SAVE US, MISTER!
>> SAVE US, MUSTARD!
>> MEOW.
>> MEW!
>> SHUT UP.
WHAT'S WITH ALL THIS MUSTARD
STUFF ANYWAY?
NOW, IF YOU APOLOGIZE I MAY ONLY
HURT YOU A LITTLE BIT.
HMM?
HUH?
WHAT'S THIS?
>> IF IT HADN'T BEEN FOR YOU
SHOWING UP, I'D--I'D--
>> WHAT, YOU'RE ACTUALLY GOING
TO FIGHT ME?
>> I WOULDN'T HAVE HAD TO PROVE
MYSELF, AND MISUKI WOULDN'T
HATE ME.
HOW DARE YOU!
>> WHAT THE--
>> AAH!
>> [GASP]
>> HEH HEH HEH HEH.
>> OH, POOR MASTER.
>> NOW IT'S YOUR TURN,
YOU LITTLE TWERPS.
HUH?
WHAT?
>> I'M NOT DONE...
>> OOH!
>> AAH!
>> YAY!
>> YOU LITTLE MAGGOT!
>> I CAN SEE IT, THE FLOW
OF DEMONIC ENERGY.
>> AAH!
>> LOOK, IT'S THE MASTER'S
DEADLY TECHNIQUE!
>> HERE IT COMES!
>> IT'S THE WIND SCAR!
>> MEOW!
>> AAH!
>> IT'S NOT THE WIND SCAR
AT ALL, IT'S THE--
>> HEART SCAR!
>> OW!
>> OOH!
>> IT'S EVEN BETTER THAN
THE WIND SCAR.
>> EH, EH!
>> HEART SCAR!
>> YOU ARE TRULY AMAZING,
MASTER.
>> ALL OF YOU, JOIN IN!
>> YES, MASTER!
COME ON, YOU GUYS.
>> YEAH!
>> HEART SCAR!
>> YOU WERE TERRIFIC, MASTER.
>> MISTER.
>> MUSTARD.
>> MEW.
>> MEOW.
>> WE'VE LEARNED A GREAT DEAL
FROM YOU, MASTER SHIPPO.
>> LIKE YOUR FOX DEMON TECHNIQUE
THE HEART SCAR.
>> WE HOPE YOU'LL ALLOW US
TO USE IT.
>> USE IT IF YOU PLEASE.
>> WE WILL NOW HAVE MUCH MORE
CONFIDENCE IN OURSELVES.
>> AND CAN NOW GO LOOKING
FOR OUR MOTHER AND FATHER.
>> OUR TIME TOGETHER WAS SHORT,
BUT WE WILL NOT SOON FORGET YOU.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH, MASTER.
>> AND SO, IT IS TIME TO LEAVE.
>> HMM.
HMM?
>> [CRYING]
MISUKI!
>> BOY, THAT LITTLE BRAT.
NEXT TIME I SEE HIM, I'LL WHOOP
HIM FOR GOOD.
HUH?
>> HMM?
>> UH-OH.
WHAT...WHAT HAPPENED?
>> WELL, ANOTHER DEMON
VANQUISHED.
>> THAT WAS EASY.
>> [CHANTING]
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH,
YOU'VE DONE US A GREAT SERVICE.
>> OH, NOT AT ALL.
TO BE HONEST, THE DEMON WASN'T
ALL THAT MUCH OF A CHALLENGE.
IN FACT, I'M A LITTLE
DISAPPOINTED IT WAS OVER
SO QUICKLY.
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER, SHIPPO?
IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG?
>> I'M JUST FINE.
>> OH, COME ON, ARE YOU JUST
GRUMPY 'CAUSE YOU DIDN'T GET
TO SLAY THE DEMON?
>> LOOK!
I DON'T CARE ABOUT ANY OF THAT,
OK?
OH!
UHH...
UMM, HI THERE, MISUKI.
>> MM...
HMM.
>> ERR...ERR...
>> HEY, SHIPPO, WHAT'D YOU DO
TO THE POOR GIRL?
SHE SURE SEEMS MAD ABOUT
SOMETHING, HUH?
>> HEART SCAR!
>> OW!
OW!
HEY, WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
THIS REALLY HURTS!
>> SO, WHAT'S ALL THAT ABOUT?
>> WHO KNOWS.
>> ANOTHER WAY IN WHICH THE
GREAT BUDDHA TESTS OUR PATIENCE.
>> HUH.
>> TAKE THIS, HEART SCAR!
>> AAH!
>> MISUKI!
>> UHH, I CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT MIROKU.
>> SANGO, IS THERE REALLY
NOTHING BETWEEN YOU AND MIROKU?
>> UH-HUH...WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
>> YOU GUYS WERE ALONE
ON MT. HAKUREI.
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN BETWEEN
YOU TWO?
>> HOW COULD YOU EVEN ASK THAT,
KAGOME?
MIROKU AND I DON'T HAVE THAT
KIND OF RELATIONSHIP.
>> I THINK MIROKU HAS FEELINGS
FOR YOU, SANGO.
>> NEXT, ON "INUYASHA..."
TRAP OF THE CURSED WALL HANGING.
>> WELL, THEY SAY HONEST WORDS
COME OUT AT A TIME OF CRISIS.