- INUYASHA DEFEATED GOSHINKI,
THE DEMON CREATED
FROM NARAKU'S BODY.
KAIJINBO USED ITS FANGS TO FORGE
THE EVIL SWORD TOKIJIN,
WHICH HE THEN WIELDED
AGAINST INUYASHA.
HIS STRANGE EYES
AND ACTIONS CONVINCED US
THAT HE WAS POSSESSED
BY THE WICKED SWORD.
- PLAYTIME IS OVER.
- YOU SHOULD HAVE KILLED ME
WHILE YOU HAD THE CHANCE...
BEFORE I BECAME A DEMON AGAIN.
- I'LL SLICE YOU
IN HALF, INUYASHA!
ARRGH!
- DAMN THAT OLD MAN!
[GASPS]
[GROWLING]
- IT'S A DRAW!
[SHIPPO GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
- I'M NOT GOING
TO STAND FOR ANY DRAW.
THE TOKIJIN IS STRONG ALL RIGHT,
BUT KAIJINBO DOESN'T
KNOW HOW TO HANDLE IT.
I COULD HAVE DONE HIM
IN ALREADY IF TETSUSAIGA
DIDN'T WEIGH SO MUCH.
WHAT THE HELL WAS
TOTOSAI THINKING,
MAKING IT SO BLOODY HEAVY?
- PATHETIC!
YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE THE STRENGTH
TO HOLD UP YOUR OWN SWORD!
- DAMN IT!
- PREPARE YOURSELF!
THIS TIME,
YOU'LL MEET YOUR MAKER!
- NOT IF I CAN HELP IT!
ARRGH!
[GRUNTING]
[LAUGHS]
- PATHETIC, TOTOSAI!
I WOULD HAVE EXPECTED
MUCH BETTER FROM--
[GASPING]
- INCREDIBLE!
- YES.
THE SWORD HELD UP, BUT
KAIJINBO HIMSELF WAS UNABLE
TO WITHSTAND ITS POWER.
THE VERY SWORD HE FORGED
OVERPOWERED HIM.
THE WRETCHED FOOL DESERVED IT.
[PANTING]
[GROWLS]
- TOTOSAI,
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU!
- SOMETHING ABOUT THE SWORD
YOU DON'T CARE FOR?
- HOW IN THE HELL
DO YOU FIGURE I CAN CARRY
AROUND SUCH A HEAVY SWORD?
ONE THRUST AND I NEED
TO STOP AND REST!
- DO YOU WISH TO KNOW HOW TO
HANDLE THE HEAVY TETSUSAIGA?
- HUH?
- YOU MEAN,
THERE'S A WAY TO DO IT?
- AND IT'S SIMPLE.
- HMM.
[WIND RUSTLING]
- YOU AREN'T GOING TO TELL ME
THAT THE ANSWER
IS IN BUILDING UP
MY OWN STRENGTH, ARE YOU?
[GASPS]
- OH!
- I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN!
- THE OLD GUY SHOULDN'T
HAVE EVEN BROUGHT IT UP.
- MM-HMM!
- STRANGE THAT THE EVIL
AURA AROUND THE SWORD
STILL HASN'T DISSIPATED.
- INDEED.
NO! THE EVIL WON'T
ALLOW ME TO EXTRACT IT!
WHO COULD HAVE COMMISSIONED
KAIJINBO TO FORGE SUCH A SWORD?
- WE'LL HAVE TO CONSTRUCT
A BARRIER AROUND TOKIJIN
TO CONTAIN THE AURA.
OTHERWISE, WE WON'T BE ABLE
TO CONTROL ITS EVIL.
- MIROKU, CAN'T YOU PUT SOME
KIND OF SACRED SPELL ON IT?
- THE AURA'S TOO STRONG.
I'M NOT SURE ANY
OF MY SPELLS WOULD BE ABLE
TO SEAL IT COMPLETELY.
- WHAT ABOUT YOUR IDEA
TO CREATE A BARRIER, THEN?
- EASIER SAID THAN DONE.
WE'LL NEED TO HIRE MEN TO BUILD
IT, AND THAT REQUIRES MONEY,
WHICH WE'RE SADLY LACKING.
- THEN MAKE SOME MONEY WITH
YOUR FAKE FORTUNE-TELLING.
- I MAKE AN HONEST LIVING,
I'LL HAVE YOU KNOW!
- YOUR JOB AS A MONK IS TO HELP
PEOPLE, SO HOW ABOUT HELPING US?
- POINT TAKEN.
IF I DO AGREE TO THIS, I'LL NEED
TO KEEP SOME OF THE MONEY
TO ENTERTAIN MYSELF
WITH THE LADIES.
I MAY NOT MAKE
AS MUCH AS WE NEED.
HMM.
- COULDN'T YOU FORGET
THE LADIES JUST THIS ONCE?
- I'VE HEARD MORE
THAN I NEED TO.
WE'RE WASTING TIME HERE.
I'LL USE TETSUSAIGA
TO SMASH IT TO BITS.
[GRUNTS]
WHAT?
AAH! UGH!
- IS TOKIJIN UNBREAKABLE?
- ITS EVIL POWER
IS AWESOME.
- ALMOST AS IF IT'S ALIVE.
- WHO DO YOU THINK
ASKED KAIJINBO TO MAKE IT
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
- WE CAN TALK ABOUT THAT
LATER, BUT RIGHT NOW,
WE SHOULD DISTANCE
OURSELVES FROM IT.
- MMM.
- YOU MEAN YOU WANT US TO RUN?
ANYONE CAPABLE OF DRAWING
OUT A SWORD OF SUCH EVIL
WOULD HAVE ENORMOUS POWER.
YOU'RE NO MATCH AT PRESENT.
- HMPH!
I'M WAITING HERE.
- INUYASHA.
- BUT IF YOU STAY BY THE SWORD,
YOU MIGHT BE IN DANGER.
- HE'S RIGHT.
IT'S WISER TO DISTANCE
YOURSELF FOR NOW.
- NO.
DO WHAT YOU WANT,
BUT I'M NOT GOING TO MOVE
A SINGLE MUSCLE.
[SIGHS]
- KAGOME, COME HERE A MOMENT.
KNOWING INUYASHA'S CHARACTER,
HE REALLY ISN'T VERY LIKELY
TO MOVE AWAY FROM THE SWORD.
I SUGGEST WE STAY NEAR
AND KEEP WATCH OVER HIM.
- OK.
- WE'LL WAIT FOR ONE ENTIRE DAY,
WHEN HE'S CALMED DOWN SOMEWHAT.
TOMORROW MORNING, IF HE STILL
INSISTS ON STAYING BY THE SWORD,
THEN YOU CAN USE YOUR COMMAND ON
HIM, KAGOME, TO MAKE HIM SIT.
I'LL THEN STEAL UP
FROM BEHIND HIM
AND STRIKE HIM HARD
WITH MY STAFF,
KNOCKING HIM UNCONSCIOUS.
AND THAT'S WHEN WE WILL GATHER
HIM UP AND FLEE FROM THIS PLACE.
- ISN'T THAT GOING
A LITTLE OVERBOARD?
- PERHAPS, BUT DRASTIC TIMES
CALL FOR DRASTIC MEASURES.
- ALL RIGHT.
LET'S DO IT THEN.
- TILL TOMORROW MORNING.
- I WONDER IF I SAID SOMETHING
THAT I SHOULDN'T HAVE SAID.
[WIND RUSTLING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
- HMM.
[FIRE CRACKLING]
[SIGH]
- WHAT COULD BE TAKING
LORD SESSHOMARU SO LONG?
[GASPS]
- THAT FOOL KAIJINBO!
WHERE IN THE WORLD COULD HE HAVE
GOTTEN TO WITH YOUR SWORD?
- LORD SESSHOMARU!
[LAUGHS]
- STOP, RIN.
DO NOT MOVE.
[GASPS]
- HMM.
- A WOMAN.
- [SNIFFING]
I KNOW THAT SCENT.
SHE SMELLS MUCH LIKE
THE STRANGE BEAST THAT OFFERED
TO LEND YOU
THE SEVERED HUMAN ARM.
THE DEMON THAT DISGUISED HIMSELF
WITH A BABOON PALATE.
HIS WRETCHED PLAN TOOK US
TO HELL AND BACK.
CURSE HIM!
YOUR ARM WAS ALMOST BURNED OFF!
AND I WAS BEATEN
TO A PULP BY THAT MONK!
OH, SIMPLY RECALLING
THAT INCIDENT MAKES ME ILL!
- I RECALL THE SCENT.
IT IS THE SAME AS THE BEAST
THAT ATTEMPTED TO TRAP ME,
THE ONE WHO IS KNOWN AS NARAKU.
- SO, YOU MUST BE INUYASHA'S
BROTHER SESSHOMARU.
YOU'RE VERY CLEVER.
I AM KAGURA,
THE WIND SORCERESS,
AN INCARNATION OF NARAKU.
- INCARNATION?
- CORRECT.
SESSHOMARU, THE FANGS YOU
DELIVERED TO KAIJINBO
TO MAKE YOUR SWORD
WERE THOSE A DEMON
CALLED GOSHINKI.
LIKE ME, HE WAS ALSO
CREATED FROM NARAKU.
- ALL VERY INTERESTING,
BUT DID YOU SEARCH ME OUT
TO SIMPLY TELL ME THIS?
- HMM.
- CAN YOU NOT DETECT ITS SCENT?
TOKIJIN REEKS
OF GOSHINKI'S AURA.
IT IS CLOSER THAN YOU THINK.
[GUST OF WIND]
YOU ARE THE SWORD'S
RIGHTFUL OWNER.
- I AM NOT SORRY
TO SEE HER LEAVE SO SOON.
I DON'T BELIEVE I'VE SEEN
SUCH AN ARROGANT WOMAN.
- RIN, YOU'RE FREE TO MOVE NOW.
- YES, MY LORD!
AHH!
[RIN STRETCHES AND LAUGHS]
- THE TOKIJIN.
- SPEAKING OF STRANGE WOMEN.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
- WOULD YOU GET OFF MY BACK?
STOP SAYING THE SAME
THING OVER AND OVER!
- HMM?
- I WILL NOT STOP
UNTIL I HAVE YOUR PROMISE!
YOU MUST VOW NEVER
TO ABANDON TETSUSAIGA AGAIN!
- HMPH!
- SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK
WE SHOULD DO, KAGOME?
- HUH?
- I'VE BEEN THINKING.
PERHAPS I SHOULD COME RIGHT OUT
AND TELL INUYASHA THE TRUTH.
- THE TRUTH.
ABOUT HIS SWORD?
THAT TETSUSAIGA KEEPS INUYASHA'S
DEMON ASPECT LOCKED INSIDE HIM?
- YES.
HE DOESN'T KNOW THAT, WHICH IS
WHY HE ABANDONS IT SOMETIMES.
- MM-HMM.
INUYASHA TRANSFORMED WHILE HE
WAS TRYING TO KILL GOSHINKI.
MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT AND WE SHOULD
TELL HIM ABOUT TETSUSAIGA.
- YOU MUST NOT TELL HIM!
- MYOGA, IT'S YOU.
- YOU KNOW WHAT
MASTER INUYASHA IS LIKE.
IF HE LEARNS THE SECRET,
HE'LL SURELY ABANDON THE SWORD
AND COME TO RELY ON HIS
TRANSFORMED CLAWS AND FANGS.
- YES.
I SUPPOSE HE'LL
FIND THEM ADDICTIVE.
- OF COURSE.
AFTER ALL, INUYASHA IS
A SIMPLETON AT HEART, REMEMBER?
- MM-HMM, WITHOUT A DOUBT.
- HMM.
- HUH?
- YOU CERTAINLY
KEEP YOURSELF BUSY.
CHANGING INTO A HUMAN ONE
MINUTE, A GOBLIN THE NEXT.
- I'M A DEMON, NOT A GOBLIN.
IT'S NOT EXACTLY LIKE I HAVE
ANY IDEA WHAT'S GOING ON HERE.
- DON'T YOU KNOW
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
YOU REALLY ARE DIMWITTED!
- HMPH!
- TOTOSAI!
- WHAT'S HE GOING TO SAY?
- NOT THE SECRET!
- MYOGA TOLD ME THAT
YOU TRANSFORM INTO A FULL DEMON
WHEN YOU'RE ON
THE VERGE OF DYING.
THAT'S NOT TOO
SURPRISING, REALLY,
SEEING AS YOU ARE A HALF-DEMON.
BUT IF YOU ASK ME,
YOUR STRENGTH DOESN'T LIE
IN YOUR DEMON NATURE.
AS I EXPLAINED TO YOU,
THE WEIGHT OF YOUR
REPAIRED TETSUSAIGA
COMES FROM THE FANG
I USED TO FORGE IT.
- HMM.
- ORIGINALLY, TETSUSAIGA
WAS FORGED FROM YOUR
FATHER'S FANGS ALONE.
IN OTHER WORDS, YOU ARE RELYING
ON YOUR FATHER TO PROTECT YOU.
BUT NOW TETSUSAIGA
IS DIFFERENT.
NOW YOU MUST MASTER
YOUR OWN FANG,
AND YOU MUST PROTECT YOURSELF.
[GASPS]
ONCE YOU MANAGE TO FREELY
WIELD THIS NEW TETSUSAIGA,
YOU WILL HAVE TRULY DISCOVERED
YOUR OWN STRENGTH.
- HMM.
[APPLAUSE]
HUH?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
IT IS JUST AS YOU
HAVE SAID, TOTOSAI.
- YEP, EXACTLY.
- YOU CAN DO IT, INUYASHA.
YOU'VE GOT THE WILLPOWER.
YOU CAN DO ANYTHING
YOU SET YOUR MIND TO.
- YEAH, I GUESS SO.
WHY DO I GET THIS FEELING
I'VE BEEN CONNED?
[THUNDER]
[WIND HOWLING]
HMM?
- [ROARING]
- [GROANING]
- [GASPING]
- SESSHOMARU.
- AAH! OH, NO! NOT HIM!
- WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- JUST WHAT I WOULD ASK YOU.
I'VE MERELY COME FOR THIS SWORD.
IT SEEMS THE DEMON
YOU KILLED WAS SO BITTER,
IT DESIRED REVENGE
EVEN AFTER ITS REMAINS
WERE FORGED INTO A SWORD.
- WHAT?
- HOW DOES HE KNOW THAT TOKIJIN
WAS CREATED FROM
GOSHINKI'S FANGS?
- IT MUST MEAN THAT--
- I WAS THE ONE WHO COMMISSIONED
KAIJINBO TO MAKE THIS SWORD.
[GASPING]
- SESSHOMARU,
YOU MUST NOT TOUCH TOKIJIN!
EVEN YOU WILL BE POSSESSED
BY THE SWORD'S EVIL AURA.
HEED MY WARNING,
I IMPLORE YOU!
- PATHETIC FOOL.
JUST WHO DO YOU TAKE ME FOR?
- THE EVIL AURA!
IT'S...DISSIPATING!
- THE EVIL AURA WAS
OVERTAKEN BY SESSHOMARU.
I DON'T CARE MUCH FOR HIM.
- HMM. I SEE THE SWORD HAS
CHOSEN ME AS ITS MASTER.
DRAW YOUR SWORD, INUYASHA.
THERE'S SOMETHING
I WISH TO VERIFY.
[WIND RUSTLING]
- SOMETHING ABOUT ME?
- DON'T DO IT, INUYASHA!
- WOULD YOU LET GO OF ME?
- DO YOU HONESTLY THINK
YOU CAN DEFEAT HIM?
- HUH.
I CAN'T EXACTLY TELL HIM TO COME
BACK WHEN I'M FINISHED TRAINING.
- PRECISELY.
COME AT ME, LITTLE BROTHER.
I'LL MAKE IT EASY.
I SHALL COME FOR YOU.
- HUH. YOU'RE GOING
TO REGRET THIS, SESSHOMARU!
OH, THIS THING IS WAY TOO HEAVY.
[GRUNTS]
AAH! AAH!
- THE BEST HE CAN DO
IS BLOCK THE ATTACK.
- HIS SWORD IS
TOO POWERFUL FOR HIM.
- THIS ISN'T LOOKING GOOD.
- IS THERE NO CHANCE THAT
INUYASHA CAN DEFEAT HIM?
- YEAH. HE STILL DOESN'T KNOW
HOW TO HANDLE TETSUSAIGA.
BESIDES, HE'S UP
AGAINST TOKIJIN,
A DANGEROUS SWORD
IN ANYONE'S HANDS,
AND NOW THAT IT'S BEING
WIELDED BY SESSHOMARU...
[GRUNTING]
- AW, DAMN IT TO HELL.
[GRUNTS]
- JUST AS I THOUGHT.
HIS SCENT IS
BUT THAT OF A HALF-DEMON.
WHEN HE DEFEATED GOSHINKI,
HIS BLOOD CHANGED FOR SURE.
WHAT COULD IT MEAN?
I MUST WITNESS HIS
TRANSFORMATION WITH MY OWN EYES.
- I'LL HAVE TO FINISH HIM
OFF WITH ONE BLOW.
OTHERWISE, I'LL BE KILLED.
[WIND RUSTLES]
- WHAT? HAVE YOU ALTERED
YOUR COMBAT STRATEGY?
USUALLY YOU CHARGE AT ME
BLINDLY WITH GREAT HASTE.
- HUH. WHATEVER YOU SAY.
ARRGH!
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
- AHH. TETSUSAIGA HAS
BECOME HEAVIER, I SEE.
- IT'S A LOT HEAVIER,
YOU STUPID JACKASS.
- HMPH. THE SWORD
IS TOO HEAVY FOR YOU.
YOU ARE BETTER OFF WITHOUT IT!
- AAH!
[GRUNTING]
- LOOK AT TETSUSAIGA!
- [GASPING]
INUYASHA!
- HE DOESN'T STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST HIS BROTHER!
- [SIGHS]
[GROWLING]
DAMN IT ALL!
- MASTER INUYASHA, HURRY
AND TAKE HOLD OF TETSUSAIGA!
- MYOGA, YOU AGAIN?
[SIGHS]
DON'T NEED IT.
- STOP! I'M WARNING YOU!
- ARRGH!
- COME BACK, INUYASHA!
- HE'S GOING TO FIGHT HIM
WITH HIS BARE HANDS!
- STOP!
YOU MUSTN'T BE SO RASH!
- I CAN'T USE THAT LUG
OF A SWORD, NOW, CAN I?
- I BEG OF YOU!
- SHUT UP AND STAY BACK!
- AAH!
- ARRGH!
AAH!
[GROANING AND SCREAMING]
- HE'S BEEN THROWN
BY THE POWER OF THE SWORD!
[PANTING]
- YOU BASTARD!
- I'VE SEEN ALL THAT I NEEDED.
DIE!
- LOOK OUT, INUYASHA!
HE'S COMING FOR YOU!
THAT SCENT AGAIN!
[GROWLING]
- INUYASHA.
OH, NO!
HE'S TRANSFORMED AGAIN!
- YOU PEOPLE TAKE INUYASHA
AND FLEE FROM HERE.
[GASPING]
- TOTOSAI.
- INUYASHA!
- KAGOME, NOW!
- SIT!
- AAH!
[SIZZLING]
- BUT, MY LORD,
WHY DID YOU NOT GO AFTER HIM?
HE WAS IN THE PALM
OF YOUR HANDS.
M-MASTER SESSHOMARU?
- TO THINK THAT
HE MADE ME, SESSHOMARU,
TREMBLE WITH FEAR
FOR EVEN A MOMENT.
[WIND WHISTLING]
INUYASHA, IN THAT INSTANT.
- HE'S STRONG.
HE MIGHT BE ABLE TO KILL NARAKU.
HMM.
[WIND GUSTS]
NARAKU HOLDS MY LIFE
IN HIS HANDS,
BUT I HAVE NO INTENTION
OF REMAINING A SERVANT FOREVER
TO THE LIKES OF HIM.
I AM THE WIND!
ONE DAY, I SHALL BE FREE!
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- WE MEET JUROMARU,
NARAKU'S FOURTH INCARNATION.
HE IS SO EXPRESSIONLESS,
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE TO TELL
WHERE HE'S LOOKING.
HE MOVES WITH SUCH
LIGHTNING SPEED,
EVEN INUYASHA'S
NO MATCH FOR HIM.
JUROMARU HAS AN OLDER BROTHER
NAMED KAGEROMARU,
AND THEY COME AT US
LIKE A TAG TEAM.
WE'VE GOT MIROKU AND SANGO
ON OUR SIDE, THOUGH,
AND EVEN KOGA COMES TO OUR AID.
NO WAY CAN WE LOSE.
NEXT TIME, "JUROMARU
AND KAGEROMARU."
SEE YOU SOON!