>> INUYASHA BROKE THROUGH
NARAKU'S BARRIER, BUT BEFORE
INUYASHA COULD FINISH HIM OFF,
NARAKU ESCAPED SERIOUSLY
INJURED.
THE ONLY REASON HE GOT AWAY WAS
BECAUSE HE RESORTED TO A DIRTY
TRICK--USING KOHAKU.
SURPRISINGLY, IT WAS SESSHOMARU
THAT SAVED KOHAKU.
NARAKU HAD DISAPPEARED, AND WE
WERE ACTUALLY GRATEFUL TO HAVE A
BIT OF A BREATHER, ESPECIALLY
INUYASHA.
SO ON WE GO, CONTINUING OUR
JOURNEY TO DESTROY NARAKU AND
GATHER ALL THE SHARDS OF THE
SACRED JEWEL.
>> MMM...
>> [BARKING]
>> [GRUNTING]
YOU BETTER BACK DOWN, OR I'LL
GET SERIOUS.
>> SHORT-TEMPERED AS ALWAYS.
>> HUH?
HMM?
>> HA HA HA!
>> WHO ARE YOU, AND WHY DID YOU
SEND YOUR WOLVES AFTER ME?
YOU GOT A BONE TO PICK WITH ME
OR SOMETHING?
>> ISN'T THAT AYAME, THE
GRANDDAUGHTER OF THE OLD
CHIEFTAIN?
>> YEAH, I THINK SO, BUT I HEARD
SHE WENT NORTH WITH THE ELDER
A LONG TIME AGO.
>> SHE MUST HAVE COME BACK,
THEN.
>> AYAME?
>> I CAME TO GIVE YOU GRAMPS'
MESSAGE.
>> WHAT MESSAGE?
>> YOU ARE GOING TO TAKE ME FOR
YOUR WIFE, JUST LIKE YOU
PROMISED, KOGA.
>> MY WIFE?
>> HUH?
>> YOU HAVE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS,
DON'T YOU?
WITH THOSE IN YOUR POSSESSION,
YOU'LL BE WORTHY OF RULING THE
CLAN, SO COME WITH ME, AND LET'S
GET MARRIED.
>> LISTEN, STOP JOKING AROUND.
WHY SHOULD I MARRY YOU?
>> UH, YOU DON'T REMEMBER?
>> REMEMBER WHAT?
>> KOGA, YOU PROMISED TO MARRY
ME WHEN I CAME DOWN FROM THE
NORTHERN MOUNTAINS.
>> KOGA, YOU MADE SUCH
A PROMISE?
>> HOW ARE YOU GOING TO BREAK
THIS TO KAGOME?
>> HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> GRAMPS TOLD ME TO BRING YOU
BACK--WITH FORCE, IF NECESSARY.
>> WE'RE GONNA FALL!
[BOTH SCREAMING]
>> KOGA, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> LET GO OF MY HAND!
GET LOST, WILL YOU?
>> DON'T LET HIM GET AWAY.
>> I ALREADY HAVE A FIANCEE
NAMED KAGOME WHO I'M
GONNA MARRY.
I WOULDN'T HAVE MADE ANY
PROMISES TO WED YOU.
>> AAH!
>> A FIANCEE?
KAGOME?
>> WAIT UP, KOGA!
>> DON'T TELL ME HE'S SERIOUSLY
FORGOTTEN.
>> [WOLVES HOWL]
>> HMM...
HE DID PROMISE...
ON THE LIGHT OF THE LUNAR
RAINBOW.
>> HEAR ANYTHING ABOUT WHERE
NARAKU WENT?
>> WE CHECKED EVERYWHERE.
>> WE ASKED ALL OVER, BUT THERE
WEREN'T EVEN ANY RUMORS
ABOUT NARAKU.
>> I SEE.
IT SEEMS INUYASHA HASN'T BEEN
ABLE TO PICK UP ANY SCENT OF
NARAKU, EITHER.
>> NOT A WHIFF.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT A DEMONIC
AURA THAT STRONG COULD DISAPPEAR
SO EASILY, THOUGH.
>> NOT MUCH WE CAN DO, I GUESS.
>> KAGOME, I DON'T SUPPOSE
YOU'VE BEEN ABLE TO SENSE THE
JEWEL SHARDS, EITHER.
>> NO, NOT AT ALL--
NOT EVEN A TWINGE.
>> NO SENSE GETTING
OVERLY WORRIED.
IF WE JUST KEEP COLLECTING THE
SACRED JEWEL SHARDS AS USUAL,
I'M SURE NARAKU WILL EVENTUALLY
COME AFTER THEM HIMSELF.
>> FORGET IT.
WE CAN'T JUST WAIT AROUND.
>> WHAT CHOICE DO WE HAVE?
>> HUH?
>> I WONDER HOW MANY MORE SHARDS
THERE ARE BESIDES THE ONES
THAT NARAKU ALREADY HAS IN HIS
POSSESSION.
>> WHO KNOWS?
>> [THINKING] I HAVE
3 SHARDS HERE.
THEN THERE'S THE ONE EMBEDDED IN
KOHAKU'S BACK.
AND KOGA HAS A COUPLE, TOO.
>> [SIGH]
>> [WHIMPERS]
>> IT WAS A LONG TIME AGO, BUT
IT'S STILL A PROMISE.
>> ALL RIGHT. DON'T OVERDO IT.
WHEN IT GETS TO BE TOO HARD,
DON'T YOU WORRY.
ONE DAY I'LL MAKE YOU MY WIFE,
AYAME.
>> HMM.
I WAS JUST A CHILD BACK THEN, SO
THERE'S NOT MUCH I CAN DO IF
KOGA DOESN'T REMEMBER.
MAYBE I SHOULD RETURN TO THE
MOUNTAINS.
>> MY TERRITORY IS BEING
OVERRUN.
WITHOUT THE SACRED JEWEL, WE
CANNOT OVERCOME THIS STRUGGLE.
FIND KOGA AND BRING HIM HERE AS
SOON AS YOU CAN.
>> HMM.
I CAN'T GIVE UP AND GO HOME NOW.
I'LL TRY AGAIN.
I'LL FIND HIM AND TRY ONE
MORE TIME.
>> [SNIFFS]
I DON'T LIKE THE LOOKS OF THIS
AT ALL.
[THINKING] THIS CASTLE REEKS
OF NARAKU'S SCENT, YET THERE'S
NO SIGN OF HIM AT ALL.
THIS GOUGE IN THE LAND...
>> KOGA, THE CASTLE
IS TOTALLY EMPTY.
>> LET'S GO.
>> HUH? WHERE TO?
>> WHERE ELSE?
WE'RE GOING TO FIND THAT MANGY
MUTT AND QUESTION HIM.
THAT STUPID MUTT SMELL IS ALL
OVER THE PLACE.
SOMETHING MUST HAVE HAPPENED
HERE BETWEEN HIM AND NARAKU.
>> I GET IT.
>> INUYASHA MIGHT KNOW
SOMETHING.
HEY, WAIT!
>> DON'T LEAVE US!
>> NARAKU ISN'T HERE, BUT IF
HE'S NEARBY, HE'S SURE TO COME
AFTER ME FOR THE SACRED JEWEL
SHARDS IN MY LEGS.
>> [BARKING]
[SCREECH]
>> [WOLVES HOWLING]
>> HMM.
I PICKED UP HIS SCENT, TOO.
KOGA WAS HERE NOT TOO LONG AGO.
FEEL THAT?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS ABOUT
THIS PLACE, BUT IT GIVES ME
THE CREEPS.
[RUMBLING]
WHAT WAS THAT?
AAH!
>> [GROWLING]
>> WHAT IS THAT THING?
>> [WOLVES YELP]
>> UHH!
WHAT IS THAT THING, AND WHY IS
IT AFTER ME?
GINTA, HAKKAKU.
>> OH, NO. IT'S AYAME!
>> WHAT IS SHE DOING HERE?
>> HOW SHOULD I KNOW?
>> HOLD IT RIGHT THERE.
WHAT WERE YOU TWO DOING IN THAT
CREEPY CASTLE?
WHERE'S KOGA?
AND WHAT'S WITH THAT DEMON?
>> DEMON?
AAH!
DID THAT NIGHTMARE COME OUT OF
NARAKU'S CASTLE?
>> NARAKU'S CASTLE?
>> YOU DON'T KNOW BECAUSE YOU'VE
BEEN IN THE MOUNTAINS
WITH THE ELDER.
JUST RECENTLY, OUR COMRADES IN
THE NORTH AND EAST WERE ALL
SLAUGHTERED.
>> YEAH.
A DEMON NAMED NARAKU
SLAYED THEM ALL.
>> KOGA HAS BEEN LOOKING FOR
NARAKU TO GET REVENGE.
>> I HAD NO IDEA.
>> [GINTA AND HAKKAKU SCREAM]
>> IT'S COMING AGAIN!
>> WHAT'S WRONG?
IS SOMETHING TROUBLING YOU,
KAGOME?
>> I SENSE THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> IT'S THAT WHIRLWIND.
>> THOUGHT I SMELLED SOMETHING.
NOW I'M STARTING TO RECOGNIZE
THE STENCH.
>> YOU'RE MAD ALREADY?
>> I'LL TEACH THAT SKINNY WOLF A
LESSON FOR COMING HERE TO FLIRT
WITH KAGOME!
>> INUYASHA!
>> UHH!
>> KOGA?
>> HELLO, KAGOME.
YOU MUST HAVE MISSED ME.
>> YEAH, SURE, RIGHT.
>> HEY, MUTT, WHERE'S NARAKU?
I KNOW YOU KNOW, SO FESS UP NOW.
>> IS THAT REALLY WHAT YOU CAME
HERE FOR?
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> THEN DON'T WASTE ANY TIME
FLIRTING AROUND WITH KAGOME!
>> HURRY UP AND ANSWER
MY QUESTION!
>> TAKE IT EASY, YOU TWO.
WE'RE STILL LOOKING FOR NARAKU
AS WELL.
>> THAT'S WHAT I DON'T
UNDERSTAND.
WHAT WOULD FORCE NARAKU TO
ABANDON HIS CASTLE AND RUN AWAY?
>> WANT TO KNOW THE TRUTH, WOLF?
IT'S BECAUSE I BUSTED THROUGH
NARAKU'S BARRIER WITH
THE TETSUSAIGA!
SHOCKED AT MY STRENGTH?
WELL, YOU SHOULD BE.
>> YOU MEAN YOU GOT THAT CLOSE
TO NARAKU?
AND YOU LET HIM GET AWAY
FROM YOU?
HOW STUPID CAN YOU GET?!
>> UH...
>> I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
IF I'D BEEN THERE, NARAKU WOULD
BE DEAD AND GONE BY NOW.
>> I'M NOT GONNA PUT UP
WITH THIS.
>> INUYASHA, CALM DOWN.
>> JUMPING TO DUMB CONCLUSIONS.
I'LL KILL HIM!
[THUNDER]
>> FEEL THAT?
>> THAT'S NARAKU'S SCENT.
[CREAKING]
>> KOGA!
THERE'S SOMETHING WEIRD--
>> NARAKU'S CASTLE!
>> HUH?
>> [GROWLING]
>> IT'S HUGE!
>> WHAT IS THAT THING?
>> ANOTHER NARAKU INCARNATION?
>> IT'S SOME KIND OF HAIR DEMON!
>> THAT'S WHAT WAS
IN THE CASTLE.
>> NO MISTAKE ABOUT IT.
AYAME SAW IT, TOO.
>> AYAME?
SHE WAS WITH YOU?
WHERE IS SHE?
WHAT HAPPENED TO HER?
>> WE LOST HER WHEN WE STARTED
RUNNING FROM THE DEMON.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
[THINKING] WHY DIDN'T I SENSE
THIS DEMON SOONER?
>> SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
>> STAY BACK, KAGOME.
THIS UGLY HAIR DEMON MUST BE
AFTER YOU AND YOUR JEWEL SHARDS.
>> OK.
>> YOU'RE A REAL EYESORE, DEMON,
BUT AT LEAST YOU CAN TALK.
TRY TALKING TO MY FIST,
HAIRBALL!
>> LOOK AT THAT BRUTE STRENGTH!
>> ANSWER ME.
WHERE'S NARAKU GONE TO?
KAGOME!
>> MUTT, YOU CAN TAKE CARE OF
THE DEMON.
I'LL GET KAGOME OUT OF HERE TO
SOMEPLACE SAFE.
>> HUH? HEY!
HE'S GOT SOME KIND OF NERVE,
I TELL YOU.
>> IT JUST FELL.
>> IT WASN'T TOO STRONG,
CONSIDERING IT WAS A DEMON
CREATED BY NARAKU.
>> THAT WAS NO ACCIDENT.
IT WENT OVER ON PURPOSE.
THAT THING'S AFTER THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARDS.
>> HEY, KOGA, WHERE ARE YOU
TAKING ME?
>> WHERE?
SOMEPLACE WHERE THE DEMON WON'T
COME AFTER US.
HUH?
>> KOGA!
>> AYAME!
>> AYAME?
>> KOGA, THAT GIRL IS A MORTAL,
IDIOT.
ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR MIND?
>> NO, AND I DON'T HAVE TIME TO
STAND AROUND GABBING.
KAGOME, RUN FOR IT.
>> HUH?
>> KAGOME?
LITTLE HUSSY!
THAT'S THE NAME OF THIS
SO-CALLED FIANCEE YOU MENTIONED.
>> FIANCEE?
WHOSE?
>> MY KOGA'S, THAT'S WHOSE!
>> KOGA, WHY DID YOU TELL HER
WE WERE ENGAGED?
>> 'CAUSE I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> YOU CAN'T DECIDE ON YOUR OWN.
>> I'M KOGA'S ONLY FIANCEE!
YOU CAN DROP DEAD!
>> AS IF YOUR TRICKS WOULD WORK
ON ME.
KEEP IT UP,
AND I'LL GET SERIOUS.
>> HOW COULD YOU FALL
FOR A MORTAL?
WHERE'S YOUR WOLF DEMON TRIBE
PRIDE?
>> LAY OFF!
I LOVE KAGOME.
YOU HAVE NO RIGHT TO LECTURE ME.
>> KAGOME!
>> YES?
WHAT?
>> I DON'T LIKE THIS!
YOUR NAME SOUNDS JUST LIKE MINE.
>> [THINKING] ONLY THE FINAL
SYLLABLE, "ME."
>> EVEN IF YOU WANTED TO MARRY
THAT GIRL, YOU CAN'T GO AGAINST
THE TRIBE'S CODE AND MARRY
A MORTAL.
>> THE ELDER'S RULES AND CODES
HAVE NOTHING TO DO WITH ME.
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK I SAID I'D
MARRY YOU, ANYWAY?
[GROWLS]
>> [GROWLS]
YOU PROMISED ME.
>> HUH?
>> ON THE NIGHT
OF THE LUNAR RAINBOW.
DON'T YOU REMEMBER AT ALL?
>> LUNAR RAINBOW?
>> LUNAR?
THE MOON COMES OUT AT NIGHT.
HOW CAN THERE BE RAINBOWS
AT NIGHT?
>> I WAS STILL ONLY A YOUNG GIRL
BACK THEN.
[PANTING AND CRYING]
UHH!
I GOT LOST NEAR THE NEST OF THE
BIRD OF PARADISE DEMONS.
I WAS ABOUT TO BE DEVOURED.
AAH!
OH.
>> COME ON OUT.
YOU'RE SAFE NOW.
>> HUH?
>> YOU KNOW, THE ELDER
IS WORRIED.
>> OH.
>> I GUESS IT'S NOT EASY BEING
THE ELDER'S GRANDDAUGHTER.
IS HE GOING TO THE NORTHERN
MOUNTAINS, TOO?
>> UH-HUH.
HE SAID HE WOULD TRAIN ME THERE.
>> I SEE.
YOU'RE GOING TO USE THAT FLOWER
IN TRAINING?
>> UH-HUH.
IT HAS THE SAME NAME AS ME, SO
I'M TAKING IT BACK TO THE
MOUNTAINS.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR
SAVING ME.
>> ALL RIGHT. DON'T OVERDO IT.
WHEN IT GETS TO BE TOO HARD,
DON'T YOU WORRY.
ONE DAY I'LL MAKE YOU MY WIFE,
AYAME.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH, WHEN YOU COME DOWN FROM
THE NORTHERN MOUNTAINS.
>> HMM.
LOOK!
A RAINBOW.
>> A LUNAR RAINBOW.
UH, ARE YOU POSITIVE?
ARE YOU SURE I SAID THAT AND NOT
SOMETHING ELSE?
>> IT'S SUCH A ROMANTIC STORY,
AND YOU DON'T REMEMBER?
>> I KEPT THOSE WORDS
IN MY HEART.
THEY WERE THE ONLY THING THAT
KEPT ME GOING THROUGH THE HARD
TRAINING IN THE MOUNTAINS.
>> HEY, KOGA!
HOW CAN YOU FORGET SUCH A
SERIOUS PROMISE?
YOU'RE DESPICABLE!
>> KAGOME...
♪ EVERY HEART ♪
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> STUPID INUYASHA!
YOU LET NARAKU ESCAPE!
>> YOU'RE THE STUPID ONE, KOGA.
YOU'RE ENGAGED TO MARRY AYAME,
AND YET YOU'RE STILL FLIRTING
WITH KAGOME.
>> I AM NOT ENGAGED!
>> GET A GRIP.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHO ARRANGED IT.
SHE'S GONNA BE YOUR BRIDE.
>> SHUT UP!
I'VE GOT MORE IMPORTANT THINGS
TO TAKE CARE OF.
NEXT TIME,
"KOGA'S BRIDE-TO-BE."
SORRY, AYAME.
THAT'S HOW IT GOES.
>> STOP THE ACT,
YOU STUPID WOLF.