>> IT ALL STARTED WITH THE
SACRED TREE.
>> FIGHTING AND SEARCHING FOR
OUR DREAMS.
>> A STRONG BOND FORMS BETWEEN
US.
>> A NEW HOPE, A BRIGHT FUTURE
BEGINS NOW.
>> NARAKU'S GREED LEADS US TO
THE FINAL SHARD AT THE BORDER
BETWEEN THIS WORLD AND THE NEXT.
SESSHOMARU ARRIVES TO FACE HIS
ENEMIES IN A FINAL BATTLE AT THE
GRAVESIDE OF INUYASHA'S FATHER.
>> THE FINAL JEWEL SHARD GUIDES
US.
>> ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE
WELL, A NEW DAY AWAITS.
"FEUDAL FAIRY TALE: INUYASHA."
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> IN PURSUIT OF NARAKU, WE
COME TO THE BORDER BETWEEN THIS
WORLD AND THE AFTERLIFE, AND
THAT'S WHERE WE MEET HOUSENKI,
WHO'S BEEN RESIDING INSIDE
INUYASHA'S FATHER.
>> ARRGH.
>> THERE'S NO MISTAKE THAT
HOUSENKI POSSESSES THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARD, BUT IT SEEMS HE
HAS NO INTENSION OF GIVING IT
TO US.
NOT ONLY THAT, THE SHARD INSIDE
HOUSENKI IS BEGINNING TO TURN
BLACK BECAUSE IT'S BEING
INFLUENCED BY NARAKU'S SHARDS.
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
>> WINDSCAR!
>> ARRGH!
>> I KNOW.
IF I CAN PURIFY THAT SHARD
SOMEHOW.
MY ARROW WILL PROBABLY WORK.
GO!
ALL RIGHT!
I GOT IT.
>> YOU'RE WASTING YOUR TIME.
>> I DIDN'T PURIFY THE SHARD.
>> KAGOME, AIM FOR THAT SAME
SPOT ONCE MORE.
>> WHY?
>> HURRY UP AND SHOOT.
>> ALL RIGHT. HANG ON.
>> JUST BECAUSE KAGOME'S ARROW
DIDN'T REACH THE SHARD DOESN'T
MEAN IT HAD NO EFFECT.
I'LL AIM FOR THE SAME SPOT.
WINDSCAR!
>> IT BROKE OPEN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
NOW I CAN GET THE SHARD.
>> YOU IMBECILES.
>> UNH!
>> INUYASHA!
>> YOU AND I, ALL OF US, WE'RE
NOTHING BUT PUPPETS MANIPULATED
BY THE BLACK JEWEL.
>> INUYASHA.
INUYASHA!
[ECHOING]
>> IN THIS REALM OF FIRE IS A
GATE THAT CONNECTS TO THE OTHER
SIDE.
OVER HERE.
>> WHERE? HERE?
>> LORD SESSHOMARU, TELL ME,
ARE YOU ABSOLUTELY CERTAIN WE
CAN TRUST THAT KAGURA?
SHE MAY BE LURING YOU INTO A
TRAP AGAIN.
>> BE SILENT.
I WAS TALKING TO THE TENSAIGA,
NOT TO YOU.
>> OH.
THE TENSAIGA.
>> LET'S GO.
>> HUH?
WAIT FOR ME, LORD SESSHOMARU.
>> INUYASHA, INUYASHA!
>> [SIGHS]
HE'S COME AT LAST, THE ONE WHO
POSSESSES THE BLACK JEWEL.
>> INUYASHA.
LET ME OFF.
I'M GOING TO LOOK FOR INUYASHA
ON FOOT.
SET ME DOWN.
YOU TRY AND FIND HIM, TOO.
>> KAGOME!
>> BE CAREFUL.
>> KAGOME, I SENSE AN EVIL AURA.
>> THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD, IT'S
COMING.
>> SO HAS INUYASHA MET HIS END?
I WITNESSED THE WHOLE THING.
>> WHAT?
>> NARAKU.
>> KAGOME, WE'RE IN TROUBLE!
>> EVEN IF I KEEP IT TOGETHER,
I DON'T THINK IT WILL HELP THIS
TIME.
>> NARAKU, IF YOU'VE BEEN
WATCHING, YOU SHOULD KNOW
BETTER.
INUYASHA WASN'T KILLED, NOT
EVEN CLOSE!
>> HEH HEH HEH!
>> NO WAY!
IT DIDN'T HAVE ANY EFFECT ON
HIM.
>> SO EVEN KAGOME'S SACRED
ARROW WAS UNABLE TO BREAK
THROUGH THE BARRIER.
>> YOU ARE THE ONE WHO
POSSESSES THE BLACK JEWEL?
>> HEH HEH HEH!
>> I'VE GOT A BAD FEELING ABOUT
THIS.
IT CERTAINLY IS STIFLING IN
HERE, ISN'T IT?
>> OK. THIS IS AS FAR AS I'M
GOING TO TAKE YOU.
I DON'T WANT TO GET INVOLVED IN
THIS.
>> HUH? WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY
THAT, KAGURA?
IS IT DANGEROUS UP AHEAD?
>> BE QUIET, FOOL.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO ASKED ME TO
SHOW YOU THE WAY.
>> OHH.
>> I WARNED YOU THAT I WOULDN'T
GUARANTEE YOUR SAFETY.
>> WAIT FOR ME, LORD SESSHOMARU!
>> THIS MUST BE THE GATE THAT
CONNECTS THIS WORLD WITH THE
AFTERLIFE.
SO.
>> DO YOU WISH TO PASS?
>> HUH?
AAH! WHO SPOKE JUST NOW?
THE STATUE?
>> DO YOU WISH TO PASS, OR DO
YOU NOT WISH TO PASS?
>> OF COURSE, WE WANT TO PASS.
THAT'S THE WHOLE REASON WE CAME
HERE.
>> THEN YOU SHALL PASS.
>> AAH!
OHH!
>> THE ONLY WAY TO PASS THAT
GATE IS TO ALLOW YOURSELF TO BE
KILLED BY THE GUARDIANS AND
BECOME ONE OF THE DEAD.
>> UNH!
HYAH!
>> EVEN IF GOZU AND MEZU WERE
BEATEN.
IF YOU FORCE THE GATE OPEN,
YOU'LL BE ENGULFED IN A STRANGE
LIGHT THAT WILL TURN YOU TO
STONE.
WHAT'S THIS?
AAH!
NOW WHAT WILL YOU DO,
SESSHOMARU?
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING, LORD
>> [GRUNTING]
DAMN IT!
HUH?
TETSUSAIGA.
STAY STILL, WOULD YOU?
I CAN STILL FIGHT?
NARAKU, I'M NEVER GONNA GIVE
IN, NOT UNTIL I DESTROY YOU.
>> HEH HEH HEH!
POOR HOUSENKI.
IT SEEMS YOU WERE QUITE
WEAKENED.
>> [SIGHS]
[MOANING]
>> HE WENT THROUGH THE BARRIER
AND NARAKU'S BODY.
>> I SEE.
I UNDERSTAND YOU WERE A GREAT
DEMON WHEN YOU WERE ALIVE.
I'M QUITE IMPRESSED AND
SURPRISED YOU STILL HAVE THE
POWER TO FIGHT ME OFF.
>> HE'S GONNA TAKE THE JEWEL
SHARD.
NOT ON MY WATCH YOU DON'T!
>> KAGOME'S ARROW!
UNH!
KAGOME, ARE YOU OK?
>> UH, YEAH.
THANK YOU.
HUH?
THE LIGHT FROM THE SHARD HAS
TURNED JET BLACK.
THE IMPURITY FROM THE JEWEL
SHARD IS SPREADING THROUGH
HOUSENKI'S BODY.
>> HA HA HA!
IT WOULD SEEM YOU HAVE HELPED
ME OUT IMMENSELY.
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD WAS
HIDDEN DEEP IN THE ARMOR OF
ADAMANT AND PROTECTED BY HIS
DEMONIC POWERS.
AS CORRUPT AS I AM, IT WAS EVEN
BEYOND MY REACH.
>> SO THE ONLY REASON YOU COULD
GET IT IS BECAUSE WE SHATTERED
HOUSENKI'S BODY?
>> HEH HEH HEH!
YOU BROKE OPEN HOUSENKI'S
ARMOR, AND HOUSENKI IN TURN
WOUNDED INUYASHA.
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD REACTED
TO ALL THAT HATRED AND BECAME
EVEN MORE TAINTED.
>> IN OTHER WORDS, YOU HAD THIS
WHOLE THING PLANNED IN ADVANCE.
>> YES. MY PLAN WORKED
PERFECTLY.
>> EERGH.
>> THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD WANTS
TO BECOME WHOLE.
>> WASN'T THAT THE WINDSCAR?
>> THAT MUST MEAN HE'S BACK!
>> INUYASHA!
>> MASTER INUYASHA!
>> THANK GOODNESS. HE'S ALL
RIGHT!
>> NARAKU, COME ON.
>> SO YOU'RE STILL ALIVE, ARE
YOU, INUYASHA?
ALTHOUGH FROM THE LOOKS OF IT,
YOU TOOK QUITE THE BEATING FROM
HOUSENKI.
>> YOU MADE THE MISTAKE OF YOUR
LIFE.
YOU GOT COCKY AND CAME CRAWLING
OUT OF YOUR HOLE.
THIS IS THE MOMENT I'VE BEEN
WAITING FOR.
>> THE RED TETSUSAIGA.
>> HE PLANS TO DRAW NARAKU
OUT OF HIS BARRIER.
>> YOU'RE A DEAD MAN, NARAKU!
>> THINK HE CAN DO IT?
IS THERE ANY CHANCE OF VICTORY
WITH THAT ATTACK?
>> WAIT A MINUTE.
>> I'LL BUST RIGHT THROUGH THE
THING!
>> EVEN THE RED TETSUSAIGA
WASN'T ENOUGH.
>> IT'S THE RED TETSUSAIGA THAT
BREAKS THROUGH BARRIERS.
>> HE DIDN'T.
HE COULDN'T BREAK THROUGH
HAKUDOUSHI'S BARRIER.
>> YOU DON'T GET ANY STRONGER,
DO YOU, INUYASHA?
AND YOU STILL DON'T UNDERSTAND.
EVEN THE TETSUSAIGA HAS NO
EFFECT ON ME.
THAT DULL SWORD IS TOTALLY
USELESS.
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU THINK.
WINDSCAR!
>> DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND THAT
THIS IS FUTILE?
>> THAT'S THE SAME TECHNIQUE HE
USED ON MOUNT HAKUREI.
>> YEAH, THE ONE THAT DEFLECTS
THE WINDSCAR.
>> IT'S OVER.
WINDSCAR!
>> UNH!
>> AAH!
>> KAGOME!
>> INUYASHA--THAT IDIOT!
HE SHOULDN'T LET NARAKU GET TO
HIM!
>> NOW WE'RE IN TROUBLE.
WE GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE.
>> YOU CAN BE SLICED TO BITS BY
THE VERY WINDSCAR YOU CREATED.
>> I'VE STILL GOT ONE MORE
THING I HAVEN'T TRIED.
FEEL THE SWIRLING ENERGIES OF
DEMONIC AURA.
THIS WILL FINISH YOU OFF.
BACKLASH WAVE!
>> HEH HEH HEH!
>> DID I GET HIM?
UNH!
[GROANING]
TETSUSAIGA.
>> INUYASHA!
>> MASTER INUYASHA!
>> IMPOSSIBLE.
THE BACKLASH WAVE DIDN'T WORK.
>> HEH HEH HEH!
INUYASHA, YOUR TIME HAS FINALLY
COME.
>> DAMN YOU, NARAKU.
>> ONLY THE DEAD CAN PASS
THROUGH THIS GATE.
THOSE WHO WISH TO PASS SHALL
FIRST DIE BY OUR HANDS.
>> HMM. INTERESTING.
>> AH. HE DID IT.
NOTHING'S IMPOSSIBLE FOR MY
LORD.
OHH!
>> IT IS FUTILE.
>> IT CAN'T BE.
>> SO EVEN SESSHOMARU WAS
UNABLE TO PASS.
>> WE CANNOT BE SLAIN BY A
SWORD OF THIS WORLD.
>> TENSAIGA.
SO IS THAT HOW IT IS?
THEN I WILL USE THE TENSAIGA TO
DESTROY THEM.
>> ONCE THE LIGHT OF THE GATE
HITS HIM, HE'LL TURN TO STONE.
>> YOU MAY PASS.
>> HE WHO WIELDS THE SWORD OF
THE NETHERWORLD.
>> THEY'RE KNEELING BEFORE HIM.
>> YOUR SWORD CUTS DOWN THOSE
WHO DO NOT BELONG IN THIS WORLD.
>> IT IS AS IF WE OURSELVES
HAVE BEEN CUT.
>> SO YOU WILL NOT ENGAGE IN A
NEEDLESS FIGHT?
VERY ADMIRABLE.
>> I KNEW IT.
SESSHOMARU'S THE ONLY ONE WHO
CAN KILL NARAKU.
>> HA HA HA!
INUYASHA, YOUR WINDSCAR, THE
BARRIER-BREAKING RED
TETSUSAIGA, AND EVEN YOUR
BACKLASH WAVE WERE ALL USELESS
AGAINST ME.
THERE IS NOTHING ELSE YOU CAN
USE.
YOU HAVE NOTHING LEFT TO
DESTROY ME.
YOUR PRECIOUS TETSUSAIGA IS
USELESS.
>> YOU KEEP TELLING YOURSELF
THAT.
THIS FIGHT AIN'T OVER YET.
>> LOOK. NARAKU IS TRYING TO
GET THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
>> HITA THROW!
>> YOU DID IT!
>> NICE SHOT, SANGO.
>> THAT MUST MEANS HE'S
VULNERABLE OUTSIDE THE BARRIER.
>> A MIASMA.
>> YOU'RE NOT SERIOUS.
>> OH, NO. THE MIASMA WILL HARM
INUYASHA IN HIS WEAKENED STATE.
>> [COUGHING]
>> HEH HEH HEH!
FINALLY, I HAVE IT IN MY GRASP,
THE LAST SHARD OF THE SACRED
JEWEL.
>> THE LAST SHARD?
UNH!
AAH!
>> I HAVE NO USE FOR YOU
ANYMORE.
>> YOU WON'T ESCAPE.
>> SAIMYOSHO!
>> MIROKU, YOU CAN'T USE THE
WIND TUNNEL.
>> HEH HEH HEH!
CHOOSE FOR YOURSELF.
WILL IT BE A QUICK DEATH FROM
SUCKING IN THE POISONOUS
SAIMYOSHO, OR WOULD YOU PREFER
TO STAY IN THIS GRAVEYARD AND
LIVE FOR ALL ETERNITY?
>> FOR ETERNITY?
>> IN THIS GRAVEYARD?
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT,
NARAKU?
>> THE RIVER OF BLOOD THAT YOU
AND I CROSSED HAS ALREADY
CEASED TO FLOW.
YOU CANNOT RETURN TO THE WORLD
OF MEN FROM WHENCE YOU CAME.
>> YOU SEE?
I TOLD YOU WE MIGHT NOT BE ABLE
TO RETURN.
>> YOU SAY THE PATH IS CLOSED,
BUT I DOUBT IT.
I'M SURE YOU'RE GOING BACK.
>> YES, I SHALL.
I ALONE.
>> NARAKU'S SO SMUG.
I CAN'T TAKE MUCH MORE OF HIS
ATTITUDE.
NARAKU, DON'T THINK YOU'RE
GONNA GET AWAY.
>> DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND,
INUYASHA?
IT'S ALL OVER.
HMM?
HUH?
>> WHAT WAS THAT?
>> SESSHOMARU.
>> SESSHOMARU?
>> HUH?
>> HOW DID HE GET HERE?
SESSHOMARU, DID YOU RUSH OVER
TO SAVE YOUR KID BROTHER?
SUCH A KIND SIBLING, COMING TO
THE RESCUE.
>> WHAT'S SESSHOMARU DOING HERE?
HUH?
>> INUYASHA.
>> HUH?
>> COME ON.
INUYASHA!
>> WHY YOU?
WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
>> HOW DARE YOU, A HALF-DEMON,
DEFILE FATHER'S FINAL RESTING
PLACE?
>> OHH!
>> HMM.
VERMIN.
>> HEH HEH HEH.
>> LORD SESSHOMARU.
>> DAMN IT.
>> YOUNG ONE.
>> HUH?
>> DO YOU STILL HAVE THE
STRENGTH TO FIGHT?
>> HUH?
>> [MUSIC]
>> EACH TIME YOU CUT ME, THE
MIASMA WILL INCREASE, AND
EVENTUALLY, EVERYONE HERE WILL
PERISH.
>> I'M NOT SO SENTIMENTAL AS TO
HOLD BACK MY SWORD FOR THE SAKE
OF MERE HUMANS.
>> THAT'S WHAT I WAS AFRAID OF!
>> THE MIASMA IS COMING!
>> CUT ME!
>> HOUSENKI.
>> YOU MUST CUT ME IN ORDER TO
BREAK THROUGH NARAKU'S BARRIER.
>> NEXT TIME: "DESTROY NARAKU
WITH THE ADAMANT BARRAGE."
>> ONE SLASH OF MY SWORD, AND
I'LL PUT AN END TO THIS ONCE
AND FOR ALL!