>> [THINKING] IS IT POSSIBLE
THAT A DEMON CAN DUPLICATE
THE SACRED JEWEL?
>> WHAT'S HAPPENING?
HUH?
>> OH!
INUYASHA SHATTERED THE JEWEL IN
HIS HAND!
>> MMM. YOU FOOL.
THE SACRED JEWEL DOESN'T SHATTER
THAT EASILY.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT, INUYASHA.
BUT HOW COME I SENSED ITS
PRESENCE, THEN?
>> BECAUSE IT'S AN IMITATION OF
THE REAL SACRED JEWEL.
>> HMM?
>> IT WOULD SEEM THAT THERE IS A
DEMON TRYING TO CREATE A
DUPLICATE OF IT.
>> ARGH!
>> WIND TUNNEL!
>> THE JEWEL MAY BE INFERIOR TO
THE REAL SACRED JEWEL, BUT IT
STILL EMPOWERS DEMONS WITH MORE
STRENGTH.
>> AND UNFORTUNATELY FOR YOU,
IT'S TOXIC TO HUMANS.
>> IT'S AN EVIL SPIRIT.
THAT JEWEL WILL DEFILE THE HUMAN
SOUL.
>> IT'S PROBABLY THE POWER OF
THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AAH!
>> [SCREAMING]
>> HMM.
IT'S DAYBREAK.
>> [GROANING]
>> HUH.
YOU'VE FINALLY COME TO.
>> MMM.
WHAT HAPPENED TO ME, ANYWAY?
>> YOU WERE BURIED IN THE SOIL.
>> HUH?
>> WE HAD QUITE THE TIME DIGGING
YOU OUT.
>> YES, ESPECIALLY SINCE WE WERE
SOMEWHAT INJURED OURSELVES.
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO KAGOME?
AND INUYASHA?
>> KAGOME MUST HAVE BEEN
KIDNAPPED BY THAT BULL-DEMON
WHILE WE WERE STILL BURIED.
>> SHE'S KIDNAPPED?
>> YES.
INUYASHA HAS GONE ON AHEAD TO
TRY TO SEE IF HE CAN FIND HER.
>> WELL, MY FRIENDS, WE REALLY
SHOULD BE ON OUR WAY.
>> YES.
LET'S HURRY.
>> [THINKING] DAMN!
THE BULL'S SCENT WAS SO STRONG.
WHERE'D IT GO?
I DON'T SMELL KAGOME EITHER.
ALL THAT'S LEFT IS--
HUH?
>> [ROARING]
>> [GRUNTING]
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
>> [CACKLING]
IF WE KILL YOU, OROCHIDAYU WILL
GIVE US MORE SACRED JEWELS.
>> SO, YOU MUST DIE, HALF-DEMON!
>> [GRUNTING]
DIE, FILTHY WORMS!
HUH?
>> DON'T UNDERESTIMATE US.
>> I WARN YOU, WE POSSESS SACRED
JEWELS.
>> YOU DON'T SAY.
WELL, THEN, I'LL JUST DESTROY
YOU ALONG WITH YOUR FAKE JEWELS.
>> MMM...
[THINKING] WHERE AM I?
WE BATTLED THAT BULL-DEMON,
AND...WAIT A MINUTE.
WHERE IS EVERYONE?
>> [LAUGHING]
SIMPLY DELECTABLE.
THEY LOOK SO DELICIOUS.
>> [THINKING] IT'S ONE OF THOSE
FROG-DEMONS FROM BEFORE.
IT'S THAT BOY!
>> HMM?
AHH.
>> [PANTING]
[GASP]
WHO'S THAT?
IZUMO!
>> AH, KAGOME.
ARE YOU BY YOURSELF?
>> YEAH.
I'M SO GLAD YOUR OK.
>> THE DEMONS HAVE DEMANDED MY
ASSISTANCE.
THEY WANT TO USE MY KNOWLEDGE TO
CREATE A REAL SACRED JEWEL FOR
THEMSELVES, AND NOT MERELY A
REPLICA.
>> BUT IS THAT POSSIBLE?
>> IT WOULD APPEAR THAT THE
DEMONS HAVE ALSO BEEN STUDYING
UP ON THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> HEY, WAIT!
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS--
GOOD, THEY'RE STILL SAFE.
ALTHOUGH...
>> YOU ARE PROBABLY THINKING
THAT THERE IS NO ESCAPE FROM
HERE.
BOTH THEIR WORKPLACE AND THEIR
RESIDENCE ARE JUST UP AHEAD.
MAKE SURE YOU GET SOME REST.
>> WAIT!
THE VILLAGERS HAVE BEEN CAPTURED
BY THE TOAD-DEMON.
WE HAVE TO RESCUE THEM BEFORE HE
EATS THEIR SOULS.
>> WE HAVE NO WEAPONS TO DEFEND
OURSELVES.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE HAVE TO FIND SOMETHING.
[GASP]
THE TOAD-DEMON IS AFRAID OF
FIRE.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> [GROANING]
>> [SCREECHING]
>> AAH!
>> SHIPPO!
UNH!
THERE'S SO MANY OF THEM!
>> GO AFTER THEM...
GET YOUR REWARD.
>> IRON REAVER
SOUL STEALER!
UNH!
[PANTING]
[GROWLING]
DAMN!
>> [GROWLING]
>> THOSE WHO DISTINGUISH
THEMSELVES WILL BE REWARDED WITH
A REAL SACRED JEWEL.
>> [CHUCKLING]
>> I WAS TOLD TO LIVE IN THIS
HOUSE.
>> ARE YOU GOING TO OBEY THOSE
DEMONS?
>> IF THAT IS THE ONLY WAY FOR
ME TO STAY ALIVE, THEN IT IS MY
ONLY CHOICE.
>> I'M SURE INUYASHA WILL COME
TO RESCUE US ANYTIME.
>> HAVE YOU NO INTEREST AT ALL
IN THE SACRED JEWEL, KAGOME?
>> INTERESTED IN WHAT WAY?
>> YOU MUST HAVE AT LEAST ONE
WISH THAT YOU WANT THE SACRED
JEWEL TO GRANT.
>> HMM.
YEAH, I GUESS.
I WANT TO RETRIEVE THE SHARDS
THAT NARAKU HAS IN HIS
POSSESSION.
I HAVE TO DO THAT ON MY OWN,
THOUGH.
>> WE SHOULD CHECK INSIDE THE
MANSION.
WOULD YOU HELP ME?
>> YOU BET.
MAYBE WE COULD EVEN BUILD A
FIRE.
[GIGGLE]
>> [PANTING]
[THINKING] DAMN!
THERE'S NO END TO THIS.
>> FOUND HIM!
>> HUH?
>> [GROWLING]
>> HA! BRING IT ON!
>> [SCREECHING]
>> [CHATTERING]
>> I THINK THEY'VE GONE.
>> BUT WE CAN'T STAY HIDING HERE
LIKE THIS FOREVER.
>> I'M WORRIED ABOUT KAGOME.
>> SO AM I, SHIPPO.
BUT WE HAVE TO REST A LITTLE
WHILE OR WE'LL ALL COLLAPSE.
>> [GASP]
>> FOUND 'EM!
>> MIROKU!
>> LET'S GO.
SANGO.
>> OK.
>> ISN'T THERE ANYTHING USEFUL
AROUND HERE?
WHAT KIND OF DEMON'S MANSION IS
THIS?
EH?
>> [BIRD CAWING]
>> IZUMO?
>> THE SACRED JEWEL WAS BORN
FROM THE IMMENSE SPIRITUAL
POWERS OF A PRIESTESS NAMED
MIDORIKO.
>> [GASP] YES, I'VE HEARD THAT
BEFORE.
>> IT WAS CREATED DURING A
BATTLE BETWEEN MIDORIKO AND THE
DEMONS.
MIDORIKO TRIED TO DESTROY THE
DEMONS, AND THEY IN TURN TRIED
TO DESTROY HER.
THE SOULS OF THE TWO SIDES WERE
CAPTURED AND BECAME ONE.
>> YES?
>> THE PURE SOUL OF THE
PRIESTESS MIDORIKO AND THE EVIL
SOULS OF THE DEMONS ARE
INTERMINGLED IN THE SACRED
JEWEL.
THE IMITATION SACRED JEWELS ALSO
HAVE BOTH HUMAN AND DEMON SOULS
SEALED WITHIN THEM.
HOWEVER, THAT ALONE IS NOT
ENOUGH.
[SPEAKING JAPANESE]
COURAGE, FRIENDSHIP, KNOWLEDGE,
AND LOVE ARE NECESSARY IN ORDER
FOR THE SACRED JEWEL TO ATTAIN
TRUE POWER.
>> IZUMO?
AAH!
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER, KAGOME?
>> HUH!
>> THE BIRDS HAVE ALL GONE.
>> 'CAUSE IT'S GETTING DARK?
>> THE BIRDS HAVE NO FEAR OF THE
DARK.
IT'S ME.
I AM THE ONE WHO FEARS IT.
AND IN TURN, THOSE BIRDS FEAR
ME.
>> LISTEN, IZUMO.
>> IZUMO WAS THE NAME GIVEN TO
MY DECEASED FATHER.
HE WAS A SCHOLAR, EXCELLING IN
POETRY.
THE FLOWERS AND BIRDS WERE HIS
PASSION.
IZUMO WAS MY FATHER.
>> [GASP]
YOU MEAN...
>> THE NAME MY MOTHER GAVE ME IS
GYUOU.
THAT IS HOW I APPEAR DURING THE
DAY.
>> [GASP]
>> AND THIS IS HOW I LOOK AT
NIGHT.
>> YOU'RE A HALF-DEMON.
>> VERY CLEVER OF YOU, KAGOME.
AAH! AAH!
GET OFF ME.
AAH!
GET AWAY FROM ME!
BY DAY I AM THUS, A MAN LIKE MY
FATHER WAS.
BUT AT NIGHT I AM A DEMON LIKE
MY MOTHER.
I WILL CREATE A REAL SACRED
JEWEL TO FREE MYSELF FROM THIS
HALF-DEMON FATE.
>> SO YOU WERE THE ONE BEHIND
ALL THIS.
YOU'VE BEEN DECEIVING US ALL
ALONG.
>> I TRAVELED TO MANY COUNTRIES
TO LEARN ABOUT THE SACRED JEWEL,
AND THAT'S HOW I FOUND OUT ABOUT
YOU.
WITH YOUR SOULS, I CAN CREATE A
SACRED JEWEL.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY OUR
SOULS?
>> PRIESTESS!
YOUR SPIRIT AND THE JEWEL SHARDS
WILL FORM THE FOUNDATION OF THE
NEW SACRED JEWEL.
HOWEVER, THAT'S NOT ENOUGH.
SACRED JEWELS REQUIRE SOULS.
HENCE, I MUST COLLECT MORE
SPIRITS.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> THE SPIRIT OF COURAGE WILL
COME FROM THAT HALF-DEMON.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> THE SPIRIT OF KNOWLEDGE WILL
COME FROM THE MONK.
>> HIRAIKOTSU!
UNH!
>> THE SPIRIT OF LOVE WILL COME
FROM THE SLAYER.
>> MIROKU! SANGO!
RUN INTO THAT VALLEY AND HIDE!
>> AND THE SPIRIT OF FRIENDSHIP
WILL COME FROM THE LITTLE
FOX-DEMON.
THE 4 SPIRITS WILL COME TO
DEFINE GOOD, AND I SHALL CREATE
THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> I WON'T LET YOU DO IT.
YOU CAN'T TREAT US LIKE
MATERIALS TO MAKE YOUR JEWEL
WITH.
>> YES, PRIESTESS.
FIGHT, RESIST, AND MAKE YOUR
SOUL GROW EVEN STRONGER.
ONLY VULTURES WILL COME NEAR
THIS ABOMINABLE BODY.
BIRDS TAKE FLIGHT AT THE SIGHT
OF ME.
FLOWERS WILT FROM MY BREATH.
I'M SICK OF IT!
>> [GASP]
>> WITH THE POWER OF THE SACRED
JEWEL, I WILL POSSESS EVERYTHING
THAT IS BEAUTIFUL IN THIS WORLD.
>> WHAT EXACTLY ARE YOU AFTER?
>> ONCE I HAVE THE SACRED JEWEL,
I WILL BECOME FULLY HUMAN.
THEN I WILL ABANDON THIS SOUL.
>> [PANTING]
OUT OF THE WAY!
>> [SCREECHING]
>> MOVE IT!
KAGOME!
WHERE ARE YOU?
>> [PANTING]
>> THERE IS NO ESCAPE FROM ME,
KAGOME.
>> KAGOME!
>> HUH!
>> KAGOME, YOU'RE OK.
>> NO!
GET BACK!
STAY AWAY!
>> WE'RE HERE TO RESCUE YOU.
>> HUH?
AAH!
[GRUNTING]
>> MIROKU!
>> HE'S TRAPPED.
HUH?
[GRUNTING]
>> NO!
>> SHIPPO, RUN FOR IT!
>> AAH!
>> SHIPPO, NO!
>> HEH HEH HEH.
>> KIRARA.
>> GET HER.
>> DIE!
[GRUNTING AND GROANING]
>> HUH?
THAT'S KAGOME!
>> AAH! AAH!
[GRUNTING]
>> KAGOME!
>> [GRUNTING]
>> SO, THIS IS WHERE THE DEMONS
HAVE BEEN HIDING.
>> INUYASHA, THERE'S MORE OF
THEM BEHIND YOU.
>> HUH?
>> [GROWLING AND SPITTING]
>> [GROAN]
WHO'S GONNA TAKE ME ON NEXT?
>> HUH?
>> DON'T JUST STAND THERE.
BREAK DOWN HIS DEFENSES.
BUT, GYUOU!
WHAT ABOUT OROCHIDAYU?
>> OROCHIDAYU IS DEAD.
NOW YOU MUST OBEY ME.
>> NOT ON YOUR LIFE, HALF-DEMON.
>> [THINKING] HALF-DEMON?
>> YOU'RE JUST A HALF-DEMON AND
YOU DARE ORDER US AROUND?
NOW THAT OROCHIDAYU IS GONE,
I REFUSE TO BE YOUR--
AAH!
>> GAMA, TAKE HIS SOUL
AND PRESERVE IT AT ONCE.
HURRY UP!
>> HUH.
DAMN BULL.
SO, YOU'RE BEHIND ALL OF THIS,
AND YOU'RE A HALF-DEMON AS WELL.
NOT THAT IT MAKES ANY
DIFFERENCE.
NOW, WHY DON'T YOU COME FOR ME?
>> BRING HIM TO HIS KNEES AND
RECEIVE THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> WIND SCAR!
>> AAH!
>> [GROWL]
>> PLEASE, LET EVERYONE GO.
>> NO.
I NEED THEIR SOULS TO CARRY OUT
MY PLANS, AND YOURS AS WELL.
>> TELL ME, WHICH SOUL DO YOU
HAVE NOW?
IZUMO'S?
OR IS IT GYUOU'S?
>> MY OWN SOUL IS NOW IN A STATE
OF UTTER CONFUSION.
THAT'S WHY WITH THE SACRED
JEWEL, I WILL OBTAIN A HUMAN
SOUL.
>> LISTEN TO ME, GYUOU.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO KILL US IN
THE PROCESS, YOU ARE NEVER GOING
TO BECOME HUMAN.
>> HUH? WHY NOT?
>> IT'S OBVIOUS.
THE JEWEL WILL BE TARNISHED BY
YOUR GREED.
>> SILENCE!
>> UNH!
>> WITH THE SACRED JEWEL, I CAN
BECOME AN UNDEFILED HUMAN BEING.
>> IZUMO, PLEASE!
YOU'VE GOTTA STOP THIS.
EVEN WHEN YOU'RE GYUOU ON THE
OUTSIDE, YOUR SOUL STILL BELONGS
TO IZUMO.
>> ENOUGH!
>> UNH!
AAH!
IZUMO!
>> I WILL ABANDON THIS BODY.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> INUYASHA!
>> ENOUGH ALREADY.
>> INUYASHA, YOUR COURAGE IS
NECESSARY.
I NEED IT IN ORDER TO SUCCEED.
AND IN ORDER TO GET YOU,
I WILL DO ANYTHING.
>> HUH?
HE SWALLOWED THEM.
>> [GASP]
>> [GROWL]
I WILL CREATE AN AUTHENTIC
SACRED JEWEL.
>> YOU ARE ONE STUBBORN BASTARD.
UNH!
>> HANG ON, MIROKU.
>> INUYASHA.
YOU MUST SHARE MY FEELINGS.
DON'T YOU DETEST YOUR HALF-DEMON
EXISTENCE?
DON'T DENY IT.
>> HALF-DEMON. HALF-DEMON.
I'VE HEARD ENOUGH.
I'M ME. I'M STRONG.
WHO CARES WHAT I LOOK LIKE?
>> WHAT? YOU WRETCH!
>> WHO ARE YOU CALLING WRETCH?
WIND SCAR!
>> AAH!
THE SACRED JEWEL.
I NEED THE JEWEL!
>> HUH, YEAH.
>> I MUST HAVE THE JEWEL BEFORE
DAY BREAKS.
>> COME ON.
PLEASE WAKE UP, MIROKU.
>> [GRUNT]
>> INUYASHA!
>> [ROAR]
>> [STRAINING]
>> THE SUN IS RISING.
NOT YET!
IT'S TOO EARLY!
HEAR ME, SUN.
I WILL CHANGE MY DESTINY.
REJECTED BY HUMANS, EVEN DEMONS
WOULDN'T ACCEPT ME.
ALL BECAUSE I WAS BORN A
HALF-DEMON.
>> UNH!
SO WHAT?
COULDN'T YOU HANDLE IT?
QUIT COMPLAINING...
UNH!
AND MAKE SOMETHING OF YOURSELF.
>> [ROARING]
DAMN YOU!
[WAILING]
THE SUN!
NOT YET!
PLEASE, JUST GRANT ME A FEW MORE
MOMENTS.
AAH!
PLEASE, SUN!
>> WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
>> THE IMITATION SACRED JEWEL.
[PANTING]
I REGRET IT.
>> IT'S HIM!
>> IZUMO WAS A HALF-DEMON.
>> HUH?
>> HE WAS GYUOU AT NIGHT AND A
HUMAN DURING THE DAY.
THE DEMONIC AURA IN THE
IMITATION SACRED JEWEL WAS TOO
TOXIC FOR HUMANS.
>> AAH!
OH...
KAGOME, AM I GOING TO DIE AS A
HUMAN?
>> IZUMO.
>> HEY, THANK YOU.
THANK YOU ALL.
>> HUH?
HMM.
>> HEY, WHAT'S THE MATTER,
KAGOME?
>> NOTHING.
BE RIGHT THERE.
>> [WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> THE MIASMA HAS GONE INSIDE MY
BODY!
THE TOXIC POISONS!
>> JAKEN HAS BEEN STUNG BY ONE
OF NARAKU'S POISONOUS INSECTS.
WE HAVE TO FIND THE ANTIDOTE
FLOWER OR JAKEN'S LIFE IS IN
DANGER.
>> HEAR ME, RIN.
I HAVE BEEN BLESSED TO ACCOMPANY
LORD SESSHOMARU ON HIS TRAVELS.
I CAN DIE IN PEACE.
>> NO, JAKEN.
DON'T DIE!
NEXT TIME, "JAKEN FALLS ILL."
>> OH, DEAR.
IS THIS REALLY THE END?