- [GRUNTING]
- [GASP]
- AAH! OH...
- NO, DON'T, KOHAKU!
HAH!
WHY DO YOU DO THIS, KOHAKU?
A WEB. A SPIDER WEB!
HE'S THE ONE.
[GRUNTING]
- SANGO, WHAT HAVE I DONE?
NO!
SANGO!
[GROANING]
- AAH!
- A WHITE BABOON?
- YES.
- IT'S NARAKU.
HE'S CLOSE BY.
- TELL ME EVERYTHING YOU SAW
AT THE VILLAGE OF THE SLAYERS.
- THE SLAIN BODIES
OF COUNTLESS VILLAGERS
AND THE HALF-DEMON
THAT ATTACKED THEM.
HIS NAME IS INUYASHA.
INUYASHA SEEKS THE POWER
OF THE SACRED JEWEL
TO TRANSFORM HIMSELF INTO
A FULL-FLEDGED DEMON.
- THE SHIKON JEWEL.
- HE MUST HAVE BELIEVED
THAT HE WOULD FIND THE JEWEL
AT THE VILLAGE
AND THUS ATTACKED IT.
- SANGO.
- RETURN MY WEAPON...
AND MY ARMOR.
I SHALL AVENGE MY VILLAGE...
AND DESTROY THIS INUYASHA
WHO HAS SLAIN MY KIN!
- WE CANNOT TRAVEL
ANY FURTHER BY HORSE.
[HORSE NEIGHING]
IS SANGO DEAD?
- [GRUNTS]
I WILL NOT DIE.
I WILL NOT DIE
UNTIL I KILL INUYASHA.
- HMM. GOOD.
BUT ARE YOU IN ANY CONDITION
TO FIGHT A DECENT BATTLE?
- [GROANING]
SLAYING DEMONS
IS MY SOLE DUTY IN LIFE.
- I ASSUME
YOU CANNOT BE DETERRED?
VERY WELL.
THEN I SHALL SEND NARAKU
WITH YOU.
HE IS MY ADVISOR
AND IS WELL VERSED
IN THE WAYS OF DEMONS.
HIS KNOWLEDGE
WILL PROVE USEFUL.
WHEN YOUR MISSION IS COMPLETE,
HEREUPON RETURN TO ME.
YOU HAVE LOST ALL OF YOUR FAMILY
AND FELLOW VILLAGERS.
I AM MUCH SADDENED FOR YOU
AND YOUR PLIGHT.
- [GRUNTING]
I WILL NEVER RETURN TO
THIS PLACE.
I DO NOT HAVE MUCH TIME LEFT.
PLEASE, BODY,
HOLD UP A LITTLE LONGER.
HOLD FAST UNTIL I CAN COMPLETE
MY FINAL TASK.
[RATTLING]
- SO THIS IS THE CAVE WHERE
THE SHIKON JEWEL WAS CREATED.
- YES.
WE ARE CURRENTLY HEADED TOWARDS
THE OUTSKIRTS OF THE VILLAGE,
TO THE LIMESTONE CAVE.
THIS VILLAGE ACTUALLY SERVED AS
A KIND OF FACTORY.
- FACTORY?
- YES. THEY MADE WEAPONS
AND ARMOR
FROM THE SKINS AND BONES OF
SLAIN DEMONS.
THE VILLAGERS THREW ALL
THE UNUSED PORTIONS INTO
THIS CAVERN.
- [GRUNTING]
- THIS PLACE IS FILLED WITH
A COLLECTION OF DEMON REMAINS.
IT IS FABLED THAT DEEP INSIDE
THIS PARTICULAR LIMESTONE CAVE
LIES THE CARCASS OF
AN ABSOLUTELY GARGANTUAN BEAST.
- HMM.
- THE SACRED JEWEL
FORMED HERE?
- YES, ACCORDING TO THE LOCAL
LEGEND, AT LEAST.
- GOOD WORK, MYOGA.
- THANK YOU FOR THE COMPLIMENT,
MASTER INUYASHA.
ANYTHING TO HELP.
I'M MORE THAN JUST A PARASITE.
- YEAH, TILL THE GOING
GETS ROUGH.
THEN YOUR BIG TALK ABOUT LOYALTY
AND COURAGE DRIES UP,
AND YOU TAKE OFF ON ME AGAIN.
- MASTER, HOW COULD
YOU DOUBT MY LOYALTY?
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
HOW COULD I?
- DO YOU THINK
WE SHOULD VENTURE IN?
- YEAH, DEFINITELY.
LET'S GO IN.
- WAIT! HOLD ON A MINUTE,
MASTER INUYASHA!
- WHAT NOW?
AAH!
AH! UNH!
- A STRONG BARRIER
HAS BEEN PLACED OVER
THE ENTRANCE OF THE CAVE
TO PREVENT TRESPASSERS
LIKE US FROM CASUALLY
WANDERING IN AND OUT.
- BE QUICKER WITH THAT KIND
OF INFORMATION NEXT TIME, OK?
- [PANTING]
- SANGO, WHAT HAVE I DONE?
NO!
SANGO!
- ARE YOU
IN GREAT PAIN, SANGO?
- I'M FINE.
- POOR THING.
YOU COULDN'T DIE EVEN IF
YOU WANTED TO, COULD YOU?
WOULD YOU CARE TO TRY THIS?
- BUT THAT'S A...
SACRED JEWEL SHARD!
HOW DID YOU GAIN
POSSESSION OF THAT?
WHERE DID YOU GET IT FROM?
- I'VE HAD IT
FOR A LONG TIME.
I'M WILLING TO
LEND IT TO YOU.
- TO--TO ME?
- I IMAGINE
YOU'VE COME TO BELIEVE
THAT THE SACRED JEWEL
IS ONLY USED FOR EVIL,
BUT IT MAY BE USED
FOR GOOD AS WELL.
- AARRRGGGHH!
UNH!
- INUYASHA?
- UHH! DAMN IT.
- YOU THINK IT'S HOPELESS?
- WELL, I CAN'T FORCE
MY WAY IN,
AND ANY OF THE VILLAGERS
WHO MIGHT HAVE KNOWN
HOW TO GET PAST THE BARRIER
ARE NOW GONE.
- NOT ALL OF THEM WERE KILLED.
- WHAT?
- I REMEMBER
THE BEST OF THEIR SLAYERS
WERE AT SOME CASTLE
DURING THE ATTACK.
- RIGHT.
THE DEMONS DECIMATED
THE VILLAGE
BECAUSE IT LACKED
THEIR MOST TALENTED SLAYERS.
OTHERWISE, THEIR ATTACK
WOULD HAVE BEEN EASILY THWARTED.
- GOT IT.
SO WE HAVE TO FIND OUT
WHERE THAT CASTLE IS
AND SEE IF THERE ARE
ANY SURVIVING SLAYERS
WHO CAN TELL US MORE
ABOUT THE SECRET OF
THE SACRED JEWEL.
HOPEFULLY, ONE OF THEM ALSO
KNOWS THE MAGIC TRICK FOR
ENTERING THIS STUPID CAVE.
LET'S GO.
WE DON'T HAVE ALL DAY.
HURRY UP, KAGOME,
OR WE'LL LEAVE YOU BEHIND.
- HUH?
WAIT UP! I'M COMING!
- UH, MYOGA,
A LITTLE HELP.
WHERE EXACTLY
IS THIS CASTLE?
- HUH? DON'T TELL ME
YOU'RE LOST.
MASTER,
WITH ALL DUE RESPECT,
I ASSUMED YOU KNEW
WHERE YOU WERE GOING.
- LISTEN, FLEA, YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO'S SUPPOSED TO KNOW.
I CAN'T THINK OF EVERYTHING.
- WHY NOT FOLLOW YOUR NOSE,
INUYASHA?
THE CASTLE CAN'T BE
TOO FAR AWAY.
YOU'RE A DEMON.
YOU SHOULD BE ABLE TO
SNIFF IT OUT FROM HERE.
- YEAH, WELL, I CAN'T REALLY GET
A WHIFF OF ANYTHING FROM HERE.
- [MEOWS]
- UH, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- AAH!
- ARE YOU INUYASHA?
I'VE COME TO GAIN MY REVENGE.
- OH, YEAH?
AND WHO ARE YOU?
- SANGO.
- IS SHE FROM THE VILLAGE?
- MASTER INUYASHA, TRUST ME.
YOU MUST NOT FIGHT HER.
- HERE IT COMES. YAAH!
- YOU'VE REALLY GOT TO
WORK ON YOUR TIMING.
[GRUNTING]
- THE TETSUSAIGA
IS BEING PUSHED BACK.
- INUYASHA!
- HEY, WHAT ARE YOU
COMING AFTER ME FOR?
- SILENCE!
I'M HERE TO AVENGE MY PEOPLE!
- UNH!
UNH!
MYOGA, WHAT'S SHE
TALKING ABOUT, ANYWAY?
- I HAVEN'T
THE FAINTEST IDEA.
BUT HERE IT COMES AGAIN!
- UHH!
- WE'VE GOT TO DO SOMETHING
ABOUT HER WEAPON.
- I AGREE.
WIND TUNNEL!
I GOT IT!
- MIROKU, LOOK OUT!
IT'S NARAKU'S INSECTS!
YOU'LL BE POISONED
IF YOU SUCK THEM IN!
- WHAT ARE THEY DOING HERE?
- WHAT? NO WAY!
NARAKU.
- INUYASHA,
SHE WILL DESTROY YOU,
SO YOU MIGHT AS WELL
ACCEPT YOUR FATE.
- KEEP DREAMING, MONKEY.
IT'S YOU THAT'S GOING DOWN!
[GRUNTING]
- I AM YOUR OPPONENT,
NOT HIM.
- IF YOU KEEP INTERFERING
LIKE THIS,
I'M GONNA HAVE TO
TAKE CARE OF YOU!
- JUST TRY IT!
MAYBE MY DEFENSELESS VILLAGE
WAS QUICK FOR YOU TO SLAUGHTER,
BUT I WON'T DIE SO EASILY.
- HEY, THAT SLAYER BELIEVES
INUYASHA ATTACKED HER VILLAGE.
- I BET NARAKU LIED TO HER
ABOUT THAT.
- HYAH!
- [GASP]
SHE HAS A SHIKON JEWEL SHARD
IN HER BACK!
- [GRUNTING]
NOW, BEFORE HER WEAPON
RETURNS.
- POISON POWDER!
- AAH! MIASMA!
- IT'S EASY TO OVERWHELM
THE DELICATE SENSES
OF A DOG-EARED MONGREL
LIKE YOU.
- I CAN'T GET CLOSE.
- HA! THE SLAYER WILL
FINISH HIM OFF IN NO TIME.
WELL, WELL,
IF IT ISN'T THE HOLY MONK.
- NARAKU, PREPARE TO DIE.
- MY APOLOGIES
FOR NOT OBLIGING YOU,
BUT ALL I SHALL PREPARE TO DO IS
GATHER THE JEWEL SHARDS.
- WHATEVER YOU'VE BEEN SCHEMING,
IT IS ALL OVER.
- HA!
- AH! HYAH! AAAAAHHHH!
- [GASP]
- HE DID IT!
AAH!
- HUH?
- KAGOME!
- AAH!
- HUH?
- HA HA HA HA!
- THIS SHARD
IS NOT FOR THE LIKES OF YOU.
NOW THAT I POSSESS IT,
THERE'S NO REASON TO LINGER.
- NOT WITHOUT A FIGHT,
NARAKU!
- I BID YOU FAREWELL.
- YOU'RE NOT GOING
ANYWHERE, NARAKU!
- UNH!
[COUGHING]
- SANGO, I WILL AWAIT YOU
AT THE CASTLE.
I TRUST YOU'LL NOT FAIL TO KILL
INUYASHA BEFORE YOU RETURN.
- CAN I REALLY TRUST NARAKU?
- [MEOWS]
- HUH?
KIRARA, YOU'RE STILL ALIVE!
- [MEOWS]
- KIRARA,
I WANT YOU TO FOLLOW HIM,
AND IF HE DOES
ANYTHING STRANGE, KILL HIM.
- [GROWLS]
[SNARLS]
- I WILL NOT LET YOU ESCAPE!
- COME BACK, NARAKU!
UNH!
- PREPARE TO FIGHT, INUYASHA,
OR DIE ON THE SPOT.
- LISTEN,
WHY DON'T YOU BACK OFF?
I'M NOT INTERESTED!
- I HAVE TO GET HIM NOW
WHILE I STILL HAVE
SOME LIFE LEFT IN ME.
HYAH!
- WILL YOU CUT IT OUT?!
- NO!
- NOT SO TOUGH NOW,
ARE YOU?
- POISON POWDER!
- UNH!
- AAH!
MY POISON SHIELDING MASK!
WHAT'S HE DOING?
HE--HE'S NOT TRYING
TO SAVE ME, IS HE?
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
- UHH!
- HE'S THE ONE
WHO ATTACKED MY VILLAGE.
- INUYASHA?
- AAH!
- YOU IDIOT,
HAVEN'T YOU REALIZED THAT MAYBE
NARAKU HAS BEEN TRICKING YOU?
GIVE IT UP!
I HAVEN'T EVEN GOT STARTED,
AND YOU'RE COVERED IN BLOOD.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I--I DIDN'T REALIZE
I LOST SO MUCH BLOOD.
I HAVEN'T FELT ANY PAIN
FROM MY WOUNDS.
- [PANTING]
- INUYASHA, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- I'LL LIVE.
- KOHAKU, ARE YOU AFRAID OF
BECOMING A SLAYER?
- N-NO, OF COURSE NOT.
I'M NOT AFRAID.
- OH, YEAH?
I'LL LET YOU IN ON
A LITTLE SECRET.
ALL OF US ARE JUST A LITTLE
AFRAID OF FIGHTING DEMONS.
- HUH? EVEN YOU, SANGO?
- YEP, AND NOT JUST ME,
BUT FATHER
AND ALL OF THE OTHERS, TOO.
BUT WE NEVER FIGHT ALONE.
WE'RE ALWAYS WITH SOMEONE.
WE FIGHT TOGETHER SIDE BY SIDE
WITH OUR FAMILY AND FRIENDS.
THE STRENGTH OF OUR NUMBERS
GIVES US OUR COURAGE.
- [GROANING]
- AAH!
- HELP ME, SANGO.
I'M SO AFRAID.
- KOHAKU.
- IS SHE DEAD?
- I THINK SHE JUST FAINTED.
SHE HAS A SACRED JEWEL SHARD
EMBEDDED IN HER BACK.
I CAN SEE IT.
- NO WONDER.
I COULD TELL FROM THE START
SHE WAS BADLY INJURED
FROM THE SMELL OF HER BLOOD.
NARAKU MUST HAVE USED
THE SACRED JEWEL
TO MANIPULATE HER INTO
FIGHTING ME TO THE DEATH.
- [PANTING]
YOU CAN'T LOSE ME
THAT EASILY!
HUH?
AH!
THANKS.
I APPRECIATE THE RIDE.
NARAKU!
WHAT'S THAT?
[GRUNTING]
- [SNARLING]
- AAH! UHH!
- [SNARLS]
- DO NOT TAKE ME
LIGHTLY, MONK.
- DAMN YOU, NARAKU!
- HEY, SANGO!
SANGO!
[NO AUDIO]
- I HAVE NO VOICE.
MY BODY WON'T MOVE.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH ME?
I'M BEING...CARRIED.
BY WHO?
IT'S YOU!
- SO YOU'RE CONSCIOUS.
- PUT ME DOWN!
WHAT ARE YOU UP TO?
- BE QUIET.
- IT'S OK.
WE'RE GOING AFTER NARAKU BECAUSE
HE STOLE A JEWEL SHARD FROM US.
- HE CALLED YOU SANGO, RIGHT?
WELL, SANGO,
YOU BUG ME ANYMORE,
AND I'LL DUMP YOU OFF
RIGHT HERE.
- WHAT?
- INUYASHA, WE'VE REALLY GOT TO
WORK ON YOUR PEOPLE SKILLS.
NO WONDER EVERYONE THINKS
YOU'RE RUDE.
HE PUTS ON A BIG TOUGH-GUY ACT
TO TRY AND HIDE THE FACT THAT
HE'S A TOTAL SOFTY UNDERNEATH.
- HUMPH. YOU WISH.
- SANGO, INUYASHA
AND THE REST OF US
DIDN'T WANT TO
LEAVE YOU BEHIND.
YOUR WOUNDS ARE DEEP.
- YOU'RE MYOGA.
- LET'S GET A MOVE ON.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA GET AWAY
WITH THIS, NARAKU!
- IS NARAKU'S APPEARANCE
AN ILLUSION?
- ILLUSION OR NOT,
IT IS TIME YOU FOUND OUT
FOR YOURSELF FIRSTHAND!
- [GRUNTING]
- NO MATTER HOW MUCH I STRIKE,
HE REVERTS BACK!
HE'S GONNA PIERCE
THROUGH ME!
- AAH!
MIROKU, WHAT THE HECK
ARE YOU DOING?
YOU'RE SUCH A USELESS MONK.
- INUYASHA, BEHIND YOU!
- SO, YOU'RE STILL ALIVE,
INUYASHA.
- HUH. IF YOU THINK A MERE HUMAN
CAN KILL ME, THINK AGAIN.
- THE LAST TIME I LOOKED,
YOU WERE LOSING TO
A WOUNDED SLAYER.
- SHUT UP!
ADMIT IT, NARAKU.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO TURNED THAT
PACK OF DEMONS ONTO THE VILLAGE
AND ANNIHILATED EVERYONE!
- ALL I DID WAS MENTION
TO THE DEMONS
THAT THE VILLAGE GUARD HAPPENED
TO BE THIN THAT DAY.
- HUH? IT WAS HIM!
- YOU WERE AFTER
THE JEWEL SHARDS
IN THE VILLAGE,
WEREN'T YOU?
- YOU'RE NOT AS SLOW
AS YOU LOOK, MONK.
THE VILLAGERS SHOULD HAVE
BEEN PREPARED TO DEFEND
SUCH VALUABLE BOUNTY.
- YOU COULD HAVE JUST
TAKEN THEM.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO KILL
EVERYBODY!
- NARAKU!
- SANGO?
- THE DEMONS IN THE CASTLE
AND THE DEMON SPIDER
WERE ALL PART OF YOUR TRAP,
WEREN'T THEY?
- TRAP? IS THAT WHAT YOU CALL
MY SIMPLE DIVERSIONS?
I THOUGHT THE SLAYERS
OF YOUR VILLAGE
COULD HANDLE
ANY SORT OF DEMON.
THEY LITERALLY DID NOT LIVE UP
TO THEIR BOASTS.
- DAMN YOU!
[GRUNTING]
- SANGO!
- FOOL.
NO USE IN ME LENDING YOU
THE SACRED JEWEL
IF ALL YOU DO IS
CHOOSE TO DEFY ME.
- SANGO!
- THE JEWEL SHARD WAS
SUPPRESSING MY PAIN.
NARAKU!
- HA! IT WOULD HAVE BEEN
EASIER FOR YOU TO DIE
BELIEVING THAT INUYASHA WAS
YOUR SWORN ENEMY, NOT ME.
- [GASPING]
F-FATHER...
- AAH! OH!
- KOHAKU...
- YOU REALLY LIKE
TO MESS AROUND WITH
PEOPLE'S FEELINGS,
DON'T YOU, YOU CREEP?!
- ARE YOU THINKING ABOUT KIKYO
WHEN YOU SAY THAT?
- YOU'LL PAY FOR THAT.
ARRGGH!
DAMN HIM.
AND GOOD RIDDANCE.
- IS THIS THE NARAKU
I WAS PURSUING?
NO. IT CAN'T BE.
[INSECTS BUZZING]
- UGH!
- THAT WAS TOO EASY.
HE COULDN'T HAVE HAD THE POWER
TO MAKE KIKYO AND ALL THOSE
OTHER PEOPLE SUFFER SO MUCH.
- INUYASHA, WATCH OUT!
- [GASP]
- HIS BODY IS MOVING
WITHOUT HIS HEAD ON!
- HA HA HA HA!
I WILL NOT DIE SO EASILY.
- IS THAT A TALKING HEAD,
OR AM I IMAGINING THINGS?
- HE JUST REVERTS BACK.
HE'S USING THE POWER
OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
I CAN USUALLY SEE
JEWEL SHARDS,
SO WHY DIDN'T I
NOTICE IT BEFORE?
- HE'S A DEMON,
AND I DIDN'T SENSE IT AT ALL.
EVEN NOW, I CAN'T SENSE
ANY DEMON SPIRIT IN HIM.
WAIT A MINUTE.
HOW CAN THAT BE POSSIBLE?
IT MUST MEAN...
INUYASHA, THAT'S NOT HIM!
IT'S A PUPPET!
- PUPPET?
- IN DEMON PUPPETRY,
THE MASTER CONTROLS THE PUPPET
WITH SOMETHING HIDDEN DEEP
INSIDE THE BODY.
HIS HEART!
AIM STRAIGHT FOR HIS HEART!
- HA HA!
YOU FIGURED IT OUT.
- HUMPH.
TAKE THIS. HYAH!
- HE DID IT!
- WHAT IS THAT?
- THIS IS DEMON PUPPETRY.
THE HAIR WRAPPED AROUND THIS
DOLL INSIDE BELONGS TO NARAKU.
- WELL, THAT WAS MORE THAN
A DOLL WE JUST FOUGHT.
- IT WAS A COUNTERFEIT NARAKU.
THE REAL NARAKU WAS PROBABLY
HIDING SOMEWHERE SAFE
WHILE CONTROLLING THIS PUPPET.
- MY LORD,
NEITHER THE GIRL SLAYER
NOR NARAKU HAVE RETURNED.
DO YOU THINK THEY ARE SLAIN?
- IT IS POSSIBLE.
CONTINUE A STRICT GUARD
AROUND THE CASTLE.
- YES, MY LORD.
- THIS CASTLE AND THIS BODY
HIDE MY TRUE IDENTITY.
I WILL USE THEM BOTH
TO GREAT SATISFACTION,
MY DEAR KAGAWAKE.
HA!
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- SHIKON MEANS "4 SOULS,"
BUT WHY IS IT IN A JEWEL FORM,
AND WHY DOES IT MAKE DEMONS
MORE POWERFUL?
DEEP INSIDE A CAVE
NEAR THE SLAYERS' VILLAGE
LIES THE MUMMIFIED REMAINS
OF A PRIESTESS
WHO DIED IN A BATTLE
CENTURIES AGO,
AND UNDER THE LIGHT
OF THE SHIKON JEWEL,
A GIANT DEMON AWAKENS.
NEXT TIME, "SECRET OF THE JEWEL
OF FOUR SOULS REVEALED."
SEE YOU SOON!