- LAST TIME,
I WAS PULLED INTO
A HIDDEN WELL
ON MY FAMILY'S SHRINE.
I'M JUST A GIRL
IN MIDDLE SCHOOL, OK?
NOTHING THAT WEIRD
HAS EVER HAPPENED TO ME.
THERE WAS A BOY, INUYASHA,
PINNED TO A TREE
WHEN I CAME OUT.
THE SPELL SHOULD HAVE
HELD FOREVER,
BUT SOMEHOW I BROKE IT.
NOW MONSTERS ARE AFTER
THE SACRED JEWEL OF 4 SOULS,
AND HERE I AM STUCK IN
THE FEUDAL AGE OF JAPAN.
- IRON REAPER SOUL STEALER!
- BUT HOW'D IT GET
INSIDE MY BODY?
WHY WOULD I HAVE A JEWEL
WANTED BY DEMONS?
- IF YOU HAND
THE JEWEL OVER RIGHT NOW,
I WONT HAVE TO START SHARPENING
MY CLAWS ON YOU.
- PAY NO HEED
TO INUYASHA, CHILD.
- THE SACRED JEWEL
MAKES MONSTERS MORE POWERFUL.
IS IT CURSED?
- I HATE HAVING TO WAIT,
AND I HATE THE SMELL OF YOU.
YOU WANT ME
TO SCRATCH YOUR BACK?
- YOU REALLY TRIED
TO HIT ME JUST NOW,
DIDN'T YOU?
- SHOOT HIM! QUICKLY!
[SHOUTING]
- HUH! WHO DO YOU PEOPLE
THINK I AM?
YOU THINK YOU CAN HURT ME
LIKE I DID THAT CENTIPEDE?
- LADY KAEDE,
METHINKS MAYHAP
THAT WE MIGHT HAVE CHANCED
THE CENTIPEDE.
- SOMEHOW I KNEW
THAT IT WOULD EVENTUALLY
COME TO THIS.
- PREPARE YOURSELF.
- PREPARE? FOR WHAT?
- HA! NOW IT'S MINE.
HMM?
WHAT THE HECK ARE THESE?
[GASPS]
- QUICKLY, CHILD!
THE WORD OF SUBJUGATION.
- HUH? WHAT WORD?
- IT MATTERS NOT.
YOUR WORD HAS POWER
TO HOLD HIS SPIRIT.
- HA!
HOW CAN YOU OVERPOWER ME
WHEN YOU CAN'T SIT UP!
- A WORD TO HOLD HIS SPIRIT?
BUT HOW WILL I KNOW
WHICH ONE?
SIT, BOY!
- HMM?
- SIT, BOY!
- UNH!
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
IT WORKED.
- WHAT THE HECK
IS THIS THING?
- I'M SORRY, INUYASHA,
BUT EVEN YOU LACK THE POWER
TO REMOVE IT.
- WE'LL SEE ABOUT THAT!
I'D COME UP THERE
AND FINISH YOU OFF,
IF YOU DIDN'T LOOK
HALF-DEAD ALREADY.
- THE WORD, PLEASE.
- SIT, BOY!
- WELL THEN,
SHALL WE HEAD HOME?
- THAT WAS EASY.
WISH I'D SAID IT
EARLIER.
- HOW'S THAT?
PERHAPS I'LL PUT MORE UNGENT
ON YOUR BELLY.
- I NOTICED
YOU'RE REBUILDING THE HOUSES
WRECKED BY
MISTRESS CENTIPEDE.
WHAT A PAIN.
- PAIN? YES--
AND JUST BEGINNING.
NOW THAT THE SACRED
SHIKON NO TAMA
IS BACK AMONG US,
FAR WORSE
THAN MISTRESS CENTIPEDE
WILL COME TO CLAIM IT.
- WORSE THAN YESTERDAY?
- AND NOT JUST DEMONS.
THERE ARE HUMANS WHOSE HEARTS
ARE MORE EVIL, STILL,
AND ONLY THE JEWEL
HAS THE POWER TO MAKE REAL
THEIR PETTY,
GRASPING AMBITIONS.
[GASPS]
- SPEAKING OF PETTY,
WHAT ARE YOU STILL DOING HERE?
- I'M WAITING
FOR THE JEWEL.
- WITH THE BEADS
AROUND HIS NECK,
HIS THREAT IS DIMINISHED.
IT IS PERHAPS THE ONLY WAY
WE CAN ALLOW HIM
SO CLOSE TO THE JEWEL.
- WHY DO YOU
WANT THE JEWEL ANYWAY?
IT SEEMS TO ME
YOU'RE STRONG ENOUGH
AS IT IS.
WHAT POWER
CAN THE JEWEL GIVE YOU
YOU DON'T ALREADY HAVE?
- AH, BUT HE'S JUST
HALF-DEMON.
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M SICK OF HEARING
SOME DRIED UP WITCH
I JUST MET
TALK LIKE SHE KNOWS ME.
- SO YE DON'T REMEMBER.
I THOUGHT AS MUCH.
I'M YOUNGER SISTER TO KIKYO,
SHE WHO BOUND YE
TO THE TREE--KAEDE.
- YOU'RE KAEDE?
SO YOU'RE THE BRAT, HUH?
50 YEARS HAVE PASSED
AND I HAVE GROWN OLD.
IF YOU'RE THIS OLD,
KIKYO MUST BE PUSHING 100.
I'M SURE GLAD
I DON'T GOTTA WORRY
ABOUT BEING OLD,
AT LEAST NOT FOR AWHILE.
- KIKYO DIDN'T WORRY, EITHER.
KIKYO DIED.
IT WAS ON THE SAME DAY
SHE SHOT YE WITH THE ARROW.
- GEE, SORRY TO HEAR IT--
NOT THAT I REALLY CARE
OR NOTHING.
IT'S ONE LESS THING
FOR ME TO WORRY ABOUT.
- I WOULDN'T LET MY GUARD DOWN
JUST YET, INUYASHA.
- I NOW KNOW THAT KAGOME
IS THE REINCARNATION
OF MY SISTER.
- HUH?
- AND IT ISN'T JUST BECAUSE
YE RESEMBLE HER.
- AAH!
STOP IT!
- THE JEWEL OF 4 SOULS
WAS IN YOUR BODY.
THAT ALONE IS PROOF ENOUGH.
IT'S UP TO YE NOW, CHILD,
TO TAKE OVER ITS PROTECTION.
- ME? PROTECTING THIS?
WHO AM I KIDDING?
- SHE'S THE REINCARNATION
OF WHO?
- YOU GOTTA ADMIT
THERE'S SOMETHING
OTHERWORLDLY ABOUT HER.
- ABOUT WHO?
- THEY'RE SAYING
THAT GIRL THERE
IS REALLY KIKYO.
- THAT'S LADY KIKYO,
FOR THOSE WHO RESPECT HER!
- ME, I KNEW
IT WAS LADY KIKYO ALL ALONG.
LADY KIKYO'S COME BACK
JUST AS SHE LEFT.
[MURMURING]
- I GOTTA GET OUT OF HERE.
- SHE DIED
AND I NEVER KNEW.
HMM?
- HEY, DON'T YOU WANT TO EAT?
- WHERE'D YOU GET
ALL THAT STUFF FROM?
- THE VILLAGERS
GAVE IT TO ME.
WHY NOT COME DOWN FROM THERE
AND HELP ME EAT IT?
- WHATEVER YOU'RE UP TO,
I AIN'T BUYING IT.
- BUYING WHAT?
LISTEN, IT'S FAIR TO SAY
YOU DON'T LIKE ME, RIGHT?
- WAY MORE THAN FAIR.
- WHATEVER.
IT'S NOT EVEN ME
YOU DISLIKE,
IT'S THIS KIKYO PERSON.
I'M NOT KIKYO, OK?
I'M KAGOME.
CAN'T WE JUST CALL A TRUCE?
- HA! I KNEW IT!
WHAT YOU DON'T GET IS THAT
I'M ONLY AFTER THE JEWEL.
YOU'RE JUST TRYING TO LURE ME
INTO A FALSE SENSE OF SECURITY.
- OH, REALLY?
THAT'S FUNNY,
CONSIDERING ALL I HAVE TO DO
TO MAKE YOU OBEY
IS SAY THE WORD "SIT."
WHOOPS. SORRY ABOUT THAT.
- OH, MAN.
- IT'S TWO DAYS NOW
THAT I'VE BEEN OVER HERE.
- GRANDPA...
SOTA, MOM...
THEY MUST BE SO WORRIED.
I GOTTA GET BACK
ONE WAY OR THE OTHER.
- THEY'VE ALL COME JUST BECAUSE
THEY SMELL THE JEWEL.
STINKIN' VULTURES.
[ROOSTER CROWS]
- INUYASHA'S FOREST.
A DRY WELL.
- IT'S HOW I CAME HERE
AFTER ALL.
THERE'S GOTTA BE
SOME KIND OF HINT
HOW TO GET HOME.
- KAGOME?
KAGOME?
- WE LOOKED EVERYWHERE,
BUT SHE'S NOT HERE.
- COULD IT BE
SHE'S GONE OFF ON HER OWN?
WE SPOKE OF THOSE
WHO SEEK THE SACRED JEWEL,
YET WE SPOKE
NOT NEARLY ENOUGH.
- THERE.
THAT'S THE WELL
I CAME OUT OF.
[SHOUTING]
- HA HA HA!
- OW!
- HEY, BOSS!
WE CAUGHT THE GIRL
JUST LIKE YOU SAID WE SHOULD.
- HA HA HA!
HER KIMONO'S SHORTER THAN MINE.
YOU GONNA CATCH COLD
IF YOU GO AROUND
IN THAT DRESS.
- DON'T DO THAT!
IT'LL RIP!
- WHAT'S THE MATTER,
PRINCESS?
OUR HANDS TOO DIRTY FOR YOU?
- MARRY ME
AND I'LL BUY YOU A NEW ONE.
- HEH HEH HEH.
- STOP LAUGHING.
- HAND OVER THE JEWEL,
RIGHT NOW.
[GASPS]
HA HA HA!
- HEY!
- HEY, BOSS,
TRY TAKING IT OFF
IN ONE SWING
LIKE A DANDELION.
- LET GO!
- STOP SQUIRMING.
- AAH!
WHAT DID YOU DO THAT FOR?
[NERVOUS CHUCKLING]
- BOSS! BOSS!
WHERE ARE YOU AIMING?
SHE'S WHO YOU WANT.
- WAIT! WAIT!
CAN'T YOU TELL
THERE'S SOMETHING WRONG
WITH YOUR BOSS?
NOW GET YOUR BUTTS IN GEAR,
OR NEXT IT'LL BE YOU TWO.
DO I HAVE TO TELL YOU
EVERYTHING?
AAH!
HERE I AM
IN FEUDAL JAPAN,
PLAYING "DUCK, DUCK, GOOSE"
WITH AN 8-FOOT TROLL.
- STUPID GIRL.
I DON'T CARE
WHERE SHE GOES,
BUT SHE TOOK THE JEWEL
WITH HER.
- ARE YOU OK?
- WE GOTTA GO AROUND.
IT'S BLOCKED.
- CAN YOU STAND?
- THANK YOU FOR SAVING ME.
THANK YOU.
- I WANT THE JEWEL.
GIVE IT TO ME.
- HE'S AFTER THE JEWEL.
I WISH I DIDN'T HAVE IT.
- AND NOT JUST DEMONS.
THERE ARE HUMANS WHO SEEK IT
TO MAKE REAL
THEIR PETTY,
GRASPING AMBITIONS.
- MAYBE I SHOULD HAVE
LISTENED...
BUT I'LL WORRY
ABOUT THAT LATER.
- HMM?
- THANKS FOR NOTHING.
THAT'S RIGHT.
TAKE HIM.
- JEWEL...
GIVE IT TO ME.
- THE WALL! PUSH IT OUT!
ALL AT ONCE!
- GOT IT.
SORRY, BOSS. NO GOOD.
- WHAT DID YOU JUST--
I'M NOT YOUR BOSS!
INUYASHA.
- WE'RE OUTTA HERE, BOSS!
- THANKS AGAIN.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU ACTUALLY CAME.
- IS IT SAFE?
WHERE'S THE JEWEL?
- JEWEL?
- OH, NO!
TELL ME YOU DID NOT
JUST SAY THAT.
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
OH, WHAT IS THAT SMELL?
IT'S LIKE ROTTING MEAT OR--
- WHAT'S THAT?
- HOW MUCH YOU WANT TO BET
THAT BIRD RIPPED
HIS LIVING HEART OUT
AND MADE ITSELF
A BLOODY NEST?
- I KNEW THERE WAS
SOMETHING WRONG.
THE BIRD MADE HIM A PUPPET.
- CARRION CROWS
DON'T FIGHT ON THEIR OWN
WHEN THERE'S
DEAD BODIES HANDY.
THEY AIN'T SO TOUGH,
BUT THEY'RE HELLA NASTY.
- IT'S GETTING AWAY.
AREN'T YOU GOING AFTER IT?
- MAYBE YOU HAVEN'T NOTICED,
BUT THE WORLD
IS FULL OF MONSTERS.
YOU WANT I SHOULD
GO AFTER 'EM ALL?
- BUT...
- NO BUT.
YOU WANT TO START
DOING THE FIGHTING?
BE MY GUEST.
IN THE MEANTIME,
WHERE'S THE JEW--
OH!
THAT STUPID CROW
IS MAKING OFF
WITH THE JEWEL.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
WHAT'S WRONG WITH--
GO AFTER HIM!
- COME ON!
- HEY!
- OH, NO, YOU DON'T.
- WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
HURRY UP AND SHOOT IT.
- SHOOT?
YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?
I'VE NEVER USED
A BOW IN MY LIFE.
- THE CROW LIVES
BY EATING HUMAN FLESH.
IF YOU THINK THAT'S BAD,
LET IT SWALLOW THE JEWEL.
- AAH! IT SWALLOWED IT!
FINE! I'LL TRY!
- THANK YOU.
AND AFTER
SHE TAKES OUT THE CROW,
IT'S HER TURN.
KIKYO WAS A MASTER ARCHER.
TAKE IT IN ONE SHOT.
- I TOLD YOU,
MY NAME'S KAGOME!
STILL, KIKYO,
GIVE ME YOUR STRENGTH.
HERE IT GOES.
WHAT THE--
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
THAT SHE WAS A MASTER ARCHER.
- SHE WAS.
IT'S YOU THAT'S THE KLUTZ.
SEE HOW BIG IT IS?
DO IT!
- OW!
- I DON'T CARE
WHAT THE OLD LADY SAYS.
YOU ARE NOT KIKYO,
YOU GOT THAT?
I AM SO OUT OF HERE.
- INUYASHA, WAIT!
- YAH!
SOMEBODY HELP!
- LOOKING FOR
YOUR NEXT MEAL ALREADY, HUH?
YOU FORGET.
YOU FIRST GOTTA
GET THROUGH ME.
- INUYASHA, NO!
YOU'LL HURT THE BOY!
- BACK OFF!
IRON REAPER SOUL STEALER!
[BOY SCREAMS]
- HELP! HELP ME!
- WHERE'D IT GO?
WHERE'S THE JEWEL?
- HELP!
HELP!
- I'M SO GLAD I TOOK LESSONS.
- HOW CAN SHE DO THAT?
- HE'S FAST.
- SHE'S AN IMP,
I TELL YA!
A WATER IMP!
SHE'S NOT HUMAN AT ALL!
- HANG ON.
I'VE GOT YOU.
- IT'S ON ITS BACK NOW.
I DON'T BELIEVE IT!
WHAT A DAY! WHAT A GIRL!
WHAT AN IMP!
- AND THEY SAY
TEENAGE GIRLS GET EXCITED.
- SAVE THE JEWEL, STUPID!
THE JEWEL!
- OH, MY BABY.
- I WAS SO SCARED.
- HMPH!
- THANKS FOR SAVING ME.
- THANK YOU. THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
- IT'S OK.
- I KNEW IT.
HEY, IT'S GETTING AWAY.
- IT WHAT?
WELL, I GUESS
YOU'RE OFF THE HOOK
FOR NOW, PAL.
[SCREAMING]
I KNOW.
HEY, COULD I BORROW YOUR BOW?
- UH, SURE.
IT'S SO FAR.
- MY BUTT
SHE'S GONNA HIT IT.
- I CAN DO THIS.
I KNOW IT.
- I GET IT.
SHE'S SHOOTING THE FOOT.
- THE FOOT CAN'T HELP
BUT BE DRAWN BY THE JEWEL,
WHICH ALMOST GUARANTEES
IT'LL HIT.
YEAH!
- SHE HIT IT!
- THAT LIGHT--
WHERE'S IT COMING FROM?
- LADY KAEDE, THOSE LIGHTS!
- OH, WHY?
AND I LIKE NOT
THE LOOKS OF IT.
- ARE YOU SURE
IT FELL AROUND HERE?
- WELL, YEAH.
I MEAN, KIND OF--
THOUGH I'M STILL KIND OF WORRIED
ABOUT THAT LIGHT.
[GASPS]
- I DON'T THINK SO.
- I HOPE THAT'S NOT
WHAT I THINK IT--
- WHAT DO YOU THINK IT IS?
- I THINK IT'S A SHARD
FROM THE JEWEL.
- WHAT?
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- SO NOW THE SECRET JEWEL'S
BEEN SHATTERED.
SINCE EVEN ONE PIECE
CAN GIVE MONSTERS
HUGE POWER-UPS,
IT'S UP TO ME AND INUYASHA
TO GET 'EM ALL BACK.
YOU KNOW INUYASHA'S
GONNA WANT 'EM FOR HIMSELF.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
LIKE IT'S NOT ALREADY
BAD ENOUGH
WITHOUT SOME GIRL
WHO USES HAIR LIKE WIRES.
NEXT TIME ON "INUYASHA"...
SEE YOU SOON.