- INUYASHA!
- HA HA!
HUH.
HMM! SO THERE.
FINALLY, THE WAY FOR ME
TO BECOME ALL DEMON AT LAST.
HUH!
- INUYASHA!
K-KIKYO?
HOW COULD--
I THOUGHT--
- [GRUNTING]
- BIG SISTER!
- LADY KIKYO!
THAT WOUND, IT--
- YOU'RE HURT REALLY BADLY.
- I FORGOT WHO I--
AND NOW SEE WHAT--
UH...
ALL FOR THIS,
THE SACRED JEWEL WHICH--
UH!
- YOU'RE IN PAIN.
LET SOMEONE--
- I WON'T FEEL IT MUCH LONGER,
AND SO I GIVE THIS TO YOU--
THE SHIKON NO TAMA,
WHICH YOU MUST BURN
WITH MY BODY.
IT MUST NOT FALL INTO THE HANDS
OF THOSE WHO WOULD ABUSE IT.
UNG...UH.
- SISTER KIKYO.
SISTER KIKYO!
- I SHALL TAKE IT WITH ME
TO THE OTHER WORLD.
- SHIKON NO WHAT?
- SHIKON NO TAMA, MY GIRL--
THE JEWEL OF 4 SOULS.
- YOU DON'T ACTUALLY THINK
TOURISTS ARE GONNA BUY THESE
DUMB KEY CHAINS, DO YOU?
- THAT IS NOT JUST A KEY CHAIN.
THAT CRYSTAL THERE AT THE END
IS A REPLICA OF
AN ANCIENT JEWEL WHICH--
HMM?
- HMM?
- AHEM. AS I WAS SAYING,
THAT CRYSTAL IS A REPLICA
OF AN ANCIENT JEWEL WHICH--
MMPH!
AN ANCIENT JEWEL--
- YOU DO REMEMBER IT'S
MY BIRTHDAY TOMORROW, RIGHT?
- HA HA HA!
I'D PLANNED TO WAIT
ANOTHER DAY, BUT--
- SO YOU DID GET SOMETHING.
HAND IT OVER.
- THAT, MY DEAR, IS
AN AUTHENTIC MUMMIFIED HAND
OF A WATER IMP, WHICH--
- HERE, BUYO. EAT.
- WAAH! THAT'S AN ANTIQUE!
[MUTTERS]
- REPLICA THIS,
AUTHENTIC THAT.
HERE, EVERYTHING
HAS GOT A STORY.
- WHY, THESE PICKLES
ARE FULL OF HISTORY.
- NOT HALF AS FULL AS YOU ARE.
- MM!
- THE THOUSAND-YEAR-OLD
SACRED TREE,
THE LEGEND
OF THE HIDDEN WELL--
I'VE HEARD THESE STORIES
ALL MY LIFE,
AND I'VE NEVER BELIEVED
A WORD OF IT...
THAT IS, TILL TODAY,
MY 15th BIRTHDAY.
I'M LEAVING.
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU--
- NOTHING.
- YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO PLAY IN THERE.
- I'M NOT. IT'S THE CAT.
- DID HE GO DOWN TO THE WELL?
- BUYO!
I DON'T KNOW WHERE ELSE
HE CAN BE.
- SO GO DOWN.
- BUT WHY DO I
GOT TO BE THE ONE?
- BECAUSE YOU'RE THE ONE
THAT'S LOOKING FOR HIM.
[SCRATCHING]
- AAH!
SOMETHING IS DOWN THERE!
- UH, YEAH. THE CAT.
THAT SOUND
FROM INSIDE THE WELL--
[THUD]
HMM? AAH!
- AAH! BUYO.
- [PURRS]
- YOU MAKE FUN OF ME
BECAUSE I'M SCARED,
AND THEN YOU'RE ALL, "AAH!"
- LOOK WHO'S TALKING,
MR. "WHY DO I HAVE TO GO?"
[SCRATCHING]
- UH...UH...
SIS, BEHIND YOU!
- [GASP]
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- ALIVE.
OH, TO BE ALIVE ONCE MORE.
ALREADY MY STRENGTH RETURNS.
YOU HAVE IT, DON'T YOU?
GIVE IT TO ME.
- WH-WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
LET GO!
- WRETCHED GIRL,
I MUST HAVE THE SACRED JEWEL.
"THE SACRED JEWEL"?
I GUESS I MUST'VE FALLEN
IN THE WELL.
MAYBE I BUMPED
MY HEAD, OR...
UH, MAYBE NOT.
EITHER WAY...
HEY, SOTA?
GET GRANDPA.
HE PROBABLY TOOK OFF, LITTLE--
[STRAINING]
WHAT THE--
I COULD BE WRONG, BUT, TOTO,
I THINK WE'RE NOT
IN TOKYO ANYMORE.
GRANDPA? MOM?
ARE YOU THERE?
SOTA!
BUYO!
IT'S LIKE THE FAMILY SHRINE
IS NOT EVEN--
OH! THE TREE.
THAT MEANS I'M PRACTICALLY HOME.
HUH?
IS THAT A...BOY?
HEY THERE. WHATCHA DOING?
OH, WOW. LIKE DOG EARS.
I THINK I WANT TO TOUCH THEM.
NOW THAT THAT'S
OUT OF MY SYSTEM...
- GET AWAY FROM THERE!
- AAH!
HUH?
UH...
YOU DIDN'T HAVE
TO TIE ME UP, YOU KNOW.
- A GIRL WITH STRANGE CLOTHES.
- IS SHE A FOREIGNER?
- YOU RECKON IT'S A WAR?
- OF COURSE IT IS,
AND RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE OF
RICE-PLANTING SEASON, TOO.
- SHE COULD BE A KITSUNE
IN DISGUISE.
- NAH. THEM SHAPE-CHANGING FOXES
ARE A LOT TRICKIER THAN THAT.
- I'M NOT REALLY SURE OF THAT.
- TOP KNOT.
TOP KNOT, TOP KNOT, TOP KNOT.
WHAT IS THIS, THE JAPAN
OF MEDIEVAL TIMES?
- MAKE WAY
FOR HIGH PRIESTESS KAEDE!
- [SIGH]
NOW WHAT?
- UH!
- OW!
- DEMON, BE GONE.
- HEY! HEY! I'M NOT A DEMON, OK?
- ARE YE NOT?
THEN WHY WERE YE FOUND
IN THE FOREST OF INUYASHA?
- SHE COULD BE A SPY
FROM ANOTHER VILLAGE.
- IN THAT CASE,
SHE WOULD BE A FOOL.
WHO WOULD INVADE
SUCH A POOR VILLAGE AS OURS?
- HUH?
- LET ME HAVE A GOOD LOOK AT YE.
YOU'RE A CLEVER GIRL?
OR BE YE A HALF-WIT?
- WHY, YOU...
- IT'S THERE,
THOUGH I KNOW NOT WHY.
- HUH?
- STEW?
- WOW. THAT LOOKS GREAT.
REAL FOOD.
- BEAR US NO ILL WILL, CHILD,
FOR THOUGH I NOW SEE
YE MEAN US NO HARM,
IN THESE TROUBLED TIMES OF WAR,
NO STRANGER MAY BE WELCOMED
AMONG US WITHOUT DEEP DISTRUST.
- WE REALLY AREN'T IN TOKYO
ANYMORE, ARE WE?
- TO-KY-O? NEVER HEARD OF IT.
IS THAT WHERE
YOUR PEOPLE ARE FROM?
- UH, YEAH.
SO I, UH, SHOULD GET GOING...
THOUGH I'VE NO IDEA HOW
TO GET BACK, OF COURSE.
- SISTER, PLEASE, YOU MUST.
- TAKE THE JEWEL, KAEDE,
AND SEE THAT IT IS BURNED
WITH MY BODY.
- 50 YEARS
HAVE PASSED SINCE THEN.
[BELL TOLLING]
WHAT'S GOING ON?
OH.
- OH!
- IT'S A MONSTER!
AAH! AAH!
- AAH!
- HA HA!
- IT'S THAT THING.
- GIVE ME THE SACRED JEWEL.
- IT SAID SACRED JEWEL.
ARE YE ITS TILL?
- UH, I HAVE NO IDEA.
I MEAN, I'VE HEARD
OF THE JEWEL, BUT I--
- I MUST HAVE IT. I MUST!
- THAT THING--IT'S AFTER ME.
- SPEARS, ARROWS--
NOTHING WORKS.
- WE MUST LURE IT
TO THE DRY WELL.
- THE DRY WELL?
- IN THE FOREST OF INUYASHA.
- THE WELL I CLIMBED OUT OF.
WHICH WAY IS THE FOREST?
WHERE THE LIGHT
IS SHINING, RIGHT?
- WAIT.
- I'LL DRAW IT AWAY!
HOW IS IT SHE CAN SEE
BUT CANNOT BE SEEN
IN THE FOREST OF INUYASHA?
- LADY KAEDE!
- SOMEONE WILL SAVE ME, RIGHT?
THEY'VE GOT TO.
GRANDPA? MOM? ANYBODY?
WHOEVER YOU ARE,
PLEASE, SOMEBODY, HELP ME!
[MONSTER ROARING]
- I SMELL IT--
THE BLOOD OF THE WOMAN
WHO KILLED ME,
AND IT'S COMING CLOSER.
UGH!
- THE JEWEL--GIVE IT TO ME!
- I TOLD YOU, I DON'T HAVE IT!
UH! AAH! AAAH!
AAAAAH!
OH!
- HELLO, KIKYO.
PLAYING WITH BUGS NOW, ARE WE?
- HUH?
DID HE JUST TALK?
SO YOU'RE ALIVE?
- WHY YOU TAKING
SO LONG TO KILL IT?
JUST DO HER LIKE YOU DID ME.
YOU LOOK PRETTY DUMB
THERE, KIKYO.
THE KIKYO I KNOW
WOULDN'T WASTE HER TIME.
- THAT DOES IT.
KIKYO, KIKYO, WHOEVER SHE IS,
SHE'S NOT ME
BECAUSE MY NAME IS--
- SHE'S HERE.
[MONSTER ROARS]
- GOOD. NOW PULL!
[MEN STRAINING]
- SO I WAS SAVED.
- YOU'RE PATHETIC, KIKYO.
- I'M NOT KIKYO!
LOOK. I'M TELLING YOU,
I'M NOT HER,
WHOEVER HER IS.
- AND I'M SAYING
YOU GOT TO BE HER
BECAUSE IF YOU'RE NOT,
THERE'S NO WAY THAT YOU
COULD SMELL SO--
YOU'RE NOT HER.
- I KNOW. MY NAME IS KAGOME.
KA-GO-ME.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
KIKYO WAS CUTER, MUCH CUTER.
- WHAT'D YOU--
AAH!
LET GO OF ME!
- OW, OW, OW! YOU LET GO!
- INUYASHA HAS REVIVED.
- HOW CAN THAT BE?
THE SEAL
SHOULD HAVE HELD FOREVER.
- GIVE ME THE SACRED JEWEL!
- SACRED JEWEL?
- STOP IT!
HEY.
I DID THAT BEFORE, TOO,
IN THE WELL...
BUT HOW'D I DO IT, THOUGH?
[GASP]
WHAT'S HAPPENING NOW?
IT CAME FROM INSIDE ME.
IS THAT THE SACRED JEWEL?
- GIVE ME THE JEWEL, QUICK!
- WHAT?
- HURRY!
- WHOA!
- I HEARD SOME HALF-DEMON SPAWN
WAS AFTER THE SACRED JEWEL.
IT'S YOU, ISN'T IT?
- HALF-DEMON? WHAT IS HE?
- HALF'S ALL I NEED
TO KICK YOUR SCALY HIDE.
ANYTHING MORE THAN THAT
WOULD BE A WASTE OF MY TIME.
- LISTEN. YOU TALK BIG,
BUT CAN YOU BACK IT UP?
- HMM?
- CAN YOU OR NOT?
- WHAT CAN HE DO,
PINNED THERE LIKE THAT,
OR YOU, FOR THAT MATTER?
YOU'RE POWERLESS TO STOP ME.
HA HA HA!
YOU'RE HELPLESS,
THE BOTH OF YOU.
- DON'T YOU DARE!
- IT SWALLOWED THE JEWEL!
- LADY KAEDE, WHAT SHALL WE DO?
- LOOK. IT'S RE-ARMING.
- AT LAST, MY POWER IS COMPLETE.
- IT'S CRUSHING ME!
- HEY, CAN YOU
PULL OUT THIS ARROW?
- HUH?
- LOOK. CAN YOU PULL OUT
THIS ARROW OR NOT?
- I--
I DON'T KNOW.
- NAY, CHILD.
ONCE THE ARROW IS REMOVED,
THEN INUYASHA WILL BE FREE
TO DESTROY US ALL.
- DON'T BE STUPID, YOU OLD HAG!
AT LEAST WITH ME,
YOU'VE GOT A CHANCE,
WHEREAS THAT THING
IS GONNA EAT YOU.
- [ROARS]
- AND WHAT ABOUT YOU?
ARE YOU READY TO DIE YET?
- I--I DON'T KNOW WHAT
I SHOULD DO, BUT...
GIVEN THE CHOICE...
I CHOOSE TO...
AAH!
- IT'S GONE,
MY SISTER'S SPELL BANISHED.
- UM, UH...INUYASHA?
- [LAUGHING]
- RAAH!
- AAH! UH! UH!
HUH?
- WICKED CHILD.
- NASTY HAG.
- [ROARS]
- GRIM REAPER,
SOUL STEALER!
- HA!
- WELL, NOW I KNOW.
HE IS STRONG.
UGH! IT'S STILL MOVING!
- FIND THE GLOWING FLESH
QUICKLY.
THAT'S WHERE THE JEWEL WILL BE.
IT MUST BE REMOVED AT ONCE,
LEST THE FLESH
OF MISTRESS CENTIPEDE REVIVE.
- WHOA, WHOA.
TELL ME YOU'RE JOKING.
THERE. IT'S THAT ONE.
[KAEDE CLEARS THROAT]
HUH?
BUT...
- ONLY YE MAY POSSESS
THE SACRED JEWEL...
YE WHO SO RESEMBLE
THE DEAD KIKYO.
- BUT HOW'D IT GET
INSIDE MY BODY?
WHY WOULD I HAVE A JEWEL
WANTED BY DEMONS?
- EXACTLY.
HUMANS CAN'T USE IT,
SO WHY BOTHER TO KEEP IT?
IF YOU HAND THE JEWEL OVER
RIGHT NOW,
I WON'T HAVE TO START
SHARPENING MY CLAWS ON YOU.
- WHAT?
WHAT?
YOU MEAN,
HE'S NOT THE HERO?
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
TURNER ENTERTAINMENT GROUP
CAPTIONED BY THE NATIONAL
CAPTIONING INSTITUTE
--www.ncicap.org--
[WOMEN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- HALF-DEMON
ALSO MEANS HALF-HUMAN, RIGHT?
SO WHY ISN'T HE ON OUR SIDE?
ALL THESE DEMONS AFTER THE JEWEL
WHICH WAS INSIDE OF ME,
ALL BECAUSE I LOOK
LIKE THIS KIKYO PERSON...
AND WHAT AM I DOING
BACK IN FEUDAL JAPAN, ANYWAY?
NEXT TIME ON "INUYASHA"--
"SEEKERS OF THE SACRED JEWEL."
SEE YOU SOON.