>> HERE WE COME.
IT'S THE START OF "INUYASHA."
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL THE
SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY NARAKU WITH
MY TETSAIGA.
>> MIROKU'S A BIT LECHEROUS,
BUT HE CARRIES THE BURDEN OF
NARAKU'S CURSE, THE WIND TUNNEL.
DID MIROKU SENSE THE SAME
SADNESS IN THAT WOMAN?
>> IT'S UP TO ALL OF US.
>> TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FEUDAL FAIRY TALE, "INUYASHA."
[WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
[WIND SWIRLING]
>> UNH...
[GRUNTING]
OHH.
>> POOR THING.
YOU GOT LOST IN THE SNOW.
>> OH, FATHER.
HMM?
>> YOU'LL BE FINE NOW.
>> WHO ARE YOU?
>> I GO BY THE NAME KOYUKI.
YOU CALLED FOR YOUR FATHER.
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN TO HIM?
>> HE DIED.
THAT'S WHY I'M ON MY OWN.
YOU SEE, I HAVE NO RELATIVES.
>> IF YOU HAVE NO RELATIVES AND
NOWHERE TO GO, THEN COME TO MY
HOUSE.
>> OH.
SHE WAS A BEAUTIFUL WOMAN, WITH
FAIR SKIN AS WHITE AS THE SNOW
ITSELF.
>> AAH!
>> HUH?
OW.
WHAT DID YOU DO THAT FOR?
>> SORRY, I WAS JUST GETTING A
MOSQUITO.
DO CARRY ON.
>> THE POINT I WAS TRYING TO
MAKE WAS THAT I ONCE TRAINED
HERE, SO I KNOW THESE PARTS VERY
WELL.
>> AND WHAT ABOUT THAT WOMAN?
WHAT HAPPENED NEXT?
>> NOTHING HAPPENED.
THAT'S IT.
7 YEARS HAVE PASSED SINCE THE
DAY I MET HER.
I WAS STILL SO YOUNG AND
INNOCENT, WITH ROUND CHEEKS SO
ROSY AND SUPPLE.
[SMACK]
>> HMM!
>> HEH.
OOP, GOT IT.
SEE THE BLOOD?
>> HMM?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> PLEASE OPEN YOUR EYES.
COME ON, SAY SOMETHING.
DON'T DIE ON ME!
>> HANG IN THERE.
>> WHY WOULD THERE BE SNOW AT
THIS TIME OF YEAR?
>> WAKE UP!
[GASP]
HE'S COME TO.
THAT'S A GOOD SIGN.
>> WONDERFUL.
>> WHAT A RELIEF.
>> EXCUSE ME.
PERHAPS I CAN BE OF SOME
ASSISTANCE TO YOU.
MAY I ASK WHAT HAS HAPPENED TO
THIS POOR MAN?
>> MONK, I'D BE GLAD TO TELL
YOU.
A SNOW DEMON HAS BEEN RECENTLY
PLAGUING THIS LAND.
>> SEVERAL VILLAGE MEN HAVE
BEEN FOUND LIKE THIS, IN A
FROZEN STUPOR.
>> HUH?
>> I THINK YOU'D BETTER RETURN
TO THE HUT AND TELL EVERYBODY
WHAT'S GOING ON.
>> BUT WHAT ABOUT YOU?
>> I'LL GO TAKE CARE OF THE
DEMON AND PUT AN END TO THESE
ATTACKS.
DON'T WORRY.
THE EVIL PRESENCE DOESN'T SEEM
TO BE TOO STRONG.
>> [MEN GASP]
>> I HOPE THE MONK CAN MANAGE ON
HIS OWN.
HE SEEMS TO BE QUITE YOUNG.
>> RUMOR HAS IT THE DEMON
PRESENTS ITSELF AS A BEWITCHING
WOMAN WITH SKIN AS WHITE AS
SNOW.
>> MOST MEN ARE CAPTIVATED BY
HER BEAUTY AND FOLLOW HER DEEP
INTO THE SNOWY PASSES.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> HUH?
>> AHH.
NO SIGN OF NARAKU HERE, EITHER.
UH, KAGOME, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> I WAS CLEANING OUT MY
BACKPACK, AND I FOUND ALL THESE
FIREWORKS.
I BROUGHT THEM FROM HOME A WHILE
BACK TO SHOW YOU ALL, BUT I KIND
OF FORGOT THEY WERE IN HERE.
>> HMM?
>> MIGHT AS WELL CHECK ONE TO
MAKE SURE THEY DIDN'T GET DAMP.
>> HMM.
HEY, HOW DID YOU MAKE THAT
HAPPEN?
>> THIS IS CALLED A SPARKLER.
ISN'T IT SO PRETTY?
>> OHH.
>> SNOW IN THE MIDDLE OF SUMMER?
HOW CAN THAT BE?
>> [BREATHING HEAVILY]
AAH!
HUH?
MIROKU?
MIROKU, IT'S SANGO.
I'M RIGHT HERE.
OHH.
>> ARE YOU A TRAVELER?
YOU SEEM TO BE HAVING TROUBLE
CROSSING IN THE SNOW.
IS THERE ANYTHING I CAN DO TO
ASSIST YOU?
>> YES, THERE IS.
I WAS WONDERING, COULD YOU
POSSIBLY FIND IT IN YOUR HEART
TO BEAR MY CHILD?
>> HMM.
>> HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN?
I HAVE ALREADY BIRTHED YOUR
CHILD.
>> AAH!
HUH?
>> HUH?
>> COME WITH ME AND HOLD YOUR
BABY.
>> MIROKU, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
MIROKU?
[GROWL]
>> DON'T WORRY.
I'LL SPLIT THEM WITH YOU.
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY--
"NO WORK, NO FOOD."
WHY SHOULD WE HAVE TO SHARE WITH
THE OTHERS?
HMM?
>> JUST IN TIME FOR FOOD.
>> PERFECT TIMING AS USUAL.
I BET YOU SMELLED THE FISH.
THAT'S WHAT YOU CAME BACK FOR.
>> HARDLY.
IT'S SNOWING OUT THERE.
>> HUH?
NO WONDER IT'S SO COLD.
>> AREN'T SANGO AND MIROKU BACK?
>> NO, NOT YET.
>> YEAH, WELL, THEY'LL GET
HUNGRY SOON.
>> HEY!
THAT FISH BELONGS TO KIRARA AND
ME!
>> DON'T BE SO STINGY.
COME HERE AND HAVE SOME, KAGOME.
IT'S GOOD.
>> YEAH. JUST A SECOND.
AH!
SANGO, MIROKU!
HUH?
>> HUH?
>> SORRY WE CAME IN AND MADE
OURSELVES AT HOME WHILE YOU WERE
OUT.
>> DON'T WORRY.
I WOULD HAVE DONE THE SAME IN A
BLIZZARD LIKE THIS.
>> HELP YOURSELF TO SOME BOAR
MEAT.
IT'LL BE READY SOON.
>> IT'S GOOD!
>> BUT IT'S STILL ALMOST RAW.
>> LIKE HE CARES.
HE'S SUCH AN ANIMAL.
>> I THINK YOU'D BETTER STAY
HERE WITH US UNTIL THE SNOW
MAIDEN PASSES THROUGH.
>> SNOW MAIDEN?
>> OH, YES.
IF A YOUNG MAN WALKS ALONE ON A
SNOWY DAY LIKE THIS, A YOUNG
WOMAN STOPS HIM, AND IF HE
FOLLOWS HER, HE'S SEALED HIS
FATE.
THE NEXT DAY, HE'S FOUND
PITIFULLY FROZEN.
>> THEY SAY THAT THE WOMAN IS A
SIGHT TO BEHOLD AND HAS A FACE
NOT SOON FORGOTTEN, WITH SKIN
AS WHITE AS THE SNOW ITSELF.
I'D LIKE TO SEE HER JUST ONCE
WITH MY OWN EYES, EVEN IF IT
MEANT FREEZING!
[GRUNTING]
OW! OUCH!
HEY!
>> MIROKU'S IN DANGER.
>> MAYBE NOT.
ISN'T SANGO WITH HIM?
>> OH.
THEN MAYBE HE IS OK.
>> YOU PEOPLE JUST DON'T
UNDERSTAND.
>> HMM?
>> AS IF MIROKU WOULD LEAVE A
PRETTY WOMAN ALONE.
THE QUESTION IS, HOW WILL SANGO
REACT?
GIVES ME THE SHIVERS JUST
THINKING ABOUT IT.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
SANGO HAS FEELINGS FOR--
>> DON'T BOTHER!
WE'VE TALKED ABOUT THIS A
HUNDRED TIMES, AND HE STILL
DOESN'T GET IT.
>> CAN'T ARGUE WITH YOU THERE.
>> STILL, IF THIS IS ANOTHER
DEMON THAT'S SUDDENLY CAUSING
TROUBLE BECAUSE NARAKU ISN'T
AROUND ANYMORE, THEN WE CAN'T
JUST SIT AROUND AND IGNORE IT.
I'M GOING AFTER THEM.
>> INUYASHA, WAIT.
I'M COMING WITH YOU.
>> WAIT!
>> HUH?
>> TAKE THIS.
>> IT'S A SPECIAL RESTORATIVE.
>> MIROKU!
>> SANGO!
[SNIFFING]
[GROWL]
>> WHAT IS IT, KIRARA?
OH! COME HERE!
>> HUH?
UNH!
SANGO!
>> SANGO, DRINK THIS, QUICK.
IT'S MEDICINE.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO WORK WONDERS
WHEN YOU HAVE HYPOTHERMIA.
>> WOW! IT REALLY DOES WORK!
>> IT'S A MIXTURE OF STRONG
LIME, VIPER, NEWT, AND WORMS.
>> [GRUNTS]
[RETCHES]
[COUGHING]
>> WELL, AT LEAST THE MEDICINE
SEEMS TO HAVE HELPED.
>> SO WHERE'S MIROKU?
>> [GASP]
MIROKU.
>> HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN?
I HAVE ALREADY BIRTHED YOUR
CHILD.
>> HMM. I CAN PICTURE IT.
HE'S ENJOYING HIS HAPPY NEW
FAMILY OF 3.
>> HMM?
>> A BARRIER.
>> RIGHT THIS WAY, MY DEAR
HUSBAND.
WE'VE ARRIVED AT OUR HOME.
>> THIS WOMAN IS NOT OF THIS
WORLD, BUT WHY WOULD SHE BE
HARMING HUMANS?
DOES SHE KILL MEN IN ORDER TO
FEED ON THEIR LIFE SPIRIT?
[GASP]
>> [SCREAMING]
[LAUGHTER]
>> "DADDY"?
ARE THEY REALLY ALL MINE?
>> DEAR, KEEP THEM COMPANY FOR A
FEW MINUTES, WILL YOU?
I'LL PREPARE SOME RICE GRUEL FOR
OUR MEAL.
>> RIGHT.
RICE GRUEL.
AAH!
>> YOU'LL FIND THE DIAPERS IN A
PILE BY THE BABIES.
>> THANKS.
THERE'S SO MANY OF THEM.
THEY'RE EVERYWHERE.
[SIGH]
>> DON'T DO IT.
>> HUH?
>> DON'T TELL ME YOU'VE
FORGOTTEN ABOUT YOUR CHILDREN,
MIROKU.
THEY ARE YOUR CHILDREN.
YOU CAN BE SURE OF THAT.
>> THEY'RE MINE?
ALL OF THEM?
>> [SCREAMING AND LAUGHING]
>> I HEARD IT WITH MY OWN EARS!
SHE SAID THE CHILD WAS HIS!
>> HA! COME TO THINK OF IT,
MAYBE IT'S TIME FOR HIM TO
SETTLE DOWN.
HEY, THIS COULD BE THE PERFECT
OPPORTUNITY.
>> [GRUNT]
>> WHAT A DOOFUS.
>> WOULD YOU TWO KNOCK IT OFF?
DON'T TAKE THAT DEMON'S WORD SO
LITERALLY.
>> HUH? A BARRIER.
>> A DEMONIC AURA IS COMING FROM
BEYOND THERE.
>> YEAH!
I'LL TEAR THE THING WIDE OPEN!
UNH!
YAAH!
FOLLOW ME.
>> [CRYING]
>> SHH. IT'S OK.
THERE, THERE.
DON'T CRY.
>> AH-CHOO!
>> STOP THAT!
DON'T BLOW YOUR RUNNY NOSE IN MY
KIMONO.
PUT THAT DOWN!
MY STAFF IS NOT A PLAYTHING.
>> MIROKU?
>> YES.
>> YOSAKU NEEDS TO BE FED,
SUTUMATSU REALLY NEEDS TO BE
CHANGED, AND I NEED YOU TO SING
UTURA A LULLABY AND PUT HER DOWN
FOR HER NAP.
OK?
>> YES, RIGHT AWAY.
>> OK. OK, DON'T CRY NOW.
ISN'T THAT NUMMY?
DID YOU HAVE A LITTLE WIDDLE?
♪ GO TO SLEEP ♪
YOU KNOW BETTER THAN TO PEE
THERE!
>> HUH?
>> THE TOILET'S OVER HERE!
HMM.
HMM?
THAT'S KIND OF YOU.
HAVE YOU HONESTLY BEEN TAKING
CARE OF ALL THESE CHILDREN ON
YOUR OWN?
>> OF COURSE.
THAT'S WHAT A MOTHER DOES, LOOK
AFTER HER CHILDREN.
>> TELL ME, ARE THEY HONESTLY
ALL MINE?
>> THEY ARE CHILDREN WHOSE
VILLAGES WERE BURNED DOWN IN THE
WAR AND CHILDREN WHO WERE PARTED
WITH THEIR MOTHERS SOON AFTER
BIRTH AND LEFT ALONE IN THE
WORLD.
I BEGAN TAKING THEM IN, AND SOON
I HAD THIS MANY.
>> THAT'S A HUGE BURDEN YOU'VE
TAKEN ON.
>> INDEED IT IS, BUT THEY
DESERVED A CHANCE AT HAPPINESS.
>> BE CAREFUL.
WE'RE GETTING CLOSE.
>> ♪ GO TO SLEEP, GO TO SLEEP ♪
>> HEY, LISTEN.
ISN'T THAT MIROKU'S VOICE?
>> WELL, I GUESS EVEN A LECHER
LIKE HIM WOULD DOTE ON HIS OWN
CHILD.
>> [GASP]
>> [GRUNTS]
>> INUYASHA!
>> HMM?
>> LOOK!
>> HUH?
A HOUSE.
>> HA!
WE FOUND IT.
>> HEH HEH HEH!
SHE'S FAST ASLEEP, THE LITTLE
PUMPKIN.
THAT'S MY GOOD GIRL.
THERE, THERE.
SUCH A SWEET LITTLE GIRL.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE A
HEARTBREAKER.
>> [GRUNTS]
HUH?
>> THERE, THERE.
THAT'S A GOOD BABY.
CLOSE THOSE PEEPERS.
>> YOU SEE THAT?
>> YEAH, THE DEMON MUST HAVE PUT
MIROKU UNDER A SPELL.
>> COME ON, SNAP OUT OF IT,
MIROKU!
>> ♪ GO TO SLEEP
GO TO SLEEP ♪
>> MIROKU!
UNH!
AAH!
>> INUYASHA!
>> YOU THERE...
>> UNH!
>> TURN BACK.
LEAVE US.
>> HUH?
>> OH?
I SEE.
SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
SNOW BEAST, I SUMMON YOU!
[GROWLING]
[ROAR]
>> SHE'S NOT STRONG ENOUGH TO
TAKE ON THAT DEMON.
IT'S TOO COLD FOR HER.
>> DEFEAT THEM AND TAKE
POSSESSION OF THE SACRED JEWEL
SHARDS.
>> THINK AGAIN
BECAUSE I'M GONNA KILL YOU.
YAH!
UNH!
HEH! SO MUCH FOR HIM!
TOO BAD.
I WAS EXPECTING MORE OF A
CHALLENGE.
>> AAH!
>> INUYASHA!
>> HUH?
HEY, WHAT THE--
UNH!
>> HURRY, RUN FOR IT!
[CHUCKLES]
>> SLEEP TIGHT, LITTLE BLOSSOM.
OH, KOYUKI?
>> YES?
>> I HEARD SOME KIND OF
DISTURBANCE OUTSIDE.
IS EVERYTHING OK?
>> SOME STRAY DOGS BROKE INTO
THE GARDEN, THAT'S ALL.
>> OH.
>> THERE'S NOTHING TO WORRY
ABOUT, MY DEAR.
>> I'LL CHASE THEM OUT IN NO
TIME AT ALL.
>> COME ON!
UNH!
AAH!
>> THE CHILDREN!
>> UNH!
MIROKU!
>> HUH? INUYASHA?
>> COME TO YOUR SENSES.
>> I NEVER LOST MY SENSES.
HUH? HMM?
SNOW?
>> YOU WON'T GET AWAY FROM ME.
>> YOU RESEMBLE SOMEONE,
A WOMAN I ONCE KNEW.
VERY MUCH SO.
I DIDN'T WANT TO BE ROUGH ON
YOU.
I'M SORRY.
UNH!
>> AAH!
>> DON'T EAT ME!
I DON'T TASTE GOOD!
>> AAH!
HIRAIKOTSU!
IT'S FAST.
>> DON'T WORRY.
I'LL GET IT.
WIND SCAR!
[GRUNT]
IT JUST WON'T DIE!
>> I DESPISE IT.
DESPISE IT!
>> WHY WOULD ONE AS GENTLE AND
KINDHEARTED AS YOU INTENTIONALLY
DECEIVE MEN AND DO THEM HARM?
>> I DESPISE THEM.
I HATE THIS WORLD.
>> HMM.
>> I HATE THAT I WAS BORN INTO A
WORLD LIKE THIS.
I HATE IT!
>> I ONLY WANT FOR YOU TO FIND
ETERNAL PEACE.
FORGIVE ME.
>> AAH!
>> HUH?
I DON'T LIKE THE LOOKS OF THIS.
HOW ARE WE GONNA KILL THAT THING
FOR GOOD?
>> USE HEAT.
THAT DEMON'S WEAKNESS IS HEAT
AND FIRE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I'LL USE MY FOX FIRE!
TAKE THAT! AND THAT!
SO MUCH FOR THAT BRILLIANT IDEA!
OOH!
>> WAIT.
I KNOW.
I'VE GOT THIS.
THIS WAY!
I'LL TAKE YOU ON!
>> KAGOME!
[GROWLS]
>> HIRAIKOTSU!
[SCREAMING]
>> NOW IS MY CHANCE.
WIND SCAR!
HUH?
>> IS THAT A SNOW DEMON, TOO?
>> WHO CARES?
IT'S GOING DOWN.
>> WAIT.
>> HUH?
>> THAT'S ENOUGH.
WE'VE DONE OUR JOB HERE.
HER SPIRIT HAS BEEN FREED FROM
THE SNOW MAIDEN.
HMM.
IT WAS THE SOLE OF A WOMAN WHO
HAD LOST HER LIFE BECAUSE OF THE
WAR.
AFTER HER DEATH, SHE TOOK IN THE
SPIRITS OF THE CHILDREN AND
BABIES WHO HAD ALSO DIED IN THE
WAR, AND SHE DEVOTED HERSELF TO
TAKING CARE OF THEM.
THEN, AT SOME POINT, THE SNOW
DEMON MUST HAVE FOUND HER AND
TAKEN POSSESSION OF HER SPIRIT.
>> IT'S TRAGIC.
>> IT IS TRAGIC.
THERE'S SO MUCH SUFFERING IN
WARTIME, ESPECIALLY FOR WOMEN.
>> MIROKU, GOT A LITTLE QUESTION
FOR YOU.
HOW COME YOU FOLLOWED HER WHEN
SHE TOLD YOU ABOUT THE KIDS?
YOU MUST HAVE REMEMBERED HER.
>> [GRUNTS]
>> INUYASHA!
>> HE REALLY IS A BULLY.
>> I'LL TELL YOU.
>> MIROKU PURPOSELY FELL UNDER
HER SPELL IN ORDER TO SAVE THE
POOR WOMAN THE DEMON INHABITED.
>> HUH?
>> THAT'S IT.
THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
>> MIROKU WOULD NEVER FATHER
SCORES OF ILLICIT CHILDREN.
RIGHT?
>> UNH!
>> HMM. ANOTHER MOSQUITO.
>> HMM?
>> I'M READY TO GO.
>> SAME HERE.
>> YEP, ME, TOO.
>> SHE HONESTLY RESEMBLED
KOYUKI, THE BEAUTIFUL WOMAN WHO
SAVED ME WHEN I WAS VERY YOUNG.
SHE'S STILL HAPPY AND ALIVE
SOMEWHERE.
I WANT TO BELIEVE THAT.
HMM?
ONE LAST SNOWFLAKE.
[WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> THE NORTHERN MOUNTAIN, JUST
BEYOND WHERE NARAKU DISAPPEARED.
>> THE WOLF-DEMON TRIBE THAT
LIVES THERE HAS BEEN ATTACKED.
>> A DEMON NAMED KYOKUTSU
POSSESSES A SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
DEMON, HE ROSE UP
FROM THE GRAVE!
>> I'LL TAKE YOUR SACRED JEWEL
SHARD, TOO!
>> NEITHER HUMAN NOR DEMON.
WHAT IS THIS RESURRECTED DEMON
AFTER?
NEXT TIME, "ASSAULT ON THE
WOLF-DEMON TRIBE!"
>> FORGET IT.
WE AVENGE MY FRIENDS FIRST.