- OH, I'M TIRED.
- AT LEAST WE'RE STILL ALIVE.
- I'M A FARMER,
NOT A SOLDIER.
- RIGHT NOW, I'M JUST
HAPPY TO BE BREATHING.
- WHICH WE WOULDN'T BE,
IF NOT FOR THAT PRIESTESS.
- LET'S GIVE THANKS
FOR HER, HUH?
[MOANING]
LOOK! HEY!
I THINK HE'S WAKING UP!
- GOOD NEWS.
YOU'RE NOT DEAD.
[CHUCKLES]
GUESS HER MEDICINE
DID THE TRICK.
- PRIESTESS! LOOK!
OUR FRIEND HERE IS ALIVE!
- NEE!
- STILL, EVIL SEEKS
THIS MAN'S LIFE.
- PRIESTESS, YOU OK?
- YOUR FRIEND
WILL BE JUST FINE,
MAY EVEN BE UP
AS EARLY AS TOMORROW.
- WE ARE SEEKING
THE PRIESTESS CALLED KIKYO!
- THE MEN TELL ME OF ONE
WHO TENDS TO SOLDIERS
INJURED ON BOTH SIDES OF BATTLE,
WHOSE STRANGE MAGICS CAN REVIVE
EVEN THOSE
ON THE BRINK OF DEATH.
- I AM SKILLED IN NO SUCH MAGICS
BUT ONLY IN THE ART OF HEALING.
- WE SHALL HEAR
MORE AT THE CASTLE.
PREPARE TO LEAVE.
- LORD KAGEWAKI,
MASTER OF THE HITOMI CLAN,
HAS BEEN IN DELICATE
HEALTH SINCE BIRTH.
SINCE HIS FATHER'S DEATH
AND OWN SUCCESSION,
HIS HEALTH HAS WORSENED.
NOW HE REFUSES
BOTH CLAN PHYSICIAN
AND HIS NEAREST VASSALS.
- NONE MAY ENTER.
I'M SORRY.
- BUT I HAVE BROUGHT
THE PRIESTESS WHO WILL
CURE LORD KAGEWAKI.
- THE LORD HAS FORBIDDEN
ENTRY TO ANYONE.
FURTHER, HE REFUSES
ALL VISITORS...
- I SENSE
A GREAT WRONGNESS,
ALMOST A VEIL.
- WAIT! WHERE ARE YOU--
- SO, HE'S THE LORD.
HE HAS NO LIFE IN HIM, AS THOUGH
HE IS DEAD FROM THE NECK DOWN.
- KIKYO.
- WE HAVE FAILED, MY LORD.
FORGIVE US.
SHE'S COME DESPITE
YOUR ORDERS.
- SHE CLAIMS SHE CAN
HEAL YOU, MY LORD.
- BE QUIET.
LEAVE ME!
- YES, LORD.
- TELL ME YOUR NAME,
NOW THAT YOU'VE DISTURBED ME.
- MY NAME IS KIKYO.
- KIKYO IS ALIVE.
THE WOMAN I MYSELF
TRAPPED 50 YEARS AGO.
THE WOMAN WHO DIED, TAKING
THE SACRED JEWEL WITH HER.
HOW CAN SHE BE--
[THUNDER]
- HUH?
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
- OVER HERE, TOO.
ALL DRIED UP.
- BUT HOW DID IT HAPPEN?
WE'VE HAD PLENTY OF RAIN.
- IT STARTED ABOUT A MONTH AGO.
- OH.
- IT'S RAIN!
- THAT'S NOT RAIN.
- AND IT'S RED, LIKE BLOOD.
WHAT IN THE NAME OF--
[SHOUTING]
- RAINING DEMON PARTS, WAS IT?
HOW ODD.
- IT WAS AWFUL!
AND NOT JUST THAT.
IT COMPLETELY RUINED
ALL OF OUR FIELDS.
- WOULD THAT IT WERE
ONLY THE FIELDS.
THE OLD, THE YOUNG, THE WEAK--
SO MANY HAVE BECOME SICKENED.
- I SHOULD THINK SO.
I AM DEFINITELY DETECTING
AN EVIL PRESENCE IN THIS AREA.
LEAVE IT TO ME.
- SO HERE WE COME
TO SAVE THE DAY AGAIN.
DO WE HAVE TIME FOR THIS?
WHAT ABOUT NARAKU, HUH?
OR DOES HE NOT MATTER ANYMORE?
- I WON'T LET YOU GO!
EVEN IF YOU BEG FOR FORGIVENESS!
HA!
- NOBODY'S FORGOTTEN ANYONE,
BUT KAGOME'S ARROW--IT REALLY
DID HIM SOME DAMAGE.
EVEN NARAKU WOULD BE
DOWN FOR A WHILE AFTER
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
BESIDES, I'VE ALREADY
ACCEPTED PAYMENT FOR
SERVICES RENDERED, SO...
- WHEN'D THAT HAPPEN?
- YOU HAVEN'T DONE
ANYTHING YET!
THE PAYING PART OF IT DON'T
USUALLY COME UNTIL AFTERWARDS!
- IF YOU WAIT, YOU'LL GET
CHEATED ON THE TIP.
- TAKING BRIBES!
- NOT BRIBES.
TITHES.
- HUH? SANGO?
WHAT'S WRONG?
- THE MIASMA.
I THINK IT'S AT THE BASE
OF THAT MOUNTAIN.
I WAS JUST WONDERING
IF SOMEONE OTHER THAN NARAKU
COULD PRODUCE SUCH POISON.
- SOMEONE OTHER THAN NARAKU?
- WELL, KIKYO?
HE'S BEYOND YOUR HELP THEN?
- YES. I'M AFRAID
THERE'S NOT MUCH I CAN DO.
- REALLY. SO IT IS
NO ORDINARY ILLNESS.
YOU, TOO, WILL ABANDON HIM.
- I AM MERELY A PRIESTESS.
MIGHTN'T I BE ALLOWED TO LEAVE?
HMM?
- YOU MOST CERTAINLY MAY NOT BE
ALLOWED TO LEAVE THIS PLACE.
IT IS THE LORD'S WISH
THAT YOU STAY.
- HMM.
- KIKYO OUGHT
TO HAVE DIED.
I'LL KILL HER AGAIN,
BUT NOT UNTIL I'VE
DISCOVERED HER TRUE SELF.
TONIGHT MY DREAMS
BECOME REALITY,
AND WHO BETTER
THAN SHE TO SEE THEM.
- THE POISON EVEN
KILLED THE GRASS.
- WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
WHATEVER'S GOING ON HERE,
I DON'T LIKE IT.
HUH?
- LOOK! I THINK THAT'S WHERE
THE MIASMA'S COMING FROM.
[COUGHING]
SANGO?
ARE YOU OK?
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
YOU'RE STILL SICK.
- SANGO, KAGOME,
YOU STAY HERE.
IT'S JUST A DEMON HUNT.
THERE'S NO SENSE
DRAGGING EVERYONE ALONG.
MIROKU, YOU COMING?
- YOU SEEM RESISTANT
TO THE POISON, SHIPPO.
WILL YOU LOOK AFTER THINGS?
- LEAVE EVERYTHING TO ME.
BUT PROMISE YOU'LL BE CAREFUL.
THAT MIASMA'S PRETTY STRONG.
- I CAN FEEL IT,
THE PULL OF A STRONG
MIASMA COMING CLOSER.
- AAH! AAH!
- OPEN UP.
AFTER THAT, BRING ME
A BOW AND AN ARROW.
- THE POISON IS
GETTING WORSE, SANGO.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
- I'M OK.
BUT WHAT ABOUT YOU?
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
I'M FINE.
- WHAT'S GOING ON IN THERE?
IT'S LIKE I'M BEING PULLED IN.
SOMETHING REALLY BAD
MUST BE HAPPENING.
- I WISH INUYASHA AND MIROKU
WEREN'T IN THE MIDDLE OF IT.
- WE REALLY MUST BE
CLOSE BY NOW.
[COUGHING]
- AW! COME ON, SUCK IT UP!
YOU SAID YOU COULD HANDLE IT.
WHAT'S WRONG?
- I CAN, AND I WILL.
IT'S JUST I HAVE
TO GO A BIT SLOWER.
WITHOUT MY TRAINING, I WOULDN'T
BE ABLE TO DO IT AT ALL.
[RUMBLE]
- HUH?
SOMETHING'S THERE.
LET'S GO.
- RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
[GASPS]
UGH!
- WH-WHAT IS THAT?
- PIECES OF...DEMONS.
[ROARING]
- BUT...WHY ARE THEY
FIGHTING EACH OTHER?
- THERE MUST HAVE
BEEN A BATTLE,
HUNDREDS OF THEM FIGHTING,
KILLING, DYING.
THE LOSERS' BODIES
WERE THROWN INTO HERE.
WHAT'S LEFT OF
THEIR BODIES, THAT IS.
- BUT THERE'S GOT
TO BE A REASON.
- SO THEN THE LAST ONE
STANDING--
- GETS TO KEEP ALL THE PARTS.
[ROARING]
- I'M STILL HERE!
THE PROMISE WAS THAT
THE FINAL WINNER
WOULD LEAVE
THIS PLACE ALIVE.
WHY HAVE I NOT YET MOVED ON?
- OH, NO!
THAT MEANS HE--
UNLESS I'M NOT YET
FINAL WINNER.
- NOT YET, YOU'RE NOT.
- INUYASHA, WAIT.
- LET GO OF ME!
- I HOPE I'M NOT
RIGHT, BUT...
IF I AM, INUYASHA WILL--
[ROARING]
- YOU FIGHT ME!
- THEY'RE TAKING TOO LONG.
- YES. LET'S GO.
[GRUNTING]
- SANGO, NO.
YOU CAN'T.
YOU'RE STILL TOO WEAK
FROM BEFORE.
YOU'LL DIE IN THERE!
COME ON.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
THE MIASMA'S ONLY MAKING
YOUR CONDITION WORSE.
[GASPS]
OH!
- KIKYO!
- SO, INUYASHA IS INSIDE.
- KIKYO. WASN'T THAT
THE NAME OF THE PRIESTESS?
- KAGOME, NO!
- ARE YOU GOING TO FOLLOW HER?
- I HAVE TO, BUT YOU STAY
HERE WITH SANGO, OK?
- KAGOME, WAS THAT WOMAN--
- KIKYO? YEAH.
I DON'T KNOW WHY,
BUT WHATEVER THE REASON,
IF KIKYO'S HERE,
I'M SURE IT CAN'T BE GOOD.
- KIRARA. TAKE KIRARA.
AND PLEASE, BE CAREFUL.
- I WILL. THANKS.
- THE DEAD SOULS INSIDE ME
TRYING TO GET OUT--
ARE THEY DRAWN BY THE MIASMA?
BUT THERE'S ANOTHER
FORCE AT WORK.
COULD IT BE THE ONE
WHO LIVES IN THE CASTLE?
[GRUNTING]
[ROARING]
- NOW TO FINISH HIM OFF.
THE WOUND!
IT'S...CLOSING BACK UP!
- INUYASHA, NO!
STAY YOUR SWORD!
DON'T FIGHT!
- DON'T BE STUPID!
I HAVE TO!
IF I DON'T,
I'LL BE KILLED!
- HE'S...A PRODUCT OF...
I DON'T KNOW!
- LISTEN THIS IS SIMILAR TO A
TECHNIQUE CALLED FUKO.
IT'S HOW YOU MAKE A CREATURE CALLED KODOKU.
- FUKO? KODOKU?
WHAT THE HECK ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT!?
- IT'S A KIND OF SORCERY.
YOU PUT TOGETHER LIZARDS,
POISONOUS WORMS, WHATEVER.
THEN, WELL, YOU LET THEM
FIGHT IT OUT.
THE ONE THAT'S LEFT BECOMES
A CREATURE CALLED KODOKU.
- FASCINATING.
AND YOUR POINT IS?
- YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE LEFT.
ONCE I KILL YOU--
- I WILL BE THE WINNER.
- UGH!
HERE'S SOMETHING ELSE
WITHOUT A POINT!
AAH!
- HE'S RIGHT.
IT IS POINTLESS.
UNLESS THE SPELL CAST IN HERE
IS BROKEN, INUYASHA WILL--
- WHO'S THERE?
- INUYASHA.
- K-KIKYO.
- THE DEAD SOULS
ARE...LEAVING.
THIS EXPLAINS IT.
THE MIASMA--WHERE IT'S FROM.
[GRUNTING]
- BUT WHY?
- SHE'S HERE SOMEWHERE.
- SOON IT WILL COME,
THE DEMONS I SEALED IN THERE,
BEYOND COUNTING.
ONE BY ONE, THEY KILLED EACH
OTHER, UNTIL BUT ONE REMAINED.
A VICTOR WHO WILL
BECOME MY NEW BODY.
- KIKYO!
[ROARING]
AAH!
KIKYO!
[PANTING]
[MEOWS]
- KIRARA, WHAT?
OH, NO! THE JEWEL!
[GASPS]
- I CAN SENSE
ANOTHER JEWEL.
AND...NO, THIS ISN'T IT.
THERE'S ANOTHER.
SOMEONE HAS ANOTHER FRAGMENT.
UNLESS...
[COUGHING]
- THE MIASMA--
IT'S BECOMING THICKER
WITH ALL OF KIKYO'S DEAD SOULS.
- MIROKU!
YOU'RE ALIVE!
HANG IN THERE, OK?
- KAGOME.
[SCREECHES]
- KIRARA! NO!
- WHAT'S GOING ON DOWN THERE?
- RECOMBINANT
GENERATION SORCERY,
AND INUYASHA'S ABOUT TO BECOME
PART OF THE EXPERIMENT
IF WE DON'T STOP HIM.
- HOW SO?
I DID SENSE THE JEWEL
A WHILE BACK.
COULD THIS BE A TRAP?
- THE MIASMA'S TOO POWERFUL, AND
WE BOTH KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS:
NARAKU IS INVOLVED.
[ROARING]
- THE WOMAN IS NOT HUMAN.
SHE, TOO, WILL BECOME
A PART OF ME!
[LAUGHS]
- YOU KEEP THAT
FILTHY HAND OFF OF HER!
- OH!
[ROARING]
[LAUGHING]
- UGH!
- INUYASHA, NO!
STAY CALM!
- NO. I WILL NOT STAY CALM!
I AM GOING TO PROTECT KIKYO!
- KAGOME.
[ROARING]
- KAGOME!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I HAVE TO GET
KIKYO OUT OF THERE.
- IF I DON'T, INUYASHA
WILL KEEP PROTECTING HER.
HE WOULD NEVER, EVER
LET HER BE HURT,
NO MATTER HOW THAT HURTS ME.
[GRUNTING]
[MOANING]
- YOU'RE CONSCIOUS.
CAN YOU STAND?
- YOU LITTLE FOOL.
BY COMING HERE, YOU RISK
INUYASHA'S LOSING YOU FOREVER.
- WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
INUYASHA IS TRYING SO HARD
TO SAVE YOU, BUT YOU--
KIKYO.
- INUYASHA! NO!
- AAH!
- DON'T KILL HIM!
[GASPS]
KIKYO.
[LOUD RUMBLE]
HUH? NOW WHAT?
- THE SPELL IS BROKEN.
THE MIASMA, GONE.
[SCREAMING]
- INUYASHA!
- KAGOME!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- I'M FINE!
WHAT ABOUT KIKYO?
DOWN THERE!
- NARAKU!
YOU SHOT HIM WITH
YOUR ARROW, REMEMBER?
HE NEEDED A BODY,
SO HE HAD THOSE DEMONS
KILL EACH OTHER
AND COMBINE TO A NEW ONE.
- THE MOUNTAIN MIST LURED YOU.
YOU TOOK THE BAIT,
AND I CAST MY SPELL.
[CHUCKLES]
YOU COULD HAVE JOINED ME
IN HERE, INUYASHA,
IF ONLY YOU HAD THE COURAGE.
SO THIS IS THE WOMAN
WHO RESTORED ME TO LIFE.
I MIGHT NOT HAVE HAD THIS NEW
BODY AT ALL IF NOT FOR HER.
- YEAH, RIGHT, LOSER!
SHE DID IT TO SAVE
INUYASHA, NOT YOU,
SO WIPE THAT STUPID
SMILE OFF YOUR FACE!
- AND YET I STILL KNOW HER
TO BE THE FOOLISH WOMAN
WHO FOLLOWED YOU
IN DEATH 50 YEARS AGO.
- NO! DON'T YOU DARE!
DON'T YOU TOUCH HER!
NOT NOW OR EVER!
AAH!
AAH! AAH!
[COUGHING]
- INUYASHA!
- HOW DARE HE?
HOW DARE HE!
- NO. IT MAKES NO SENSE.
- IF HER TRUE WISH
WAS TO SAVE INUYASHA
AND NOT BREAK THE SPELL,
WHY DO THE ONE THING
SHE OUGHT NOT TO HAVE DONE?
BUT SHE DID.
KIKYO AS GOOD AS GAVE ME
THIS BODY HERSELF.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- SO NARAKU HAS A NEW BODY.
DON'T THINK
WE'RE HAPPY ABOUT IT.
WE'RE ACTUALLY KIND OF WORRIED.
INUYASHA'S GOT KIKYO,
MIROKU, HIS WIND TUNNEL,
AND SANGO HAS KOHAKU.
YOU WILL SAVE US,
WON'T YOU, KIKYO?
YOU KNOW THOSE ARE
OUR JEWEL SHARDS, RIGHT?
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
NEXT TIME,
"KIKYO CAPTURED BY NARAKU."
SEE YOU SOON!