- [GASPING, GIGGLING]
- MASTER HITEN IS HANDSOME,
BUT MASTER MANTAN IS
POSITIVELY DASHING.
- WHAT I WOULDN'T GIVE TO
RUN MY FINGERS THROUGH HIS
LUXURIOUS BLACK LOCKS.
- HA HA HA!
JUST AS I SUSPECTED.
HAVING A THICK HEAD
OF HAIR IS ALL I NEEDED
TO MAKE ME AS POPULAR
AS MY ELDER BROTHER HITEN.
OH! MY TRESSES!
[MOANING]
- AAH!
- OH, NO!
- NO, WAIT,
I HAVE SPECIAL ORDNANCE.
I CAN MAKE IT GROW BACK! HONEST!
OH, NO, I'M LOSING MY CHARISMA.
I MUST FIND SOME HAIR.
HUH?
AAAAHHHHH!
OOMP!
SINCE REACHING PUBERTY,
MY DREAMS HAVE ALL ENDED
IN THE SAME MANNER.
MY HAIR FALLS OUT, DASHING MY
HOPES IN ONE CRUSHING BLOW.
OH, WHAT I WOULD GIVE
FOR A FULL HEAD OF
SILKY-SMOOTH HAIR.
IT MAY NOT DEEM ME HITEN'S
EQUAL WITH THE FAIRER SEX,
BUT I'M CONFIDENT THAT WITH
SOME COVERAGE ON MY CRANIUM,
I WOULD ATTRACT
AT LEAST A FEW COURTESANS.
- TIME TO HUNT, MANTAN.
- I'M WITH A STUD DOG.
- UHH-YAAH!
- [MUTTERING, SCREAMING]
- AWAY, LITTLE RODENTS.
- AAAAAHHHH!
- IF I HIT HIM THERE,
I CAN BRING HIM DOWN.
- [MOANING]
- WHAT'S HIS PROBLEM?
- AAAARRRGHHH!
- I BELIEVE I'VE HEARD MY FILL.
IT'S CLEAR THAT YOU DO HAVE
SOME JEWELS FOR US, INUYASHA--
JEWELS THAT WILL BE MINE!
- NOT IN MY LIFETIME, PAL.
- AAAAHHHH!
YAAAAHHH!
NO ONE CAN WITHSTAND
MY ATTACKS FOR VERY LONG.
- [GRUNTING]
- YOU DO HAVE POWER,
BUT NO STYLE.
THIS SHOULD BE
AN INTERESTING BATTLE.
- AND HOPEFULLY YOUR LAST.
- HUH. YOU WISH ME TO DRAW OUT
THIS GAME, I SEE.
FINE. I SHALL RELISH IN
YOUR PROLONGED SUFFERING.
- HA HA! I'VE HEARD
SIMILAR THREATS FROM
A NUMBER OF POOR FOOLS
WHOSE MEMORIES I KEEP ALIVE
BY DANCING ON THEIR TOMBSTONES.
- PERHAPS IN YOUR DREAMS.
ENOUGH DELAY.
TIME TO MEET YOUR OWN
UNFORTUNATE DEMISE!
- UGH!
- HYAAH!
AAAAA-JHUUU!
ENJOY YOUR LAST
MOMENTS OF LIFE.
- ONE TOUCH OF THIS LIGHTNING,
AND I'M A GONER.
[GRUNTING]
- BOY, HITEN'S BUSY.
I'M CERTAIN INUYASHA
CAN HOLD HIM OFF.
MEANWHILE, I'LL FIND
A WAY TO SAVE KAGOME.
- INUYASHA!
- HA HA HA!
GIVE HIM A SEND-OFF
THAT IS UNRIVALED!
I'LL LEND MY ASSISTANCE.
- NO FAIR!
THAT'S TWO AGAINST ONE!
- AAAAHHH!
OOMPFF!
- ONE DOWN. OHH!
AAAAHHHH!
- AH! AH!
- HA! KAGOME!
- HA! A TRUE WARRIOR NEVER
PUTS A WOMAN BEFORE A BATTLE.
- UGH! HOLD ON, KAGOME.
I'LL COME FOR YOU
AS SOON AS I FINISH HIM OFF.
- HURRY, 'CAUSE GRAVITY ISN'T
EXACTLY ON MY SIDE HERE.
UGH! UHH!
OH, WELL, AT LEAST THE FALL
DIDN'T KILL ME.
- NO, BUT I MIGHT.
- AAH! I THOUGHT YOU WERE DEAD!
- WENCH!
- AAAAHHHH!
UH!
[GASP]
- TIME TO USE MY FOX MAGIC!
- HMMM?
HAAAAAAHHHH!
OOOMPFF.
- GET AWAY
WHILE YOU CAN, KAGOME!
- NO ARGUMENTS HERE.
WOW, NICE MOVE DOWN THERE.
- AW, IT WAS NOTHING.
- IT'S FAR TOO
EARLY FOR CELEBRATION.
- YOU AND YOUR BIG MOUTH.
- SHIPPO'S SO-CALLED
FOX MAGIC IS ALL ABOUT ILLUSION.
- THAT'S AN ILLUSION?
LOOKS PRETTY REAL TO ME.
- AND YET IT IS NOT.
BEHOLD.
- THAT FOX TYKE
WILL PAY FOR HIS TRICKS.
OH, OH, OHHH...
OH, NO, MY BEAUTIFUL HAIR!
GONE! THEY'RE ALL GONE!
EVERY LAST ONE OF
MY HAIRS HAS FALLEN!
- AAAAAHHHHH!
- YOU HAVE PLUCKED
MY LAST STRANDS OF HAIR!
- LOOKS LIKE WE'VE ADDED
FUEL TO THE PROVERBIAL FIRE.
- YOU SAID IT.
- I CAN SMELL YOUR FEAR.
I'LL HUNT YOU DOWN
AND USE ONE FOR MY HAIR POTION
AND THE OTHER FOR A NEW PELT.
- GOT ANY BRIGHT IDEAS?
SOMETHING TELLS ME
WE'RE IN TROUBLE.
WAIT A MINUTE.
THAT ARROW.
MAYBE I COULD USE IT AGAIN.
SHIPPO, I NEED YOUR HELP.
- HHMMM?
- GRRRR...
OVER THERE!
HHMMM.
THERE'S THE LITTLE WENCH.
DID YOU HONESTLY THINK YOU
COULD ELUDE A THUNDER BROTHER?
- YEAH, ACTUALLY,
YOU SLIMY MUDSKIPPER.
- HUH?
- FUNNY, I JUST CAN'T DO
A THING WITH MY HAIR TODAY.
- OH!
WHAT TRICKERY IS THIS?
- I'LL BE TAKING THAT ARROW
BACK, IF YOU DON'T MIND.
- AAHH!
YOU'RE THAT MISERABLE FOX.
- IN THE FLESH AND BLOOD.
HERE FOR MY FATHER'S REVENGE.
- HOLD HIM DOWN, SHIPPO.
THIS MAY BE OUR LAST CHANCE.
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS HIT
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD
IN HIS FOREHEAD.
HERE GOES NOTHING!
- URGH!
DAMN YOU, WENCH!
- OH!
AAAAAHHHH!
- YOUR TURN.
- UURRHHH...
INUYASHA, HELP.
- HUH! UH! KAGOME!
- DIDN'T THINK MY ADVICE
ABOUT WOMEN WORTH HEEDING?
- AAAHH!
UGH...
- PATHETIC.
YOU DON'T LIVE UP
TO YOUR REPUTATION.
HUMAN COMPASSION WILL
PROVE YOUR UNDOING, HALF-BREED.
WHICH SHOULD DIE FIRST,
THIS CURSED WRETCH OR THAT ODD
WOMAN HE'S PREOCCUPIED WITH?
- I'LL DEAL WITH
THIS LOSER AFTERWARD.
I'VE GOTTA SAVE KAGOME FIRST.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK, MANTAN?
SHOULD WE PUT THESE FOOLS
OUT OF THEIR MISERY
OR MAKE THEM
SUFFER A LITTLE LONGER?
- I'M IN NO RUSH, HITEN.
I'M QUITE ENJOYING MYSELF.
HRRR! WHAT IS IT ABOUT THE
SIGHT OF A WOMAN BEFORE DEATH
THAT IS SO
EXQUISITELY IRRESISTIBLE?
- AAAAH! LET HER GO!
- HHHHRRR!
- AAAAHHHH!
OH! OOH! AAHH...
OH...GRRRRRRR...
- HA HA HA HA!
WHEN I'M DONE,
I HAVE A SURPRISE FOR YOU.
MY GIRTH HAS BEEN
EXPANDING OF LATE,
AND I COULD USE
ANOTHER SMALL FOX PELT
TO KEEP WARM AT NIGHT.
IT'LL BE LIKE A FAMILY REUNION.
- GRRRRR...
- SHOULD I SLAY YOU FIRST OR
SKIN YOU ALIVE LIKE YOUR FATHER?
PERHAPS I SHOULD SEVER
YOUR TOES AND USE THEM
FOR A NEW SET OF EARRINGS.
- VERY CLEVER, MANTAN.
IF I DIDN'T KNOW YOU BETTER,
I'D SAY YOU WERE
BECOMING QUITE THE VILLAIN.
- HU-HA! HU-HA! HU-HA!
HOW KIND OF YOU
TO SAY SO, HITEN.
HU-HA! HU-HA!
- GRRR! YOU WON'T
GET AWAY WITH THIS!
ARGH! GRRRR...
- HMMM, TRYING TO
HASTEN YOUR FATE?
- I WON'T LET GO,
NOT IF IT KILLS ME.
- RELEASE ME AT ONCE,
YOU LITTLE PEST.
- GRRRR...
- RELEASE ME IMMEDIATELY,
FOX TYKE.
REMOVE THOSE BABY TEETH
FROM ME NOW,
OR I'LL HAVE TO RETHINK
THE ORDER OF MY VICTIMS.
- UH!
- MANTAN, CAREFUL YOU DON'T SOIL
THAT PRECIOUS
FOX STOLE OF YOURS.
WOULDN'T WANT TO
SEE IT SOAKED WITH BLOOD.
- THANKS FOR THE TIP, HITEN.
- GRRRRRR...
- HEY, I'LL BE THE FIRST TO
ADMIT I'VE RACKED UP MY SHARE
OF BAD KARMA IN THE PAST,
BUT I'M INNOCENT
COMPARED TO YOU TWO SWINE.
BLADES OF BLOOD!
- FINALLY, THIS IS
STARTING TO GET INTERESTING.
- YAAHH!
- NICE THROW IF
YOU'RE AIMING AT THE ROCKS.
- DID I GET HIM?
- HUH?
- OOOOHHHHH!
OOMPFF.
- MANTAN, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- OH, SHIPPO.
THE TETSUSAIGA.
I'VE GOT TO
BRING IT TO INUYASHA.
- DON'T LEAVE MY FATHER.
- HUH? YES, OF COURSE.
BUT I CAN'T CARRY
THE SWORD AND YOUR FATHER BACK.
- MANTAN!
- KAGOME, GET OUT OF THERE
BEFORE HE KILLS YOU!
- AAAH!
UGH. OHHH...
- UNH! MANTAN.
- OHHH, HITEN, THEY'RE GONE.
EVERY LAST STRAND
OF MY HAIR HAS FALLEN,
AND WITH THEM MY HOPES
OF BECOMING HAPPY.
- DON'T BE SO FOOLISH, MANTAN.
WE CAN MAKE IT GROW BACK.
- IT'S NO USE KIDDING MYSELF.
I'LL NEVER HAVE
YOUR BEAUTIFUL HAIR.
YOU WERE FORTUNATE ENOUGH
TO INHERIT FATHER'S LOOKS,
BUT FATE SMOTE ME.
IT WAS MY UNFORTUNATE
LOT IN LIFE TO RESEMBLE
OUR HOMELY MOTHER,
WITH HER RECEDING HAIRLINE AND
DECIDEDLY REPTILIAN COUNTENANCE.
HOW I LONGED FOR
THE LOOKS OF YOU AND FATHER.
- BEAUTY ISN'T ABOUT
WHAT'S ON THE OUTSIDE.
I WOULDN'T CHANGE
A THING ABOUT YOU, BROTHER.
I LOVE EVERY LAST
BALD INCH OF YOU.
- THANK YOU,
EVEN IF YOU DON'T MEAN IT.
SAY A PRAYER
FOR ME WHEN I'M GONE.
PRAY THAT I'LL BE REBORN
AS A FUZZY CATERPILLAR,
COVERED IN HAIR
FROM HEAD TO FURRY TOE.
NO, BROTHER,
WHO AM I TRYING TO KID?
I'D RATHER BE REBORN BALD AGAIN.
I'D MAKE THAT SACRIFICE IF I
COULD BE REBORN AS YOUR BROTHER.
WOULDN'T THAT BE NICE, HITEN?
- MANTAN!
PLEASE DON'T DIE!
- KAGOME!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- I'M OK,
BUT I DROPPED THE TETSUSAIGA
WHEN WE WERE HIT
BY THE LIGHTNING ATTACK.
- NO PROBLEM.
LOTS MORE WHERE
THAT CAME FROM.
- I JUST WANTED YOU TO KNOW
I'M SORRY I MESSED UP.
- DAMN RIGHT YOU MESSED UP.
YOU MESSED UP BIG TIME!
BUT SWORD OR NO SWORD,
YOU'RE WRONG IF YOU THINK
I'M GONNA LET HITEN
GET THE BETTER OF ME!
- MANTAN...
YOU WRETCHES!
YOU SLAUGHTERED MY BROTHER!
MY DEAR MANTAN.
[SOBBING]
REST ASSURED THAT WE SHALL
ALWAYS BE AS ONE, BROTHER.
AAAUUGH!
- HITEN'S A CANNIBAL?
- WAIT. THINGS ARE NOT
ALWAYS WHAT THEY APPEAR.
HITEN BIT INTO
HIS BROTHER'S HEAD
TO FUSE THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS
WITH HIS OWN BODY.
MASTER, YOU MUST BE EVEN
MORE CAREFUL THAN BEFORE,
FOR HITEN NOW HOLDS
THE POWER OF 5 JEWEL SHARDS.
- GEE, YOU THINK?
HEY, YOU WANT TO TRY
EXPLAINING YOUR NOTICEABLE
ABSENCE UP UNTIL NOW?
- [COUGHING]
- CONVENIENT HOW YOU DISAPPEARED
JUST WHEN THE GOING GOT ROUGH.
- YOU CATCH THAT?
THAT'S WHAT WE CALL SARCASM.
AS IN, IT WASN'T CONVENIENT
THAT YOU BAILED ON US WHEN
WE NEEDED YOU MOST.
- I DIDN'T BAIL ON YOU.
I HAD TO MAKE AN ITCH
THAT NEEDED SCRATCHING.
- LOOK OUT!
- HOW DARE YOU
STRIKE DOWN MY BELOVED BROTHER?
I SHALL NOT STOP
TILL I'VE RETURNED THE DEED.
- HIS THUNDER PIKE
IS EVEN STRONGER THAN BEFORE.
HE HAS THE POWER OF
5 JEWEL SHARDS NOW,
AND I HAVE A REAL
FIGHT ON MY HANDS.
KAGOME, TAKE SHIPPO
AND GET AS FAR AWAY FROM
HERE AS YOU'RE ABLE TO.
- WE CAN'T LEAVE YOU.
- DO IT NOW.
HMM.
- I SHALL AVENGE MY BROTHER!
PREPARE TO DIE!
- I CAN'T AVOID IT!
- MY LORD,
USE THE SHEATH OF TETSUSAIGA.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- USE THE SHEATH, AND IT WILL
STAVE OFF THE LIGHTNING BOLT.
QUICKLY!
- YOU'D BETTER BE RIGHT.
[GRUNTING]
- WHAT?
- HUH?
WOW, IT REALLY WORKED.
- JUST AS I PRESUMED.
THE SHEATH KEEPS THE ALMIGHTY
TETSUSAIGA'S POWER IN CHECK,
SO NATURALLY IT CAN REPEL
A MERE LIGHTNING BOLT.
WHEW! GLAD MY HUNCH
WAS CORRECT ON THAT ONE.
- YOU SENT ME INTO BATTLE
ARMED WITH A MERE HUNCH?
- I WOULDN'T EXACTLY CALL IT
A MERE HUNCH, MY LORD--
MORE LIKE
A HIGHLY EDUCATED GUESS.
BUT LET'S GET BACK TO
THE MORE PERTINENT MATTER
OF ESCAPING WITH OUR LIVES.
- NO CHANCE.
I'M GONNA USE THIS BABY
TO DEFEAT THAT DEMON.
- HAAAH-YAHHH!
- IF I CAN BLAST THROUGH
THE CORE, I CAN DEFEAT HIM.
HUH?
AAAAAHHHH!
- SPLENDID PLAN--
IN THEORY, THAT IS.
- UGH!
- INUYASHA!
- HUH?
FATHER'S FUR.
- SHIPPO, YOU ALL RIGHT?
- KAGOME?
WHAT HAPPENED TO MANTAN?
- INUYASHA BROUGHT HIM DOWN.
BUT NOW HITEN'S
THIRSTY FOR REVENGE.
- HAAAA-AHH!
- INUYASHA'S GETTING TIRED.
- HITEN'S HARD TO MATCH
WITH THOSE FLYING WHEELS.
- HITEN USES WHEELS TO FLY.
THAT'S IT!
- THOSE EXTRA JEWEL SHARDS
HAVE INCREASED HIS SPEED.
- WHAT ARE YOU
SEARCHING FOR, KAGOME?
- OH, RIGHT, WHAT GOOD'S
AN ARROW WITHOUT A BOW?
- COMING RIGHT UP.
DON'T ASK QUESTIONS.
JUST LET ME TAKE CARE OF THIS.
- HE'S GONNA
TRANSFORM INTO A BOW.
I WANTED A BOW, NOT A SNAIL.
- I AM A BOW.
- HAAAA-YAAH!
- OOHHH!
- WHAT'S TAKING YOU, KAGOME?
HURRY UP AND FIRE.
- I ONLY HAVE ONE ARROW LEFT,
AND I'M NOT EXACTLY
A MARKSMAN, YOU KNOW.
- YOU WILL BE
WITH ME AS YOUR GUIDE.
- HUH? THANKS, SHIPPO.
LET'S GET THAT SUCKER.
YEAH!
THE GIRL CAN SHOOT.
- HE'S MINE.
- YOUR CONFIDENCE IS ANNOYING.
- WHAT'S HE THINKING?
MASTER INUYASHA MAY BE STRONG,
BUT TAKING HOLD OF THE THUNDER
PIKE IS FOOLHARDY INDEED.
OH, MY!
- WAIT A MINUTE, MYOGA.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
FIGHTING WITH INUYASHA.
- LET GO OF THE PIKE, MY LORD.
- I DON'T NEED
THIS THING ANYMORE.
- DON'T LET GO OF
THE SHEATH, FOOL.
IT'S YOUR ONLY CHANCE
TO TRIUMPH.
- I'LL DO THINGS MY WAY.
NOT BAD FOR A HALF-BREED,
HEY, HITEN?
- WELL, THAT'S
ONE WAY OF DEFEATING HIM.
- WHATEVER
WORKS FOR YOU, I SAY.
- HEY-HO FOR MASTER INUYASHA.
HE SLUGGED HIM
RIGHT IN THE KISSER!
DOWNED HIM IN THE FINAL ROUND
WITH THE OLD RIGHT HOOK!
YEAH!
- WEREN'T YOU JUST CALLING HIM
A FOOL A FEW MINUTES AGO?
- OHH.
I'VE NEVER BEEN
STRUCK IN THE FACE BEFORE,
AND I REFUSE TO
ALLOW IT AGAIN.
- UH-OH. THIS IS BAD.
- HE'S GONNA EXPLODE.
- I'LL SEE YOU IN HELL,
YOU SWINE!
- THE SHEATH'S
STARTING TO CRACK!
- [GRUNTING]
- I SHALL RELISH YOUR DEMISE
MORE THAN ANY OTHER, HALF-BREED.
- MASTER INUYASHA IS POWERFUL,
BUT IF THE TETSUSAIGA SHEATH
SHOULD SHATTER...
- THEN HE'LL LOSE.
I'VE GOTTA GET THE TETSUSAIGA
TO INUYASHA SOMEHOW.
- RIGHT, I'M ON IT.
- SHIPPO, COME BACK.
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS.
GET BACK HERE.
- HUH?
- WAIT, COME BACK!
- OH, NO. HITEN MUST HAVE
GAINED MANTAN'S ABILITIES
AS WELL AS HIS JEWEL SHARDS.
- KAGOME!
RUN FOR IT!
- AAHH!
- KAGOME!
- HUH, WOULDN'T WASTE
MY BREATH ON HER.
- KAGOME!
- WHAT A SHAME.
IT SEEMS THAT SHE AND
THAT FOX CHILD ARE DEAD.
- YOU'LL PAY FOR THIS.
YOU'VE SLAUGHTERED MY FRIENDS!
DAMN YOU!
- HAAH!
THAT'S RIGHT, HALF-BREED.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND IT.
HE FIGHTS AS WELL AS
ANY REAL DEMON I'VE
EVER ENCOUNTERED.
- YOU'LL REGRET THE DAY
YOU EVER CROSSED ME.
I PROMISE YOU THAT.
- I THINK THE BLOOD'S
GONE TO YOUR HEAD
EVER SINCE YOU LOST
YOUR BELOVED WOMAN.
WHEN WILL YOU EVER LEARN
THAT NO WOMAN IS WORTH
RISKING A BATTLE OVER?
A BROTHER'S REVENGE,
ON THE OTHER HAND,
IS WELL WORTH
FIGHTING TO THE DEATH FOR.
- THE SHEATH IS ABOUT TO BREAK!
- HE'S MINE.
- TETSUSAIGA.
- THE SHEATH HAS SUMMONED
THE TETSUSAIGA.
- TETSUSAIGA!
- OOHHH...
I WAS DEFEATED.
THIS HALF-DEMON,
HE DEFEATED BOTH OF US.
- LORD INUYASHA,
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
- I DON'T CARE ABOUT THEM.
IF ONLY I'D TAKEN CARE OF
HITEN SOONER,
I COULD HAVE SAVED
KAGOME AND SHIPPO.
- INUYASHA.
- HUH?
KAGOME?
- INUYASHA, YOU FOUGHT
THE BATTLE HARD AND WELL.
- AND IN THE END I WAS FINALLY
ABLE TO AVENGE MY FATHER.
- WITNESS--THE SOULS HAVE COME
TO BID YOU A FINAL FAREWELL
BEFORE THEY MAKE THEIR DEPARTURE
TO THE OTHER SIDE.
- HUH?
WAIT!
DON'T LEAVE ME!
- HUH?
- KAGOME!
HUH?
- INUYASHA?
- BUT--HEY, YOU'RE STILL HERE.
- YEAH. WHAT'S WITH
THE "DON'T LEAVE ME" STUFF?
- FATHER? YOU MUST HAVE
USED FOXFIRE TO PROTECT
US DURING THE BATTLE.
- I SHOULD CLARIFY.
WHEN I SAID SOULS,
I REALLY MEANT TO SAY FOXFIRE
THAT SHOT OUT FROM
THE FUR OF SHIPPO'S FATHER.
- YEAH, SURE, I MAKE
THAT MISTAKE ALL THE TIME.
- WELL, YOU'RE ONLY HUMAN--
OR HALF HUMAN.
- DO YOU MIND?
- HUNH!
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT
FOR THAT SAPPY "YOU FOUGHT
THE GOOD FIGHT" LINE.
DIE IF YOU'RE GONNA DIE.
IT'S NOT LIKE
IT MATTERS TO ME ANY.
- HUH?
- [MUTTERING INDISTINCTLY]
- COME ON, INUYASHA.
YOUR LIPS ARE FLAPPING,
BUT I'M NOT GETTING ANY AUDIO.
HOW ABOUT TELLING ME
WHY YOU'RE SO UPSET?
- I BELIEVE MASTER INUYASHA
IS ASHAMED THAT HE BELIEVED
YOU WERE DEAD,
AND IN A MOMENT OF GRIEF
MAY HAVE REVEALED MORE THAN
HE BARGAINED FOR.
- WHAT ARE YOU STILL TAGGING
ALONG WITH US FOR, SHIPPO?
- WHY DO YOU THINK?
YOU NEED ME, AND YOU KNOW IT.
- GO EASY ON HIM.
HE DOESN'T HAVE A HOME,
AND BESIDES, HE'S NOT
HURTING ANYONE.
- YEAH. I'M
A DEFENSELESS ORPHAN.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO
GET BY IN THE WORLD?
- ALL RIGHT,
YOU CAN STAY WITH US,
BUT ONLY UNTIL
YOU CAN LOOK AFTER YOURSELF.
SO, SHIPPO, YOUR VILLAGE CALLED.
THEY'RE MISSING THEIR IDIOT.
- KAGOME,
HE'S BEING MEAN TO ME.
- NOW LOOK WHAT YOU'VE DONE.
YOU'VE HURT HIS FEELINGS.
SAY YOU'RE SORRY.
[WHAM]
- OWW!
- [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- THE ANCIENT SHRINE
WHERE I LIVE
IS ENSHROUDED IN
HUNDREDS OF MYTHS AND LEGENDS.
GRANDPA'S ALWAYS GOING ON
ABOUT OMENS AND EXORCISMS,
BUT UP UNTIL NOW I'VE NEVER
TAKEN THEM TOO SERIOUSLY.
BUT MY SKEPTICISM
CHANGES OVERNIGHT
WHEN AN OLD NOH MASK THAT HAD
BEEN LOCKED UP IN THE STOREROOM
BURNS THROUGH THE WRITTEN OMENS
AND COMES AFTER US.
NEXT TIME,
"TERROR OF
THE ANCIENT NOH MASK."
SEE YOU SOON.