>> SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
>> WE WERE SEARCHING FOR NARAKU
WHEN AN EVIL DEMON CAME
AFTER US.
LUCKILY, KOGA CAME ALONG AND
SAVED ME.
THEN A YOUNG GIRL FROM THE WOLF
DEMON TRIBE SHOWED UP LOOKING
FOR HIM.
>> YOU PROMISED ME.
>> ALL RIGHT, DON'T OVERDO IT.
AND WHEN IT GETS TO BE TOO HARD,
DON'T YOU WORRY.
ONE DAY, I'LL MAKE YOU MY WIFE,
AYUMI.
UH, ARE YOU POSITIVE?
ARE YOU SURE I SAID THAT AND NOT
SOMETHING ELSE?
>> HMM...
>> DO YOU THINK NARAKU SENT THAT
HAIR DEMON AS A DIVERSION
FOR US?
>> WE'LL FIND OUT ONCE WE
CAPTURE IT.
>> MAYBE IT KNOWS WHERE TO FIND
NARAKU.
>> HOW ABOUT SAVING THE TALK
TILL AFTER WE RESCUE KAGOME?
I HOPE YOU'RE SAFE, KAGOME.
>> HRMPH.
>> AND THE ELDER OF THE WOLF
DEMON TRIBE IS YOUR GRANDFATHER?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
I CALL HIM GRAMPS.
>> YOU MUST HAVE A REASON FOR
COMING DOWN THE MOUNTAIN
LIKE THIS.
>> YES, I DO.
A STRANGE MIASMA HAS DESCENDED
FROM THE NORTHERN MOUNTAINS
RECENTLY.
>> OH, YEAH?
>> GRAMPS SAID IT SMELLS
OF A DEMON.
>> A DEMON?
>> MM-HMM.
AROUND THE TIME WHEN THE MIASMA
DESCENDED, INFIGHTING INCREASED
AMONG THE WOLF DEMON TRIBES
IN THE EAST AND NORTH AND THOSE
IN THE SOUTH AND WEST.
SO GRAMPS DECIDED TO MARRY ME
OFF TO ONE OF THE STRONG YOUNG
WARRIORS TO BUILD AN ALLIANCE.
>> OH, YOU MEAN LIKE A POLITICAL
MARRIAGE.
HUH.
>> LUCKILY, KOGA AND I WERE
ALREADY PROMISED TO EACH OTHER.
>> I THINK I'D REMEMBER
IF WE WERE!
>> GRAMPS BELIEVED THAT KOGA
WOULD BE ABLE TO FIND FOLLOWERS.
AND I DIDN'T MIND THE THOUGHT OF
MARRYING KOGA.
>> SO IT WASN'T JUST A POLITICAL
MARRIAGE.
>> DAMN, EVERYONE'S GETTING ALL
WORKED UP OVER A STUPID MIASMA.
YURA'LL MAKE ME MAKE PEACE.
BUT ALL YOU GOT TO DO IS CRACK
THEIR HEADS TOGETHER AND THEY'LL
START LISTENING.
>> IF IT WERE THAT EASY,
THEN WE WOULD HAVE DONE IT!
IN ORDER TO BRING THE TRIBES
TOGETHER, WE NEED THEIR TRUST.
US GETTING MARRIED AND SETTLING
DOWN IS THE ONLY SOLUTION.
>> GEE, SORRY, BUT IT JUST AIN'T
MY STYLE.
>> KOGA!
>> WHAT I WANT TO DO MORE THAN
ANYTHING RIGHT NOW IS GET
NARAKU'S HEAD.
I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR ANYTHING
ELSE IN MY LIFE, GOT IT?
>> YOU WON'T CHANGE YOUR MIND?
>> NO CHANCE.
GO BACK TO THE MOUNTAIN.
>> GRR!
>> KOGA!
>> OH...
>> AYUMI, MAYBE YOU SHOULD STOP
LISTENING TO WHAT THE ELDER SAYS
AND START DOING WHAT YOU WANT
TO DO.
>> [GROWLING]
SHARD.
>> AYUMI, THIS CONVERSATION
IS OVER.
>> WAIT A MINUTE, KOGA.
>> IT'S A DEMONIC AURA.
>> IS SOMETHING COMING?
>> DAMN THAT INUYASHA!
HE MUST HAVE LET THE DEMON
GET AWAY!
[SNIFFS]
I CAN SMELL IT.
IT'S CLOSE BY.
>> OH, NO!
KOGA, LET'S GO BACK TO INUYASHA
AND THE OTHERS.
>> THERE'S NOTHING TO WORRY
ABOUT, KAGOME.
I'M HERE TO PROTECT YOU.
>> I APPRECIATE THE OFFER AND
EVERYTHING, HUH...
>> COME ON, KOGA, WE DON'T HAVE
TIME FOR THIS.
KOGA KEEPS SAYING HE LOVES HER,
BUT I'M NOT SO SURE SHE FEELS
THE SAME WAY.
>> AAH!
>> HEY, DEMON, I'LL TAKE YOU ON,
THEN YOU CAN ANSWER A FEW
QUESTIONS FROM ME, GOT IT?
>> HUH?
>> UH, WHERE'D HE GO?
THAT WAY?
HUH?
>> UH, THE HAIR'S COMING
AFTER US.
>> TO STALL US?
>> IT DOESN'T WANT TO
LET US PASS.
INUYASHA, GO TO KAGOME!
MAKE SURE SHE'S ALL RIGHT!
>> ON MY WAY.
I'LL SAVE YOU, KAGOME.
>> [GROWLING]
YOU WON'T GET AWAY NOW.
I'LL DEVOUR YOU WHOLE, SACRED
JEWEL SHARD AND ALL.
>> AYUMI, I SHOULDN'T BE ASKING
YOU THIS, BUT WOULD YOU TAKE
CARE OF KAGOME?
>> WHO, ME?
LOOK AFTER HER?
>> KAGOME, YOU WAIT HERE WITH
AYUMI.
>> HANG ON, KOGA!
>> SIZE ISN'T ALL THAT COUNTS,
BIG GUY!
WAIT AND SEE!
UP AND OVER.
AAH!
YOU'VE COME THIS FAR
TO HUNT ME DOWN.
NOW HOW ABOUT YOU TELL ME WHERE
NARAKU IS?
>> THE HAIR FELL OUT.
>> HUH?
>> DAMN!
>> KOGA!
AAH!
>> STRIKE THE DEMON.
>> UH!
A SCARED ARROW?
IS KAGOME A PRIESTESS?
>> DAMN YOU!
>> ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, AYUMI?
DON'T WORRY, I'LL GET HIM
OFF YOU.
>> WHY DON'T YOU GET AWAY?
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> KOGA'S DOING THIS FOR YOU.
HE'S DOING IT TO PROTECT YOU.
>> DON'T SELL KOGA SHORT, AYUMI.
HE'S FIGHTING TO PROTECT
BOTH OF US.
>> AAH!
>> IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
>> INUYASHA!
>> ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, KAGOME?
>> YEAH, WE'RE ALL FINE HERE,
THANKS.
>> INUYASHA?
HE MUST BE ONE OF
KAGOME'S FRIENDS.
>> KOGA, WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
HOW COULD YOU PUT KAGOME IN
DANGER LIKE THIS?
>> YEAH, LOOK WHO'S TALKING.
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT FOR
LETTING THE DEMON ESCAPE.
>> I'LL PROTECT KAGOME, SO YOU
CAN STAY OUT OF THIS, WOLF CUB.
>> I'M THE ONE WHO'S GONNA
PROTECT HER.
>> YOU'RE DOING A LOUSY JOB
SO FAR.
>> GRR.
>> KOGA, INUYASHA'S HERE,
SO DON'T GO OVERBOARD
ON MY ACCOUNT.
>> KAGOME!
>> WAIT A MINUTE.
IS KOGA...
>> [GROWL]
>> WATCH OUT, INUYASHA.
DON'T GET TANGLED UP IN THAT
DEMON'S HAIR.
>> HUH, DON'T WORRY, KAGOME.
JUST WATCH ME.
I'LL GET HIM WITH ONE STRIKE
OF MY WINDSCAR.
>> DAMN MUTT.
TRUST YOU TO COME INTO THE
PICTURE, TRYING TO GET
ALL THE GLORY.
I'M GONNA GET THE DEMON!
>> COULD THIS BE
AN UNREQUITED LOVE?
AAH!
>> OOH!
WHOA!
>> I'LL DEVOUR YOU WHOLE,
SWORD AND ALL.
>> HURRY, INUYASHA,
YOU HAVE TO SAVE HIM.
>> I DO?
>> YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN DO IT.
HURRY BEFORE HE'S EATEN ALIVE!
GET GOING!
>> I REALLY COULDN'T CARE LESS
WHAT HAPPENS TO KOGA.
>> UH!
UH!
>> BUT I CAN'T LET YOU HAVE THE
SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
AH!
MAN, I GOT NOTHING BUT HAIR!
WHAT?
>> INUYASHA!
>> NO ONE WILL STOP ME NOW.
I'VE FINALLY BEEN FREED FROM THE
NARAKU.
>> DAMN YOU!
HUH? WHAT?
>> I'LL USE THE SACRED JEWEL
POWER AND RETURN TO MY FORMER
SELF.
>> WHAT?
>> KAGOME!
>> IS EVERYONE ALL RIGHT?
>> YOU'RE HERE.
>> WHO'S THE GIRL OVER THERE?
>> HER NAME IS AYUMI,
APPARENTLY KOGA'S FIANCEE.
>> HUH?
FIANCEE?
>> WE CAN TALK LATER.
>> WHAT'S THE DEMON'S STORY?
WHERE DID IT COME FROM?
>> HE JUST SAID THAT HE'D BEEN
FREED FROM NARAKU.
>> HUH?
TELL US WHAT THIS IS ALL ABOUT!
>> THAT NARAKU, HE ABANDONED THE
CASTLE AND ME ALONG WITH IT.
>> MEANING IT WASN'T ANOTHER ONE
OF NARAKU'S INCARNATIONS.
>> JUST SOMEONE HE DIDN'T NEED
ANYMORE?
>> YEAH, I CAN SEE HIM
GETTING LEFT BEHIND.
>> HUH.
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN.
YOU'RE TOO UGLY EVEN FOR ONE OF
NARAKU'S DEMONS.
ARGH!
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING, KOGA,
WASTING YOUR TIME SCRAPPING WITH
TRASH LIKE THIS BIG HAIRBALL?
>> YEAH, WELL...
>> UH...
UH...
UH!
>> I GUESS I'LL HAVE TO PROTECT
YOU AS WELL, AYUMI.
NOW STAY THERE, OUT OF THE WAY.
YOU MUTT.
I'LL COME BACK AND DEAL
WITH YOU LATER.
>> OH, REALLY?
>> YEAH.
HEY, DEMON, SORRY TO HEAR YOUR
SOB STORY ABOUT BEING ABANDONED.
DOES THAT MEAN YOU DON'T KNOW
WHERE NARAKU IS?
>> ARGH!
>> AAH!
>> DON'T BE SO HASTY, KOGA.
WE STILL HAVE QUESTIONS
TO ASK IT.
>> DON'T WORRY, YOU'LL GET YOUR
OPPORTUNITY.
ALL RIGHT, DEMON, TELL US
EVERYTHING YOU KNOW,
OR YOU'LL BE SORRY.
>> IT'S USELESS TO
SEARCH FOR HIM.
NARAKU HAS ESCAPED TO A PLACE
WHERE NO ONE CAN TOUCH HIM.
>> HUH?
>> AHH!
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN WHERE NO ONE
CAN TOUCH HIM?
>> HA HA HA!
UNFORTUNATELY FOR YOU, THAT'S
ALL I KNOW.
>> HUH?
>> NARAKU CUT ME OFF BEFORE HE
COULD ACCOMPLISH HIS PLANS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT NARAKU INTENDS
TO DO NEXT.
HA HA HA!
SERVES YOU RIGHT!
>> IT APPEARS TO BE TELLING
THE TRUTH.
>> DAMN, NOT A SINGLE SCRAP
WE CAN USE.
>> HUH.
IF HE DOESN'T KNOW, THEN THERE'S
NOT MUCH WE CAN DO.
HUH.
NOT MUCH, BUT THERE IS ONE THING
THIS TRASH OF A DEMON
IS GOOD FOR.
YAH!
OOH, LET GO OF MY ARM!
>> KOGA!
>> AYUMI!
>> ARGH!
>> SHE DISPELLED HIS MANAKORA!
>> IT'S THE SPIRITUAL POWER
OF THE IRIS!
>> I'LL DEVOUR YOU!
>> KOGA!
>> AYUMI!
>> AAH!
>> THE DEMON'S EATEN THEM!
>> KOGA!
AYUMI!
>> DAMN, I CAN'T USE
THE WINDSCAR.
>> HA HA HA!
FINALLY I HAVE THE SACRED JEWEL
SHARD INSIDE ME.
HA HA HA!
ARGH!
>> AHH!
>> HE NEVER STOOD A CHANCE.
>> KOGA!
YOUR ARM.
THIS IS MY FAULT FOR JUMPING IN.
>> HUH.
THIS IS NOTHING
BUT A FLESH WOUND.
>> HEY, KOGA!
>> YOU'VE FINALLY CAUGHT UP.
>> HUH?
>> I WANT YOU TWO TO REMEMBER
THAT SCENT.
MAKE SURE ALL THE WOLVES DO
AS WELL.
>> ARE YOU PLANNING TO USE THAT
DEMON'S SCENT TO HAVE YOUR
WOLVES SEARCH THE SURROUNDING
AREA FOR NARAKU'S WHEREABOUTS?
>> HUH.
AS IF THAT'D WORK.
IF MERE WOLVES WERE ABLE TO
SNIFF NARAKU OUT, I'D HAVE DONE
IT MYSELF A LONG TIME AGO.
HUH?
HEY, WHERE'D HE GO?
KOGA?
HUH?
WHY, THAT LOUSY--
>> KAGOME, I'M SORRY TO SAY I
HAVE TO BE ON MY WAY NOW.
NEXT TIME WE MEET, I PROMISE TO
BRING YOU NARAKU'S HEAD
ON A PLATTER.
>> LOOK HOW HARD HE'S TRYING,
AND SHE DOESN'T EVEN LIKE HIM.
>> I THINK I'LL PASS.
[NERVOUS LAUGHTER]
>> DON'T LOOK LIKE THAT, KAGOME.
I PROMISE YOU'RE THE WOMAN WHO'S
GONNA BE MY WIFE.
>> WHAT?
>> UH, HEY, WAIT A SEC, KOGA.
A LONG, LONG TIME AGO,
WAY BEFORE YOU MET ME,
YOU PROMISED THAT YOU'D MARRY
AYUMI.
YOU'RE ALREADY ENGAGED TO
SOMEBODY ELSE.
>> LIKE I SAID,
I DON'T REMEMBER.
>> SURE YOU DO.
THINK BACK TO A NIGHT OF
A LUNAR RAINBOW.
YOU MUST REMEMBER SOMETHING.
>> HMM...
LET'S SEE.
RAINBOW...
HUH?
OH, MAN.
MM-HMM.
>> [MOANING]
>> [GROWLING]
>> I'LL MAKE YOU MY WIFE...
WHEN YOU COME DOWN FROM
THE MOUNTAINS.
>> LOOK!
>> HUH?
A LUNAR RAINBOW.
AH...
OH...
[GULPS]
UH, SORRY, BUT I STILL
DON'T REMEMBER.
>> ARE YOU SURE?
DON'T YOU REMEMBER THE RAINBOW?
>> LIKE I SAID,
I REALLY DON'T REMEMBER.
BESIDES, SHE WAS TINY.
HUH.
IT WAS A LONG, LONG TIME AGO.
>> HE'S RIGHT.
LET'S JUST FORGET ABOUT
THE PAST.
I UNDERSTAND HOW IMPORTANT IT IS
FOR YOU TO GO AFTER THIS NARAKU.
>> IS KAGOME PART OF A LOVE
TRIANGLE WITH KOGA AND AYUMI?
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
IT'S MORE LIKE AYUMI CAME TO GET
KOGA AND TAKE HIM BACK WITH HER.
>> BUT KOGA LOVES ONLY KAGOME.
UNLIKE SOME OTHER GUY, HE'S NOT
A TWO-TIMER.
OH!
WHAT'D YOU DO THAT FOR,
INUYASHA?
>> HUH.
SERVES YOU RIGHT.
>> GET YOUR REVENGE ON NARAKU
AND GRAMPS AND I WILL SOMEHOW
MANAGE TO WORK THINGS OUT
WITH THE OTHERS.
>> OK.
>> HMM.
REMEMBER, THOUGH, THAT DOESN'T
MEAN I'LL STOP HOPING YOU'LL
LIVE UP TO YOUR PROMISE.
>> [COLLECTIVE GASP]
>> I'M THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN BE YOUR WIFE.
>> MY WOMAN HAS TO BE ABLE TO
SENSE THE JEWEL SHARDS,
LIKE KAGOME.
SHE CAN SENSE 'EM.
>> SHE CAN?
SHE SENSES WHERE THEY ARE?
UH, THEN I'LL MAKE MYSELF ABLE
TO SENSE THEM, TOO!
>> HUH?
>> YOU WILL, WILL YOU?
AS IF YOU COULD DO THAT.
>> I CAN!
>> YOU CAN'T!
>> I CAN, I SAID!
>> YOU CAN'T, I SAID!
[BOTH GROWLING]
>> HA HA!
>> WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
>> YOU'LL FIND OUT LATER, KOGA.
>> HEY, WAIT!
>> SEE YA!
>> HEY, MIROKU, IF A PERSON
TRAINED, COULD THEY MAKE
THEMSELVES SEE THE SACRED JEWEL
SHARDS LIKE KAGOME?
>> I HIGHLY DOUBT IT.
>> AYUMI CERTAINLY BELIEVES SHE
CAN DO IT.
>> SHE SURE HAS A LOT OF
CONFIDENCE.
>> THAT FOOL AYUMI.
>> OK, KOGA, NOW THAT THAT'S
SETTLED, WHY DON'T YOU HAND OVER
THE JEWEL SHARDS TO SOMEONE WHO
CAN ACTUALLY MAKE GOOD USE
OF THEM?
>> NO WAY!
SEE YA, KAGOME.
>> GOOD-BYE!
>> LUCKY MOVE.
>> YOU KNOW, INUYASHA, I THINK
KOGA'S IDEA ABOUT USING HIS
WOLVES MAKES A LOT OF SENSE.
>> NO CHANCE.
IT'S WAY TO SIMPLE.
IF HIS SCENT COULD BE TRACKED,
THEN WHY WOULD NARAKU LEAVE ALL
THIS TRASH BEHIND?
HUH.
IT'S THE SOURCE OF HIS SCENT.
IT'D BE WAY TOO SLOPPY.
>> AHH...
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> IT'S LIKE NARAKU'S COMPLETELY
CONFIDENT THAT NO ONE WILL EVER
BE ABLE TO FIND HIM.
HE DOESN'T EVEN CARE
IF ANYONE TRIES.
>> HMM.
THAT MAKES A LOT OF SENSE.
AND...
>> HUH?
>> DON'T PLAY DUMB.
WHERE DO YOU THINK NARAKU WENT?
COME ON, SHARE YOUR THEORY
WITH US.
>> HUH.
HRMPH.
YOU'LL HAVE TO FIGURE IT OUT
FOR YOURSELF.
>> HUH.
>> IN OTHER WORDS, HE HASN'T
FIGURED IT OUT YET.
>> I'LL HAVE TO BE SHARPER
THAN EVER.
>> INUYASHA'S RIGHT, THOUGH.
THE DEMON SAID THAT NARAKU HAD
ESCAPED TO A PLACE WHERE NO ONE
COULD GET TO HIM.
WHERE WOULD WE EVEN START
TO LOOK?
>> WE WERE CLOSE TO THE RIVER ON
THAT NIGHT, TOO.
I WON'T LET NARAKU GET THE
BETTER OF ME.
BUT THERE'S NO GUARANTEE THAT
I'LL BE ALIVE AFTER I GET
MY REVENGE.
AYUMI, FORGET ABOUT THAT
NIGHT WE SAW THE RAINBOW.
>> I WON'T FORGET.
I WON'T EVER FORGET THAT HE
PROTECTED ME...
EVEN IF THE RAINBOW FADES.
>> DAMN IT.
JUST WHEN I BECAME ABLE TO BREAK
THROUGH NARAKU'S BARRIER.
>> AHH.
I'M SURE THAT WE'LL FIND NARAKU
SOONER OR LATER IF WE ALL WORK
TOGETHER.
>> AND EXACTLY WHO DO YOU MEAN
BY "ALL"?
ARE YOU INCLUDING KOGA?
EVEN HIS WOLF DEMON FIANCEE HAS
GIVEN UP ON HIM.
IS THAT REALLY THE KIND OF LOW
LIFE YOU'RE GONNA DEPEND ON?
>> UH, DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE
STILL JEALOUS.
>> OF COURSE NOT.
I'M NOT JEALOUS.
>> YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
>> GRR...
LET'S JUST DROP IT, ALL RIGHT?
>> SURE.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO STARTED IT.
>> GRR...
>> COME ON, WHY DON'T YOU JUST
FINISH WHAT YOU WERE SAYING?
>> FORGET IT.
>> NOT LIKELY.
AHH...
IF ONLY INUYASHA COULD BE A BIT
MORE OPEN...
LIKE KOGA AND AYUMI ARE WITH
THEIR FEELINGS.
A LUNAR RAINBOW.
>> HUH.
AIN'T NO SUCH THING AS A RAINBOW
AT NIGHT.
>> THERE IS...
TO THOSE PEOPLE WHO CAN SEE IT.
>> REALLY?
UH...
>> AHH...
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> EVER SINCE NARAKU
DISAPPEARED, ALL KINDS OF DEMONS
WHO HAVE BEEN QUIET UP UNTIL NOW
HAVE STARTED TO ACT UP.
>> WHICH GIVES THE EXORCISTS AND
SLAYERS LOTS OF WORK.
>> LOOKS LIKE WE'VE GOT SOME
COMPETITION.
>> HOW CAN THAT OLD EXORCIST
STAND UP TO MANAKORA?
>> SHE MUST BE EITHER VERY
POWERFUL OR VERY DENSE.
>> LET'S WRAP THIS UP
AND GO HOME.
NEXT TIME, "THE EVIL WITHIN
DEMON'S HEAD CASTLE."
>> A BEAUTIFUL PRINCESS?
I BETTER TAKE CARE OF HER.
>> WHATEVER.
>> THANKS.