- [BIRDS SINGING]
- [GRUNTING]
- THERE.
- AH.
- HMM?
- AHH.
- YOU SURE YOU DIDN'T
FORGET ANYTHING?
- I DON'T GET
TO GO BACK VERY OFTEN,
AND A GIRL'S GOT TO KEEP
THE SHOPPING GODS APPEASED,
YOU KNOW.
THIS IS FOR YOU.
- YES! DRIED POTATOES.
- AND FOR SHIPPO.
HERE YOU GO!
- WOW! THANK YOU, KAGOME!
THIS IS YUMMY.
AAH!
OH, LOOK, IT'S SPINNING
ALL BY ITSELF!
- HERE YOU GO, MIROKU.
- ACCEPTED WITH PLEASURE.
- WHERE'S SANGO?
- SHE HASN'T COME BACK
FROM HER VILLAGE YET.
[CRUNCHING]
- IT'S BEEN DAYS,
SO I THOUGHT FOR SURE
SHE WOULD HAVE COME BACK BY NOW.
- SHE HASN'T BEEN
TO HER VILLAGE IN A WHILE.
SHE PROBABLY HAD LOTS TO DO.
YOU KNOW,
BESIDES REPAIRING HER WEAPON.
- MAYBE SHE'S NOT
GONNA COME BACK
BECAUSE OF A CERTAIN LECHER
WHO WON'T LEAVE HER ALONE.
- I AM GUILTY OF NO SUCH THING!
- SURE, WHATEVER.
- SANGO CAN HANDLE HERSELF,
SO I KNOW THAT
I SHOULDN'T BE WORRIED,
BUT STILL...
- [BIRDS CHIRPING]
- [HAMMERING]
[FIRE CRACKLING]
- [GRUNTING]
[SIZZLING]
- HUH.
WELL, IT'S NOT AS GOOD
AS FATHER'S HANDIWORK WAS,
BUT I HAVE TO ADMIT,
YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT BAD.
AHH.
- [BIRDS CHIRPING]
- DEAR FATHER,
MY FAMILY, AND FRIENDS,
WE'VE FINALLY COME HOME AT LAST.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME FOR
TAKING SO LONG TO BRING
YOUR REMAINS BACK.
UNH!
- NOW, SANGO, DO YOU THINK
YOU CAN CONTINUE
AS A DEMON SLAYER?
- WHY, YES, FATHER.
I BELIEVE I'M SUITED
TO THIS OCCUPATION.
- I SEE.
SANGO, I HAVE TRAINED YOU
NOT MERELY SO YOU CAN
CONTINUE OUR TRADITION.
I WANT YOU TO LIVE
A STRONG LIFE.
- OH, FATHER, WHAT WAS IT
YOU WERE TRYING TO TELL ME?
- [GROWLING]
- HUH?
UNH!
- [SNARLING]
[ROARING]
- AAH!
[MOANING]
- [SNARLS]
- PLEASE STOP!
DON'T HURT HER! LET HER GO!
- KILLALLA!
- [GROWLING]
- WHO ARE YOU,
AND WHAT DO YOU WANT HERE?
- SISTER!
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- WE HAVEN'T HAD
FOOD OR WATER FOR 3 DAYS.
- [STOMACH GROWLING]
- MMM, MMM, MMM.
- ISN'T THIS DELICIOUS, SERENA?
- MM-HMM.
- THERE'S MORE.
DO YOU WANT ANOTHER SERVING?
- YES, PLEASE.
- HUH?
- UM, PARDON MY MANNERS.
I AM SERENA.
- AND I'M HER SISTER,
SASUNA. HA HA!
- THE TWO OF US RECENTLY SET OUT
FROM OUR VILLAGE FOLLOWING LEADS
IN SEARCH OF THE DEMON SLAYERS'
HIDDEN VILLAGE.
- SO YOU ATTACKED ME,
DESPITE THE FACT THAT
YOU KNEW I WAS A SLAYER?
- WE JUST WANTED
TO TEST YOUR SKILLS.
YOU REALLY ARE QUITE GOOD, MISS.
OH!
- WILL YOU TAKE US ON
AS YOUR APPRENTICES?
- APPRENTICES?
- YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU COULD USE A GOOD RUBDOWN.
HA HA HA!
- TEACHER, PLEASE, ACCEPT US.
- NO.
- OH, COME ON, PLEASE, TEACHER?
- I SAID NO.
- PLEASE, TEACHER!
- I AM NOT YOUR TEACHER,
AND NO MEANS NO.
NOW, WOULD YOU LET ME GO?
I'M IN A HURRY!
- WE CANNOT RETURN HOME
TO OUR VILLAGE
UNTIL YOU TAKE US IN
AS YOUR PUPILS
AND TRAIN US
IN THE ART OF DEMON SLAYING!
- PLEASE!
[WAILING]
- [SIGH]
I SUPPOSE I SHOULD HEAR YOU OUT.
- YOU SEE,
MY SISTER SASUNA AND I
LIVE IN A SMALL FARMING VILLAGE
HIGH UP IN THE MOUNTAINS.
WE WANTED TO EXPAND THE FARM,
SO WE STARTED
CLEARING THE MOUNTAIN
BELONGING TO OUR LOCAL DEITY.
THAT WAS WHEN THE DEMONS
BEGAN ATTACKING US.
- LOTS OF THEM,
NOT JUST ONE OR TWO.
- AND SADLY,
MANY OF THE VILLAGERS
HAVE BEEN SLAUGHTERED.
THE ABLE-BODIED PEOPLE
HAVE MOVED TO ANOTHER VILLAGE.
BUT THE ELDERLY AND THOSE
WITH CHILDREN CANNOT LEAVE,
AND THEY SPEND EVERY
WAKING MOMENT LIVING IN TERROR.
- I SEE.
THE DEITY'S FOREST HAD ACTED
AS A BARRIER FOR YOU.
- YES, AND IT WAS
ABOUT THAT TIME
THAT WE HEARD OF A VILLAGE
OF DEMON SLAYERS.
- AS YOU CAN SEE,
THERE ARE NO SLAYERS
LEFT IN THIS VILLAGE.
- OHH.
- HMM.
- MAYBE I COULD GO BACK TO
YOUR VILLAGE WITH YOU TO HELP.
- BUT OUR VILLAGE DOESN'T
HAVE ANY MONEY TO PAY YOU.
WE HAVE COME ONLY TO LEARN.
WE HAD NO INTENTION WHATSOEVER
OF HIRING A DEMON SLAYER
TO BRING BACK HOME WITH US.
- BESIDES,
OUR VILLAGE IS FAR AWAY.
- EVEN IF WE DID STAVE THEM OFF
ONCE OR TWICE,
THOSE DEMONS WOULD RETURN,
SO PLEASE TEACH US
TO DEFEND OURSELVES.
WE WILL TRAIN HARD
FOR OUR PEOPLE.
- SASUNA.
- I'LL DO MY BEST.
- YOU MUST UNDERSTAND,
THE ART OF DEMON SLAYING ISN'T
SOMETHING ONE LEARNS OVERNIGHT.
I SUPPOSE I COULD TEACH YOU HOW
TO DETER LESSER DEMONS, THOUGH.
- OH!
- THANK YOU!
- MIROKU AND THE OTHERS
WILL WAIT FOR ME,
EVEN IF I COME BACK
ONE OR TWO DAYS LATE.
THESE ARE THE WEAPONS
YOU'LL USE TO WARD OFF DEMONS.
- RIGHT!
HMM?
UH...
- HMM.
- THIS IS AS GOOD A PLACE
AS ANY TO START.
DON'T JUST STAND THERE,
HELP ME FAN.
- [COUGHING]
WHAT IS THIS?
- A POWDERED MIXTURE OF HERBS
AND REMEDIES THAT DEMONS DETEST.
- SO THIS WOULD SLAY A DEMON?
- IT WOULD BE ENOUGH
TO PROTECT THE VILLAGE.
- [SQUAWKING]
- [COUGHING]
- THIS SMOKE IS INCREDIBLE!
ARE YOU SURE IT WILL WARD OFF
THE DEMONS, THOUGH?
- [COUGHING]
- UM, SISTER--I MEAN, TEACHER,
ISN'T THERE A MORE EXCITING
TECHNIQUE THAT YOU CAN SHOW US?
- LEARNING TECHNIQUES
WITHOUT FULLY UNDERSTANDING THEM
CAN BE DANGEROUS.
THE DAY IS ALMOST OVER,
SO I'LL SHOW BOTH OF YOU HOW
TO MAKE THIS POWDER TOMORROW.
- HMM.
- SANGO STILL HASN'T COME BACK.
HMM?
- UM, I'D LIKE TO ASK YOU
A QUESTION, KAGOME.
- YEAH?
- DO YOU BELIEVE THAT
STROKING A WOMAN'S BOTTOM
COULD DESTROY THE MUTUAL TRUST
BETWEEN TWO PEOPLE?
- FIRST OF ALL,
TRUST IS BUILT BY RESPECTING
EACH OTHER'S PERSONAL SPACE.
- IS THAT REALLY HOW IT IS?
- IF SANGO DOESN'T COME BACK,
IT'S YOU I'M GOING TO BE
POINTING THE FINGER AT.
- SHE'LL COME BACK, ALL RIGHT.
[METAL JINGLING]
- HE SOUNDS CONFIDENT,
BUT HE SURE DOESN'T LOOK IT.
- HUMPH!
- SERENA, LET ME DO IT!
HAH!
THAT WAS EASY ENOUGH
TO BREAK OFF.
CAN'T BEAT A NINJA'S SKILLS! HA!
- THANKS. I COULDN'T
HAVE DONE IT WITHOUT YOU.
- LOOK AT ALL THIS!
- THIS IS EXACTLY
LIKE OUR FATHER TOLD US.
THESE MATERIALS ARE THE SECRET
TO THE SLAYER'S WEAPONS.
- THESE THINGS?
- THE FANGS, BONES,
HIDES OF DEMONS.
- NO WONDER SLAYERS CAN
WARD OFF THEIR ATTACKS.
- THEN WE CAN
BECOME JUST AS STRONG
IF WE TAKE THESE MATERIALS.
- WE'LL BE ALMOST INVINCIBLE.
- [GASPS]
- WHAT DID YOU STOP FOR?
- WHAT ARE YOU TWO UP TO?
I WANT THE TRUTH!
YOU'RE NO ORDINARY
VILLAGE GIRLS.
- HAH!
- UNH!
- THOSE MOVES.
- CORRECT. BOTH MY SISTER AND I
COME FROM A VILLAGE OF NINJAS.
- [ROARING]
- ONE DAY THE CLAN LORDS
DEMANDED THAT WE SLAY A DEMON,
SOMETHING WE HAD
NEVER DONE BEFORE.
- WE WERE ABLE TO USE OUR NINJA
SKILLS TO DESTROY THE ONE DEMON.
BUT OTHERS CAME SEEKING REVENGE.
OUR PEOPLE KNEW
ONLY NINJA TACTICS,
AND NEARLY ALL WERE DEVOURED
BY THESE DEMONS.
- [SCREAMING]
- SERENA, I THINK IT'S SAFE
FOR US TO COME OUT NOW.
- FATHER!
- FATHER, NO!
FATHER, HOLD ON.
- [MOANING]
- SERENA, SASUNA,
YOU NEED TO BE STRONG FOR ME,
BOTH OF YOU.
[GROAN]
- FATHER!
- THOSE WERE OUR FATHER'S
DYING WORDS TO US.
- "BE STRONG."
HE MUST HAVE WANTED US
TO RESTORE OUR VILLAGE
TO ITS FORMER GLORY.
I'M CERTAIN THAT'S
WHAT HE WAS TRYING TO TELL US.
- HMM.
- HOLD ON.
- DO IT NOW, SERENA.
- AH!
- [COUGHING]
- OH, NO.
SOME OF THOSE REMAINS
HAVEN'T BEEN EXORCISED
OF THE DEMON SPIRITS YET,
MEANING THEY'LL SUMMON
OTHER DEMONS BACK HERE!
KILLALLA!
HURRY, KILLALLA.
THOSE GIRLS ARE IN DANGER!
- [PANTING]
- WAIT FOR ME, SASUNA.
- HURRY UP!
YOU'RE ALWAYS SLOWING ME DOWN.
I'LL TAKE SOME
OF YOUR LOAD FOR YOU.
- [HEAVY BREATHING]
- I'M SORRY.
- NO WONDER FATHER SETTLED
ON ME AS HIS HEIR,
EVEN THOUGH YOU'RE THE ELDEST.
- FORGIVE ME.
I'LL TRAIN HARD,
AND ONE DAY I WILL
BECOME A STRONG NINJA
EXACTLY LIKE FATHER
WANTED ME TO BE.
- HMM?
- [GASP]
- COME ON, LET'S HURRY.
- [PANTING]
- OH, NO!
WHAT'S THAT?
- [SNARL]
[HISSING]
- AAH!
- BOTH OF YOU,
GET ON KILLALLA NOW!
WE'RE GOING BACK TO THE VILLAGE.
- WE'RE NOT RETURNING THESE.
- YOU MUST DISCARD THEM AT ONCE!
HUNDREDS OF DEMONS ARE COMING
IN SEARCH OF THE DEMONIC AURA
THOSE WEAPONS ARE EXUDING.
- HUH?
- IT'S THE TRUTH. NOW, HURRY!
- [GROWLING]
- WE'RE TOO LATE.
I'LL HAVE TO DESTROY
THOSE DEMONS,
THEN WE'LL ESCAPE.
- SISTER, BE STRONG.
THE TIME HAS FINALLY COME FOR US
TO SHOW FATHER OUR COURAGE.
- WE'LL DO OUR NINJA
ANCESTORS PROUD.
WE HAVE A CHANCE AS LONG
AS WE HAVE THESE WEAPONS.
- SERENA, SASUNA,
YOU NEED TO BE STRONG FOR ME,
BOTH OF YOU.
[GROAN]
- I TRAINED YOU
NOT MERELY SO YOU COULD
CONTINUE OUR TRADITION.
I WANT YOU TO LIVE STRONG.
- OH, FATHER.
- HA!
- HAH!
- WAIT! YOU'RE MISTAKEN!
- HUH?
- THIS IS NOT HOW YOUR FATHER
WANTED YOU TO BE.
YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE ME, PLEASE!
- HUH?
- WHAT WOULD YOU KNOW ABOUT HIM?
- THERE ISN'T A FATHER
IN THE WORLD
THAT DOESN'T WISH
FOR HIS DAUGHTER'S HAPPINESS.
YOUR FATHER WASN'T TELLING YOU
TO CONTINUE THE NINJA TRADITION.
HE WANTED YOU
TO BE STRONG INSIDE.
HE WANTED YOU TO BE HAPPY.
THAT'S WHAT HE REALLY MEANT.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- NOW CLIMB ON TOP OF KILLALLA,
AND MAKE SURE
YOU STAY CLOSE TO ME.
- [GROWLING]
- BE STRONG FOR ME, BOTH OF YOU.
- HE WANTED YOU
TO BE STRONG INSIDE.
HE WANTED YOU TO BE HAPPY.
- [DEMONS GROWLING]
- SASUNA!
- HUH? WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
AAH!
- SANGO'S RIGHT, I'M SURE OF IT.
- UNH!
- SANGO!
- [GROWLING]
- HIRAIKOTSU!
- LET'S GO!
STAY OUT OF MY WAY!
- [ROARS]
- HYAH!
- [GROWLING]
- [GRUNTING]
- AAH!
- OH!
- [GROWLING]
- AAH!
- SASUNA!
- TAKE THAT!
AAH!
UNH!
- SASUNA!
SASUNA?
- [WEAKLY] SERENA.
- STAY BACK!
- [GRUNTING]
- [SNARLING]
- [GROWLING]
[METAL JINGLES]
- SANGO!
- [GRUNTING]
- MIROKU!
- WIND SCAR!
- HEY, SANGO, IT'S NOT LIKE YOU
TO HAVE YOUR DEPARTURE DELAYED
BY THE LIKES OF DEMONS.
- INUYASHA.
- I'LL TAKE OVER NOW.
- WIND TUNNEL!
- HI, SANGO!
- WE CAME BACK TO GET YOU.
- THANK YOU.
- LET'S BE ON OUR WAY, SISTER.
- HMM.
- BE STRONG, BOTH OF YOU.
- WELL, MIROKU WAS WORRIED,
SO WE DECIDED TO COME.
IT'S A GOOD THING WE DID, TOO.
- WELL, I'M GLAD
WE MADE IT ON TIME.
- MIROKU, WERE YOU ACTUALLY
THAT WORRIED ABOUT ME?
- OH, CALL IT A PREMONITION,
IF YOU WILL.
I KEPT SEEING YOUR FACE, SANGO,
NO MATTER WHAT I DID.
I SIMPLY COULDN'T
GET YOU OUT OF MY MIND.
IT'S THE TRUTH.
- [SLAP]
- THANK YOU FOR YOUR CONCERN.
- DON'T MENTION IT. HA HA HA!
- WHEN IS HE EVER GONNA LEARN?
PLEASE DON'T LET ME GROW UP
TO BE LIKE HIM.
- MM-HMM.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- KAGOME, NARAKU'S BROUGHT IN
AN EVIL PRIESTESS
THAT FOUGHT WITH KIKYO
A LONG TIME AGO.
- OH, NO! I CAN'T FIGURE IT OUT!
I CAN'T FOLLOW THE LESSONS!
- SHE'S USING THE SACRED JEWEL
TO CAST A SPELL ON YOU.
- EVERYONE KEEPS TELLING ME
TO BREAK UP WITH INUYASHA, TOO.
- WOULD YOU LISTEN TO ME?
- DO YOU KNOW
WHAT THEY CALL YOU?
MY VIOLENT, POSSESSIVE,
TWO-TIMING BOYFRIEND!
- WHY? WHAT DID I EVER DO?
- NEXT TIME...
RUN, INUYASHA!
- TWO-TIMING?!