>> HERE WE COME.
IT'S THE START OF "INUYASHA."
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL THE
SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY NARAKU WITH
MY TETSUSAIGA.
>> THE PHANTOMS OF 7 TOMBS,
MORE OF THE BAND OF 7 APPEAR.
SOMEWHERE AHEAD IS NARAKU.
THEN OUT OF NOWHERE, SESSHOMARU
APPEARS.
>> IT'S UP TO ALL OF US.
>> TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FEUDAL FAIRY TALE!
>> "INUYASHA!"
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
[GRUNTING]
>> INUYASHA,
HAVE YOU NO HEART?
>> OH, GET OVER IT
AND TELL ME WHO GAVE YOU THE
SACRED JEWELL SHARD BEFORE I
HAVE TO SERIOUSLY HURT YOU.
>> HA HA HA HA!
SO, HE'S AT IT AGAIN.
BUT JAKOTSU HASN'T CHANGED
ONE BIT.
[LAUGHS]
[SLURPS]
HA HA HA HA!
SORRY TO SPOIL THE MOOD.
>> "THE STEALTHY POISON MASTER,
MUKOTSU."
>> JAKOTSU, I'LL ASK ONE MORE
TIME.
WAS IT NARAKU WHO GAVE YOU THE
SACRED JEWELL SHARD?
>> I'M NOT REALLY SURE.
I'VE NEVER MET THE MAN.
>> THAT'S IT.
I'VE HAD IT WITH YOUR STUPID
LITTLE JOKES.
>> HUH?
>> HUH?!
SMOKE?
>> JUST WHEN IT WAS GETTING FUN.
DAMN YOU, MUKOTSU!
INUYASHA, YOU BETTER LEAVE WHILE
YOU ARE STILL ABLE.
>> WHAT THE HECK ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT?
AAGH!
[GRUNTING]
OW!
WHAT IS THAT STUFF?
>> IT'S POISONOUS GAS.
>> SEE YOU SOON, INUYASHA.
>> MAN, IS HE ANNOYING.
>> THE QUESTION IS WHERE IS
THE POISON COMING FROM?
>> HMM, THAT NARAKU!
JUST WAIT!
I'LL SHOW HIM A THING OR TWO.
I CAN ASSURE YOU.
HA HA HA HA.
>> HMM.
I CAN SMELL HIM.
NARAKU'S SERVANT.
THE BOY.
>> SO, I WAS WONDERING,
LORD SESSHOMARU, WHY DO YOU
SEEK NARAKU?
>> DON'T YOU KNOW ANYTHING?
IT'S BECAUSE NARAKU ABDUCTED YOU
THAT LORD SESSHOMARU IS BENT ON
VENGEANCE.
>> HUH?
IT'S ALL BECAUSE OF ME?!
>> DON'T BE SO CONCEITED,
YOU SILLY CHILD.
IT'S NOT ABOUT YOU.
LORD SESSHOMARU'S HONOR
HAS BEEN INSULTED.
DON'T LET HIS CALM DEMEANOR FOOL
YOU.
UNDERNEATH, HE IS A BOILING,
ANGRY, SEETHING MASS OF--
OOF.
HUH?
UH-OH!
[THUMP]
I GOTTA LEARN TO KEEP MY MOUTH
SHUT.
>> I SEE WHAT YOU MEAN.
[BUZZING]
>> DOES IT HURT, SANGO?
>> I THINK IT'S OK.
>> I DON'T THINK JAKOTSU COULD
HAVE GONE VERY FAR YET.
>> YOU'LL FOLLOW?
>> WELL, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I STILL HAVEN'T MANAGED TO GET
ANY INFORMATION ABOUT NARAKU OUT
OF HIM.
>> YES, BUT, INUYASHA,
AREN'T YOU WORRIED ABOUT THAT
POISONOUS GAS?
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> WELL, JAKOTSU SEEMED TO KNOW
SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
MAYBE IT'S ANOTHER ONE OF THE
BAND OF 7.
>> HUH?
>> BUT JAKOTSU SEEMED TO BE IN
DANGER, TOO.
>> MIROKU, YOU STAY HERE AND
PROTECT KAGOME AND SANGO.
>> OK.
>> THERE WE GO.
JUST LIKE MOTHER USED TO MAKE.
HUH?
WHY, HELLO, JAKOTSU!
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME!
OOH!
>> HELLO YOURSELF.
SO, MUKOTSU, YOU TRIED TO DO ME
IN WITH YOUR POISON, TOO, HUH?
>> HA HA HA HA HA!
DON'T BE ANGRY.
I KNEW YOU COULD HANDLE
YOURSELF.
>> HUH!
>> SO, TELL ME ABOUT THE OTHERS.
>> WELL, RENKOTSU IS BUSY TAKING
CARE OF GINKOTSU.
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO GINKOTSU?
>> HE'S...
YOU KNOW.
HE NEEDS ALL THESE NEW GUNS AND
GUN POWDER.
>> HA HA HA!
AND I SUPPOSED HE NEEDS
TO OIL THEM WELL...
CORRECT?
>> HUH?
>> HEY.
WHAT'S ALL THIS ABOUT?
I SEE.
INUYASHA'S COMING AFTER ME ALL
ALONE!
>> HA HA HA HA.
SO, THAT MEANS THE OTHERS ARE
ALL BY THEMSELVES.
AND THIS KAGOME GIRL POSSESSES
SACRED JEWELL SHARDS.
>> THEY'RE ALL YOURS, MUKOTSU.
>> HUH?
WELL, THEN,
I'LL TAKE THE SACRED JEWELL
SHARDS.
>> AND I'LL KEEP INUYASHA ALL
FOR MYSELF.
>> HE IS OF NO CONCERN TO ME.
WHAT ABOUT KAGOME?
>> ALL YOURS.
ENJOY.
>> HA HA HA HA HA HA.
I WILL.
>> HMM?
YOU HAVE BUSINESS AT THIS
SHRINE, YOUNG MAN?
>> YES.
THIS WILL DO RATHER NICELY.
>> WHAT?
>> THIS SHRINE WILL DO NICELY
FOR THE BAND OF 7.
>> ARE YOU SAYING THAT
YOU'RE ONE OF THE BAND OF 7?!
>> THAT OUTFIT OF YOURS WILL DO
QUITE NICELY AS WELL.
HMM.
>> AAGH!
[SCREAMS]
>> HEY, KAGOME, LOOK!
IT'S A WELL!
>> GOOD.
WE COULD USE SOME WATER.
>> HUH?
THERE'S SOMEONE ON THE GROUND.
>> OH, NO!
HEY, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
[GASPS]
SHE'S DEAD.
[WHIMPERS]
WHAT'S THIS?
>> ARE THEY ALL DEAD?
KAGOME, I THINK WE BETTER GET
AWAY FROM HERE.
>> UH-HUH.
>> HA HA HA HA HA HA!
>> AAGH!
POISONOUS GAS!
>> YOU CANNOT ESCAPE FROM
MUKOTSU'S POISON.
[GROANING]
>> KAGOME, PLEASE HANG IN THERE.
>> HA HA HA HA!
SO, KAGOME,
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO HAS THE
SACRED JEWELL SHARDS, CORRECT?
>> KAGOME!
KAGOME!
>> PLEASE, SHIPPO,
RUN AWAY.
>> NO, I WON'T!
>> DON'T BE AFRAID.
I DON'T INTEND TO KILL YOU.
NO, MY PRETTY.
THIS IS MY SPECIAL TOXIN WHICH
WILL PARALYZE YOUR BODY...
BUT YOUR MIND WILL REMAIN
QUITE ALERT.
IT HAS NO EFFECT ON DEMONS
THOUGH.
>> YOU LEAVE KAGOME ALONE!
FOX MAGIC!
MAGIC TOP!
[GROANING]
HOW'D YOU LIKE THAT?!
>> SHIPPO!
[GROANING]
>> HA HA HA HA HA!
[CHUCKLES]
>> HUH?
>> MIROKU, STAY BACK.
>> IT'S POISON.
SO, HE'S THE ONE BEHIND THE GAS.
>> SANGO, MIROKU,
PLEASE RUN.
>> HA HA HA HA!
>> I KNOW!
I'LL GET INUYASHA.
>> YOU MUST BE ONE OF THE BAND
OF 7.
>> HA HA HA HA HA!
YES!
I'M MUKOTSU, POISON MASTER.
>> SO, TELL ME, POISON MASTER,
SOMEONE MUST HAVE RESURRECTED
YOU AND SENT YOU AFTER US.
IS NARAKU BEHIND ALL THIS?
>> HA HA HA HA HA!
COULDN'T TELL YOU.
YOU'LL HAVE TO ASK THE
CAPTAIN...
SHOULD YOU SURVIVE, THAT IS.
>> RUN AWAY!
>> HA HA HA HA HA!
THAT SHOULD DO THE TRICK.
>> SANGO!
MIRO...
MIROKU!
OH, NO!
>> NOW THEN, KAGOME,
THE INTRUDERS ARE GONE.
IT'S JUST YOU AND ME NOW.
HA HA HA HA HA HA!
>> INUYASHA!
WHERE DID YOU GO?!
>> JAKOTSU'S SCENT!
I'M GETTING CLOSER.
HUH?
>> HEY, INUYASHA.
>> WHAT THE HECK ARE YOU DOING?!
>> IT'S MY SCENT YOU'RE
TRACKING, IS IT NOT?
WELL, I THOUGHT I'D MAKE IT JUST
A LITTLE EASIER FOR YOU.
>> SAY GOOD-BYE.
>> HA HA HA HA HA!
WE'RE SURROUNDED BY A BARRIER OF
POISONOUS GAS.
NO ONE CAN DISTURB US.
MY, WHAT A RARE BEAUTY.
I'M SO FORTUNATE GETTING MARRIED
TO SUCH A PRETTY GIRL.
>> WHAT?!
MARRY?!
>> YOU SEE, BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
THERE ARE SOME WHO FIND ME
UNATTRACTIVE.
HA HA HA HA!
FIRST THE BRIDAL PREPARATIONS,
THEN WE'LL HAVE THE CEREMONY.
>> CEREMONY?
A MARRIAGE CEREMONY?
>> HA HA HA HA HA HA.
[GRUNTING]
>> ARE YOU RUNNING AWAY?
>> I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF THIS.
>> OH, INUYASHA,
I LOVE IT WHEN YOU'RE ANGRY.
[GRUNTING]
>> HIS SWORD...
IT'S SOMEHOW ABLE TO DISRUPT THE
TETSUSAIGA'S WIND SCAR.
>> THE FUN IS JUST BEGINNING!
[GRUNTS]
>> IF I STOP THAT SWORD OF YOURS
FROM MOVING AROUND, IT WILL BE
ALL OVER!
>> HA.
DO YOU THINK YOU CAN STOP THE
GREAT SWORD JAKOTSUTOU?
>> I'M SURE OF IT!
>> INUYASHA!
>> HUH?
>> ANOTHER ONE OF THE BAND OF 7
HAS KAGOME!
SHE NEEDS YOUR HELP RIGHT NOW!
>> KAGOME!
[GRUNTS]
>> NOW, NOW.
DON'T FORGET ME.
>> SHUT UP!
LET'S GO, SHIPPO!
>> OH, I DON'T THINK SO.
>> GIDDYAP.
>> HUH?
[LAUGHING]
WHAT ON EARTH IS THIS?!
HEY, INUYASHA!
COME BACK!
>> I HAVE MY FAULTS,
BUT I'LL BE A GOOD HUSBAND TO
YOU.
HA HA HA HA HA.
NOW, KAGOME, IT'S TIME FOR THE
RITUAL MARRIAGE DANCE.
TRY TO KEEP UP.
HA HA HA HA HA!
♪ TODAY'S OUR WEDDING DAY
AND THIS I KNOW IS TRUE
YOU'RE THE ONE FOR ME
AND I'M THE ONE FOR YOU ♪
MY LOVELY LITTLE BRIDE.
>> WHAT IS HE DOING?
>> SHE CAN'T GO RUN AND HIDE
FOREVER BE BESIDE ME.
HA HA HA.
>> IF ONLY I CAN GET AHOLD OF
THAT SACRED JEWELL SHARD.
>> SHE CAN'T RUN.
SHE CAN'T HIDE.
HA HA HA HA.
SUCH A FINE BRIDE.
SUCH A FINE BRIDE, INDEED.
NOW, HOW ABOUT SOME RICE WINE?
HUH?
[ROARS]
>> KAGOME!
>> HOW DARE YOU INTERRUPT MY
CEREMONY?!
>> LEAVE HIM TO ME.
[GRUNTS]
>> HA HA HA HA HA!
THAT LITTLE MASK OF YOURS WON'T
WORK.
THIS POISON ENTERS THROUGH THE
EYES AND SKIN.
[GRUNTS]
>> SANGO!
[COUGHS]
[SNARLS]
>> HA!
[MEWS]
HA HA HA HA HA!
THAT'S EVERYONE.
I, OF COURSE, AM UNAFFECTED.
NOTHING AT ALL CAN HARM ME.
AGH!
[CHOKING]
[GASPING]
>> DID I GET HIM?
[GROWLS]
>> HOW DARE YOU?!
[GRUNTS]
>> GUESS NOT.
>> KAGOME!
SAY IT ISN'T SO!
DOES MY FACE REPEL YOU, TOO?
>> I...
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
BESIDES, THAT'S HARDLY
THE ISSUE HERE.
>> KAGOME, THOUGH IT
PAINS ME TO SAY IT,
YOU ARE NOT FIT TO BE MY BRIDE.
[GRUNTING]
>> I CAN'T MOVE.
KAGOME!
>> YOUR DOWRY OF JEWELL SHARDS
SHALL STILL BE MINE.
>> INUYASHA!
>> NOW DIE!
HUH?
>> INUYASHA!
[GRUNTS]
>> HUH?
SESSHOMARU.
>> SESSHOMARU SAVED ME?
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
I THOUGHT OUR ONLY OPPONENTS
WOULD BE INUYASHA AND HIS GROUP
OR KOGA OF THE DEMON-WOLF TRIBE.
>> TELL ME, IS INUYASHA HERE?
>> AND WHO ARE YOU?
>> I WAS ABOUT TO ASK YOU THAT.
>> YOU...
TRIED TO KILL ME AND YOU DON'T
EVEN KNOW ME?!
[GROANS]
>> YOU FELT THE PAIN OF MY
TOXIC CLAWS AND YET YOU'RE
STILL ABLE TO RUN?
>> HA HA HA!
TAKE THIS!
HA HA HA HA!
TASTE MY POISON!
HUH?
WAIT!
GAH!
PLEASE, WAIT!
I'M SORRY!
I WAS TOO HASTY!
PLEASE SPARE ME!
DON'T KILL ME!
[WHIMPERING]
TO SHOW YOU MY SINCERITY...
HERE'S A LITTLE PRESENT.
HA HA HA HA HA!
HA HA HA HA HA.
GOOD-BYE, MY FRIEND.
THIS POISON EVEN KILLS DEMONS
LIKE YOU.
HUH?
IT'S NOT WORKING.
YET IT'S MY VERY FINEST POISON!
AAGH!
[SCREAMING]
>> YOUR PRIMITIVE CONCOCTIONS
ARE NO MATCH FOR MY SUPERIOR
POWERS.
>> KAGOME!
SESSHOMARU?
WHAT?!
KAGOME!
>> AGH!
THEY ALL LOOK LIKE THEY'RE DEAD!
>> GRRR!
WHAT DID YOU DO TO THEM,
SESSHOMARU?
>> NO.
>> HUH?
>> IT'S NOT WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE.
SESSHOMARU SAVED US.
>> NO, I DIDN'T SAVE YOU.
HE COULDN'T ANSWER MY QUESTION,
SO I GOT RID OF HIM.
SIMPLE AS THAT.
>> WHAT QUESTIONS?
>> I CAUGHT THE BOY KOHAKU SENT.
>> HUH?
>> DOES THAT MEAN NARAKU IS
NEAR?
>> DAMN THAT INUYASHA!
TOTALLY IGNORING ME!
BUT WHO IS THIS OTHER
SELF-IMPORTANT DEMON?
I'VE NEVER HEARD TELL OF HIM
BEFORE.
HE GOT RID OF MUKOTSU AS EASILY
AS IF HE WERE SWATTING A FLY.
HMM.
I BETTER NOT STICK AROUND.
>> ANSWER ME, INUYASHA.
WHERE IS NARAKU?
>> WE HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO FIND
HIM YET EITHER.
BUT NOW WE'VE GOT THESE PHANTOMS
POSSESSING SACRED JEWELL SHARDS
COMING AFTER US.
I'M SURE NARAKU'S CLOSE BY.
>> THAT'S ALL I NEED TO KNOW.
>> MMM!
SESSHOMARU!
>> PLEASE SAY SOMETHING, SANGO!
MIROKU, WAKE UP!
MIROKU!
IT'S THE POISON.
THE POISON GOT TO THEM!
>> KAGOME!
>> HMM?
I'M ALL RIGHT.
MIROKU...
AND SANGO...
PROTECTED ME.
NOW, PLEASE HURRY.
THE ANTIDOTE...
IN MY BAG.
>> KAGOME!
GRR!
I KNEW IT.
I SHOULD HAVE STAYED WITH HER.
>> LORD SESSHOMARU IS SURE LATE.
NOW I WISH I HAD GONE WITH HIM.
>> NONSENSE!
THERE WERE DEFINITELY SIGNS OF
POISON WHERE LORD SESSHOMARU WAS
GOING.
IF YOU HAD GONE WITH HIM, YOU'D
BE PUSHING UP DAISIES FOR SURE.
[SIGHS]
>> I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
HUH?
KOHAKU?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> WHAT IS IT, RIN?
>> HUH?
OH, IT'S NOTHING.
>> HMM.
>> LORD SESSHOMARU, IF YOU SEE
HIM AGAIN, WILL YOU KILL KOHAKU?
>> I SEE.
FIRST KYOUKOTSU AND NOW MUKOTSU.
>> YUP.
>> SO, WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME
ABOUT MUKOTSU'S KILLER?
>> HE HAD COLD, EXPRESSIONLESS
EYES.
QUITE MANLY I SUPPOSE
YOU COULD SAY.
BUT, I GUESS IF IT CAME DOWN TO
IT, I'D STILL HAVE TO CHOSE
INUYASHA.
>> I BELIEVE WE'RE LOSING FOCUS,
JAKOTSU.
>> BUT, RENKOTSU,
THERE STILL SEEMS TO BE MANY
THINGS WE HAVEN'T BEEN TOLD.
>> HMM?
>> TAKE FOR INSTANCE THIS NARAKU
PERSON WHO REVIVED THE 7 OF US.
WHO IS HE EXACTLY?
>> HMM?
NARAKU?
>> BROTHER, HAVE YOU EVER
MET HIM?
>> NO, ONLY BIG BROTHER HAS MET
NARAKU.
NARAKU HANDED HIM THE SHARDS OF
THE SACRED JEWELL--
INCLUDING ONES FOR US.
NARAKU TOLD HIM THAT IF WE GOT
RID OF ALL WHO SOUGHT NARAKU,
THE SHARDS WOULD BECOME OURS.
>> WHAT AN AGREEMENT.
TWO OF THE BAND OF 7 ARE ALREADY
DEAD.
SO, FROM 7, THAT LEAVES ONLY 4.
>> 7 MINUS TWO IS 5.
>> HUH?
WAIT.
ONE, TWO...
>> BUT, JAKOTSU, YOU SAID THAT
INUYASHA'S FRIENDS WERE EXPOSED
TO MUKOTSU'S POISON.
>> YES.
MUKOTSU'S POISON IS VERY
PERSISTENT.
BY NIGHTFALL, THEY'LL PROBABLY
ALL BE DEAD.
>> WELL, WE GAVE THEM THE
ANTIDOTE, BUT NOW THEY NEED
REST--AND LOTS OF IT.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE SHOULD REALLY FIND A SAFER
PLACE FOR THEM.
>> HA HA HA HA.
THIS GETS EVEN MORE INTERESTING.
AS IT TURNS OUT,
OUR BROTHER GINKOTSU IS HEADED
THEIR WAY AS WE SPEAK.
GINKOTSU...
MORE THAN A MATCH FOR ANY DEMON.
[RUMBLING]
[BIRD SQUAWK]
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> MASTER INUYASHA...
HOW DID YOU TRAVEL SO FAR IN MY
ABSENCE?
THIS IS THE NORTH COUNTRY.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO A HOT
SPRING?
>> A REJUVENATING SPA.
IT WORKS ON BODY CHILLS,
ACHES, PAINS, AND RINGWORM.
>> WE HAVEN'T GOT TIME FOR THAT!
MIROKU, THERE'S MORE OF THEM!
DAMN IT!
I'LL KILL YOU!
>> NEXT ON "INUYASHA,"
THE GHASTLY STEEL MACHINE.
THERE'S A SACRED JEWELL SHARD IN
HIS NECK!
COULD HE BE ONE
OF THE BAND OF 7?
DON'T MISS IT!