>> HUH?
ARE THEY CALLING ME?
IS THAT IT?
[GROANING]
A WATERFALL.
[GASPS]
KIKYO?
[BUZZING]
>> EVERYONE WAS DEAD?
>> YES, EVERYONE WHO WAS IN THE
BIRTHING ROOM.
ACCORDING TO THE VASSALS WHO
FOUND THEM THE FOLLOWING
MORNING, THERE WAS SOMETHING
VERY STRANGE ABOUT THEIR DEATHS.
>> DO YOU THINK DEMONS WERE
RESPONSIBLE?
>> I HAVE NO IDEA WHO DID IT.
I DO KNOW THAT WE SHOULD COUNT
OUR BLESSINGS THAT OUR LADY AND
HER NEWBORN WERE LEFT UNHARMED.
>> BUDDHA MUST HAVE PROTECTED
THEM FROM INJURY.
>> A FINE BABE.
A FINE BABE, INDEED.
>> MY LORD?
>> HUH?
YES, MY DEAREST?
>> NOTHING.
IT'S NOT IMPORTANT, REALLY.
>> DO NOT WORRY, MY LOVE.
I'VE SEEN TO IT THAT SECURITY
HAS BEEN TIGHTENED.
WHATEVER DEMON OR VILLAIN DID
THIS, IT WILL NOT GET NEAR THE
CASTLE.
I FINALLY HAVE AN HEIR.
I SHALL PROTECT HIM WITH MY
LIFE.
>> IS THAT INFANT TRULY MINE?
AND THAT YOUNG GIRL CLAD IN
WHITE, WAS SHE MERELY AN
ILLUSION?
I DON'T KNOW.
>> I'M SORRY FOR THE TROUBLE.
>> NO TROUBLE.
>> GROWING OLD IS NOTHING BUT
GRIEF, I TELL YOU.
SPRAINED MY BACK CARRYING A
SMALL BUNDLE OF FIREWOOD.
HOW EMBARRASSING.
>> YOU SHOULD GO EASY ON
YOURSELF.
>> WHAT'S YOUR NAME, YOUNG MAN?
>> HUH?
>> I SAID WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
DO YOU HAVE A PLACE TO STAY?
>> UH-UH.
>> WELL THEN COME TO MY HOME.
I CAN OFFER YOU SOMETHING TO
EAT.
>> AH, THAT'S VERY KIND OF YOU.
OH, AND MY NAME IS KOHAKU.
>> KOHAKU?
NOW THERE'S A FANCY NAME.
>> THINK SO?
>> MMM.
[BUZZING]
>> HERE I GO!
AAH!
>> AH.
>> SANGO, I THINK THAT'S THE
LAST OF THEM.
>> UGH, YEAH.
>> CHILALA, YOU DID A GOOD JOB.
AAH!
WHAT, ARE THERE MORE OF THEM?!
>> YOU'VE BEEN BUSY.
SO THERE WERE DEMONS SNIFFING
AROUND HERE, TOO?
>> INUYASHA, IT'S YOU.
>> DON'T SCARE US LIKE THAT!
>> HEY, WHERE'S KAGOME?
WHAT HAPPENED TO HER?
>> UH...
>> SHE LEFT.
SHE WENT AFTER THE SOUL
COLLECTORS.
>> THE SOUL COLLECTORS?!
>> YEAH, AND WE HAVEN'T SEEN OR
HEARD FROM HER SINCE.
>> SHE WENT THROUGH SOME KIND OF
BARRIER.
>> WHERE IS THIS BARRIER THEN?
TAKE ME THERE!
>> KIKYO, ARE YOU ALIVE?
OR ARE YOU...
>> HER LIFE IS FADING.
>> HMM?
>> THE MIASMA IS SPREADING VERY
RAPIDLY.
>> MIASMA?
>> YOU MUST MAKE YOUR
DECISION...
>> WHETHER OR NOT YOU WILL SAVE
HER.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN DECISION?
I DON'T GET IT.
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO KIKYO?
>> AFTER MOUNT HAKARE WAS
DESTROYED, SHE WAS STRUCK BY ONE
OF NARAKU'S TENTACLES AND FELL
INTO A DARK RIVER OF MIASMA.
BUT HER BODY WAS MADE OF SECRET
BONES AND SOIL FROM HER GRAVE,
SO THE MIASMA COULD NOT DISSOLVE
HER FLESH.
>> HOWEVER, THE MIASMA THAT
ENTERED THROUGH HER WOUNDS
SPREAD THROUGHOUT HER BODY.
THE WOUND IN HER CHEST STILL HAS
NOT HEALED, AND THE MIASMA IS
EATING AWAY AT HER.
>> THERE IS ONE WHO CAN SAVE
HER.
>> ONLY YOU HAVE THE POWER.
>> I'M THE ONLY ONE WHO CAN SAVE
KIKYO?
>> YOU ARE HER ONLY HOPE.
>> YOU HOLD HER LIFE IN YOUR
HANDS.
>> AND YOU EXPECT ME TO CHOOSE?
WHAT DO I HAVE TO DO?
WHAT DO I DO TO SAVE HER?
>> THEN YOU CHOOSE TO SAVE HER?
>> OF COURSE I DO!
I'M THE ONLY ONE WHO CAN HELP
HER, RIGHT?
SO I WILL.
>> ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS TOUCH
HER.
>> THAT WILL BE ENOUGH TO PURIFY
THE MIASMA.
>> OK, SO ALL I GOTTA DO IS
TOUCH HER.
>> PLEASE MOVE QUICKLY.
>> THE VESSEL IN WHICH HER
SPIRIT IS HOUSED IS DAMAGED, AND
IT IS BECOMING DIFFICULT TO
CONTAIN KIKYO'S SOUL.
IF WE DON'T PURIFY THE MIASMA
BEFORE THE SUN SETS, HER SOUL
WILL DISSIPATE.
>> GOT IT.
AAH!
THIS WATER HURTS.
NARAKU'S MIASMA IS OOZING OUT OF
HER.
AAH!
IS THIS MIASMA THAT HAS SEEPED
INTO THE WATER?
IS ALL OF THIS FROM KIKYO'S
BODY?
SORRY.
I'VE GOT TO TAKE A LOOK.
OH!
THIS IS TERRIBLE.
YOU POOR THING.
WHAT'S WRONG?
THEY SAID ALL I HAD TO DO WAS
TOUCH HER.
WHAT DO I HAVE TO DO?
HOW CAN I GET KIKYO TO WAKE UP?
HUH?
WHAT?
WHAT IS THIS?
>> IT IS SOIL FROM HER GRAVE.
>> YOUR HAND PURIFIED IT.
>> RUB IT INTO HER WOUND.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THE MIASMA IS PUSHING OUT THE
SOIL.
>> THE POWER OF THE MIASMA GROWS
STRONGER WHEN DARKNESS SETS IN.
>> YOU MUST SAVE HER SOUL BEFORE
THE SUN SETS.
>> OW!
IT HURTS SO MUCH!
I FEEL LIKE I'M GONNA BE THROWN
BACKWARD.
UGH!
IT'S PITCH BLACK!
I CAN'T SEE A THING.
WHAT NOW?
IS THAT KIKYO?
>> I'M RUNNING SO LATE.
>> HEY, ISN'T THAT THE SACRED
JEWEL?
WHAT AM I SEEING?
>> THAT INUYASHA.
HMM, MAYBE HE OVERSLEPT.
>> IS THIS WHAT HAPPENED BEFORE
KIKYO DIED?
DIDN'T THESE THINGS HAPPEN 50
YEARS AGO?
[LAUGHING]
WATCH OUT?
>> UGH!
>> YOU CAN TRY TO PRETTY
YOURSELF UP WITH THIS, BUT YOU
CAN'T HIDE YOUR TRUE NATURE.
>> WHAT?
>> THIS ROUGE DOESN'T BECOME YOU
AT ALL.
DEMON BLOOD IS GOOD ENOUGH FOR
YOU.
>> INUYASHA?
>> THAT'S NOT HIM!
>> UGH!
>> IT'S NOT HIM!
THAT IS NOT INUYASHA!
HE WOULD NEVER SAY SOMETHING
LIKE THAT!
>> I HAVE NO DESIRE WHATSOEVER
TO BECOME HUMAN.
>> WHY CAN'T YOU SEE THAT,
KIKYO?
>> BUT I SHALL TAKE THE SHICOME
JEWEL NONETHELESS.
THANKS.
THIS JEWEL IS ABOUT TO ABSORB A
GREAT DEAL OF PAIN AND SUFFERING
WHEN I USE IT TO SLAUGHTER THE
VILLAGERS.
>> KIKYO, THAT'S NARAKU!
>> YOU TRAITOR.
>> CAN'T YOU SEE THAT?
>> TRAITOR!
UGH!
[GROANING]
>> SHE WILL NOT MAKE IT IN TIME.
KIKYO'S SOUL IS ALREADY
BEGINNING TO FADE AWAY.
>> THIS IS THE SPOT!
THIS IS WHERE KAGOME
DISAPPEARED.
>> WHERE?
WHERE IS SHE?
[GROANING]
>> I DON'T GET IT.
KIKYO'S SHOULDER AND CHEST
INJURIES ARE THE SAME AS THE
ONES SHE HAS NOW.
>> CURSE YOU.
CURSE YOU!
>> THIS PLACE.
>> DIE, INUYASHA!
I BELIEVED IN YOU.
I TRUSTED YOU.
INUYASHA!
[GRUNTING]
>> KIKYO.
HOW COULD...
I THOUGHT...
>> SISTER KIKYO!
>> LISTEN TO ME, KAEDE.
TAKE THE SACRED JEWEL AND BURN
IT WITH MY BODY.
>> I GET IT.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
>> THAT WAY IT WILL NEVER FALL
INTO THE HANDS OF EVIL AGAIN.
>> KIKYO'S SOUL CAN'T GET PAST
THIS MOMENT IN TIME.
>> KIKYO!
SISTER KIKYO!
>> INUYASHA.
>> THIS IS THE EXACT MOMENT THAT
TIME STOPPED FOR KIKYO.
WHAT HAPPENED TO ME?
WAS I DREAMING A DREAM?
WHAT WAS IT ABOUT?
OH, MY HEAD FEELS SO FOGGY.
THE WOUNDS ARE CLOSING!
WE'VE ALMOST DONE IT!
HANG IN THERE!
COME ON.
YOU CAN MAKE IT, KIKYO!
INUYASHA REALLY WANTS TO SEE YOU
AGAIN, SO HANG IN THERE!
>> INUYASHA.
>> YOU CAN DO IT.
YOU WANT TO SEE INUYASHA, TOO!
YOU DO, RIGHT?
THE WATER IS BECOMING CLEARER.
THE MIASMA'S BEEN PURIFIED.
I'M SO GLAD.
SOUL COLLECTORS?
KIKYO.
>> WHY DID YOU SAVE ME?
>> HUH?
WELL, YOU'RE THE ONE WHO CALLED
ME HERE, AREN'T YOU?
>> YOU HAD A CHOICE WHETHER OR
NOT TO SAVE ME.
>> THAT'S WHAT EVERYONE KEEPS
SAYING, BUT IT HARDLY BOILS DOWN
TO A MATTER OF CHOICE.
IF THERE'S A PERSON RIGHT THERE
WHO I CAN SAVE, AND I'M TOLD
THAT SHE CAN ONLY BE SAVED BY
ME, OF COURSE I'D CHOOSE TO SAVE
HER.
>> INDEED, THEN I WON'T THANK
YOU SINCE YOU MADE THE CHOICE.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN YOU WON'T
THANK ME?
>> DID YOU SEE ANYTHING WHILE
YOU WERE IN THE WATER?
>> HUH?
LIKE WHAT?
>> IF YOU DON'T REMEMBER, SO BE
IT.
>> WAIT!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING TO?
>> INUYASHA WILL BE HERE SOON.
HE'LL BE LOOKING FOR YOU.
>> HUH?
>> I WILL GO INTO HIDING FOR A
TIME.
I MUST RESTORE MY STRENGTH.
>> AREN'T YOU EVEN GONNA SEE
INUYASHA?
HEY, KIKYO, WHAT ABOUT INUYASHA?
HUH!
EVER SINCE INUYASHA HEARD ABOUT
THE SAINT HAJIDI, HE'S THOUGHT
ABOUT NOBODY BUT YOU!
I HATE TO EVEN ADMIT THIS, BUT
YOU'RE THE ONE INUYASHA WANTS TO
BE WITH.
>> YOU HEAR THAT?
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER, INUYASHA?
>> THAT SOUND.
IT'S A WATERFALL!
>> HEY, WAIT.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
>> LET'S FOLLOW HIM.
WHO KNOWS.
THE BARRIER MIGHT HAVE BEEN
DISPELLED.
>> YOU MUST MAKE YOUR
DECISION...
>> WHETHER OR NOT YOU WILL SAVE
HER.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE THOSE 2.
LIKE THEY WERE TESTING ME OR
SOMETHING.
WHAT WERE THEY TRYING TO PROVE?
WAS THIS ABOUT INUYASHA?
DID SHE THINK I WOULDN'T SAVE
HER BECAUSE SHE'S IN MY WAY?
THAT'S GOTTA BE IT!
OF ALL THE DIRTY TRICKS!
HOW THEY EVEN THINK I COULD BE
THAT AWFUL?
ARGH!
>> KAGOME.
SHE'S ALL RIGHT.
>> KAGOME!
>> THANK GOODNESS YOU'RE ALL
RIGHT.
>> WHAT ARE YOU SNIFFING AROUND
FOR?
IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR KIKYO,
SHE'S ALREADY GONE.
WHY DON'T YOU GO AFTER HER?
>> YOU MEAN KIKYO WAS ACTUALLY
HERE?
>> YES, BUT SHE LEFT AWHILE AGO.
I TOLD HER TO STAY AND SEE YOU,
REALLY.
>> HUH?
>> I KNEW IT.
HE'S HAPPY.
>> INUYASHA, WHAT'LL YOU DO?
GO AFTER HER?
>> KAGOME, DID SOMETHING HAPPEN
WITH YOU AND KIKYO?
>> I FELT SO DETERMINED WHEN IT
WAS HAPPENING.
I NEVER THOUGHT I'D FEEL LIKE
THIS NOW.
>> KAGOME!
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
WHAT'S WITH THE LONG FACE?
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU!
>> OH, BE QUIET.
>> HUH?
>> THIS WHOLE MESS IS ALL YOUR
FAULT!
ARGH!
I HATE YOUR GUTS!
>> WHAT'S WITH KAGOME?
>> SHE LOOKS SCARY.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU THINK I
DID, BUT YOU BETTER KNOCK IT OFF
BEFORE I GET SERIOUSLY MAD!
>> INUYASHA, STAY--
>> HUH?
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK, MIROKU?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED,
BUT I'M GUESSING IT'S INUYASHA'S
FAULT.
>> KAGOME'S USUALLY RIGHT ABOUT
THESE THINGS.
>> APOLOGIZE?
FOR WHAT?
>> LOOK AT POOR KAGOME.
HAVE YOU EVER SEEN HER LOOK SO
SAD AND DEJECTED?
>> YEAH, SO WHAT'S YOUR POINT?
>> INUYASHA, LET ME ASK YOU ONE
QUESTION.
ARE YOUR SURE YOU DON'T WANT TO
GO AFTER KIKYO?
>> IT'S HARDLY EVEN AN OPTION.
NOT WITH KAGOME LIKE THIS.
>> SO YOU MEAN IF KAGOME HAD
SENT YOU OFF WITH A SMILE, YOU'D
HAVE GONE?
>> I'M TOTALLY THE WORST.
I WAS UPSET AND TOOK IT ALL OUT
ON INUYASHA.
OH, MAYBE HE HATES ME NOW.
HUH?
WHAT IS IT?
>> ARE YOU STILL MAD AT ME?
>> AREN'T YOU GOING AFTER KIKYO?
>> WHEN I WAS UP THERE ALONE AT
THE BASE OF THE MOUNTAIN, I MET
SAINT HAJIDI, BUT IT TURNED OUT
TO BE KIKYO'S PUPPET.
I FOUND OUT THAT THE REAL KIKYO
WAS OVERCOME BY NARAKU'S MIASMA
AND THAT HER LIFE WAS NEARING
ITS END.
HOW'S KIKYO?
I MEAN HOW DID SHE SEEM?
>> BADLY INJURED AND
UNCONSCIOUS.
BUT THEN...
I MANAGED TO PURIFY THE MIASMA,
SO I THINK SHE'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
>> YOU MEAN YOU DID THAT FOR
HER?
>> YEAH.
>> HMM.
I SEE.
>> IT'S ONLY NATURAL.
OF COURSE HE'D BE WORRIED ABOUT
HER.
INUYASHA, GO AFTER KIKYO.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
>> I'M NOT!
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO SHOULDN'T BE
WORRIED.
YOU SAVED KIKYO, DIDN'T YOU?
>> UH-HUH.
>> WELL, THEN SHE'S GOTTA BE OK.
I WON'T GO AFTER HER.
>> ARE YOU SURE?
SERIOUSLY?
>> YEAH!
SO TAKE BACK WHAT YOU SAID
EARLIER.
>> HUH?
>> DON'T PRETEND YOU FORGOT
ALREADY.
YOU SAID THAT YOU HATED ME A
LITTLE WHILE AGO.
>> REALLY?
DID I SAY THAT?
>> GAA!
>> SORRY.
I GUESS I DID FORGET.
>> DO YOU--DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW MUCH THAT HURT?
>> SO IT DID BOTHER HIM.
>> GUESS HE'S THE SENSITIVE
TYPE.
>> THERE WAS NO UNCERTAINTY IN
KAGOME'S HEART WHEN SHE SAVED
ME.
IF THERE HAD BEEN, THE WOUND IN
MY CHEST WOULD NOT HAVE HEALED.
I CAN STILL FEEL HER WARM TOUCH.
[MUSIC]
>> AROUND THE TIME SAINT HAJIDI
APPEARED, PRINCESS ABI'S MOTHER
NOTICED A LOCATION THAT DEMON'S
AVOIDED.
>> I'LL KILL NARAKU.
>> HE'S CAUSED ME NOTHING BUT
TROUBLE.
>> PRINCESS ABI SENDS HER BIRDS
TO ATTACK, AND AMONG THOSE
DEFENDING THE PLACE IS KOHAKU!
>> I CAN ALMOST REMEMBER DOING
THIS A LONG TIME AGO, FIGHTING
ALONGSIDE MY COMRADES.
>> NEXT TIME: PROTECT AND
PLUNDER!
>> KOHAKU, YOU WILL PROTECT THE
INFANT.