- [CHANTING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
- [MOANING]
- [SCREAMING]
- WOULD YOU BE TSUBAKI,
THE DARK PRIESTESS?
- IF YOU'VE COME TO BREAK
THE CURSE, IT'S TOO LATE.
THE VICTIM HAS ALREADY PERISHED.
- I'M NOT THE LEAST BIT
INTERESTED.
IT WAS YOU I CAME FOR.
- THEN YOU MUST BE A DEMON!
- STOP THIS.
YOU ARE A TROUBLESOME HAG,
INDEED.
MY MASTER HAS ASKED ME
TO REQUEST YOUR ASSISTANCE.
- WHAT DOES A DEMON WANT
WITH ME?
- TELL ME, DO YOU STILL BEAR
A GRUDGE AGAINST KIKYO?
- KIKYO, YOU SAY?
- WHAT IS ALL THIS?
I DON'T HAVE A CLUE.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND A THING!
I DON'T GET IT AT ALL!
- KAGOME,
READ THE NEXT LINE OUT LOUD.
- UH...
OH, I'VE FORGOTTEN
EVERYTHING I'VE LEARNED.
I'M FALLING SO FAR BEHIND.
- WOW, KAGOME SURE LOOKS
BUMMED OUT THESE DAYS.
- I'LL BET
IT'S THAT OLD BOYFRIEND OF HERS.
- ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT THE ONE
WHO DUMPED HER ONCE BEFORE--
YOU KNOW, THE POSSESSIVE,
BOSSY GUY WITH ATTITUDE?
- SHE PROBABLY ISN'T
OVER HIM YET.
- HUH?
- COME ON.
TRY AND CHEER UP, KAGOME.
- OH, JUST FORGET
ABOUT THE CREEP.
- YEAH.
THE JERK'S NOT EVEN WORTH IT.
- WHO ISN'T WORTH IT?
DO THEY MEAN INUYASHA?
- WELL, YOU GUYS BROKE UP,
DIDN'T YOU?
- YOU JUST HAVE TO GET OVER HIM.
- OH, THAT.
WELL, ACTUALLY WE--
- WHAT'S HAPPENED THIS TIME?
- DIDN'T I TELL YOU?
WE MADE UP AGAIN.
- OH.
- YOU'RE BACK TOGETHER?
- WITH THAT KNUCKLE DRAGGER?
- HE DOES HAVE
HIS NICE SIDE, TOO, YOU KNOW.
- SERIOUSLY?
- THAT'S TYPICAL.
- THEN, HOW COME YOU WERE
SO DOWN?
- I'VE BEEN ABSENT A LOT,
SO IT'S HARD TO KEEP UP
WITH SCHOOLWORK.
- MAKES SENSE.
YOU DO MISS AN AWFUL LOT
OF SCHOOL.
- EVEN IF YOU NEVER MISS CLASS,
IT'S STILL DIFFICULT TO FOLLOW
SOMETIMES.
- DEFINITELY.
- [ALL SIGH]
- STILL, IF YOU KEEP UP
AND WORK HARD,
CLASSES SURE ARE FUN,
THOUGH, AREN'T THEY?
- HUH?
- WHAT'S WRONG?
WHAT?
DID I SAY SOMETHING WEIRD,
YOU GUYS?
- NOT AT ALL.
- YOU ALWAYS WERE GOOD
AT SCHOOL.
- I'VE GOT TO GET GOING.
YOU SEE, WHEN I'M LATE,
HE COMES TO GET ME.
- HE COMES TO MEET YOU?
HE MUST BE A REALLY NICE GUY,
THEN.
- HARDLY, HE'S JUST JEALOUS.
- AND POSSESSIVE.
- LATER!
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
THEY'RE BACK TOGETHER.
- I WONDER IF KAGOME
CAN HANDLE IT?
- HUH? HANDLE WHAT?
- THIS NARAKU HAS SURROUNDED
HIMSELF WITH AN OMINOUS BARRIER.
- NOW, HOLD ON TIGHT,
OLD WOMAN.
NARAKU,
I FOUND THE WOMAN.
- YOU'VE COME, TSUBAKI,
THE DARK PRIESTESS.
- WHAT IS THE MEANING
OF SUMMONING ME HERE?
- DO YOU RECALL BATTLING
A PRIESTESS NAMED KIKYO
HALF A CENTURY AGO?
YOU WERE TRYING TO STEAL
THE SACRED JEWEL.
- OH, I'M SURPRISED YOU KNOW
ABOUT SUCH AN OLD INCIDENT.
- NOW, DARK PRIESTESS,
WOULD YOU CONSIDER
USING YOUR EVIL POWERS
TO ASSIST ME?
- NARAKU, WAS IT?
HOW WOULD ASSISTING YOU BE
A BENEFIT TO ME?
- YOU SHALL HAVE
THE SACRED JEWEL.
- OH?
- THE SACRED JEWEL? OH?
YOU HAVE IT
IN YOUR POSSESSION?
- THE OLD HAG TRANSFORMED
HERSELF!
- WATCH YOUR TONGUE, YOU WRETCH,
BECAUSE THIS IS MY TRUE FORM.
- THE OLD WOMAN SOLD HER SOUL
TO A DEMON
IN ORDER TO PRESERVE HER YOUTH.
THE DEMON HAD BUT
MINOR STANDING,
SO NOW SHE MUST SEEK
EVEN MORE POWER.
- SHOW ME THE SACRED JEWEL,
IF YOU TRULY POSSESS IT.
- WHAT IS IT
THAT YOU DESIRE
FROM THE SACRED JEWEL,
PRIESTESS?
FROM WHAT I UNDERSTAND,
YOU WOULD WANT ETERNAL YOUTH.
- [GASP]
- NARAKU, WHAT EXACTLY
DO YOU WANT FROM ME?
- THIS ONE'S FOR SHIPPO,
AND THIS IS INUYASHA'S FAVORITE.
- DON'T TAKE JUST JUNK FOOD.
HERE.
HOW ABOUT THIS?
- THANKS FOR THE LUNCHBOX, MOM.
- I HAVE LOTS MORE, TOO.
- UH, GREAT. THANKS.
- OH, KAGOME, DON'T FORGET
THE SACRED SAKE AND CHARMS!
- UH, THANKS.
I'LL PASS ON THOSE, GRAMPS.
- ARE YOU CERTAIN?
- SIS, ARE YOU GOING ALREADY?
- YEP. I'M LATE.
- INUYASHA'S WAITING?
- YEAH. THEY ALL ARE.
- I WISH I COULD GO
TO THE FEUDAL ERA, TOO.
- YOU'RE SUCH A SCAREDY CAT,
THOUGH.
YOU WOULDN'T LAST 5 MINUTES
BACK THERE.
- SHE'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE STILL SO YOUNG, SOTA.
- DON'T YOU EVER GET SCARED,
SIS?
- YEAH, BUT IT'S OK.
I'M SORT OF USED TO IT NOW.
UGH, THIS WEIGHS A TON.
- SURE YOU CAN CARRY ALL THAT?
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M DOING THIS.
I'LL JUST HAVE TO LEAVE
MY TEXTBOOKS BEHIND.
- KAGOME'S LATE.
SHE SAID SHE'D BACK BY SUNDOWN.
- KAGOME IS LATE.
- HMM?
- INUYASHA, SHE SAID
THAT SHE'D BE BACK BY SUNDOWN.
UHHH...
OH! WHY ME?
- OH, SAVE IT.
- YOU CREEP! UHHH...
WHAT WAS THAT?
- DO YOU SENSE SOMETHING,
TOO, SHIPPO?
- YES, BUT I DON'T KNOW
WHAT IT IS.
- HUH?
I DON'T LIKE
THE SMELL OF THAT.
- A DEMON AURA.
- LADY KAEDE.
- OH! MIROKU.
- SO, YOU HAVE SENSED IT, TOO?
- AYE.
EVIL IS LURKING NEARBY.
- [WIND BLOWING]
- IT SEEMS TO BE SLITHERING
ACROSS THE GROUND.
- WHAT IS IT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- UP...AND OVER.
UGH, THAT WAS A WORKOUT.
AHH.
OW! AH!
HEY, SOMETHING BIT ME.
WHAT WAS IT, THOUGH?
THERE'S NOTHING HERE.
- WHAT TOOK YOU SO LONG?
- SOMETHING BIT ME.
I THINK IT CAME
FROM OVER THERE.
- WHAT?
UNH!
THERE IT IS.
IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
PAPER?
HUH?
- FINE WORK.
YOU HAVE THE GIRL'S BLOOD,
I PRESUME.
- ARE YOU FINISHED?
- YES.
NOW, TAKE ME BACK TO NARAKU.
- BOSSY WITCH.
UNH.
- UGH.
- THERE WAS
SOMETHING STRANGE HERE.
I ATTACKED IT, BUT LOOK.
- I CAN PERFORM THIS ON MY OWN.
- DO AS YOU PLEASE.
- [LAUGHING]
- IT'S TRUE!
- BUT THERE'S NO BITE MARK.
- HE'S RIGHT.
- I KNOW, BUT...
- THERE WAS DEFINITELY
SOMETHING STRANGE AROUND.
- LET ME LOOK, INUYASHA,
AT THAT PAPER.
- HERE.
- HMM.
- BY THE WAY, KAGOME,
DID YOU--
- DON'T WORRY, SHIPPO.
I DIDN'T FORGET YOUR GOODIES.
- OOH.
- MMM, HERE.
- AHH, YES!
THIS IS THE ONE!
AHH, MMM!
- FOR YOU, INUYASHA.
- THANKS.
- YOU'RE GOING TO LOVE THE LUNCH
MY MOM MADE.
- THIS IS SHIKIKAMI.
- SHIKIKAMI?
[GASP]
WHAT WAS THAT?
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS!
- WHAT IS IT, KAGOME?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- UH...
[GASP]
THE SHARDS
HAVE TURNED BLACK!
AAH!
- HUH?
- AAH!
- KAGOME!
- THE SHARDS ARE GOING
INSIDE ME!
- KAGOME!
- SHARDS THAT ENTER HER FLESH
THEN SYNCHRONIZE WITH
THIS SACRED JEWEL
WHICH HAS BEEN DEFILED
WITH YOUR EVIL
AND WILL SLOWLY FESTER
IN HER BODY AND MIND.
AND THEN, NARAKU,
THIS YOUNG WOMAN WILL BE MINE
TO CONTROL.
- TSUBAKI, DON'T UNDERESTIMATE
THIS YOUNG WOMAN KAGOME.
- DON'T MAKE ME LAUGH.
SHE DIDN'T EVEN REALIZE SHE HAD
BEEN PLACED UNDER A CURSE.
I EXPECTED THE REINCARNATION
OF KIKYO
TO BE MUCH MORE FORMIDABLE.
NOW, WHAT SHALL I DO?
KILL HER IMMEDIATELY
OR PERHAPS...
- HEH HEH HEH.
LET'S MAKE INUYASHA SUFFER
THROUGH ANOTHER NIGHTMARE,
A NOSTALGIC DREAM
ABOUT THE WOMAN HE LOVES...
KILLING HIM.
- CAN YOU HEAR ME, KAGOME?
- SAY SOMETHING.
- KAGOME!
- WHAT'S THE MEANING OF THIS,
LADY KAEDE?
- THAT EVIL
WE SENSED EARLIER--
SOMEONE WAS PLACING A CURSE
ON KAGOME.
- SOMEONE'S CURSED HER?
- I BELIEVE THE DARK PRIESTESS
IS BEHIND THIS.
KAGOME WAS BITTEN AT THE WELL
BY THE DARK PRIESTESS'
SHIKIKAMI.
- DARK PRIESTESS?
- AYE. INUYASHA,
YOU MUST CERTAINLY KNOW OF THEM.
THIS IS A WICKED PRIESTESS
WHO SPECIALIZES IN CURSES.
IT WAS HER DARK ENCHANTMENT
THAT TURNED
THE JEWEL SHARDS BLACK.
- AND NOW IT LOOKS LIKE THEY'VE
ENTERED KAGOME'S FLESH!
- THE POISON COULD KILL HER
UNLESS WE DO SOMETHING.
- LET'S GO, SANGO.
WE'LL DESTROY
THIS DARK PRIESTESS.
THAT'S THE ONLY WAY
TO BREAK THE CURSE.
- HANG ON.
I'M GOING WITH YOU.
- INUYASHA...
- IT WOULD BE BEST FOR YOU
TO STAY HERE WITH KAGOME.
- YOU'RE MOST NEEDED HERE.
- YES, YOU'RE RIGHT.
- UNH!
I SENSE EVIL COMING
FROM THIS DIRECTION.
- UP HERE!
GET ON, MIROKU!
- YEAH. GOOD LUCK!
- KAGOME!
- [MOANING]
- KILL HIM.
- WHO?
- KILL WHO?
- KILL INUYASHA.
KILL INUYASHA.
KILL HIM.
- WHO?
- KILL HIM.
- KILL WHO?
- KILL INUYASHA.
KILL INUYASHA.
- STOP.
PLEASE, STOP.
- HUH, THE DEFIANT YOUNG WENCH
IS RESISTING.
- AS I TOLD YOU,
THIS KAGOME WOMAN IS
THE REINCARNATION OF KIKYO,
THE PRIESTESS.
TAMING HER WILL REQUIRE
MORE THAN A LITTLE EFFORT.
- KIKYO.
HAH!
THAT WRETCH.
LONG AGO KIKYO WAS INFATUATED
WITH A HALF-DEMON,
AND HER POWERS WERE
THUS WEAKENED.
IT SHOULD HAVE BEEN
THE PERFECT OPPORTUNITY
TO STEAL THE SACRED JEWEL
FROM ITS GUARDIAN.
YAH!
- [GROWLING]
-BUT IT WASN'T TO BE.
- YAH!
- OH, THAT WENCH.
SHE HURLED MY CURSE
STRAIGHT BACK AT ME!
AAH!
- NOW LEAVE,
AND I WILL SPARE YOUR LIFE.
- SUCH A SMUG COUNTENANCE.
SIMPLY RECALLING IT
MAKES MY BLOOD BOIL.
- [MOANING]
- OH, WILL SHE BE ALL RIGHT?
TELL ME SHE'S GOING TO MAKE IT.
OW!
[GROWLING]
OH. HMM.
- MMM. I SHALL CHANGE THE WATER.
- IT'S OVER THERE.
- GOOD. LET'S HURRY.
- DO YOU THINK
KAGOME CAN BE SAVED?
- PERHAPS.
KAGOME IS LIKELY FIGHTING
THE CURSE WITH ALL HER MIGHT.
- LUCKILY,
SHE'S STRONG-WILLED.
- AYE. THE MORE TIME IT TAKES
TO BREAK THE CURSE,
HOWEVER,
THE WEAKER SHE'LL BECOME.
- WILL IT TAKE MUCH LONGER?
- SHE SHOULD STOP RESISTING
SOON ENOUGH.
NOW THEN, NARAKU,
YOU SHALL HAVE
WHAT YOU WISHED FOR.
- DAMN IT!
HAVEN'T MIROKU AND SANGO FOUND
THE DARK PRIESTESS YET?
DAMN!
KAGOME IS LYING HERE
SUFFERING,
AND I'M JUST SUPPOSED
TO SIT AND DO NOTHING?
HUH?
OH!
KAGOME?
- [MOANING]
- HUH?
UNH!
- DIE, INUYASHA!
- WHY, KAGOME?
- KILL INUYASHA.
- GET AWAY.
- KILL HIM.
- RUN, INUYASHA.
- HUH? KAGOME, YOU'RE...
- STUBBORN WOMAN.
I HAVE CONTROL OF HER BODY,
BUT HER MIND IS STILL
RESISTING ME.
- HEH HEH HEH.
THIS IS BECOMING
EVEN MORE ENTERTAINING.
TSUBAKI, IF INUYASHA
SHOULD FLEE FROM HER,
THEN TAKE THE CHANCE
TO KILL KAGOME.
- RUN!
- KAGOME'S POSSESSED
BY THE DARK PRIESTESS.
WHAT'S TAKING YOU,
MIROKU?
- THE DEMONIC AURA
IS GETTING STRONGER.
- HURRY, KIRARA.
- THERE IT IS!
- [ALL SCREAM]
- [GRUNTING]
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT,
MIROKU?
- UNH...
WHAT THE...
- I FEEL IT.
I HAVE FACED THIS EVIL
ONCE BEFORE.
- I CAN KILL HER WITH MY CURSE
ANY TIME YOU WISH.
- HA HA HA!
WHAT WILL YOU DO NOW,
INUYASHA--
BE SLAIN BY KAGOME,
OR WILL YOU FLEE
AND BY DOING SO,
HAVE KAGOME KILLED?
- GET...AWAY.
- WHAT DO I DO?
- HA HA HA!
SUFFER, INUYASHA.
- RUN AWAY.
GET OUT OF HERE.
- [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- BEFORE SHE COLLAPSED,
KAGOME SAID SHE WAS BITTEN
BY SOMETHING.
IT WAS PROBABLY SHIKIKAMI,
A DEMON SERPENT
OF THE DARK PRIESTESS.
- HURRY, MIROKU.
WE MUST FIND THIS DARK PRIESTESS
BEFORE KAGOME KILLS INUYASHA!
- THIS BARRIER IS TOO STRONG.
I CAN'T BREAK THROUGH IT!
- LOOK!
- KIKYO?
WHAT'S SHE DOING HERE?
- NEXT TIME,
"KIKYO AND THE DARK PRIESTESS."
WHAT ON EARTH HAPPENED
50 YEARS AGO?