- I CAN'T MOVE!
- YOU FOOL!
YOU CAN RUN AND JUMP,
BUT YOU CAN NEVER
ESCAPE MY WIND.
THUNDER BLADES!
- UH!
MY SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
- NOW IS THE TIME
TO ESCAPE,
WHEN NARAKU'S BARRIER
IS WEAK.
IT'S NO USE.
YES.
HE CAN HELP ME.
HE HAS THE POWER
TO SEVER THE BOND
BETWEEN NARAKU AND I.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- YO.
- YO, YOURSELF.
- WIND SORCERESS KAGRA,
I RECALL.
- SO, YOU REMEMBER ME.
I AM VERY FLATTERED.
TAKE YOUR HAND
FROM YOUR SWORD.
I DIDN'T COME TO FIGHT,
SESSHOUMARU.
I HAVE A PROPOSITION
YOU MIGHT BE INTERESTED IN.
- PROPOSITION?
- YOU KNOW WHAT THESE ARE,
SESSHOUMARU.
I'LL GIVE YOU
THESE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
IN RETURN, I WANT YOU
TO KILL NARAKU.
- WHAT?
- FREE ME.
RELEASE ME FROM HIS GRASP.
YOU HAVE THE POWER
TO DO IT.
ONCE YOU KILL NARAKU,
ALL THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS
HE HAS GATHERED
WILL BE YOURS.
LET'S USE THOSE SHARDS
AND PROVIDE OURSELVES
WITH A LITTLE AMUSEMENT.
- YOU INTEND
TO BETRAY NARAKU?
- IT'S NOT AS THOUGH
I HAVE CHOSEN
TO LIVE UNDER HIS COMMAND.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF MY PLAN?
JOINING FORCES WOULD BE
OF MUTUAL BENEFIT.
- UNFORTUNATELY, I HAVE
NO INTEREST IN THE SACRED JEWEL.
IF YOU WISH
TO BECOME FREE,
USE THOSE SHARDS YOURSELF
AND DESTROY NARAKU.
- HMM! ARE YOU
AFRAID OF HIM?
- I'M SAYING I'M UNDER
NO OBLIGATION TO ASSIST YOU.
- UH!
- IF YOU DON'T HAVE THE RESOLVE
TO GO IT ALONE,
DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT BETRAYING HIM.
- FOOLISH COWARD!
AND YOU CALL YOURSELF A MAN?
- AH!
- I MISJUDGED YOU.
- PATHETIC FOOL.
- HA!
THAT DESPICABLE WOMAN.
YOU KNOW, I WONDER
IF SHE TRULY INTENDED
TO MAKE YOU HER PROTECTOR.
TALK ABOUT GALL.
WHERE ON EARTH
DOES SHE GET THE NERVE?
AN INCARNATION,
THAT'S ALL SHE IS.
- YOU'RE SO STRONG,
LORD SESSHOUMARU.
YOU DON'T EVEN NEED
THE POWER OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
- WIND SORCERESS KAGRA.
I WONDER IF SHE CAN USE
THE SACRED JEWEL
AND DEFEAT NARAKU
BY HERSELF.
EITHER WAY,
IT DOESN'T CONCERN ME.
- HMM?
MILORD, WHERE
ARE YOU OFF TO?
ARE YOU LEAVING ALREADY?
AAH! OH, I FORGOT SOMETHING.
COME ALONG.
- LORD SESSHOUMARU,
I'M NOT LONELY ANYMORE,
BUT I WONDER
IF MAYBE KAGRA IS.
- MILORD, WHAT SHALL WE DO
ABOUT DINNER?
- OOPS. DID I WIND IT
TOO TIGHT?
- NO. THANKS, KAGOME.
YOUR REMEDIES HAVE TAKEN AWAY
NEARLY ALL OF THE PAIN.
- LEAVE THAT HALF-DEAD WOLF
ALONE, KAGOME.
- WHAT?
- IF IT DOESN'T HURT ANYMORE,
THEN RUN ON HOME...
YOU PUNY LITTLE WOLF.
- WHO ARE YOU TO TALK?
STANDING THERE ALL WEAK
AND MORTAL, INUYASHA.
YOU'RE IN NO POSITION
TO CRITICIZE THE SHAPE I'M IN.
- I'M NOT LIKE THIS
BY CHOICE, IDIOT.
- YOU WANT TO FIGHT?
- YOU BET,
IF YOU'RE UP TO IT.
[GROWLING]
- HELLO.
DON'T YOU THINK
WE SHOULD TAKE BACK
THE JEWEL SHARDS?
- WHY DO YOU HAVE TO
COME ALONG ANYWAY?
- SHUT UP.
THOSE SHARDS BELONG TO ME,
AND I AIN'T GONNA
LET YOU HAVE THEM.
- SO, KAGRA HASN'T RETURNED
TO THE CASTLE YET?
- HMM. DOESN'T
LOOK LIKE IT.
I FEEL LIKE
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS
ARE MOVING FURTHER AND FURTHER
AWAY FROM NARAKU'S CASTLE.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
KAGRA WAS CREATED
FROM NARAKU'S BODY.
ISN'T SHE ACTING
ACCORDING TO NARAKU'S WILL?
- DOES THAT MEAN KAGRA IS
STEALING THE SHARDS ON HER OWN?
- IT'S POSSIBLE.
- DON'T YOU THINK THIS WHOLE
THING IS STRANGE, INUYASHA?
EVEN THE BARRIER.
- HMM...WHY WERE
YOU AND KOGA
ABLE TO PICK UP
THE SCENT OF THE CASTLE?
- THE BARRIER
HAS WEAKENED.
IT MUST BE BECAUSE
NARAKU'S OWN POWERS ARE WEAK.
- POWERS ARE WEAK...
JUST LIKE MINE.
- RIGHT. NARAKU
IS A HALF-DEMON AS WELL.
- HE IS THE BODY
OF A HUMAN NAMED ONIGUMO
AND GATHERED THE POWERS
OF COUNTLESS DEMONS.
- SO HE'S A HALF-DEMON,
JUST LIKE INUYASHA.
- INUYASHA LOSES HIS POWERS
ON THE NIGHT OF THE NEW MOON.
SO MAYBE NARAKU HAS A TIME
WHEN HIS POWERS WANE.
- MEANING HE HAS
A WEAKNESS, TOO.
- KAGRA...
IT'S USELESS TO FLEE.
- THE IMPUDENCE! HOW DARE HE
SAY THOSE THINGS TO ME?
DAMN HIM!
- IF YOU DON'T HAVE
THE RESOLVE TO GO IT ALONE,
DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT BETRAYING HIM.
- HA. I'LL USE IT MYSELF
AND KILL NARAKU.
HA.
- I CAN SMELL
KAGRA HERE.
[GASP]
- THANKS FOR HELPING ME.
I'M GOING ON AHEAD.
- KOGA!
- WHY, THAT LITTLE--
- KOGA, WAIT!
IS YOUR LEG WELL ENOUGH?
- MY WOUNDS ARE FINE NOW.
UNLIKE THE TWERP INUYASHA,
I'M A REAL DEMON.
- WHAT?
- SEE YA!
- WHO DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE CALLING A TWERP!
- SANGO, KOGA DOESN'T HAVE
HIS SACRED JEWEL SHARDS ANYMORE.
HE DOESN'T
STAND A CHANCE.
- WE'LL FOLLOW HIM.
ILALA, LET INUYASHA DOWN.
- AAH! UH!
- UH! INUYASHA,
I WANT YOU
TO KEEP OUT OF SIGHT
FOR A LITTLE LONGER.
- COME ON. YOU'VE GOT
TO BE KIDDING ME. AH!
- YOU'VE GOT TO BE
MORE CAREFUL. HMM?
[BUZZING]
- THE POISON INSECTS
ARE OUT.
- NARAKU'S STARTING
TO MAKE HIS MOVE.
INUYASHA CAN'T BE SEEN
LIKE THIS.
- GRR!
- KAGRA!
- KAGRA, YOU WITCH.
- WHAT IS IT THIS TIME?
LOOKING FOR MORE PUNISHMENT?
- DON'T KID YOURSELF.
YOU STOLE MY JEWEL SHARDS.
I'M TAKING THEM BACK.
- YEAH? AND YOU'RE
RELYING ON HELP
FROM INUYASHA
AND HIS PATHETIC FRIENDS?
WITHOUT THESE, YOU'RE TOO SCARED
TO FIGHT ALONE, ARE YOU?
- I'LL BEAT KAGRA!
DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT INTERFERING!
- WHAT, KOGA?
- DON'T FORGET,
I STILL HAVE MY CLAWS!
- JUST TRY IT.
- THUNDER BLADES!
- AAH! OH!
UH! GRR...
DAMN. IT'S ALL I CAN DO
TO KEEP DODGING HER.
I CAN'T GET CLOSE.
- JUST HURRY UP
AND DIE NOW!
[PANTING]
- I DON'T HAVE THE TIME
TO BOTHER WITH THE LIKES OF YOU!
- KOGA!
- STAY BACK!
- YOU'RE INFURIATING!
- IF YOU WISH
TO BECOME FREE,
USE THOSE SHARDS YOURSELF
AND DESTROY NARAKU.
- HMM...ALL RIGHT.
I WILL.
[GROANING]
DAMN IT. AH!
- I WILL USE THEM.
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
THIS ISN'T EVEN A FIGHT, KAGRA.
HUH?
NARAKU'S DEMONS!
- NARAKU.
- HE ALWAYS SENDS
SO MANY DEMONS TO ATTACK.
HYAH!
- HASN'T NARAKU REALIZED
THAT I TRIED TO BETRAY HIM?
OR IS IT ME HE'S COMMANDING
THE DEMONS TO ATTACK?
- THANKS FOR
THE TARGET, KAGRA!
DIE!
THE SHARDS!
THEY'RE MINE!
- DANCING DRAGON!
- AAH!
- HUH?
- HA. KOGA DOESN'T HAVE
THE STRENGTH RIGHT NOW
TO PUT UP A FIGHT.
- HE'LL BE KILLED
UNLESS WE HELP.
- AAH!
- AND MIROKU,
DON'T TRY AND STOP ME.
- YOU'RE GOING TO
SAVE KOGA?
- GET SERIOUS.
I JUST WANT THE JEWEL SHARDS.
IF KOGA GETS KILLED
IN THIS BATTLE,
THEN KAGRA WILL MAKE
HER ESCAPE.
I CAN'T STAND AROUND
AND DO NOTHING.
- COME BACK HERE,
INUYASHA! PLEASE!
- DON'T LET HER SEE YOU!
[PANTING]
- INUYASHA? WHAT'S UP?
HUH?
- DAY IS BREAKING.
INUYASHA IS GOING TO RETURN
TO HIS HALF-DEMON STATE.
BUT IF HE'S SEEN
BEFORE THAT...
- KAGOME, MIROKU, SANGO,
YOU'RE ALL MERE MORTALS,
YET YOU FOUGHT SO HARD,
ALL BECAUSE YOU BELIEVED
IN YOUR OWN POWER.
I CAN'T HOLD BACK,
KNOWING THAT.
OH...
- KOGA, YOU'RE A GLUTTON
FOR PUNISHMENT, AREN'T YOU?
HOW ABOUT SURRENDERING?
- GRR...
- KOGA!
- LOOK OUT, KOGA!
- I'VE DONE IT.
[GASP]
[GROANING]
[LOUD HEARTBEAT]
- KAGRA, IT CAN'T
BE MUCH FUN
KILLING A HALF-DEAD
WOLF, CAN IT?
- INUYASHA?
- I'LL TAKE YOU ON
FROM THIS POINT.
- I KNOW I SAW IT.
FOR A MOMENT,
I SAW INUYASHA.
- DO YOU THINK THAT KAGRA
MIGHT HAVE SEEN INUYASHA
IN HIS HUMAN STATE JUST NOW?
- YEAH. MAYBE.
[GROANING]
THAT INUYASHA...
IS HE CRAZY?
BUTTING INTO
MY FIGHT LIKE THAT.
- WELL, YOU'RE LUCKY
THAT HE DID.
ANY LATER, AND YOU WOULD HAVE
BEEN KILLED FOR SURE, KOGA.
- HUH. WHAT A LAUGH.
HE CAME TO SAVE ME,
KNOWING THAT KAGRA
WOULD DISCOVER
HIS DIRTY LITTLE SECRET.
- I SEE. THERE WAS
NO MOON LAST NIGHT.
INUYASHA, SO YOU LOSE
ALL YOUR POWERS
ON A MOONLESS NIGHT.
- HUH! WHAT IF I DO?
I'M BACK, SO WHO CARES?
HYAH!
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT DOESN'T MATTER ANYMORE...
BECAUSE YOU'RE GONNA DIE
RIGHT THIS MINUTE!
DANCING DRAGONS!
- WIND STAR!
- WHAT HAPPENED? HOW DID HE
CUT THROUGH MY WHIRLWIND?
- AMAZING!
- HE'S GOING TO GET ME!
- ALL OF NARAKU'S DEMONS...
- THEY PROTECTED KAGRA.
- KAGRA.
SHE ESCAPED AGAIN.
HEY, YOU PUNY WOLF,
HOPE YOU LEARNED YOUR LESSON.
NEVER INTERFERE
IN MY FIGHT WITH NARAKU.
HUH? HUH?
[GROANING]
- FOUND THEM--
MY SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
- WHAT? GIVE THEM HERE!
AH!
- NO WAY I'M DOING THAT.
HMM...
REMEMBER THIS,
MANGY MUTT--
I'VE SWORN TO AVENGE
MY COMRADES' DEATHS.
I'LL BE THE ONE
TO TAKE NARAKU'S HEAD, NOT YOU.
DON'T FORGET THAT.
- WAIT, KOGA.
WHAT YOU SAW LAST NIGHT...
I MEAN, ABOUT INUYASHA,
PLEASE DON'T TELL.
- OH, DON'T WORRY.
I COULDN'T CARE LESS
WHAT SHAPE
THAT MUTT INUYASHA TAKES.
- DOES THAT MEAN
HE WON'T TELL?
- I THINK WE CAN
COUNT ON KOGA.
THE PROBLEM IS KAGRA.
- NARAKU KNOWS NOTHING
OF MY TREACHERY.
THAT'S WHY HE USED DEMONS
TO SAVE ME.
- KANA.
WHERE IS SHE GOING?
ANOTHER ROOM
BENEATH THE CELLAR?
AAH!
- KAGRA...
DID YOU ENJOY
YOURSELF OUTSIDE?
[GASP]
- THESE DEMONS.
NARAKU BUILDS HIS BODY
WITH THESE DEMONS?
HE'S A HALF-DEMON,
JUST LIKE INUYASHA!
- KAGRA...
WHILE I SLEPT,
YOU LEFT THE CASTLE.
DON'T TRY TO DENY IT.
KAGRA, YOU ARE STILL
A PART OF ME.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO RETURN
TO MY FLESH AGAIN?
- NO. PLEASE. WAIT.
I PROMISE
I WON'T DO IT AGAIN.
THIS WILL BE
YOUR LAST CHANCE.
- I CANNOT ESCAPE
FROM NARAKU ON MY OWN.
INUYASHA...
I'LL LET YOU LIVE
FOR A WHILE LONGER.
YOU'RE MY PRECIOUS
TRUMP CARD.
- THIS WILL MAKE OUR LIVES
A LOT HARDER.
NOW THAT KAGRA KNOWS
INUYASHA'S SECRET,
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO BE
STRONGER THAN EVER, SANGO.
- I DON'T NEED YOU
TO WORRY ABOUT ME.
BESIDES, I'M THE ONE
WHO COMES THROUGH
WHEN IT REALLY MATTERS
THE MOST.
- GIVE IT A REST.
- HE'S JUST SAYING THAT.
I MEAN, BEFORE INUYASHA
MET US ALL,
HE'D ACTUALLY NEVER LET
ANYONE ELSE SEE HIS HUMAN FORM.
I THINK HE REALLY DEPENDS
ON EVERY SINGLE ONE OF US.
- HMM. YEAH,
THAT'S WHAT YOU THINK.
- NO NEED TO BE
EMBARRASSED, INUYASHA.
- I AIN'T EMBARRASSED.
- I THINK YOU ARE.
HA HA HA!
IT'S NOT EVEN AN ISSUE,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
- GRR! WOULD YOU GET OFF
MY BACK FOR ONCE!
- YOU CAN ALWAYS COUNT
ON US, INUYASHA.
- KNOCK IT OFF,
WOULD YOU!
I DON'T NEED
ANYONE'S HELP!
- HE'S ALWAYS FIGHTING, BUT
AT LEAST HE TRUSTS ALL OF US.
THAT'S WHY HE DIDN'T LOSE HOPE
ON THE NIGHT OF THE NEW MOON.
MAYBE THAT'S THE SECRET
TO HIS STRENGTH.
- WOULD YOU PEOPLE STOP
GETTING UNDER MY SKIN?
NO, I'M SERIOUS!
THAT'S THE LAST WARNING!
- I AM SHIPPO,
THE FOX-DEMON OF JUSTICE,
AND I RECEIVE
A WRITTEN CHALLENGE
FROM THE SURVIVORS
OF THE THUNDER-DEMON TRIBE.
OOH, THEY'RE PRETTY GUTSY,
THINKING THEY CAN COME AFTER ME.
NEXT TIME, SHIPPO GETS
AN ANGRY CHALLENGE.
I HAVE TO
KEEP IT TOGETHER.