>> IT ALL STARTED WITH THE
SACRED TREE.
>> FIGHTING AND SEARCHING FOR
OUR DREAMS.
>> A STRONG BOND FORMS BETWEEN
US.
>> A NEW HOPE.
A BRIGHT FUTURE BEGINS NOW.
THERE IS ONLY ON WAY TO DEFEAT
THE WICKED NORAKU
GATHERED HERE ARE KIKYO,
NORAKU, INUYASHA AND THE
REST OF US WHO'S FATES
ARE INTERTWINED
>> THE FINAL JEWEL SHARD
GUIDES US.
>> ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE
WELL, A NEW DAY AWAITS.
>> FEUDAL FAIRY TALE.
INUYASHA.
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> HMM?
>> [ROARING]
>> KAGURA!
>> THE CRYSTAL OF DEMONIC AURA
IS STILL GLOWING.
THE INFANT ISN'T HERE THEN?
[GASPS]
THAT LIGHT!
[GRUNTING]
>> MIROKU, SANGO!
>> [GRUNTING]
I'M NOT GONNA DIE HERE!
[GRUNTS]
>> WHO STRUCK KAGURA?
WAS IT GORYOMARU?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, KAGOME?!
>> YEAH.
>> THANK GOODNESS YOU'RE ALL
RIGHT NOW, MASTER!
>> YOUR POWER HAS RETURNED TO
YOU.
>> YES.
I'M GLAD THAT YOU'RE SAFE HERE,
TOO.
>> WAS GORYOMARU PROTECTING ME
FROM KAGURA?
FOR A SECOND, HIS EYES WERE SO
COLD THOUGH.
I'VE FELT THAT AWFUL FEELING
SOMEWHERE BEFORE.
>> [LOWING]
>> HMM?
WHAT SEEMS TO BE THE MATTER,
LORD SESSHOMARU?
WHAT IS THAT?!
HUH?!
WAIT A MINUTE!
ISN'T THAT KAGURA?!
>> HUH?
I THINK SOMETHING'S WRONG WITH
HER.
>> WHATEVER SHALL WE DO, LORD
SESSHOMARU?
>> FORGET ABOUT HER.
WE'RE GOING.
>> HUH?
HA!
HEY, RIN!
>> SHE'LL BE WASHED AWAY!
[SCREAMS]
>> HONESTLY!
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?!
>> MASTER JAKEN!
>> GRAB ONTO THIS, STUPID!
>> WHOA!
>> HELP!
SAVE US!
DON'T LEAVE US LIKE THIS!
SHE DRIFTED ALL THE WAY IN THIS
CONDITION?
SHE'S A GONER IF YOU WANT MY
OPINION.
>> IS SHE DEAD?
>> HMM.
HUH?
>> [GASPS]
>> OH!
WHAT ON EARTH?
OOH.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> HUH?!
>> I'M NOT DEAD.
NARAKU HAS HOLD OF MY HEART SO
I DIDN'T DIE.
SERVES HIM RIGHT.
[GASPS]
>> [GROWLS]
>> YOU PEOPLE.
>> NARAKU, KAGURA IS A TRAITOR.
YOU'RE AWARE OF THAT, AREN'T
YOU?
SO, WHY DO YOU LET HER LIVE?
>> LOOK, HAKUDOSHI,
THIS IS KAGURA'S HEART.
I COULD SQUEEZE THE LIFE OUT OF
IT RIGHT NOW IF I WANTED TO.
BUT I WON'T.
I STILL HAVE USE FOR KAGURA.
>> WHAT USE?
>> SHE'S THE PERFECT BAIT TO
LURE INUYASHA AND HIS FRIENDS
TO ME.
>> WELL, THAT MAKES SENSE.
>> HAKUDOSHI, I HAVE SOMETHING I
WANT YOU TO DO FOR ME AS WELL.
>> LORD SESSHOMARU WAS THE ONE
WHO SAVED YOU, YOU KNOW.
>> AS AN AFTERTHOUGHT.
>> SO YOU HAVE SOME COMPASSION
IN YOU AFTER ALL.
>> HRMPH!
HOW DARE YOU!
YOU SHOULD BE GRATEFUL THAT HE
RESCUED YOU!
>> WE'RE GOING.
>> HOLD IT.
AREN'T YOU GOING TO ASK WHAT
HAPPENED TO ME?
>> LOOK, I HAVE NO INTEREST IN
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU.
>> EVEN IF I TOLD YOU I FOUND
NARAKU'S HEART?
LISTEN, SESSHOMARU, YOU MUST
HAVE NOTICED BY NOW.
NARAKU NEVER DIES NO MATTER HOW
MANY TIMES HE'S SLAIN.
THAT'S BECAUSE HIS HEART IS
LOCATED SOMEWHERE ELSE.
IN ORDER TO DESTROY NARAKU,
YOU HAVE TO DESTROY HIS HEART.
>> LORD SESSHOMARU, BE CAREFUL!
DON'T TRUST HER!
IT MAY BE SOME KIND OF TRAP!
>> UH.
IT'S UP TO YOU WHETHER YOU
BELIEVE ME OR NOT, BUT IT WON'T
HURT YOU TO HANG ON TO THIS.
>> WHAT IS THAT THING?
>> A DEMONIC AURA CRYSTAL.
NARAKU STOLE A JEWEL NAMED THE
FUYOUHEKI THAT CAN HIDE HIS
DEMONIC AURA.
HE USES IT TO COMPLETELY HIDE
THE LOCATION OF HIS HEART.
>> OH!
HMM?
>> THAT CRYSTAL STOPS GLOWING
WHEN IT APPROACHES
THE FUYOUHEKI.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED WHEN I
ATTACKED GORYOMARU'S TEMPLE.
FROM WHAT I CAN TELL, THIS
GORYOMARU FELLOW IS THE
PROTECTOR OF NARAKU'S HEART.
>> WAIT A MINUTE HERE, KAGURA,
THAT WOULD MEAN GORYOMARU MUST
BE A PART OF NARAKU'S GROUP.
WHY WOULDN'T YOU OF ALL PEOPLE
KNOW THAT ALREADY?
>> NARAKU DOESN'T TRUST ME
ENOUGH TO TELL ME THINGS LIKE
THAT.
>> HMM?
>> IF WHAT YOU SAY IS TRUE,
THEN NARAKU MUST ALREADY KNOW
THAT YOU'RE AFTER HIS HEART.
HE'S SMART ENOUGH TO FIGURE OUT
THAT MUCH.
>> AH!
>> LORD SESSHOMARU.
>> AND THAT MEANS IT'S USELESS
FOR YOU TO TAKE ANY
FURTHER ACTION.
>> WHAT ABOUT YOU, SESSHOMARU?
WHY DON'T YOU GET HIM?
>> KAGURA, ARE YOU PLANNING TO
USE ME TO KILL HIM FOR YOU?
>> NARAKU CAN'T POSSIBLY BE
KILLED EXCEPT BY SOMEONE
OF YOUR CALIBER.
NO ONE ELSE SURPASSES YOU IN
TERMS OF YOUR SKILL OR DEMONIC
POWER.
>> SUCH FLATTERY!
>> HMM...
>> THANKS FOR EVERYTHING TODAY.
I'LL BE GOING NOW.
>> ALREADY?
DIDN'T YOU COME TO ASK LORD
SESSHOMARU FOR HELP?
>> NO, NOTHING OF THE SORT.
I JUST...
[SNAPS FINGERS]
>> AAH!
DARN HER!
>> I WANTED TO SEE HIM AGAIN
BEFORE I DIED.
JUST ONE MORE TIME.
THAT'S ALL.
>> SHE WENT AWAY.
>> PUT ON YOUR CLOTHES!
HUH?
LORD SESSHOMARU, WHAT SHOULD WE
DO ABOUT THIS?
>> I'LL LEAVE IT TO YOU.
>> PLEASE, MY LORD, THAT PUTS ME
IN SUCH A BIND.
>> YOU SHOULD HANG ON TO IT,
MASTER JAKEN.
>> DO YOU THINK SO?
>> THAT LADY DIDN'T SEEM LIKE
SHE WAS TRYING TO TRICK US OR
ANYTHING THIS TIME.
I'LL BET SHE WAS SECRETLY IN
LOVE WITH LORD SESSHOMARU.
>> AH!
>> SHE PRAISED HIM.
DON'T YOU REMEMBER THAT?
>> THIS KID IS SO SIMPLE-MINDED.
[BIRD CHIRPING]
>> HEY, MIROKU, ARE YOU SURE
ABOUT LEAVING THE TEMPLE
LIKE THIS?
>> YES, QUITE SURE.
I WANT TO CHECK SOMETHING
OUT TODAY.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> I HAVE A FEELING WE NEED TO
LOOK INTO THIS.
[BUZZING]
>> SANYOSHO?
HUH.
AH!
HAKUDOUSHI.
>> KAGURA, THERE'S WORK TO DO.
>> GRR...
>> THIS IS IT.
DEMONIC AURA IS POURING OUT
OF THIS PLACE.
>> CARCASSES OF DEMONS.
>> THE SCENT.
GAKUSANJIN BODY IS HERE, TOO.
>> THOSE ASCETICS WERE DUMPING
THE DEMONS THEY SLEW IN A PLACE
LIKE THIS?
>> SO IT WOULD SEEM.
THAT WOULD MEAN THEY'RE
GATHERING DEMONIC AURA
ON PURPOSE.
THAT'S BOUND TO ATTRACT OTHER
DEMONS HERE.
>> I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY WOULD THEY DO THIS?
>> THIS PLACE.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER, KAGURA?
ARE YOU FAMILIAR
WITH THIS PLACE?
>> HMM, NO.
WHY?
>> THIS TEMPLE WAS ENTRUSTED
WITH SOMETHING VERY PRECIOUS...
TILL SOMEONE TOLD INUYASHA AND
HIS FRIENDS ABOUT IT.
>> AH.
IS THIS KID TESTING ME?
>> DON'T MOVE!
>> SO YOU'RE ALIVE,
PERSISTENT WOMAN.
>> THIS IS BAD.
>> KAGURA, YOU TAKE CARE OF
THOSE LOW LIFES.
HRMPH!
>> HA!
>> EH!
>> AH!
>> [SCREAMING]
>> UH!
>> MASTER GORYOMARU!
HUH?
MY LIGHT!
AH!
>> SUCH A PATHETIC ATTACK.
>> ARGH...
>> THE SMELL OF BLOOD.
>> FROM THE TEMPLE?
>> YEAH.
WE'D BETTER GET THERE
AND QUICKLY.
>> EVERYONE, PROTECT MASTER
GORYOMARU.
>> GRANTED!
>> RUN FOR IT, ALL OF YOU!
>> DIE, WRETCHED DEMON.
>> ARGH!
>> IT DOESN'T WORK AT ALL!
>> RUN, I TOLD YOU.
>> HEE HEE.
YOUR ATTACKS ON ME ARE IN VAIN,
AND NOW THEY WILL BE RETURNED
TO YOU.
>> HAKUDOUSHI!
>> HUH?
STILL LURKING AROUND HERE, HUH?
>> INUYASHA!
>> MASTER GORYOMARU!
>> GET AWAY FROM ME.
HURRY!
ARGH!
>> MASTER GORYOMARU!
>> GORYOMARU WAS KILLED!
>> OH, MASTER, DON'T LEAVE US!
>> [WEEPING, WAILING]
>> HUH?
>> KANNA.
>> DAMMIT, IT WAS HERE AFTER
ALL.
>> HUH?
INUYASHA!
OVER THERE!
>> HUH?
WHAT'S THAT?
NARAKU'S INFANT.
>> WHAT'S IT DOING HERE?
>> WHO CARES?
WE FOUND IT, AND THAT'S ALL THAT
MATTERS!
HA!
>> KAGURA, YOU HANDLE INUYASHA
AND HIS FRIENDS.
>> HUH?
>> YOU'RE NOT GETTING AWAY!
WIND SCAR!
>> I'LL TELL YOU THIS MUCH--
GORYOMARU DIDN'T KNOW WHAT WAS
GOING ON.
>> HUH?
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE, KAGURA?
>> CAN'T YOU FIGURE IT OUT?
ALL THIS TIME, NARAKU'S HEART
WAS HIDDEN FROM DANGER RIGHT
INSIDE THIS TEMPLE.
>> NARAKU'S HEART?
YOU'RE SAYING THAT THE INFANT
IS HIS HEART?
[WIND BLOWS]
GET BACK HERE, KAGURA!
>> I DON'T HAVE TIME TO WASTE ON
THE LIKES OF YOU PEOPLE.
GOOD-BYE FOR NOW!
>> DAMN YOU!
>> [WEEPING AND WAILING]
>> TO HIDE A LEAF,
YOU CONCEAL IT IN A FOREST.
TO PREVENT THE DEMONIC CRYSTAL
FROM REACTING,
NARAKU HID THE INFANT
IN THAT TEMPLE WHERE THERE WAS A
MASSIVE AMOUNT OF DEMONIC AURA,
AND HE USED GORYOMARU TO KEEP
ACCUMULATING DEMONIC AURA.
HE'S A CLEVER ONE, THAT NARAKU.
>> YOU MUST LEAVE THIS TEMPLE
WITHOUT A MOMENT'S DELAY FOR
YOUR OWN SAFETY.
>> LEAVE THIS?
>> IF YOU VALUE YOUR LIFE,
DO AS WE SAY.
THE DEMONS WILL LEARN ABOUT
GORYOMARU'S DEATH AND SOON
HUNDREDS OF THEM WILL BE HERE.
>> [COLLECTIVE WHINE]
>> A DEMON MADE OF STONE?
AH!
>> WHAT WILL I DO?
SHOULD I KEEP FOLLOWING THEM?
>> HURRY!
WE'VE GOT TO GET TO NARAKU
BEFORE HE CAN HIDE HIS HEART IN
A NEW LOCATION.
AH!
KAGURA!
>> HRMPH!
>> OH, NO, YOU DON'T!
>> WAIT, INUYASHA.
SHE INTENDS TO BETRAY NARAKU.
>> SHE WHAT?
>> THAT'S THE ONLY THING THAT
WOULD EXPLAIN HER BEHAVIOR.
SHE WAS AFTER NARAKU'S HEART
WHEN SHE ATTACKED THE TEMPLE.
AND DESPITE HAKUDOUSHI'S ORDERS,
SHE DIDN'T TRY TO FIGHT US.
>> HUH.
>> MAYBE KAGURA IS TRYING TO
GUIDE US TO NARAKU'S HEART.
>> IT COULD BE A TRAP TO MAKE US
THINK THAT.
>> WHO THE HELL CARES IF IT IS?
AS LONG AS IT MEANS SETTLING OUR
GRUDGE AGAINST NARAKU.
>> I VALUE MY LIFE, TOO, SO I'M
GOING TO USE YOU GUYS.
HUH.
AFTER ALL, USING PEOPLE IS
NARAKU'S SPECIALTY.
>> WE LOST HER.
>> LOOK THERE!
>> IT'S A STONE DEMON.
IN THERE, HUH?
LET'S GO!
>> HUH?
I'M SENSING SOMETHING.
>> THIS SCENT.
NO MISTAKE ABOUT IT.
KAGOME, STAY CLOSE TO ME.
>> YEAH, SURE THING.
>> UH!
>> INUYASHA SENSES THE SAME
PERSON I DO IN HERE.
>> I KNOW YOU'RE IN HERE.
SHOW YOURSELF!
>> AH!
>> HA HA HA!
WELCOME, INUYASHA.
YOU'VE FINALLY COME.
>> NARAKU.
>> [LOW GROWL]
>> WHAT'S WRONG, INUYASHA?
YOU'RE FINALLY FACING THE PERSON
YOU'VE SOUGHT FOR SO LONG, YET
YOU SHOW NO JOY.
>> JUDGING FROM HIS CONFIDENCE,
NARAKU HAS ALREADY MOVED THE
INFANT CONTAINING HIS HEART TO
ANOTHER PLACE.
>> HA HA!
>> THE SACRED JEWEL--
ITS DEMONIC AURA HAS GROWN
STRONGER.
>> NOW, THEN, GIVE ME A PRESENT
BEFORE YOU GO TO THE
NETHERWORLD.
>> SAY WHAT?
>> KAGOME, I MEAN THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARD THAT YOU HAVE IN
YOUR POSSESSION.
[ELECTRICAL CRACKLING]
>> [COLLECTIVE GASP]
>> AH! AH! AH!
>> ACID!
>> WHICH MEANS WE MUST BE INSIDE
A DEMON'S BELLY.
>> WHAT?
THAT THING'S ALIVE?
>> HA HA HA!
YOU WILL ALL DISSOLVE INSIDE
THIS DEMON, LEAVING ONLY THE
SACRED JEWEL SHARD BEHIND.
>> BEFORE THAT HAPPENS, I'LL
TAKE YOUR SCARED JEWEL!
TAKE THIS!
WIND SCAR!
>> TRY WHATEVER YOU LIKE.
YOU'RE STILL NOT GETTING
OUT OF HERE.
>> WIND TUNNEL!
>> AH!
>> THE POISON FROM THE SANYOSHO
WILL GET YOU IF YOU
SEND THEM IN!
>> UH!
AH...
>> MIROKU, YOU IDIOT, DON'T BE
SO STUPID!
>> WHAT CHOICE DO I HAVE?
>> LEAVE IT TO ME.
I'LL HANDLE THIS.
I'LL BLAST NARAKU AND HIS
DEMON'S BELLY.
ADAMANT BARRAGE.
>> HE DID IT!
>> HMM?
>> HA HA HA!
>> NOT EVEN MY ADAMANT BARRAGE
CAN RIP APART THIS DEMON'S
BELLY.
>> IT'S THE POWER OF
THE SACRED JEWEL.
IT'S MAKING THIS PLACE STRONGER.
BUT IF I PURIFY IT...
>> HA HA HA...
>> HE DISAPPEARED.
>> HUH?
DAMMIT.
>> [COUGHING]
>> MIROKU, CAN YOU PUT UP A
BARRIER IN HERE?
>> YEAH.
>> TAKE CARE OF EVERYONE.
I CAN'T WASTE ANY TIME.
THIS IS MY LAST CHANCE.
>> SO THIS DEMON OF STONE
WAS NARAKU'S TRAP.
HUH?
>> HA HA...
IT'S THE END FOR INUYASHA.
>> NARAKU, HOW DO YOU THINK
INUYASHA FOUND THIS PLACE?
>> I WONDER.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, KAGURA?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I HAVE NO IDEA.
>> INUYASHA.
>> DON'T WORRY, KAGOME.
I'LL SAVE YOU.
I PROMISE.
>> THAT INFANT,
IS THAT NARAKU'S HEART?
I CAME HERE IN PURSUIT OF A
TOTALLY DIFFERENT DEMONIC AURA.
WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT I'D COME
ACROSS THE REAL HEART?
>> ADAMANT BARRAGE!
DAMMIT!
>> UH!
PLEASE, INUYASHA,
MAKE IT QUICK.
>> MIROKU, ARE YOU OK?
UH!
THE BARRIER'S COMING DOWN.
>> PUT THIS OVER.
>> INUYASHA.
>> THE DEMON'S MIASMA IS GETTING
STRONGER.
THIS IS MY LAST CHANCE.
KAGOME, GIVE ME
YOUR SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
FAST!
>> NOTHING'S STOPPING ME.
I WILL PUT AN END TO NARAKU'S
LIFE.
THAT'S WHAT THIS MEANS.
>> YOU ARE MISTAKEN.
YOU CANNOT DO IT.
>> HMM.
AH!
UH!
IS THAT THE EVIL PRESENCE THAT
LURED ME HERE?
UH!
YOU WON'T GET AWAY!
I'VE LOST THEM.
THAT DEMONIC AURA HAS FADED.
THE JEWEL THAT THE INFANT HELD,
THAT MUST BE THE STONE KNOWN
KNOWN AS FUYOUHEKI.
>> INUYASHA, HERE.
>> I'M COUNTING ON YOU, SACRED
JEWEL SHARD.
>> HE PUT IT ON TETSUSAIGA?
>> I GET IT--TO MAKE THE
TETSUSAIGA STRONGER!
>> INUYASHA...
>> UH!
HUH?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
SOMETHING IS FLOWING INTO ME
FROM THE TETSUSAIGA.
>> THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
>> INUYASHA'S USING THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARD...
WHICH MEANS THAT IT WILL NO
LONGER BE IN KAGOME'S
POSSESSION.
THE SHARD WHICH KAGOME BARELY
KEPT PURIFIED WILL IMMEDIATELY
SPREAD DEMONIC AURA WITHIN THE
DEMON'S BELLY.
INUYASHA, YOU CANNOT WITHSTAND A
DEMONIC AURA, NOT YOU, BORN OF A
WEAK HUMAN AND A DEMON.
>> ARGH...
ARGH!
DAMMIT.
MY BODY WON'T LISTEN TO ME!
MY HEAD!
ARGH!
[STRAINING]
>> INUYASHA!
>> YAH!
INUYASHA, DON'T GIVE IN TO IT!
>> [STRAINING]
>> KAGOME!
>> KAGOME...
>> INUYASHA, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
KAGOME.
HOLD ON TO ME A BIT LONGER.
JUST A LITTLE LONGER.
>> OK.
AH!
TAKE THIS, NARAKU!
ADAMANT BARRAGE!
>> HMM...
>> ARGH!
>> IT'S THE OUTSIDE!
>> WE MADE IT.
>> HUH.
WE'RE SAFE NOW, KAGOME.
>> UH.
UH...
>> KAGOME!
KAGOME, HANG ON!
KAGOME!
KAGOME...
["KAGOME" ECHOES]
>> SO THIS IS IT, THE TEMPLE
KAGURA SPOKE OF.
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> IT SEEMS THAT SOMEONE WAS
BURIED HERE.
>> HUH?
>> THERE'S NOTHING FOR US HERE.
LET'S GO.
>> HUH?
HEY, WAIT FOR ME, LORD
SESSHOMARU!
HUH!
>> THIS MEDICINAL HERB WORKS
WELL AGAINST DEMONIC ACID BURNS.
>> THANK YOU.
I APPRECIATE IT, KAEDE.
>> HOW IS MIROKU DOING?
>> HE STILL HAS SOME SANYOSHO
POISONING IN HIS SYSTEM.
>> EVEN I CAN'T HELP HIM THERE.
OH!
>> WHERE'S INUYASHA?
>> HE'S OUTSIDE OVER THERE
SULKING ABOUT SOMETHING OR OTHER
AGAIN.
>> PERHAPS I CAN EXPLAIN.
IF I KNOW MASTER INUYASHA, HE'S
PROBABLY UPSET BECAUSE HE
COULDN'T OVERCOME THE DEMONIC
AURA OF THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
>> MAKES SENSE TO ME.
>> HUH?
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE HIS DEMONIC
NATURE GOT THE BEST OF HIM.
INUYASHA STILL HAS A WAYS TO GO.
>> EXACTLY.
OW!
>> KAGOME, COME OUTSIDE WITH ME.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
>> SO HOW COME ALL THIS PRIVACY?
>> YOUR FEET MUST HURT A LOT.
>> INUYASHA?
>> THEY'RE RIGHT.
I STILL HAVE A LONG WAY TO GO.
I'M SO SORRY.
IT'S MY FAULT YOU'RE
IN SO MUCH PAIN.
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT, REALLY.
IF YOU HADN'T BEEN THERE, WE
WOULDN'T EVEN HAVE GOTTEN OUT
ALIVE, AND BESIDES...
>> HUH?
>> IN A WEIRD WAY, I WAS PRETTY
HAPPY WHEN IT WAS HAPPENING.
HMM.
I MEAN, I'M GLAD THAT I WAS BY
YOUR SIDE.
>> KAGOME...
>> HMM...
>> ME, TOO.
I'M GLAD THAT YOU WERE
BY MY SIDE.
I REALLY AM, KAGOME.
>> [MUSIC]
>> MIROKU, ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE
WELL ENOUGH TO BE UP ALREADY?
>> SORRY, SANGO.
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT FOR BEING
SO CARELESS.
>> SURE, WHATEVER.
>> LOOKS LIKE HE'S ALL BETTER.
>> COME ON, HURRY IT UP,
YOU GUYS!
AS LONG AS THERE'S A PATH...
NAH, EVEN IF THERE IS NO PATH,
WE'LL KEEP MOVING ONWARD IN
ORDER TO DESTROY NARAKU.
>> WE'LL PUT ON NEW SHOES AND
KEEP GOING 'CAUSE THIS ADVENTURE
ISN'T OVER YET.
>> WE'LL HUNT DOWN NARAKU TO THE
ENDS OF THE EARTH!
>> YEAH!