>> HERE WE COME.
IT'S THE START OF "INUYASHA."
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL THE
SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY NARAKU WITH
MY TETSUSAIGA.
>> THE BATTLE IS ABOUT TO BEGIN
ON SACRED GROUNDS.
BANKOTSU HAS USED SACRED JEWEL
SHARDS TO INCREASE THE POWER OF
HIS GIANT HALBERD BANRYUU AND
NOW AWAITS OUR ARRIVAL.
>> IT'S UP TO ALL OF US.
>> TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FEUDAL FAIRY TALE.
[WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> FATHER, IT'S STRUCK HIJIRI
ISLAND!
>> YES.
YOU MUST STAY HERE, SON.
>> WHAT ABOUT YOU?
>> I MUST CHECK THE ISLAND TO
SEE THAT SAINT HAKUSHIN'S TEMPLE
IS SAFE.
THIS IS THE STAFF ENTRUSTED TO
OUR ANCESTORS BY THE WISE ONE
HIMSELF.
>> PLEASE, FATHER, TAKE ME WITH
YOU.
>> SHINTARO, RETURN HOME AT
ONCE.
>> BUT, FATHER--
>> UNDERSTAND, IF ANYTHING
SHOULD HAPPEN TO ME, ONLY YOU,
THE SON OF THE VILLAGE HEADMAN,
WILL BE ABLE TO CARRY ON AS THE
PROTECTOR OF HIJIRI ISLAND.
REST AT EASE, SHINTARO.
I SHALL BE HOME BY SUNRISE.
>> FATHER.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK, INUYASHA?
>> THIS ISN'T IT.
IT DIDN'T SMELL MARSHY LIKE THIS
PLACE.
NARAKU'S DEMON PUPPET CARRIED
THE SCENT OF WATER AND FLOWERS.
AND IT WAS PURE, LIKE MOUNT
HAKUREI.
>> LET'S CHECK THE OTHER LAKES
AROUND HERE, THEN.
>> YOU THINK SANGO AND KILALA
ARE OK?
>> MOUNT HAKUREI.
KILALA, IT HURTS YOU TO TRY TO
GO PAST THE BARRIER, TOO,
DOESN'T IT?
SORRY TO FORCE YOU.
I WISH I HAD A CHOICE.
UP HERE!
>> SANGO.
>> HOW DID IT GO?
>> NOT GOOD.
THE MOUNTAIN BARRIER, IT'S EVEN
STRONGER THAN BEFORE.
>> I THOUGHT SO.
WE'LL NEVER BE ABLE TO BREAK
THROUGH IT.
>> ONE THING'S FOR SURE,
NARAKU'S BEEN CLOSE BY.
THERE'S NO QUESTION ABOUT IT.
WHICH MEANS WE'LL JUST HAVE TO
CHECK EVERY WATERWAY AROUND THE
MOUNTAIN.
>> PLEASE TAKE ME OUT ON THE
BOAT.
>> CAN'T DO IT.
YOU KNOW, YOU HAVE A DUTY TO
TAKE OVER YOUR FATHER'S ROLE AS
HEADMAN WHILE HE'S AWAY FROM THE
VILLAGE.
WE CANNOT DO SOMETHING THAT
WOULD PLACE YOU IN ANY DANGER.
>> FATHER HAS BEEN GONE FOR TWO
WEEKS ALREADY.
HE MUST HAVE HAD TROUBLE ON
HIJIRI ISLAND.
>> REMEMBER, MY BOY, THE ONLY
ONES ALLOWED ON THE SACRED
HIJIRI ISLAND ARE THE ACTING
VILLAGE HEADMEN, WHICH MEANS
ONLY YOUR FATHER OR YOURSELF.
>> ALL RIGHT, THEN.
JUST LET ME USE ONE OF YOUR
BOATS.
I'LL GOT THERE BY MYSELF.
>> ARE YOU CERTAIN YOUR FATHER
DIDN'T DO ANYTHING TO RAISE THE
WRATH OF SAINT HAKUSHIN BEFORE
HE SET OUT FOR THE TEMPLE?
>> WE CAN'T HAVE THE VILLAGE
CURSED BECAUSE OF HIS
WRONGDOINGS.
>> MY FATHER HAS DEDICATED HIS
LIFE TO FULFILLING HIS DUTIES AS
HEADMAN.
HE WOULD NEVER DO ANYTHING TO
HARM THE VILLAGE.
>> NEVERTHELESS, WE'D BE
PUNISHED IF WE WENT THERE.
HIJIRI ISLAND IS SACRED GROUND.
>> HEY!
I HEARD YOU MENTION SOMETHING
ABOUT SACRED GROUND.
>> WOULD YOU MIND TELLING US
WHAT IT IS YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT?
>> SEE OUT THERE, NEAR THE
CENTER OF THIS LAKE?
THERE'S AN ISLAND WHICH IS
FORBIDDEN TO COMMON FOLK.
THE DUTY OF VILLAGE HEADMAN HAS
BEEN PASSED DOWN THROUGH THE
MALES IN MY FAMILY.
ONLY THESE SELECT FEW HAVE BEEN
ALLOWED TO SET FOOT ON THE
ISLAND TO TEND TO SAINT HAKUSHIN
AND HIS TEMPLE.
>> SAINT HAKUSHIN, YOU SAY?
>> YES.
HE WAS A WISE MONK WHO LIVED
OVER 100 YEARS AGO.
>> ♪ PURE HAS BECOME IMPURE
IMPURE HAS NOW BECOME PURE
GOOD HAS NOW HAS BECOME BAD
BAD HAS BECOME GOOD
TO LIVE IS TO DIE... ♪
>> HE BECAME A LIVING BUDDHA AND
IS ENSHRINED IN A TEMPLE ON THE
ISLAND.
>> A LIVING BUDDHA?
>> IT'S A PHENOMENON CALLED
SOKUSHINBUTSU.
A MONK OF GREAT VIRTUE MEDITATES
AND FASTS UNTIL HIS DEATH.
EVENTUALLY, HIS BODY MUMMIFIES,
AND IT IS THEN THAT HE ATTAINS
NIRVANA.
>> SO WE'RE TALKING ABOUT A
DRIED-UP OLD PRUNE OF A MONK.
>> WATCH IT.
YOU MIGHT REGRET THAT.
>> YOU SAID YOUR FATHER HASN'T
RETURNED HOME FROM HIS JOURNEY?
>> RIGHT.
HE'S BEEN GONE OVER TWO WEEKS.
IT STARTED WHEN A STRANGE LIGHT
FELL ON THE ISLAND.
FATHER SAID HE WAS CONCERNED
ABOUT THE TEMPLE.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY A STRANGE
LIGHT?
>> WHAT ELSE?
IT HAD TO HAVE BEEN NARAKU.
>> SHINTARO, YOU CANNOT SOLVE
THIS ON YOUR OWN.
>> I KNOW, ELDER SISTER, BUT OUR
FATHER ALWAYS TOLD ME TO TAKE
CARE OF THINGS IF ANYTHING EVER
HAPPENED TO HIM.
>> I HEARD THE VILLAGERS MENTION
SOMETHING ABOUT A CURSE.
>> THE VILLAGERS ARE MISTAKEN.
FATHER PROTECTED THE VILLAGE ALL
HIS LIFE, SO THERE HAS TO BE A
REASON FOR HIS FAILURE TO
RETURN.
>> YES, MY SISTERS AND I ARE
EQUALLY WORRIED ABOUT OUR
FATHER.
>> AND THE VILLAGERS FEAR THERE
MAY BE A CURSE.
>> WE DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
>> LET'S CHECK IT OUT, INUYASHA.
>> YEAH, SOMETHING DOESN'T SOUND
RIGHT ABOUT THAT ISLAND.
>> YOU'LL GO THEN?
YOU WOULD DO THAT FOR ME?
>> OF COURSE WE WILL.
IT'S ONLY NATURAL FOR YOU TO
WORRY ABOUT YOUR FATHER, AFTER
ALL.
>> THANK YOU, FRIENDS.
I WILL GUIDE YOU ACROSS THE LAKE
TO THE ISLAND.
THE AREA IS ALWAYS SHROUDED IN
MIST, AND IT'S DANGEROUS IF YOU
DO NOT KNOW YOUR WAY THERE.
>> PLEASE TAKE GOOD CARE OF OUR
DEAR YOUNGER BROTHER.
>> OUR BROTHER SHINTARO IS THE
ONLY MALE BORN TO OUR FAMILY.
>> THAT MUST BE A VERY DEEP
CONCERN FOR YOU.
IF YOU'LL OBLIGE ME, I WOULD BE
MORE THAN WILLING TO HELP YOU
AND YOUR SISTERS BEAR SOME MALE
OFFSPRING.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
ARE YOU CERTAIN THAT WE CAN PUT
OUR BROTHER'S SAFETY IN YOUR
HANDS?
>> THANKS.
ANY COMPLAINTS, MEN?
>> NO.
>> NONE.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING, INUYASHA?
YOU DON'T HAVE TO THREATEN THE
VILLAGERS.
SORRY ABOUT THIS.
WE JUST WANT TO BORROW YOUR BOAT
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
>> DON'T WORRY, WE'LL BRING IT
BACK AS SOON AS WE'RE DONE.
>> IT MUST BE THE AURA FROM
HIJIRI ISLAND.
IT'S SO STRONG, KILALA ISN'T
EVEN TRANSFORMING.
>> ♪ TO LIVE IS TO DIE
TO DIE IS TO LIVE
SAINT HAKUSHIN BENEATH THE EARTH
MOUNT HAKUREI WILL RETURN TO
HIJIRI ♪
>> WHAT IS THAT?
>> IT'S A CHILDREN'S SONG THAT'S
BEEN SUNG AROUND THESE PARTS FOR
A LONG TIME.
EVEN WHEN HE WAS ALIVE, SAINT
HAKUSHIN HAD WONDROUS SPIRITUAL
POWERS.
THEY SAY HE SAVED MANY PEOPLE OF
THIS REGION.
>> OH?
>> LOOK, THAT'S MOUNT HAKUREI IN
THE DISTANCE.
AT THE BASE OF THE MOUNTAIN IS A
PLACE OF PURIFICATION.
>> A PLACE OF PURIFICATION?
>> IT'S A TEMPLE BUILT BY THE
WISE ONE HIMSELF.
IF YOU PRAY THERE, THEY SAY ALL
OF YOUR SINS WILL BE ABSOLVED.
>> MOUNT HAKUREI AGAIN.
>> HEY, YOU KNOW THE BARRIER
AROUND THE MOUNTAIN?
I WONDER WHO IT WAS THAT CREATED
IT.
>> YES.
SOMEONE, OR PERHAPS SOME THING,
HAD TO HAVE RAISED THE SACRED
BARRIER.
STRANGE, THOUGH.
IT'S THE OPPOSITE OF ANYTHING
NARAKU WOULD TYPICALLY USE.
>> SANGO'S RIGHT.
IT SEEMS MORE LIKE A HOLY PERSON
PUT UP THE BARRIER.
BUT WHY WOULD THEY DO THAT?
>> THAT'S HIJIRI ISLAND.
BE VERY CAREFUL.
THERE ARE CRAGGY ROCKS
EVERYWHERE.
IF THE BOAT STRIKES AN
OUTCROPPING--
[CRASH]
>> YEAH, THANKS FOR THE WARNING.
>> GREAT, WHAT ARE WE GOING TO
TELL THE BOATMEN?
>> CLAM UP.
KEEP COMPLAINING AND I'LL LEAVE
YOU IN THE BOAT.
>> DID I MENTION THAT I CAN'T
SWIM?
>> COME ON, MOVE IT, SHIPPO.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO SEE?
AH, THAT'S HELPFUL.
>> HEY, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT,
MIROKU?
>> YOU SAVED ME, SANGO.
>> HERE WE GO.
IT'S LIKE THE BARRIER AROUND
MOUNT HAKUREI.
NOT AS STRONG THOUGH, BY THE
LOOKS OF IT.
NOW I'M SURE OF IT.
IT'S THESE FLOWERS.
THEY SMELL JUST LIKE NARAKU'S
DEMON PUPPET.
>> THERE NEVER USED TO BE
FLOWERS LIKE THESE GROWING
AROUND HERE.
>> ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, SHIPPO?
>> SURE, I'M DOING GREAT.
>> THE SCENT IS OVERPOWERING
KILALA, TOO.
>> THIS IS ALL A LITTLE TOO
CONVENIENT.
WHY WOULD NARAKU DO THIS?
WHY WOULD HE CREATE A DEMON
PUPPET MERELY TO HELP THE BAND
OF 7 ESCAPE...
AND THEN LEAVE THE STRONG SCENT
OF THESE FLOWERS?
IT'S LIKE THEY WERE LEFT TO LURE
ME TO THESE SACRED GROUNDS.
>> WHAT'S THAT THING?
>> IT'S THE TEMPLE OF THE WISE
ONE.
IT'S DESTROYED, BUT WHY?
FATHER'S CLOTHING.
IT'S MY FATHER!
>> HIS FATHER CAME TO THIS
ISLAND A MERE TWO WEEKS AGO.
>> HE SHOULDN'T HAVE BEEN
REDUCED TO BONES IN SUCH A SHORT
TIME.
>> PERHAPS ONE OF NARAKU'S
DEMONS DID THIS.
>> YEAH, NOW I'M ALMOST POSITIVE
OF IT.
>> OK, BUT FOR WHAT REASON?
>> WHAT IS IT THAT MAKES THIS
ISLAND SO SPECIAL?
>> I SENSE A SHIKON JEWEL SHARD.
>> DAMN.
IT'S ABOUT TIME YOU SHOWED UP--
MAKING ME WAIT SO LONG IN HERE.
THIS PLACE MAKES EVEN A HUMAN
LIKE ME FEEL SICK.
IT MUST BE EVEN MORE TRYING FOR
A HALF-DEMON, RIGHT, INUYASHA?
>> BANKOTSU.
>> DAMN.
IT WAS A TRAP.
DID YOU DO ALL THIS, BANKOTSU?
>> DON'T LOOK AT ME.
I WAS ONLY TOLD TO WAIT HERE,
NOTHING MORE THAN THAT.
>> CAREFUL AROUND HIM, INUYASHA.
BANKOTSU'S HALBERD HAS SACRED
JEWEL SHARDS IN IT.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
IT GOT SCARRED DURING OUR LITTLE
MATCH THE OTHER DAY, SO I USED
THE JEWEL SHARDS TO REPAIR IT.
NOW, LET'S FINISH THIS OFF,
INUYASHA!
>> THIS TIME I'M GOING TO CUT
YOU TO PIECES!
>> I'LL BE THE ONE DOING THE
DAMAGE, HALF-DEMON.
>> BANKOTSU HAS THE UPPER HAND.
>> BECAUSE OF THE SHIKON SHARDS
IN BANKOTSU'S HALBERD.
>> DAMN IT.
I'M SICK OF YOU.
WIND SCAR!
>> WHAT?
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO THE WIND
SCAR?
WHERE IS IT?
>> NOW IT MAKES SENSE.
NO WONDER HE TOLD ME TO FIGHT
YOU HERE.
>> WHY CAN'T HE USE THE WIND
SCAR?
>> I BELIEVE IT'S BECAUSE THE
TETSUSAIGA'S DEMONIC POWER IS
BEING PURIFIED BY HIJIRI ISLAND.
FURTHERMORE, NO MATTER HOW EVIL
BANKOTSU'S SPIRIT MAY BE, HE WAS
STILL A MERE HUMAN IN LIFE.
INUYASHA HAS DEMON BLOOD IN HIM,
AND IN COMPARISON, THE EFFECT OF
HIJIRI ISLAND ON BANKOTSU IS
MINIMAL.
>> INUYASHA, YOU'RE SO MUCH
WEAKER THAN THE LAST TIME WE
FOUGHT EACH OTHER.
SURRENDER AND DIE.
I DON'T WANT TO STAY ON THIS
MISERABLE ISLAND A MINUTE LONGER
THAN I HAVE TO.
>> SOMEONE HAS TO BE PUTTING UP
THIS PURIFYING BARRIER, I KNOW
IT.
JUST AS I THOUGHT.
IT'S OVER THERE.
>> SHINTARO!
>> SAINT HAKUSHIN, PLEASE COME
TO INUYASHA'S ASSISTANCE!
THAT STAFF, IT'S FATHER'S!
>> SHINTARO.
>> SAINT HAKUSHIN ISN'T HERE.
HE'S GONE.
>> WHAT?
HOW COULD THAT BE?
>> HIS BODY WAS ENSHRINED HERE.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
DOES THIS MEAN NARAKU ATTACKED
THIS ISLAND TO STEAL THE SAINT'S
BODY?
MIROKU, SAINT HAKUSHIN'S MUMMY
HAS GONE MISSING FROM THE TOMB.
NARAKU MAY HAVE STOLEN IT.
>> SOMEONE'S STOLEN THE BODY?
THEN IT WASN'T SAINT HAKUSHIN
WHO PUT UP THE BARRIER.
IF IT WASN'T SAINT HAKUSHIN,
THEN WHO DID PUT UP THE BARRIER
ON HIJIRI ISLAND?
>> INUYASHA!
>> DAMN.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> WELL, ALL THIS TIME I WAS
CONVINCED THAT SAINT HAKUSHIN
WAS THE ONE PUTTING UP THIS
BARRIER AROUND THE ISLAND.
>> BARRIER?
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
SAINT HAKUSHIN WAS SOMEONE WHO
SAVED PEOPLE.
WHY WOULD HE PUT UP A BARRIER?
>> YOU REMEMBER THE STRANGE
LIGHT YOU AND YOUR FATHER SAW,
SHINTARO?
IT WAS A DEMON NAMED NARAKU.
>> NARAKU?
>> YES, YOU SEE, I'M CERTAIN
THAT YOUR FATHER MUST HAVE
FOUGHT NARAKU AND TRIED TO
PROTECT THE SAINT.
>> SAINT HAKUSHIN, SAVE ME!
>> THEN THAT SKELETON REALLY WAS
MY FATHER.
>> NARAKU WANTED TO USE SAINT
HAKUSHIN'S IMMENSE SPIRITUAL
POWER.
THAT'S WHY HE CAME TO THE
ISLAND.
AND I'M GUESSING THAT WHEN YOUR
FATHER DISCOVERED THAT, HE TRIED
TO STOP HIM.
>> THAT IS THE DUTY OF THE
VILLAGE HEADMAN.
SO FATHER DIDN'T DIE BECAUSE HE
WAS CURSED.
THAT'S RIGHT, ISN'T IT?
>> OF COURSE.
>> IF SAINT HAKUSHIN ISN'T IN
THE SHRINE ANY LONGER, THEN
WHERE ON EARTH IS HE?
AND WHO PUT UP THE BARRIER?
>> DAMN IT.
>> ONE LAST STRIKE.
THIS IS THE END FOR YOU,
INUYASHA!
>> INUYASHA, WE JUST NEED YOU TO
HOLD HIM OFF A LITTLE BIT
LONGER!
NOW, IF I CAN FIND THE CORE OF
THE BARRIER.
SHIPPO, I NEED TO USE YOUR
POWERS.
SHIPPO'S DEMONIC POWERS HAVE
BEEN TRANSFERRED TO THE SUTRA
CHARMS.
IT SHOULD PRODUCE A REACTION.
THEY'VE BEEN PURIFIED.
IT'S OVER THERE.
>> I'VE SEEN THAT BEFORE.
IT'S AN ALTAR ORNAMENT SAINT
HAKUSHIN ALWAYS USED.
>> SO THIS IS IT.
>> I'LL USE THIS STAFF THE SAINT
ONCE OWNED AND WE'LL TRY IT
TOGETHER.
>> MIROKU.
>> LET'S GIVE IT A SHOT, THEN.
>> GIVE ME STRENGTH TO SUCCEED,
FATHER.
>> THE FLOWERS HAVE DISAPPEARED.
>> THE WIND SCAR IS BACK.
THE BARRIER IS BROKEN.
>> THIS ORNAMENT MUST BE WHAT
CREATED THE BARRIER.
>> BUT THIS VAJRA WAS LOCKED UP
INSIDE THE TEMPLE.
>> IT CAN'T BE.
DOES THIS MEAN THAT SAINT
HAKUSHIN IS HELPING NARAKU?
>> DON'T THINK THIS WILL SAVE
YOU, INUYASHA, BECAUSE AS YOU
SEE, I'M FEELING MUCH STRONGER
NOW, TOO, NOW THAT THAT
DISGUSTING BARRIER IS FINALLY
GONE.
THE BARRIER'S GONE AND OUR
POWERS HAVE RETURNED TO NORMAL.
SO LET'S SETTLE THIS ONCE AND
FOR ALL, INUYASHA.
[WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> TAKE THIS.
DRAGON POWER!
>> MULTIPLE LIGHTNING BOLTS?
DAMN YOU FOR GETTING KAGOME AND
THE OTHERS INVOLVED.
>> ALL'S FAR IN LOVE AND WAR.
>> I'LL KILL YOU, EVEN IF IT
COSTS ME MY LIFE.
>> INUYASHA FIGHTS BANKOTSU.
DURING THEIR BATTLE, SAINT
HAKUSHIN'S POWER SAVES BANKOTSU.
>> NEXT ON INUYASHA, "THE SACRED
VAJRA AND THE MYSTERY OF THE
LIVING BUDDHA."
>> COULD SAINT HAKUSHIN BE
HELPING BANKOTSU?