>> IT ALL STARTED WITH THE
SACRED TREE.
>> FIGHTING AND SEARCHING FOR
OUR DREAMS.
>> A STRONG BOND FORMS
BETWEEN US.
>> A NEW HOPE, A BRIGHT FUTURE
BEGINS NOW.
>> I'M KEEPING IT A SECRET
FROM INUYASHA, BUT I'M GOING
BACK TO THE PRESENT FOR A
LITTLE R AND R.
THAT IS, UNTIL MY CLASSMATES,
YUKA, ERI, AND AYUMI, DEMAND
ON MEETING INUYASHA.
>> THE FINAL JEWEL SHARD GUIDES
US.
>> ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE
WELL, A NEW DAY AWAITS.
>> A FEUDAL FAIRY TALE.
"INUYASHA."
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> WELL, I'M OFF, YOU GUYS.
>> OK, TAKE YOUR TIME OVER THERE
AND REST, KAGOME.
WE'LL BE DOING SOME RECUPERATING
OURSELVES.
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE THOSE RATS
CHEWED THEM UP PRETTY BAD.
>> NOW, USE THE MEDICINE.
I'LL BRING BACK SOME MORE.
>> OK.
>> UH, KAGOME?
>> HMM?
>> UH, NEVER MIND.
SEE YOU SOON.
>> BYE.
>> [PANTING]
SHE'S ALREADY CROSSED OVER, I
GUESS.
>> HMM.
>> I SEE.
SISTER KIKYO, YOU SAY?
SO, SHE'S STILL IN THIS WORLD.
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN AS MUCH.
>> YOU DON'T SEEM VERY
SURPRISED, KAEDE.
>> NO.
A LITTLE WHILE AGO, TWO GIRLS
WHO SEEMED LIKE SHIKIGAMI
APPEARED.
THEY TOOK SOIL FROM MY SISTER'S
SHRINE.
I'M QUITE SURE WHAT IT WAS FOR.
I THINK THE SOIL WAS USED TO
HEAL WOUNDS WHICH WERE INFLICTED
ON HER BY NARAKU.
>> LISTEN, KAEDE, I DON'T KNOW
HOW YOU FEEL ABOUT IT,
BUT I FOR ONE AM REALLY GLAD
THAT KIKYO WAS SAVED.
ALSO...
THE PERSON WHO SAVED KIKYO FROM
BEING EATEN AWAY BY NARAKU'S
MIASMA, IT WAS KAGOME.
>> OH, I SEE.
KAGOME, YOU SAY?
>> MMM. MMM.
AHH.
IT'S BEEN SO LONG.
THIS FEELS SO GOOD.
>> MEOW.
>> BUYO, YOU'RE KIND OF HEAVY.
>> [YAWNING]
>> MMM...
INUYASHA.
I WONDER HOW HE'S DOING?
>> MEOW.
>> KIKYO.
>> I CAME BACK TO THE PRESENT
WITHOUT TELLING HIM.
I HOPE THAT WAS OK.
KIKYO SEEMED TO HAVE REGAINED
HER SPIRITUAL POWERS.
SHE LOOKED WELL, BUT SHE
DISAPPEARED AGAIN.
WHO KNOWS WHAT HE THOUGHT?
MAYBE INUYASHA REALLY WANTED TO
GO AFTER HER.
EVEN WHILE WE WERE ALL HEADING
BACK TO KAEDE'S VILLAGE, IT FELT
A LITTLE AWKWARD SPEAKING TO
HIM.
>> MEOW.
>> [SIGH]
>> I GUESS SHE'S MORE IMPORTANT.
I'M SECOND FIDDLE TO HER.
>> WHY?
WHY DID YOU LET KAGOME GO BACK?
>> WE DON'T HAVE TO ASK YOUR
PERMISSION FOR EVERYTHING, DO
WE?
>> HERE'S THE THING, INUYASHA.
YOU TOLD KAEDE ABOUT KIKYO
EARLIER.
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN?
>> YEAH, SO WHAT?
>> WELL, KAGOME COULDN'T EXACTLY
INTERRUPT YOU.
>> SHE WAS ONLY TRYING TO BE
CONSIDERATE OF YOU.
>> COME ON, IT WASN'T LIKE--
IT WASN'T LIKE I WAS TELLING HER
ANYTHING I DIDN'T WANT
OVERHEARD.
WHAT ARE YOU BLAMING ME FOR?
>> UGH! YOU ARE SO IRRITATING!
SIT, BOY.
GOOD.
I GUESS IT ONLY WORKS WHEN
KAGOME SAYS IT.
>> HA HA HA!
YOU ONLY FIGURED THAT OUT NOW,
STUPID?
>> [THINKING] I WAS KINDA
HOPING THAT WOULD WORK.
>> [THINKING] GEEZ.
INUYASHA'S NEVER GOING TO FEEL
SORRY FOR WHAT HE DID.
>> HUH? WHAT'S THIS?
>> WELL, A HAND ME DOWN FROM OUR
NEIGHBOR.
YOU TOLD ME A WHILE BACK THAT
YOUR BIKE WAS LOST ON THE OTHER
SIDE.
IT'S A BIT RUSTED, BUT THAT
DOESN'T MATTER, DOES IT?
>> NO.
THIS IS AWESOME!
THANKS A TON FOR THIS, MOM.
[HUMMING]
>> SIS, AREN'T YOU GOING TO
SCHOOL?
YOU'RE GOING TO BE LATE.
>> I KNOW.
I'M ALMOST DONE.
>> WHY ARE YOU BOTHERING?
IT'S GOING TO GET FILTHY DIRTY
AS SOON AS YOU TAKE IT BACK
THERE.
>> NEVER MIND.
[THINKING] IT'S NOT BAD WHEN
INUYASHA CARRIES ME ON HIS BACK.
STILL, THERE'S NOTHING LIKE
HAVING MY OWN RIDE.
HMM.
SPICK AND SPAN AND READY TO GO.
>> YOU SURE MANAGED TO GET IT
SPARKLY.
>> HEY, KAGOME!
>> [GRUNT]
>> [GROANING]
>> INUYASHA, SURPRISE, SURPRISE.
SO, YOU'VE COME TO HANG OUT WITH
US AGAIN?
>> YEAH, I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR
THAT.
SO, WHAT'S THE DEAL, KAGOME?
YOU LEFT WITHOUT EVEN ASKING ME
FOR--
[TITTERING]
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE
DOING?
YOU BROKE MY BIKE!
LOOK AT IT!
>> WHAT'S WITH YOU?
>> WHY, YOU!
GREAT!
IT'S TOTALLY BENT!
>> TOO BAD.
YOU HAD IT ALL NICE AND SHINY,
TOO.
>> [GRUNT]
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO TO GET IT
BACK IS THIS.
[GROANING]
>> INUYASHA!
>> UHH...
>> YEAH, YEAH.
I'LL FIX IT, ALL RIGHT?
>> KEEP YOUR HANDS OFF MY BIKE!
>> I SAID I'D FIX IT.
>> THANKS, BUT NO THANKS.
>> AND STOP BEING ALL HUFFY!
>> IT'S OK.
>> IT'S NOT OK!
>> SIT!
>> [GRUNTING]
>> KICKSTAND'S RIGHT IN MY
SPLEEN.
>> [PEOPLE CHATTERING]
>> HEY, DID YOU GUYS FINISH YOUR
HOMEWORK?
>> [THINKING] GEEZ.
WHAT'S INUYASHA DOING HERE
ANYWAY?
AND WHAT'S HE SO MAD ABOUT?
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> YEAH.
>> UNREAL!
>> HEY, IT'S KAGOME!
>> HI, YUKA. HI, ERI.
>> LONG TIME NO SEE!
>> WHAT'S WITH THE LONG FACE,
KAGOME?
>> DON'T TELL ME SOMETHING
HAPPENED WITH THAT BOYFRIEND OF
YOURS.
>> UH...
[THINKING] THESE GUYS DON'T MISS
A BEAT.
>> OH, ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> BOY, THAT'S ROUGH.
>> SO, IN OTHER WORDS, THAT
DELINQUENT BOYFRIEND OF YOURS IS
TWO-TIMING YOU AGAIN?
>> WELL, SORT OF.
IT'S NOT AS SIMPLE AS IT SOUNDS,
AND HE'S GOT HIS REASONS.
>> YEAH, BUT HE'S CHEATING
'CAUSE HE CAN'T DECIDE, RIGHT?
HE CAN'T CHOOSE BETWEEN YOU AND
THE OTHER WOMAN, RIGHT?
>> HUH?
[THINKING] HE'S GOT TO CHOOSE
BETWEEN US?
I KNOW THAT INUYASHA HAS
FEELINGS FOR KIKYO.
THEN AGAIN, I WAS THE ONE WHO
DECIDED TO STAY BY HIM.
I THOUGHT IT WAS OK, SEEING AS I
LIKE HIM AND ALL.
>> MAYBE IT'S BETTER THAT HE
CAN'T MAKE UP HIS MIND, 'CAUSE
IT'D BE KINDA LOUSY IF HE'S
DECIDED WHO'S FIRST AND WHO'S
SECOND.
>> HUH?
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN, FIRST AND
SECOND?
YOU MEAN WHO HE LIKES BETTER?
>> YOU GOT A POINT THERE.
>> SO, WHICH ONE DOES HE LIKE
MORE?
HIS FIRST GIRL HE LOVED OR YOU?
WHO DOES HE HAVE STRONGER
FEELINGS FOR?
>> SO, I'M FIRST OR I'M SECOND.
I GUESS IF YOU PUT IT THAT WAY,
THEN I PROBABLY COME SECOND IN
HIS MIND.
>> [GIGGLING]
>> YOU KNOW, KAGOME, BEING
SECOND PLACE ISN'T NECESSARILY A
BAD THING, RIGHT?
>> YEAH, SHE'S RIGHT.
THE SECOND BATCH OF STOCK IS
GOOD FOR MISO SOUP, AND IT'S
PRETTY GOOD FOR STEWS AS WELL.
>> GOOD RESTAURANTS ALWAYS USE
THE FIRST BATCH.
>> [GASPING]
>> YOU DEFINITELY HAVE A POINT
THERE.
>> WELL, THINK OF BASEBALL,
THOUGH.
THE CATCHER IS SECOND MOST
IMPORTANT POSITION.
HE'S THE CONTROL GUY CALLING THE
PITCHES.
>> AND THERE'S A SUPPORTING
ACTOR IN KABUKI.
HE'S ALWAYS A HUNK.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
STILL, THOUGH...
[SIGH]
>> LOOK, MAYBE YOU'D BE BETTER
OFF NOT SEEING HIM, KAGOME?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> HUH?
>> HMM, MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT'D BE ONE WAY TO DEAL WITH
IT.
>> I CAN'T HELP IT.
THE GUY FOLLOWS ME HOME.
IT'S NOT LIKE I ASK HIM TO.
LIKE FIRST THING THIS MORNING,
FOR INSTANCE.
>> HUH?!
>> HE'S AT YOUR HOUSE RIGHT NOW?
>> SHOW ME!
>> I WANT TO MEET HIM!
>> KAGOME'S BAD BOY BOYFRIEND!
>> [CHUCKLING NERVOUSLY]
>> [GRUNTING]
>> HERE YOU ARE.
I MADE YOU A LITTLE SOMETHING TO
EAT.
SO, THINK YOU CAN FIX IT?
>> YEAH, I THINK SO.
I HEARD THAT SHE GOT THIS BIKE
FROM SOMEWHERE TO REPLACE THE
ONE THAT GOT BROKEN OVER IN MY
WORLD.
>> YES.
OUR NEIGHBOR SAID SHE COULD HAVE
IT.
>> SORRY ABOUT THIS.
>> OH?
>> FOR BREAKING IT, I MEAN.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO FIX IT
THOUGH, RIGHT?
>> HUH? YEAH.
>> I HAVE FAITH IN YOU.
[GIGGLING]
>> HUH?
HMPH!
ALL RIGHT.
[GULPING]
HA! SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
YOU JUST GO LIKE THIS...
AAH!
OH, NO!
IT COLLAPSED.
DAMN IT!
WHY ISN'T THIS WORKING?
>> WHAT THE--HEY, LET GO OF ME,
YOU STUPID--
AAH! I SAID LET GO!
OK, FINE.
WE'LL DO IT YOUR WAY.
IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
THERE'S NO WAY A COUPLE OF RINGS
CAN DEFEAT ME!
THOUGHT YOU HAD ME THERE, DIDN'T
YOU, BUDDY?
AAH!
>> I WONDER WHAT HE'S LIKE, THIS
SELFISH, TWO-TIMING RUFFIAN
BOYFRIEND OF HERS.
>> I CAN'T WAIT.
>> [THINKING] I DIDN'T THINK
THEY'D REALLY COME ALONG.
AND HERE THEY WERE TELLING ME TO
STOP SEEING HIM.
COME ON, YOU GUYS.
WE'RE ALL BUSY WITH EXAMS,
RIGHT?
WE CAN'T AFFORD TO BE FOOLING
AROUND LIKE THIS.
>> SURE WE CAN!
>> THIS IS WAY MORE IMPORTANT
THAN EXAMS.
>> [SIGH]
>> BESIDES, IT SOUNDS LIKE WE
HAVE TO SET HIM STRAIGHT ABOUT A
FEW THINGS.
>> NO!
IF YOU DO THAT, HE'LL TOTALLY
FREAK ON ME!
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
>> I'M LIKING HIM LESS AND LESS
ALL THE TIME.
>> WE'D BETTER PUT THAT CREEP IN
HIS PLACE.
>> [THINKING] OH!
OH, GREAT.
I CAN'T LET THEM MEET INUYASHA.
FOR STARTERS, THEY'LL FIND OUT
HE'S A HALF DEMON.
OH, THIS ALL INUYASHA'S FAULT
FOR COMING AROUND HERE
UNINVITED!
>> LOOK AT HER.
KAGOME SEEMS REALLY UPSET AGAIN.
>> MAYBE YOU SAID TOO MUCH TO
HER THIS TIME, ERI.
>> HEY!
HOW DID IT GET TO BE MY FAULT?
>> MAYBE WE SHOULDN'T GO WITH
HER.
>> YOU SAID IT.
BESIDES, KAGOME SEEMS TO LIKE
HIM DESPITE WHAT KIND OF PERSON
HE IS.
>> THAT'S WHEN A GIRL NEEDS
SUPPORT.
>> WHAT ARE FRIENDS FOR?
>> MM-HMM.
>> HUH?
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT A THING,
KAGOME.
WE'RE ON YOUR SIDE AND WE'LL
ROOT FOR YOU ALL THE WAY.
>> NO MATTER HOW VIOLENT THIS
GUY IS.
>> NO MATTER HOW TWO-TIMING HE
IS.
>> HMPH!
>> UH...YEAH. RIGHT.
>> [TITTERING]
>> I'M HOME!
HI, INUYASHA.
AAH!
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO BE?
>> AN IRON CART, OBVIOUSLY.
>> IT LOOKS WORSE THAN IT DID
THIS MORNING.
>> WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
KAGOME WILL KILL ME IF I DON'T
FIX IT.
>> WHY DON'T YOU JUST PAY HER
BACK INSTEAD?
HEY, CHECK IT.
IS THIS THE ADAMANT STONE YOU
WERE TALKING ABOUT?
>> YEAH, THAT'S THE ONE.
>> OK, HERE'S THE THING.
THIS IS CALLED A DIAMOND.
ONE OF THESE COULD BUY LOTS AND
LOTS OF BIKES.
>> HMPH.
THEN LET ME TAKE IT FROM HERE.
I'LL MAKE A WHACK OF IT WITH MY
TETSUSAIGA!
>> SERIOUSLY, YOU COULD DO THAT?
>> HA! JUST WATCH.
ADAMANT BARRAGE!
>> [TITTERING]
>> THAT'S STRANGE.
SPEARS OF ADAMANT WERE SUPPOSED
TO COME FLYING OUT WHEN I MADE
THAT MOVE.
>> AAH! DON'T, INUYASHA!
YOU GOTTA STOP BREAKING THINGS
AROUND THIS PLACE.
>> HA, YOU'RE A PAIN FOR SUCH A
LITTLE GUY.
OK, THEN HOW 'BOUT THIS?
>> AAH!
STOP IT!
THAT'S TOO DANGEROUS!
>> LET ME DO IT UNTIL THE JEWELS
COME OUT!
>> NOT ON YOUR LIFE!
GRANDPA?
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
>> HUH?
>> INUYASHA WANTS TO WORK HERE
AT THE SHRINE FOR US PART TIME.
HE SAYS HE'LL WORK REALLY,
REALLY HARD FOR BREAKING THE
BICYCLE.
>> HA!
I'M NO CHEAP LABOR, EITHER.
>> [THINKING] OH, BROTHER.
I'M HOME ALREADY.
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
TELLING INUYASHA THAT HE'S NOT
TO COME OUT IS EVEN WORSE THAN
THE ONLY OTHER OPTION.
>> KAGOME'S BACK HAS ANGUISH
WRITTEN ALL OVER IT.
>> WE'D BETTER BE NICE WHEN WE
MEET HER DELINQUENT BOYFRIEND.
>> YOU MEAN, EVEN IF HE HAS A
GANGSTER HAIRCUT?
>> DEFINITELY.
EVEN IF HIS PANTS ARE PINK OR
PURPLE.
>> HMPH!
>> HUH?
>> WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO BE?
>> AN AVANT-GARDE SCULPTURE?
>> UGH! INUYASHA!
>> INU--
>> IS THAT HER BOYFRIEND'S NAME?
>> OH, MAYBE THAT'S HIS GANG
NAME.
HE'S DELINQUENT, RIGHT?
>> AH, ALL RIGHT.
THIS ONE GOES HERE,
AND THIS IS THE NEXT ONE.
HERE.
UGH.
>> PART TIMER, THAT BOX GOES
OVER THERE, FURTHER DOWN.
>> HMM. RIGHT.
>> INUYASHA!
>> [TITTERING]
>> HUH?
SOUNDS LIKE KAGOME'S CALLING
YOU, PART TIMER.
>> I DIDN'T HEAR ANYTHING.
>> NO? YOU SURE?
WELL, THEN BRING THAT JAR OVER
HERE.
>> HUH? THIS ONE?
>> DON'T YOU DARE BREAK IT,
EITHER;
THAT JAR HAS A LONG AND COLORFUL
HISTORY.
>> UGH!
>> SO, BE EXTREMELY CAREFUL.
>> INUYASHA, SIT!
>> AAH!
THE JAR!
>> IT WASN'T MY FAULT!
>> [THINKING] HE'S IN THE SHED.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER?
>> KAGOME?
>> [SOBBING]
>> GRANDPA, WHERE'S INUYASHA AT?
>> HE RAN AWAY.
>> UNBELIEVABLE.
HE BREAKS EVERYTHING HE LAYS HIS
HANDS ON.
>> I THINK HE ALREADY LEFT.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
THAT'S TOO BAD.
>> AND WE WERE DYING TO MEET THE
GUY, YOU KNOW?
>> HE COMES AROUND PRETTY OFTEN,
THOUGH, DOESN'T HE?
>> UH, WELL, NOT EXACTLY.
[THINKING] OH, GOOD.
IT ALL WORKED OUT, SORTA.
HE'S SUCH A WEIRDO.
>> KAGOME?
>> HUH?
>> COME GET SOME TEA.
>> ALL RIGHT.
UH, I WON'T BE LONG, YOU GUYS.
>> OH.
>> TOO BAD.
I REALLY WANTED TO SEE HIM.
>> YOU CAN SAY THAT AGAIN.
WE CAME ALL THE WAY HERE, TOO.
>> WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM, KAGOME?
YOU'VE BEEN UPSET SINCE THIS
MORN--
>> [GASP] YOU WOULDN'T BE--
>> HE'S GOTTA BE.
>> HE'S DEFINITELY!
>> HMM.
WHO ARE YOU GIRLS?
>> YES!
HE'S THE NUTCASE WHO WENT CRAZY
AT THE SCHOOL RECITAL!
>> THE ONE WHO HAD A RUN-IN WITH
HOJO DURING THE CULTURAL
FESTIVAL.
>> THAT GUY WAS KAGOME'S
BOYFRIEND?
>> [SIGH] SORRY TO KEEP YOU.
>> DID KAGOME ASK YOU TO DO THAT
BACK THEN?
>> UH-HUH, YEAH.
MORE OR LESS.
>> [THINKING] I DON'T BELIEVE
THIS!
WHY IS INUYASHA TALKING TO THEM?
AAH!
[THINKING] THEY'RE GOING TO FIND
OUT THAT HE'S A HALF DEMON!
>> SO, TELL US.
WHEN DID YOU START SEEING
KAGOME?
>> IT'S BEEN A WHILE NOW, I
GUESS.
>> WHAT'S WITH THE CRAZY DUDS?
ARE YOU WORKING AT THE SHRINE OR
SOMETHING?
>> YOUR EYES SURE ARE AN UNUSUAL
COLOR.
>> DO YOU BLEACH YOUR HAIR WHITE
OR WHAT?
>> IT'S THE COLOR I WAS BORN
WITH.
>> [GASP] WOW, THAT'S DIFFERENT.
>> YOU THINK SO?
>> CAN I TOUCH IT?
>> YEAH, I GUESS SO.
>> [THINKING] THEY'RE CARRYING
ON A CONVERSATION?
>> HEY, HE'S GOTTA BE BIRACIAL
OR SOMETHING.
>> BI WHAT?
>> WELL, KAGOME, IS HE?
>> WELL...
YOU COULD CALL IT THAT.
[THINKING] HE IS A HALF DEMON.
>> OH, HE'S SWEET!
>> AWESOME.
>> I'M JEALOUS, KAGOME.
>> SO COOL.
>> SO, YOU'VE LIVED OVERSEAS,
HAVE YOU?
>> TELL ME, WHEN DID YOU COME TO
JAPAN?
>> SEE YOU, KAGOME!
>> I'LL BE SEEING YOU.
>> KAGOME, HE'S NOT AS BAD AS
YOU MADE HIM OUT TO BE.
>> YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
I THOUGHT HE LOOKED LIKE A GUY
IN A STREET GANG OR SOMETHING.
>> WELL, HE IS A BIT DIFFERENT,
THOUGH.
>> YOU KNOW, HE'S NOT ALL LIKE I
PICTURED HE'D BE.
>> SEE YA.
>> YOU TWO GET ALONG.
>> NOW, THE REAL PROBLEM IS
HOJO.
>> YEAH, HE DOESN'T KNOW ABOUT
THE BAD BOY.
>> [THINKING] DOES THAT MEAN
THEY LIKE INUYASHA?
OH...
ALL RIGHT!
THEY THINK HE'S COOL.
>> HMM?
UH, KAGOME, WE GOTTA TALK.
YOU DON'T NEED THAT THING, I
HOPE.
>> UH, WHAT THING IS THAT?
>> YOU KNOW!
THAT IRON CART YOU USE
SOMETIMES.
LOOK, I'LL CARRY YOU ON MY BACK
WHENEVER YOU WANT, ALL RIGHT?
>> MM-HMM.
>> HMM?
>> I TOLD YOU, GRAMPS.
EARLIER TODAY INUYASHA SAID HE
CAN CREATE DIAMONDS WITH HIS
TETSUSAIGA.
WHY DON'T YOU MAKE HIM REPAY
YOU?
>> ONE, TWO...
THE THIRD ONE IS GONE!
>> YOU DON'T BELIEVE WHAT I'M
SAYING, DO YOU, GRANDPA?
>> IT'S GONE.
>> IT'S OK.
I'LL APOLOGIZE TO MOM FOR YOU.
>> HUH?
SO, YOU'RE NOT MAD AT ME, THEN?
>> NOPE, NONE OF THAT MATTERS TO
ME ANYMORE.
HMM.
>> [MUSIC]
>> A YOUNG GIRL CHOSEN TO BE THE
BRIDE OF A DEMON MAKES A
SHOCKING CONFESSION.
>> I'M TELLING YOU THAT I
ALREADY GAVE MYSELF TO MIROKU.
>> I'LL FORGIVE YOU.
I'LL FORGIVE THE PAST.
SO, COME AND LIVE WITH ME AT THE
BOTTOM OF THE LAKE.
>> SANGO, I CAN EXPLAIN.
>> DON'T COME NEAR ME.
I GUESS THIS WASN'T MEANT TO BE.
>> NEXT TIME, "MIROKU'S PAST
MISTAKE."
>> SANGO, CAN'T YOU TRUST ME AT
ALL?