>> HERE WE COME.
IT'S THE START OF "INUYASHA."
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL THE
SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY NARAKU WITH
MY TETSUSAIGA.
>> NARAKU SLAYS KIKYO, AND SENDS
HIS NEW INFANT INCARNATION TO
ATTACK THE DARKNESS IN OUR
HEARTS.
INUYASHA HAS GONE IN SEARCH OF
KIKYO, AND IS UNABLE
TO COME TO SAVE ME.
>> IT'S UP TO ALL OF US.
>> TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FEUDAL FAIRY TALE, "INUYASHA."
>> AHH.
HELP ME.
HELP ME, INUYASHA!
INUYASHA ISN'T COMING.
HE'S STILL SEARCHING FOR KIKYO.
INUYASHA ISN'T GOING TO COME
AND SAVE ME.
[HEART BEATING]
INUYASHA.
>> I FOUND IT.
I FINALLY GRASPED THE DARKNESS
IN YOUR HEART, KAGOME.
YOU CAN'T GET AWAY FROM ME NOW.
NOW HOLD ME TIGHTLY.
LET OUR SOULS UNITE
AND BECOME MY EYES.
>> INUYASHA.
>> AAH!
>> WHY YOU--
>> FIGHTING OFF THESE MEN
WITHOUT ACTUALLY KILLING THEM IS
PROVING TO BE RATHER DIFFICULT.
>> NO KIDDING.
IT'S EASIER TO DEAL WITH DEMONS.
>> NOW DIE!
>> AAH!
>> THIS ISN'T GOOD.
AT THIS RATE, WE'LL NEVER
RESCUE KAGOME.
>> KAGOME, PLEASE BE SAFE.
>> AAH!
UH, UH!
>> HMM.
THOSE TWO ARE STILL ALIVE.
AND IT SEEMS AS IF THEY REFUSE
TO KILL THE CASTLE SOLDIERS.
AS USUAL, THEY ARE FAR TOO
PRINCIPLED.
>> HEH HEH HEH.
BUT SOON THEY'LL WANT TO KILL
THE SOLDIERS.
AFTER ALL, THE SOLDIERS ARE
QUITE INTENT ON KILLING THEM.
THE MALICE OF THE SOLDIERS IS
CONTAGIOUS, AND SOON THE HUMANS
WILL KILL EACH OTHER.
>> AAH!
>> UH!
>> THE HUMAN HEART IS WEAK.
HATRED IS BRED EASILY.
THIS GIRL IS NO EXCEPTION.
>> KIKYO!
KIKYO!
I'VE BEEN UP AND DOWN THE RIVER
WHERE THE OLD PRIEST SAID.
BUT I CAN'T FIND KIKYO'S SCENT
ANYWHERE.
AND NONE OF THE VILLAGERS AROUND
HERE CLAIM TO HAVE SEEN A
PRIESTESS, EITHER.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
[SNIFFING]
WHAT IS THIS SCENT?
DEMONS!
>> PHEW!
THEY'RE GONE.
GOOD, I DON'T THINK THEY SAW ME
HERE, EITHER.
BUT INUYASHA IS NOWHERE
TO BE FOUND.
AND KIRARA AND I GOT SEPARATED.
LOOKS LIKE I'VE GOT NO CHOICE.
GUESS I HAVE TO USE THIS
TECHNIQUE.
HUH?
WHA...
>> HEY THERE, SHIPPO, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?
>> DON'T EVER SCARE ME LIKE THAT
AGAIN, INUYASHA!
AAH!
[GROWLING]
>> AAH!
AAH!
>> KIRARA?
>> KIRARA!
YOU'RE OK!
>> WHAT!
KAGOME AND THE OTHERS WERE TAKEN
TO THE CASTLE?
WHILE I WAS SEARCHING FOR KIKYO.
THEN THIS WAS ALL A SETUP?
I'VE GOT TO GO SAVE THEM!
LET'S GO!
>> QUICK, KIRARA, FOLLOW
INUYASHA!
>> PLEASE, KAGOME,
JUST HANG IN THERE.
>> HUH.
>> GET IT TOGETHER, MEN.
KILL THEM!
>> WE'RE DONE FOR.
PLEASE SAVE US!
>> I'M SORRY, SANGO.
IF I WERE TO USE MY WIND TUNNEL,
WE COULD PROBABLY ESCAPE ALIVE,
BUT...
>> IF IT MEANS KILLING ALL
THESE MEN, THEN I CAN'T
DO THAT EITHER.
HOWEVER, MIROKU...
>> SHOOT THEM!
>> UH!
IT'S OUR DUTY TO RESCUE KAGOME.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
SO THERE'S NO WAY ON EARTH I'M
ABOUT TO GIVE UP TRYING.
AAH!
>> OH!
>> MIROKU!
SANGO!
>> KEEP FIRING!
>> AAH!
>> WHAT THE...
>> INUYASHA!
>> WHY YOU--
AAH!
>> UH, UH.
>> CURSE YOU, DEMON!
>> SO, YOU'RE THE BOSS HERE,
ARE YOU?
>> GET OUT OF HERE NOW.
>> LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
>> THEY'RE ONLY HUMANS.
HUH?
THAT SMELL.
IS IT...
>> INUYASHA.
KAGOME HAS BEEN TAKEN
INSIDE THE CASTLE.
>> ON MY WAY.
UH!
DAMMIT.
THAT'S KAGURA'S SCENT.
>> MIROKU, LET'S GO.
>> RIGHT!
>> UH.
THIS IS THE PRIEST WHO TOLD US
THAT KIKYO WAS ALIVE.
SO IT WAS A SETUP.
KAGOME!
DAMMIT.
I'M JUST A BIT TOO LATE.
>> HEY THERE.
IF IT ISN'T KANNA.
HMM, A SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
>> I WANT YOU TO IMPLANT THAT
TAINTED SACRED JEWEL SHARD
INTO KAGOME.
ONCE IT IS IN, SHE WILL BE
COMPLETELY UNDER OUR CONTROL.
MY MISSION HERE IS ALMOST DONE.
IMPLANT THE SHARD, AND
I SHALL GO INTO HIDING.
>> HAH.
WITH THIS, KAGOME WILL BECOME
NARAKU'S SLAVE, YOU SAY?
SHE WILL SHARE THE SAME
FATE AS KOHAKU.
>> KOHAKU?
[GASPS]
THIS IMPURE LIGHT.
DOES SHE INTEND TO PLACE THAT
SHARD INTO ME?
NO!
I--I CAN'T MOVE MY BODY.
THIS STRANGE INFANT HAS A GRASP
ON MY SOUL.
I HAVE TO BREAK FREE.
I HAVE TO FREE MYSELF
FROM IT'S GRASP.
>> KAGURA, HOLD ON.
>> HMM?
>> SHE'S A STUBBORN ONE.
SHE'S REGAINED CONSCIOUSNESS.
>> INUYASHA!
SAVE ME!
>> IT'S USELESS.
YOU MUST REALIZE BY NOW THAT HE
WON'T COME AND SAVE YOU.
INUYASHA HAS MADE HIS CHOICE.
AND HE HAS CHOSEN KIKYO,
NOT YOU.
>> [GRUNTING]
DAMMIT, I'M SUCH AN IDIOT.
HUH?
>> GO, INUYASHA.
>> KAGOME?
>> BUT, KAGOME--
>> THIS IS NO TIME TO HESITATE,
NOW HURRY.
KIKYO MUST BE WAITING.
>> HMM. YES.
FORGIVE ME.
I'M MAKING THE SAME
MISTAKE AGAIN.
>> [GRUNTING]
INUYASHA.
>> I LOST KIKYO.
AND THEN I THOUGHT I WAS THE
ONLY ONE HURTING,
THEN ACTED SELFISHLY.
NOW I'M ABOUT TO LOSE SOMEONE
ELSE WHO'S IMPORTANT TO ME.
DAMMIT.
WAIT FOR ME, KAGOME.
WAIT FOR ME UNTIL I GET THERE!
DON'T YOU DIE ON ME!
>> REMEMBER, KAGOME, WHEN YOU
LEARNED THAT KIKYO HAD DIED.
WEREN'T YOU ACTUALLY
QUITE PLEASED?
THE WOMAN WHO CAME BETWEEN YOU
WAS GONE.
THE MOMENT INUYASHA HEARD THAT
KIKYO WAS ALIVE,
HE WENT AFTER HER AGAIN.
WHETHER SHE IS DEAD OR ALIVE,
INUYASHA'S HEART BELONGS
TO KIKYO.
DON'T YOU FEEL BITTER TOWARDS
INUYASHA?
DON'T YOU HATE KIKYO?
IT'S OK TO FEEL HATRED.
YOU ARE NOT WRONG TO HATE THEM.
FILL YOUR HEART WITH BITTERNESS
ONCE MORE...
AND LET ME GRASP YOUR SOUL.
>> YOU GOT HER.
>> I FEEL BITTER TOWARD
INUYASHA?
I HATE KIKYO?
I GUESS I HAVE EVERY REASON TO,
BUT...
>> WHAT'S GOING ON HERE,
SOMEHOW SHE REPELLED THE SHARD.
SO THERE ARE SOME THINGS EVEN
THIS DEVILISH BRAT CAN'T DO.
>> HUH?
>> YOU'RE--YOU'RE WRONG.
>> SHE SPOKE!
MY SUGGESTIVE POWERS ARE NOT
WORKING ON THIS GIRL.
>> WHAT YOU ARE SAYING TO ME IS
COMPLETELY WRONG.
INUYASHA CAN'T FORGET
ABOUT KIKYO.
AND EVEN IF I CAN BRING MYSELF
TO ACCEPT THIS RATIONALLY,
I STILL FEEL THE PAIN OF
JEALOUSY IN MY HEART.
HOWEVER, BEARING A GRUDGE
AGAINST INUYASHA
AND FEELING JEALOUSY TOWARD
KIKYO, THESE ARE NORMAL FEELINGS
THAT ANY HUMAN WOULD HAVE,
AND IT DOES NOT MEAN THAT I
SHOULD NECESSARILY FEEL
BITTERNESS TOWARD THESE TWO.
THIS ISN'T THE FIRST TIME THAT
INUYASHA HAS TRIED TO LEAVE ME,
BECAUSE HE KNEW HOW DIFFICULT
ALL THIS WAS FOR ME.
I'VE EVEN WISHED KIKYO GONE,
BUT THEN I'VE ALWAYS FELT BAD
AFTER FOR HARBORING SUCH
THOUGHTS.
I KNOW...ALL THESE FEELINGS...
THEY MEAN...THAT I...
THEY MEAN I'M IN LOVE WITH
INUYASHA!
>> KAGOME!
UH.
>> INUYASHA.
YOU CAME FOR ME.
>> KAGOME!
KAGOME.
>> NOW I SEE WHY NARAKU HATES
THAT GIRL.
>> WHY, YOU...
WHAT DID YOU DO TO KAGOME?
>> I JUST RUMMAGED AROUND INSIDE
HER SOUL A LITTLE BIT.
BECAUSE YOU CAN'T SEEM TO GET
OVER KIKYO, I WAS ABLE TO FIND
A TINY SPECK OF DARKNESS
IN THAT GIRL'S HEART.
IT'S TOO BAD.
JUST ONE MORE LITTLE STEP, AND I
COULD HAVE CRUSHED HER SOUL.
>> BASTARD.
JUST WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU?
>> INUYASHA!
>> TOOK YOU LONG ENOUGH.
>> KAGOME, ARE YOU OK?
>> KAGURA, KANNA.
>> WHAT, YOU'RE STILL ALIVE?
>> MONK AND DEMON SLAYER,
TELL ME, HOW MANY OF THE
SOLDIERS DID YOU KILL?
>> THIS INFANT,
WAS HE MANIPULATING
THE CASTLE SOLDIERS?
HATE TO DISAPPOINT YOU,
BUT WE DON'T KILL NEEDLESSLY.
THIS BABY, THE GAS THE COLOR OF
HIS SKIN.
WAS HE CREATED FROM THE CLUMPS
OF FLESH WHICH NARAKU WAS
PRODUCING AT MOUNT HAKUREI?
TELL ME.
ARE YOU NARAKU'S HUMAN HEART?
>> WHY DO YOU THINK THAT?
>> WE KNOW THAT NARAKU HID
HIMSELF AT MOUNT HAKUREI IN
ORDER TO CREATE A MORE
POWERFUL BODY.
ALSO, HE WANTED TO CAST AWAY HIS
HUMAN HEART.
NARAKU TOLD US HE CUT AWAY HIS
HUMAN HEART, WHICH CONTINUED
TO YEARN FOR KIKYO.
THAT WAY, HE COULD SLAY HER.
>> THIS BABY...IS NARAKU'S HEART
WHICH YEARNS FOR KIKYO?
IT'S ABSOLUTELY SICK!
THE UNDERHANDED WAYS NARAKU TOYS
WITH PEOPLE'S EMOTIONS!
>> [CHUCKLING]
THERE IS A POSSIBILITY...
THAT I AM INDEED THE HUMAN HEART
WHICH NARAKU ONCE POSSESSED.
I CAN CLEARLY SEE INTO A
PERSON'S HEART,
THEIR WEAKNESSES AND FRAILTIES.
I KNOW JUST WHAT TO DO
IN ORDER TO MAKE ONE SUFFER,
TO FEEL SORROW OR HATE.
THIS IS ALL FAMILIAR TO ME.
BUT IF THERE IS ONE FEELING THAT
I DID NOT INHERIT FROM NARAKU,
IT IS THE ANGUISH AND
YEARNING FOR KIKYO.
AND WHERE DO YOU THINK THAT
FEELING WENT?
THOSE DISGUSTING CLUMPS OF FLESH
YOU SAW AT MOUNT HAKUREI,
THAT'S WHERE.
>> THAT WAS NARAKU'S
ABANDONED HEART?
>> AND THAT IS WHY I FEEL
NEITHER PAIN NOR SORROW.
>> HUH.
SO IN OTHER WORDS,
YOU'RE JUST A MONSTER CREATED
FROM NARAKU'S HEART,
ALL TWISTED AND GROTESQUE.
THAT'S ALL I NEED TO HEAR.
NOW PREPARE TO DIE!
AAH!
HUH?
>> THIS INFANT,
IT CAN CREATE A BARRIER?
THIS IS THE WEIRDEST INFANT I'VE
EVER MET.
>> MY WIND SCAR IS
BEING SUCKED UP!
AAH!
>> OH, NO, EVERYONE RUN!
>> AAH!
>> DAMN HIM.
THAT BRAT, HE REPELLED
MY WIND SCAR!
>> HEH HEH HEH.
DON'T THINK THIS IS OVER
JUST YET.
I'LL BE BACK SOON.
>> SHUT UP, YOU BASTARD!
IF YOU EVER TOUCH KAGOME
AGAIN...
>> NOW THAT THE PRIESTESS KIKYO
IS NO LONGER WITH US,
THAT GIRL IS THE ONLY ONE WHO
CAN SEE THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
>> WHAT?
>> SOON, VERY SOON.
ONCE KAGOME'S EYES BECOME OURS,
THE SACRED JEWEL WILL BECOME
WHOLE ONCE AGAIN...
THE SACRED JEWEL FILLED WITH
HATE, THAT IS.
>> ARE YOU CRAZY?
THERE IS NO WAY ON EARTH
KAGOME WOULD DO ANYTHING TO
HELP NARAKU!
>> HA.
THERE ARE MANY WAYS TO CORRUPT
THAT GIRL, INUYASHA.
SO LONG AS YOU CANNOT FORGET
KIKYO.
>> GRR...
DAMN HIM.
KAGOME, I'M SORRY I LEFT YOU
ALL ALONE.
I'LL NEVER LET YOU FALL INTO
NARAKU'S HANDS AGAIN.
NEVER WILL I LET YOU SUFFER LIKE
KIKYO DID.
>> HMM.
WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU LOOK UNWELL.
>> BE QUIET.
I NEED TO SLEEP.
KAGOME'S SOUL IS STRONGER
THAN I EXPECTED.
I USED UP TOO MUCH ENERGY.
>> WHAT'S WRONG WITH HIM?
DID HIS STRUGGLE WITH KAGOME
TIRE HIM OUT?
HE MAY BE NARAKU'S OFFSPRING,
BUT APPARENTLY HE'S NOT
ALL-POWERFUL.
>> FORGIVE ME, KAEDE.
>> SAY NO MORE, INUYASHA.
MY SISTER, KIKYO,
WAS FORCED TO RETURN TO THIS
WORLD OF THE LIVING.
WHILE HERE, HER SOUL ONLY
SUFFERED.
AND SO...
>> I WAS UNABLE TO SAVE
KIKYO'S SOUL.
SHE WAS KILLED FOR A SECOND TIME
BY THAT BASTARD NARAKU.
>> SISTER KIKYO'S SOUL
HAS FADED NOW.
SHE WILL NO LONGER
HAVE TO SUFFER.
>> BUT I--
>> SO, INUYASHA, YOU NEED NOT
SUFFER EITHER.
YES, MY DEAR SISTER IS GONE, BUT
I WISH HER REMAINS COULD BE
RETURNED TO HER PROPER
RESTING PLACE.
>> I SURE HOPE KAGOME WILL BE
ALL RIGHT.
SHE'S BEEN SLEEPING EVER SINCE
WE RETURNED TO THE VILLAGE.
>> UH.
INUYASHA IS WITH HER.
>> SHE'LL BE JUST FINE.
TRUST ME.
>> HMM.
>> KAGOME, ARE YOU AWAKE?
I SEE YOU.
SO YOU DID COME FOR ME
AFTER ALL.
>> ARE YOU OK?
TAKE IT EASY.
KAGOME, I'M SORRY ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED.
I WASN'T THERE FOR YOU.
>> IT'S OK, REALLY.
>> IT IS NOT OK!
I LET YOU GET INTO
SERIOUS DANGER.
ANY LATER, AND I WOULD HAVE LOST
KAGOME, TOO.
>> BUT IF YOU WERE TO HEAR NEWS
OF KIKYO'S WHEREABOUTS,
YOU'D GO OFF TO LOOK FOR HER
AGAIN, WOULDN'T YOU?
>> NO, I WOULDN'T!
I WILL NEVER LEAVE YOU AGAIN,
KAGOME.
>> YOU'RE A LIAR.
>> I AM NOT!
>> JUST WHO DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE KIDDING?
I'VE KNOWN YOU LONG ENOUGH TO
LEARN A FEW THINGS ABOUT YOU,
YOU KNOW.
AND YOU WOULD DEFINITELY GO.
>> GRR...
>> AND IF YOU DO GO, THEN I'LL
BE UPSET.
BUT THAT'S TO BE EXPECTED,
RIGHT?
>> KAGOME.
HEY, YOU'RE REALLY MAD,
AREN'T YOU?
>> YES, I SUPPOSE I AM.
INUYASHA WILL NEVER
FORGET KIKYO.
BUT I STILL LOVE HIM, AND
THERE'S NOTHING I CAN DO.
>> THANK YOU, KAGOME.
>> I CAME BACK TO THE PRESENT
HOPING TO GET SOME SERIOUS
STUDYING DONE.
CHORUS.
DRAMA.
COOKING DEMONSTRATION!
WHY NOT?
IT'S A CULTURAL FESTIVAL.
>> KAGOME, YOU DIDN'T HELP AT
ALL WITH THE PREPARATIONS,
SO YOU'RE ON STANDBY FOR
EVERYTHING.
>> WE'RE COUNTING ON YOU,
KAGOME.
>> AND IF YOU MESS UP,
YOU'LL BE SORRY.
>> NEXT ON "INUYASHA..."
"DON'T BOIL IT!
THE TERRIFYING DRIED UP DEMON!"
I'D RATHER FIGHT A DEMON IN
THE FEUDAL ERA!