[SIGHS]
- I HOPE YOU UNDERSTAND
OUR POSITION, MIROKU.
WE CAN'T TAKE THAT GIRL WITH US.
- I KNOW.
- STILL, WE CANNOT SIMPLY
ABANDON THE ORPHAN CHILD.
- IT'S HER!
- WE HAVE FOUND KOHARU!
[GASPS]
- THE FEUDAL ERA.
KOHARU HAD LOST HER ENTIRE
FAMILY IN THE WAR
AND WAS FORCED BY HER FOSTER
FATHER TO WORK DAY AND NIGHT.
THEN, ONE DAY--
- HERE. EAT UP.
- YOUNG MIROKU CAME
TO THE VILLAGE
TO PERFORM AN EXORCISM
AND MET KOHARU.
- MIROKU, I CANNOT
BEAR TO BE PARTED AGAIN
AFTER SUCH A SHORT TIME.
- TRY TO UNDERSTAND, KOHARU.
I CANNOT GUARANTEE
THAT I WOULD ALWAYS
BE ABLE TO PROTECT YOU
IN TIMES OF BATTLE.
YOU SEE, THE DEMON I PURSUE
IS MORE DEVIOUS AND
FORMIDABLE THAN ANY OTHER.
[BIRD SHRIEKS]
KOHARU...LISTEN.
YOU ARE ABOUT TO COMMENCE
A NEW LIFE IN A NEW VILLAGE.
I KNOW YOU MUST BE AFRAID.
LIFE ITSELF IS A FRIGHTENING
IMAGE FOR EVERY HUMAN BEING.
- HUH?
- IN MY RIGHT HAND IS A HOLE,
CAPABLE OF DRAWING EVERYTHING
IN ITS PATH INTO THE VOID.
A WIND TUNNEL, IF YOU WILL.
A CURSE WAS PLACED
UPON MY FAMILY IN
MY GRANDFATHER'S TIME.
HE AND MY FATHER WERE
EVENTUALLY SUCKED UP
INTO THE WIND TUNNELS
IN THEIR OWN HANDS.
IN TIME, EVENTUALLY I, TOO,
WILL BE DRAWN INTO
THE TERRIBLE NOTHINGNESS
OF MY OWN HAND.
DESPITE THAT, I MADE UP
MY MIND TO USE
THIS TERRIBLE CURSE
AS MY STRENGTH.
THE WIND TUNNEL ALLOWS
A MERE HUMAN LIKE MYSELF
TO TAKE ON DEMONS.
SO I'VE COME TO THINK MY CURSE
IS ALSO MY GREATEST STRENGTH
TO BATTLE AGAINST EVIL.
[SIGHS]
- MIROKU IS TREMBLING.
IS MIROKU'S TALE NOTHING
MORE THAN A DECEPTION?
BEING STRONG IN LIFE...
IT'S NOT EASY.
OVERCOMING UNCERTAINTIES
IS DIFFICULT.
- HUH?
- WE WERE SEARCHING FOR
A NEW PLACE FOR KOHARU TO LIVE
WHEN WE WERE ATTACKED
BY SOME VILLAGERS WHOSE
SOULS HAD BEEN STOLEN.
[SHOUTING]
- I DON'T THINK SO!
- INUYASHA WAS FORCED TO FIGHT
THEM WITHOUT HARMING THEM.
- SANGO WAS HIT
BY HER OWN WEAPON.
- AAH!
- WHOA! WHOA!
- AND A GHOSTLY WHITE DEMON
STOLE KOHARU'S SOUL,
AS WELL AS MY OWN!
BE CAREFUL, EVERYONE.
BEWARE OF THE MIRROR!
[GASPS]
- OH!
- HOW STRANGE.
I CANNOT SUBDUE HER SOUL.
STILL, YOU ARE UNABLE
TO MOVE, ARE YOU NOT?
I DESIRE THE SHARD OF THE SACRED
JEWEL THAT YOU POSSESS.
GIVE IT TO ME.
[GASPS]
- MIROKU.
[GRUNTING]
- KOHARU!
- UGH!
AAH!
[SIGHS]
- WHAT ON EARTH IS GOING ON?
- KAGOME! SHIPPO!
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
- HOW IS SHE ABLE TO MOVE STILL?
[GRUNTS]
- SANGO! KAGOME!
SHE'S THE OTHER DEMON!
[GROWLING]
[SIGHS]
- KAGOME! ARE YOU HARMED?
WHAT HAS SHE DONE?
[SIGHING]
KIRARA! IT'S YOU!
UH-OH!
KAGOME!
- SHIPPO, WHAT EXACTLY
WENT ON HERE?
- MIROKU, DIDN'T YOU SEE
THE WHITE DEMON?
SHE WAS TRYING TO DRAW KAGOME'S
SOUL INTO HER EVIL MIRROR.
- KAGOME'S SOUL?
- UGH!
[SHOUTING]
- DEAD SOUL BLADES!
- WHAT IS WRONG, INUYASHA?
YOU DO NOTHING
BUT FLEE FROM ME.
THIS LEADS ME TO ONE BELIEF:
YOU'VE NOT RECOVERED
FROM YOUR INJURIES.
- I ONLY NEED ONE
GOOD ATTACK ON HER.
IF I CAN GET ONE GOOD SWING IN,
MY ARM CAN HANDLE IT.
- PREPARE TO DIE...
IN THE NAME OF MY COMRADES!
- HE'S SO FAST!
WHEN I FOUGHT THAT FOOL
KOGA WHO HAD BEEN
DECEIVED BY NARAKU...
- IRON REAPER!
- MY RIGHT ARM WAS WOUNDED
BY THE POWER OF THAT
FAKE SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
MY ARM HAS NOT YET RECOVERED.
STILL, IF I CAN CUT THROUGH
THE WIND SCAR IN ONE MOVE,
I CAN BRING HER DOWN.
- I NEVER IMAGINED
THAT THIS YOUNG UPSTART
WOULD TRY SOMETHING
ELABORATE SUCH AS
A WIND SCAR TO BATTLE ME.
WHEN I FIRST MET HIM IN BATTLE,
THE SACRED ARROW DISPELLED
MY WIND ASSAULT
AND CREATED A WIND SCAR.
IMPOSSIBLE!
KAGOME'S SACRED ARROW WAS
PURIFYING MY WIND POWERS!
- JUST AS I THOUGHT.
THE WIND HAS DISAPPEARED.
- SUCH A FOOL!
I ONLY NEED TO CREATE MORE!
THE WIND SCAR IS CREATED
WHEN THE DEMONIC WINDS COLLIDE.
I CONTROL ALL WIND.
- ARRGH!
- IF NOT FOR THAT ARROW,
A WIND SCAR WOULD
NEVER HAVE FORMED.
- NO GOOD.
IT WON'T WORK.
THE WIND SCAR WON'T FORM WITHIN
THE WIND SHE'S CREATED.
- HMM.
- WAIT!
THAT WAS A WIND SCAR!
HOW CAN THAT BE?
WHAT DOES IT MEAN?
IS HER CONTROL OVER
THE WIND WEAKENING?
THIS IS MY ONLY CHANCE.
I COULD SLAY HER NOW,
WITH THE WIND SCAR.
[PANTING]
- MIROKU, LOOK!
INUYASHA IS WIELDING
HIS TETSUSAIGA.
HE WILL CUT THROUGH
THE WIND SCAR.
- I MUST STOP HIM.
HE DOES NOT YET KNOW
ABOUT THE SECOND DEMON,
THE SOUL-THIEVING APPARITION.
SANGO'S WEAPON WAS
THRUST BACK AT HER.
AND THE WIND SCAR WILL BE
HURLED BACK AT INUYASHA!
- I SEE IT!
- I ALLOWED YOU TO SEE IT!
- THE WIND SCAR!
- YOU WISH TO SLICE
THROUGH IT, I IMAGINE.
- YOU ARE MINE!
[LAUGHTER]
- NOW, PERISH!
- WHAT?
AAH!
- INUYASHA!
[SOFT THUNDER]
[GRUNTING]
- IT'S HIM!
NARAKU!
[CACKLING]
- THAT WAS INDEED SIMPLE ENOUGH.
I CAME SO THAT I COULD
ASK YOU IN PERSON
HOW IT FELT TO HAVE YOUR OWN
POWER TURNED AGAINST YOU,
AND VERY EASILY,
I MIGHT ADD.
- I AM INDEED HONORED
FOR YOUR PRESENCE, NARAKU.
I RATHER EXPECTED
A DEMON PUPPET.
YOU ARE A COWARD WHO NEVER
SULLIES HIS OWN HANDS,
WHO KNOWS ONLY
HOW TO LAY TRAPS.
YOU MUST HAVE BEEN
FALSELY CONFIDENT
OR ELSE YOU WOULD NOT HAVE
DARED SHOW YOUR FACE.
- THE WIND TUNNEL.
YOU ARE FREE TO DRAW
ANYTHING INTO YOUR VOID.
BUT SURELY, EVEN YOU COULD
NOT BE THAT FOOLISH, MONK.
- THE SOULS OF KAGOME
AND THE VILLAGERS ARE
LOCKED WITHIN THAT MIRROR.
- MY COURSE OF ACTION
WAS SIMPLE.
I CREATED WIND AND VOID
AS INCARNATIONS OF MYSELF,
AND YET WITNESSED THE DAMAGE
I WAS ABLE TO INFLICT.
- INCARNATIONS?
SO MY SUSPICIONS WERE CORRECT.
NARAKU'S POWER HAS
INCREASED DRASTICALLY
IF HE IS CAPABLE OF
THIS LEVEL OF SORCERY.
WE HAVE FOUGHT KAGURA,
THE WIND SORCERESS, ONCE BEFORE.
AND THIS OTHER, SHE IS--
WAIT.
THAT IS WHY WE COULD NOT
SENSE ITS EVIL.
IT HAS NO PRESENCE.
IT'S NO WONDER THE SITUATION
WENT UNNOTICED
UNTIL IT WAS TOO LATE.
- INUYASHA, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
INUYASHA!
[GROANS]
- KIRARA.
I NEED YOU TO DO SOMETHING.
TAKE ME ON YOUR BACK.
KIRARA.
I NEED TO BE WITH INUYASHA.
- HAVE WE NOT SPOKEN
LONG ENOUGH?
SHALL WE TAKE INUYASHA'S HEAD
ALONG WITH US AS A TROPHY?
NO?
DID YOU NOT WANT TO TELL
THAT WOMAN THAT INUYASHA
HAD BEEN SLAIN?
I WAS UNDER THE IMPRESSION
THAT THIS IS WHAT YOU DESIRED.
- TRUE ENOUGH.
IT WAS ONLY THROUGH
HER COOPERATION
THAT I WAS ABLE
TO CREATE YOU AND KANNA.
WHAT EMOTIONS WOULD
RISE ON HER FACE
IF I WERE TO SHOW HER
INUYASHA'S HEAD, I WONDER?
- HOW CAN THAT BE?
NARAKU'S SACRED JEWEL
FRAGMENT IS NEARLY WHOLE.
- YOU SUGGESTED EARLIER
THAT I DO EVERYTHING
TO AVOID SULLYING MY OWN HANDS.
EVEN THE MIGHTIEST ARE
INFERIOR TO SOMEONE.
A WOMAN ATTEMPTED TO USE ME
SO THAT I WOULD MURDER
INUYASHA FOR HER.
- A WOMAN?
YOU DON'T MEAN--
- HMM. SHE IS SOME
PIECE OF WORK, THAT KIKYO.
- K-KIKYO.
- INUYASHA!
YOU'RE ALIVE!
THANK THE HEAVENS!
- KIKYO PERSONALLY HANDED
THIS SACRED JEWEL SHARD
TO ME OF HER OWN FREE WILL.
[GRUNTING]
- KIKYO!
- SHE WISHES TO GAZE
UPON YOUR FACE...
AFTER YOU'RE GOOD AND DEAD!
- AAH!
SHIPPO, STAY DOWN!
AAH!
- MIROKU!
- NOW, GIVE ME YOUR HEAD!
- THAT'S KAGOME'S ARROW!
KAGOME!
- HER AGAIN?
YOU FAILED ME, KANNA!
WHY DID YOU NOT STEAL HER SOUL?
- HER SOUL IS SPILLING
OUT OF THE MIRROR.
DOES THIS GIRL POSSESS
SUCH AN ENORMOUS SOUL?
[MOANS]
- KAGOME!
- YOU DON'T NEED
TO WORRY ABOUT ME.
HOW'S INUYASHA?
- WELL, HE'S ALIVE,
BUT HE'S SO BADLY WOUNDED
THAT HE'S UNABLE TO MOVE.
[GASPS]
- KAGOME!
- I'M SO GLAD
YOU'RE ALIVE, INUYASHA.
- I'M SO HAPPY.
HOW DID THIS HAPPEN?
HOW DID NARAKU GET AHOLD
OF THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD?
IT IS THE VERY SAME SHARD
THAT KIKYO STOLE AWAY FROM ME.
WAS IT HER THAT
GAVE IT TO NARAKU?
THOSE SHARDS THAT WE WORKED
SO HARD TO COLLECT, ONE BY ONE.
DID KIKYO GIVE THEM TO NARAKU?
EVEN SO, AFTER SHE COMMITTED
SUCH A VILE ACT,
INUYASHA STILL LOVES HER.
EVEN THOUGH HE'S
THIS BADLY WOUNDED,
HE CANNOT FORGET HER.
- WOMAN, PASS THIS MESSAGE
ON TO INUYASHA.
IF HE MUST HATE SOMEONE,
THEN HATE KIKYO,
FOR THE ONLY THING
SHE DESIRES IS INUYASHA'S DEATH.
- I'M TIRED OF HEARING
YOUR VOICE.
YOU MAKE ME SICK!
TAKE THIS!
- DON'T DO IT, KAGOME!
IT WILL FIRE BACK AT YOU EXACTLY
LIKE THE TETSUSAIGA DID.
- I GUARANTEE IT WON'T.
MY ARROW ONLY STRIKES EVIL.
[GASPS]
- THE ARROW.
- THE ARROW IS STARTING
TO PIERCE THE MIRROR!
- THE ARROW WENT THROUGH.
IT DIDN'T DEFLECT.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHY DID IT NOT
STRIKE BACK AT HER?
- I UNDERSTAND.
THE ARROW IS MADE UP OF SOULS.
THE MIRROR IS ENTIRELY FILLED.
UNLESS THE SOULS ARE RELEASED,
THE MIRROR WILL BURST.
[WHIMPERING]
- THE SOULS HAVE RETURNED
TO THEIR BODIES.
MIROKU! USE THE WIND TUNNEL!
- RIGHT.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
[GASPING]
MIROKU!
- WIND TUNNEL!
- LIFE ITSELF IS A FRIGHTENING
IMAGE FOR EVERY HUMAN BEING.
IN MY RIGHT HAND IS A HOLE
CAPABLE OF DRAWING EVERYTHING
IN ITS PATH INTO THE VOID.
IN TIME, EVENTUALLY I, TOO,
WILL BE DRAWN INTO THE TERRIBLE
NOTHINGNESS OF MY OWN HAND.
BEING STRONG IN LIFE...
IT'S NOT EASY.
OVERCOMING UNCERTAINTIES
IS DIFFICULT.
- AAH!
CURSE THEM!
THEY'VE ESCAPED!
- WE SHALL ALLOW YOU
TO LIVE FOR A WHILE YET.
THE SACRED JEWEL WILL
CONTINUE TO BESTOW ME
WITH MORE AND MORE POWER.
LET US ALL RELISH
THE IMMEASURABLE POWER OF
THE SACRED JEWEL, SHALL WE?
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
- HOW WAS IT WE ALL
AWOKE IN THE FIELDS?
- I'M FINDING IT HARD TO
REMEMBER ANYTHING AT ALL.
- SAME FOR ME.
- HEY!
CHEER UP, WOULD YOU?
BUT I SUPPOSE
IT'S NOT THAT EASY,
NOT AFTER EVERYTHING
THAT WE'VE BEEN THROUGH.
NARAKU POSSESSES NEARLY ALL
OF THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
WHAT AM I THINKING?
WE CAN'T GIVE UP
AT A TIME LIKE THIS!
I'VE GOT THIS THING ALL WRONG!
WE MUST POSSESS INCREDIBLE
POWERS OURSELVES
TO BE ABLE TO SURVIVE
A CONFLICT WITH THE NEARLY
INVINCIBLE NARAKU
AND LIVE TO TELL IT.
HOW'S INUYASHA DOING?
ANY BETTER?
- THE HERBAL REMEDIES
SEEM TO BE HELPING.
HIS FEVER'S DROPPED,
AND HE'S SOUND ASLEEP.
I'M GOING OUT TO SEARCH
FOR SOME MORE HERBS NOW.
- KIRARA AND I WILL
COME ALONG AND HELP YOU,
BECAUSE WE'RE THE ONLY ONES
AROUND HERE WITH ENOUGH ENERGY.
[MEOW]
- THANKS, YOU TWO.
- KIKYO HANDED OVER THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARD TO NARAKU.
KIKYO, WHO HAD DIED ONCE...
THEN ROSE AGAIN WITH
A BODY MADE OF CLAY.
KIKYO, WHO DESPISES ME,
WHO TRIED TO MURDER KAGOME.
WHERE ARE YOU...
MY KIKYO?
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- KIKYO HAS GIVEN NARAKU
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD
SHE STOLE FROM ME.
NARAKU'S POWER
CONTINUES TO INCREASE,
AND HE SENDS INCARNATIONS OF
HIMSELF TO HUNT DOWN INUYASHA.
THE MIND-READING GOSHINKI SINKS
HIS FANGS INTO TETSUSAIGA.
OH, NO!
INUYASHA DOESN'T STAND A CHANCE!
WAIT!
WHAT'S HAPPENED TO YOU?
NEXT TIME...
SEE YOU SOON.