>> AT TIMES, MIROKU USES HIS
SPIRITUAL POWERS TO HELP PEOPLE,
AND ON OCCASION, HE USES HIS
WIND TUNNEL TO SUBJUGATE DEMONS.
MIROKU TRAVELS WITH US OUT OF A
COMMON DESIRE TO DESTROY OUR
ARCHENEMY NARAKU.
THIS UNUSUAL MONK LOVES NOTHING
MORE THAN WOMEN AND MONEY, BUT
WHEN THERE'S REAL TROUBLE, WE
CAN ALWAYS COUNT ON MIROKU'S
HELP.
>> I SHALL BE OFF NOW, MY GOOD
PEOPLE.
>> MONK, WE CAN'T THANK YOU
ENOUGH FOR ALL YOU'VE DONE FOR
US.
>> FINALLY, WE CAN LIVE AGAIN IN
PEACE.
>> YOU SAVED OUR VILLAGE AND
GAVE US PEACE OF MIND.
>> NO SUCH THING.
I ONLY DID WHAT HAD TO BE DONE.
FAREWELL.
>> WAIT, MONK.
AT LEAST TELL US YOUR NAME
BEFORE YOU LEAVE.
>> I'D BE MORE THAN HAPPY TO
TELL YOU MY NAME.
I'M THE MONK CALLED MIROKU.
>> WE'VE BEEN SLEEPING IN THE
FIELDS FOR AGES NOW, AND I GOT
TO SAY, I SURE COULD USE A NIGHT
UNDER A ROOF.
>> LOOK, A VILLAGE!
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
AWESOME.
WE'LL BE ABLE TO GET A GOOD
NIGHT'S SLEEP FOR ONCE.
>> AND THE VILLAGERS MIGHT BE
ABLE TO TELL US NEWS ABOUT
NARAKU.
>> WELL, WHAT ARE WE WAITING
FOR?
>> LET'S GO!
>> NICE AND CLEAN.
>> IT'S HIM!
>> MIROKU!
>> IT'S MIROKU!
>> MIROKU IS COMING!
MIROKU IS COMING!
>> COME INSIDE.
>> "MIROKU IS COMING?"
>> YOU CORRUPT MONK, HOW DARE
YOU DECEIVE US?
>> HOLD ON A MINUTE.
WHAT ON EARTH DID I DO?
>> DON'T ACT INNOCENT.
>> NO NEED FOR TALK.
GET HIM!
>> WHAT'S GOING ON, MIROKU?
>> I'M TRYING TO FIGURE THAT OUT
MYSELF.
>> WHAT DO WE DO?
THERE ARE SO MANY OF THEM.
WE'LL BE FIGHTING FOREVER.
>> I AGREE.
THERE'S ONLY ONE THING TO DO
BEFORE ANYONE GETS INJURED.
RUN LIKE THE WIND AND DON'T LOOK
BACK!
[VILLAGERS SHOUTING]
>> I WONDER WHAT THAT WAS ALL
ABOUT.
>> WE ALL KNOW WHAT MIROKU'S
LIKE.
HE PROBABLY DID SOMETHING SNEAKY
AND GOT ON THEIR BAD SIDE.
>> WHATEVER IT WAS, THEY SURE
SEEMED ANGRY.
>> WHAT DID YOU DO, MIROKU?
>> I CAN'T IMAGINE.
>> YOU SURE?
>> OH, WELL.
NO SENSE IN DWELLING ON MATTERS
OF THE PAST.
>> I BET YOU CAN'T KEEP TRACK OF
ALL THE BAD THINGS YOU'VE DONE.
>> TRUST ME, INUYASHA.
IF I WAS SURROUNDED BY BEAUTIFUL
WOMEN AND LIVING IT UP EACH AND
EVERY NIGHT, I WOULDN'T FORGET
IT.
>> LISTEN.
[WOMEN GIGGLING]
>> WOULD YOU CONSIDER BEARING MY
CHILD?
[ALL SHOUTING AT ONCE]
>> I'LL BEAR YOUR CHILD.
SO, DRINK UP.
>> COME ON.
DRINK IT ALL UP, MONK.
>> ALL RIGHT, THEN.
BOTTOMS UP.
>> WE LOVE YOU, MONK!
>> YAY, MONK!
>> LOOK, ANOTHER VILLAGE!
>> TONIGHT WE'LL FIND NICE WARM
BEDS.
>> MIROKU, YOU'RE BACK!
>> WHAT THIS TIME?
>> LADIES, WHAT IS GOING ON
HERE?
>> OH, WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
YOU PROMISED I COULD HAVE YOUR
CHILD.
>> DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
I'M GOING TO BEAR HIS CHILD.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
TELL THEM, MIROKU.
>> MY, MY.
IS THAT SO?
YOU'LL JUST HAVE TO TAKE TURNS,
LADIES.
>> WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
>> YOU HAVE SOME NERVE COMING
BACK HERE, YOU FAKE MONK.
DON'T THINK YOU'LL GET AWAY
WITH THIS.
>> OH, DEAR.
THIS IS NOT BODING WELL FOR US,
LADIES.
ANY OBJECTIONS TO SHORTENING OUR
STAY IN THIS VILLAGE?
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT ME LIKE
THAT FOR?
>> YOU'RE THE ONE IN TROUBLE.
WHY SHOULD WE HAVE TO RUN?
>> THIS TIME, YOU BETTER
APOLOGIZE FOR WHATEVER IT IS
YOU'VE DONE.
>> LADIES, DON'T BE SO
HEARTLESS.
>> BESIDES, YOU MADE THE BED,
YOU SHOULD SLEEP IN IT.
TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR
ACTIONS FOR ONCE.
>> I TOLD YOU, I DIDN'T--
HEY, SHIPPO, YOU UNDERSTAND,
DON'T YOU?
YOU'VE GOT TO BACK ME UP.
>> I'M JUST A KID.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND THIS GROWN-UP
STUFF.
SORRY, MIROKU.
I HAD TO DO IT.
>> QUICKLY.
CAPTURE HIM.
>> PLEASE, STOP.
HEAR ME OUT.
>> I'LL HAVE TO MAKE IT UP TO
HIM.
I'M NEVER GOING TO GET INVOLVED
WITH WOMEN.
>> UH-HUH.
>> DID YOU SAY SOMETHING?
>> NO, NOT REALLY.
>> WILL SOMEBODY PLEASE TELL ME
WHAT EXACTLY DID MIROKU DO TO
YOU PEOPLE?
>> NOT A DAMN THING, AND THAT'S
THE PROBLEM.
>> AND SO, THE MAN BUILT HIMSELF
A FINE STOREHOUSE.
BUT HIS DAYS WERE SPENT CONSUMED
WITH WORRY.
WOULD ROBBERS BREAK IN?
WOULD A FIRE BREAK OUT?
FORTUNATELY, HE HAD HEARD OF MY
REMARKABLE SUTRA CHARMS.
WARDS OFF EVIL SPIRITS!
PROMOTES GOOD HEALTH!
PROTECTS THE HOME!
ENSURES SAFE BIRTH!
THIS SUTRA CHARM WILL TAKE CARE
OF EVERY NEED AND CONCERN.
AND FOR A LIMITED TIME ONLY, I'M
PREPARED TO OFFER YOU THIS: TWO
OF THESE INCREDIBLE SUTRA CHARMS
FOR THE PRICE OF ONE.
>> SOMETHING SEEMS FISHY ABOUT
THIS CHARM.
USUALLY, A SAFE DELIVERY CHARM
IS FOR CHILDBIRTH ONLY.
>> WHAT ARE YOU SAYING, SIR?
THAT'S WHAT MAKES THIS CHARM OF
MINE SO WONDERFUL AND THIS DEAL
SO INCREDIBLE.
IT IS A SAD DAY WHEN PEOPLE
COMPLAIN ABOUT MULTIPLE
BENEFITS.
>> WHAT IF AN EVIL SPIRIT HAS A
SAFE DELIVERY?
>> GOOD POINT.
WE WOULDN'T WANT TO AID EVIL
SPIRITS.
>> NOW DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
THIS DESPICABLE MONK TRICKED US
INTO BUYING WORTHLESS CHARMS AT
EXORBITANT PRICES!
>> YOU FELL FOR HIS SALES PITCH.
>> THAT'S NOT ALL.
>> UM, I HATE TO BE RUDE.
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> COULD YOU PERHAPS STOP EATING
FOR A FEW MINUTES AND BEGIN
EXORCISING?
>> YES, OF COURSE.
WHAT ARE WE WAITING FOR?
EVIL SPIRIT, BE GONE WITH YOU!
OK, ALL DONE.
>> THAT'S IT?
WHEN HE WAS AT MY HOUSE, HE
WENT THROUGH THE PRETEXT OF
EXORCISM AND THEN ATE AND SLEPT
LIKE THERE WAS NO TOMORROW.
>> THAT'S NOT THE HALF OF IT.
>> OK, WHAT ELSE DID HE DO?
>> EVERY TIME HE CAME TO THE
VILLAGE, HE FLIRTED WITH THE
WOMEN!
>> HOW VERY KIND OF YOU.
WHAT A WARM RECEPTION.
>> YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY INCREDIBLE,
MONK.
>> SO WHO WANTS TO SLEEP WITH ME
FIRST?
>> SO TELL ME, IS HE REALLY THE
POWERFUL MONK THEY SAY HE IS?
>> THANKS TO HIM ALL THE WOMEN
ARE--WELL, SEE FOR YOURSELF!
>> OH, MONK, EVEN UNDER ARREST,
YOU'RE SIMPLY DIVINE.
>> RELEASE THE MONK SO I CAN
HAVE HIS CHILD.
>> THERE YOU GO.
JUST THE USUAL MIROKU STUFF.
NOTHING SPECIAL.
>> HE'S NEVER BEEN THIS POPULAR
WITH THE LADIES BEFORE.
>> I BEG TO DIFFER, SANGO.
>> HOW EXACTLY AM I WRONG?
>> FIRST, ABOUT MY POPULARITY.
THE LADIES HAVE ALWAYS LOVED ME.
AND OF COURSE, BY STANDING IDLY
BY WHILE I WRONGLY SUFFER THE
HUMILIATION OF BEING TIED UP.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN WRONGLY?
>> IT'S VERY SIMPLE.
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME IN MY
LIFE THAT I HAVE BEEN TO THIS
VILLAGE.
>> STOP YOUR LYING!
HOW CAN YOU JUST SIT THERE
LOOKING SO UNBELIEVABLY SMUG AND
LIE THROUGH YOUR TEETH LIKE
THAT?
>> BUT IT'S THE TRUTH.
YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE ME.
>> FIRST YESTERDAY AND NOW
TODAY.
YOU'RE NOTHING BUT LIES!
YOU'LL PAY FOR YOUR BRAZEN
DISHONESTY.
>> COME ON, MEN.
LET'S THROW HIM IN THE RIVER.
>> JUST A MINUTE.
>> WHAT IS IT, KAGOME?
>> HE SAID IT ALL HAPPENED
YESTERDAY AND TODAY.
>> SO WHAT?
WHO CARES WHEN IT HAPPENED?
>> SO MIROKU'S BEEN WITH US THE
WHOLE TIME.
DON'T YOU GET IT?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> THEN THAT MEANS...
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE THEY DOUBTED
ME FOR EVEN A SECOND.
>> I DON'T GET IT, MIROKU.
IF IT WASN'T YOU, THEN WHO COULD
IT HAVE BEEN?
>> SO YOU ARE THE FAMOUS MASTER
MIROKU?
>> YES.
YES.
>> SO, MASTER MIROKU, WHAT IS IT
THAT BRINGS YOU TO OUR SMALL AND
HUMBLE VILLAGE?
>> WHILST ON MY TRAVELS, I
HAPPENED UPON THIS VILLAGE QUITE
BY CHANCE, AND I SENSED A VERY
SUSPICIOUS DEMONIC AURA.
>> I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN.
YOU ARE AMAZING.
HOW INCREDIBLE THAT YOU WOULD
SENSE THE PRESENCE OF THE DEMON
THAT PLAGUES OUR VILLAGE.
WE MUST ASK YOU TO SLAY THE
DEMON AT ONCE.
I COULD HAVE SWORN YOU JUST GREW
LARGER FOR AN INSTANT.
>> IT MUST BE YOUR IMAGINATION.
>> A FAKE?
>> I'M AFRAID SO.
SOMEONE USING MY IDENTITY IS UP
TO NO GOOD IN THIS REGION.
DO YOU HAVE TO LOOK AT ME LIKE
THAT?
THINK ABOUT IT.
THAT'S THE ONLY POSSIBLE
EXPLANATION.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> I'LL SAY.
>> WHY WOULD SOMEONE IMPERSONATE
YOU OF ALL PEOPLE?
>> IF I WAS GOING TO BE SOMEONE,
I'D PICK SOMEBODY IMPORTANT.
>> AND THAT IS WHY I AM
SUGGESTING THAT WE CHECK THIS
OUT.
>> WE DON'T CARE ABOUT ALL THESE
THEORIES.
>> LET'S GRAB THE REPROBATE AND
THROW HIM IN THE RIVER!
>> HEY, JUST A MINUTE.
YOU'VE GOT THE WRONG PERSON.
>> I KNOW.
WE DON'T TRUST HIM EITHER, BUT
HE SAID HE DIDN'T DO THIS TO
YOU.
>> I HEARD THAT.
>> WHY DON'T WE FIND OUT THE
TRUTH FIRST, AND THEN YOU CAN
THROW HIM IN THE RIVER.
>> I DON'T EVEN CARE ANYMORE.
JUST UNTIE ME.
>> DON'T TRY TO TALK YOUR WAY
OUT OF THIS, BECAUSE IT'S NOT
GOING TO WORK.
>> I'M NOT!
>> OK, THEN.
IF YOU'RE SOMEONE ELSE, SHOW US
PROOF.
>> HOW CAN I DO THAT?
>> THAT'S NOT GOING TO BE EASY.
>> I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF THIS
RACKET.
HEY, YOU THERE, IF YOU'RE GOING
TO INSIST THAT MIROKU IS GUILTY,
THEN HOW ABOUT YOU SHOW US SOME
PROOF?
>> WHY DOES HE ALWAYS HAVE TO BE
SO ROUGH?
>> I KNEW YOU'D SAY THAT.
THEN WE'LL SHOW YOU.
READY, MEN?
>> HERE'S YOUR PROOF?
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER?
>> HAS HE LOST HIS MIND?
>> LEAVES.
NOW IT ALL MAKES SENSE.
I HAVE UNRAVELED THIS MYSTERY.
>> MAYBE, BUT WITH YOU ALL TIED
UP LIKE THAT...
>> YOU JUST DON'T LOOK TOO
CONVINCING.
>> THAT'S WHY I KEEP ASKING YOU
TO UNTIE ME.
HASN'T ANYBODY BEEN LISTENING?
COME ON!
>> LET'S HURRY.
THE IMPOSTOR IS HEADING FOR THE
NEXT VILLAGE.
>> MIROKU, COME ON!
TELL US, WILL YOU?
JUST WHO IS THIS IMPOSTOR?
>> WE'LL KNOW FOR SURE WHEN WE
GET THERE.
HE OBVIOUSLY KNOWS ME WELL AND
CAN IMITATE ME.
IT WAS THAT LEAF THAT GAVE HIM
AWAY.
>> GO INSIDE, MONK.
>> YES, RIGHT.
>> THERE IS A SHRINE DEEP IN
THIS CAVE.
YOU CAN'T MISS IT.
>> THE SPIRIT OF A RACCOON DOG
NOW HAUNTS THE INTERIOR OF THE
SHRINE.
>> A RACCOON DOG?
THEN HE SHOULD LISTEN TO REASON.
>> THERE WOULD BE NO PROBLEM IF
IT FED ON MOUNTAIN PREY, BUT NOW
IT ATTACKS OUR LIVESTOCK IN
FIELDS.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
>> WE'VE CONFIDENT THAT YOU,
MONK MIROKU, CAN PUT AN END TO
OUR PROBLEM.
>> BUT PLEASE, DO BE CAREFUL.
>> NOTHING TO FEAR.
LEAVE IT TO ME.
YOO-HOO, RACCOON DOG!
COME ON OUT.
SHOW YOURSELF IF YOU'RE IN HERE.
THAT MUST BE THE SHRINE.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> CALM DOWN.
IT'S JUST A RACCOON DOG, NOTHING
MORE.
>> ARE YOU THE DEMON?
>> WHAT BUSINESS DOES A MORTAL
HAVE WITH ME?
>> YOU ARE A RACCOON DOG.
>> I'M A WEASEL!
>> YOU LOOK MORE LIKE A RACCOON
DOG TO ME.
>> WE DON'T EVEN LOOK CLOSE!
BUT I LOVE EATING RACCOON DOGS.
ARE YOU REALLY A HUMAN?
YOU SMELL MORE LIKE VERMIN TO
ME.
>> NOT GOOD.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
MY NAME IS MIROKU, AND IF I DO
SAY SO MYSELF, I AM A FAMOUS
MONK AROUND THESE PARTS.
>> MIROKU?
THE ONE WHO USES THE WIND
TUNNEL?
>> PRECISELY.
APOLOGIZE NOW AND I'LL FORGIVE
YOUR TRANSGRESSIONS.
>> THIS IS AN OPPORTUNE TIME.
I SHALL DEVOUR YOU AND BECOME
THE MOST POWERFUL DEMON IN THE
WORLD!
>> NO!
PLEASE DON'T HURT ME!
>> BUT HOW DID YOU GET OUT HERE?
>> I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WE SAW YOU GO INSIDE THE CAVE,
MIROKU.
>> WE'D BETTER HURRY.
>> WHERE DID THIS COME FROM?
YOU ARE A RACCOON DOG--THE
MISSING INGREDIENT FOR MY STEW.
>> STAY WHERE YOU ARE!
COME ANY CLOSER, EVIL DEMON, AND
I'LL EXPOSE YOU TO MY WIND
TUNNEL.
>> I DARE YOU.
>> ARE YOU SURE YOU WANT TO TEST
YOUR LUCK?
>> [INDISTINCT]
AND LOOK, RACCOON DOG, YOU'VE
TURNED BACK.
>> OH, NO!
>> STUPID RACCOON DOG, YOUR TIME
IS UP.
>> NO, DON'T!
I PROMISE TO STOP THIS!
PLEASE FORGIVE ME!
>> YOU'D BETTER LIVE UP TO THAT
PROMISE.
>> WHO SAID THAT?
>> OH, MASTER MIROKU!
>> BEEN A LONG TIME, HACHI.
>> SO YOU'RE THE RACCOON DOG'S
PARTNER.
>> HEY, YOU, RACCOON DOG!
>> I SAID I'M A WEASEL!
>> I DON'T CARE ABOUT THAT.
>> JUST GO BACK QUIETLY TO YOUR
MOUNTAIN.
I SIMPLY DETEST VIOLENCE, SO
LET'S BE CIVIL ABOUT THIS AND DO
THE RIGHT THING, OK?
>> YOU'RE ALL JUST RACCOON DOGS.
DON'T TALK BIG.
I'LL MAKE STEW OUT OF ALL OF
YOU.
>> I GUESS THIS RACCOON DOG
DOESN'T UNDERSTAND REASON.
WIND TUNNEL!
>> WHAT?
DAMN IT!
HE'S THE REAL MIROKU AFTER ALL.
I'M SORRY.
FORGIVE ME.
I'LL NEVER DO IT AGAIN.
I PROMISE.
>> I'M GOING TO HOLD YOU TO
THAT.
>> WHAT?
IT'S OVER ALREADY?
>> THAT WAS PRETTY QUICK.
>> WEAK RACCOON DOG.
>> NOT A RACCOON DOG, A WEASEL.
>> HEY, RACCOON DOG.
>> I'M A WEASEL, DAMN IT.
>> THAT IS NOT THE ISSUE HERE.
>> I WANT YOU TO PROMISE NOT TO
BE NAUGHTY FROM NOW ON.
>> I PROMISE.
I PROMISE.
>> I'M GLAD YOU LEARNED YOUR
LESSON.
NOW GO BACK TO YOUR MOUNTAIN.
>> OH, YES, I WILL.
EXCUSE ME.
>> NOW, I KNOW WHAT YOU'VE BEEN
UP TO, AND I WANT A FULL
EXPLANATION WITHOUT ANY LIES.
>> FORGIVE ME.
I'M SO SORRY.
>> WHY DID YOU IMPERSONATE
MIROKU IN THE FIRST PLACE?
>> I JUST DECIDED ON THE SPUR OF
THE MOMENT.
I WAS SO HUNGRY I COULDN'T BEAR
IT, AND SO I IMPERSONATED MONK
MIROKU JUST ONE TIME.
>> AND IT WENT WELL FOR YOU.
>> OH, YES.
OH, YES.
BETTER THAN I COULD HAVE EVER
HOPED.
>> RIGHT, AND BEFORE YOU KNEW
IT, YOU WERE HOOKED.
>> LIKE A SLUGGISH
BOTTOM-FEEDER.
>> LISTEN HERE, HACHI.
>> YES?
>> I HOPE YOU'VE LEARNED
SOMETHING FROM YOUR MISTAKES AND
WILL NEVER TRY ANYTHING SO
FOOLISH AGAIN.
>> I WON'T.
>> AND TO THINK, ALL THE TROUBLE
I WENT THROUGH BECAUSE OF YOU
AND YOUR DECEPTIVE WAYS.
>> YES, BUT THERE'S ONE THING I
DON'T UNDERSTAND.
OK, I REALLY DID IMPERSONATE
YOU, AND I'M SORRY, BUT I NEVER
DID ANYTHING TO TARNISH YOUR
NAME.
>> HOW UTTERLY DISRESPECTFUL OF
YOU, YOU WICKED, WICKED
CREATURE.
IS THAT HOW YOU HONESTLY SEE ME?
>> HEY, TAKE IT EASY, ALL RIGHT?
I REALLY TRIED MY UTMOST TO
PRETEND TO BE YOU.
>> YOU KNOW, NOW THAT YOU
MENTION IT--
>> HOW YOU ACTED WASN'T ANY
DIFFERENT FROM HOW MIROKU WOULD
HAVE ACTED.
>> MM-HMM.
>> HOW RUDE OF YOU.
>> THE ONLY THING DIFFERENT IS
THAT HACHIEMON WAS MORE THE
LADIES' MAN.
>> HEY, HACHI?
>> YES?
>> DO YOU THINK YOU COULD TEACH
ME YOUR METHODS?
>> METHODS FOR WHAT?
>> I MEAN THE SECRET TO YOUR
POPULARITY WITH THE LADIES, WHAT
ELSE?
>> WELL, THAT'S EASY!
NOTHING DRIVES THEM MAD LIKE
TOTAL INDIFFERENCE!
>> INDIFFERENCE.
>> MIROKU, WHAT ARE YOU TWO
WHISPERING ABOUT?
>> NOTHING.
NOTHING AT ALL.
>> SOMETHING LECHEROUS AGAIN, NO
DOUBT.
>> DON'T BE SILLY.
NOW, DOES THIS LOOK LIKE THE
FACE OF A MAN PLAGUED BY
LECHEROUS THOUGHTS?
>> WELL, YES.
>> OK, LET'S GO.
>> GOTCHA.
>> YOU GET BACK HERE THIS
INSTANT, MIROKU!
>> I THINK YOU'RE MISTAKEN.
HE'S THE REAL MIROKU.
TELL HIM WHAT'S BOTHERING YOU.
>> DON'T LISTEN TO HIM, SANGO.
HE'S THE REAL MIROKU.
TRUST ME.
>> STOP THIS FOOLING AROUND, YOU
TRICKSTER MONK!
YOU WOMANIZER!
YOU LECHER!
CROOK!
>> SOME THINGS NEVER CHANGE.
>> ANSWER ME WHEN I'M TALKING TO
YOU.
>> INDIFFERENCE IS THE KEY.
>> THAT IS NEVER GOING TO WORK
FOR ME.
[DO AS INFINITY SINGING
"SHINJUTSU NO UTA"]
>> WHY DID THAT DEMON HAVE A
FAKE SACRED JEWEL, ANYWAY?
>> SOMEONE GAVE IT TO HIM.
>> WHO?
>> A DEMON.
>> ARE YOU TRYING TO PICK A
FIGHT?
>> CALM DOWN AND FOCUS,
INUYASHA.
DEMONS ARE TRYING TO CREATE A
REAL SACRED JEWEL.
IZUMO THE SCHOLAR WAS ATTACKED,
AND INNOCENT PEOPLE ARE BEING
KIDNAPPED FROM THEIR VILLAGES.
>> NEXT TIME, "THE SACRED JEWEL
MAKER: PART 1," CAN ANOTHER
SACRED JEWEL BE MADE?