>> HERE WE COME.
IT'S THE START OF "INUYASHA."
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL
THE SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY NARAKU WITH
MY TESSAIGA.
>> MIROKU AND SANGO REACH FAR
INTO THE DEPTHS OF THE SACRED
GROUNDS OF MOUNT HAKUREI.
THERE THEY FIND AN ENORMOUS
DEMONIC AURA.
HURRY, INUYASHA, THEY'RE BOTH
IN DANGER!
>> IT'S UP TO ALL OF US.
>> TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FEUDAL FAIRYTALE.
>> "INUYASHA."
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> NOW'S YOUR ONLY CHANCE, WOLF!
>> UNH!
HE'S UP AGAIN, MUTT!
>> NOT FOR LONG!
>> INUYASHA!
I WAS WORRIED.
ARE YOU REALLY OK?
YOU'RE NOT HURT?
>> KAGOME.
>> IT LEADS FAR INTO THE
MOUNTAIN.
>> LET'S GO, SANGO.
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT, NARAKU IS
DEEP INSIDE THIS CAVE.
>> IS NARAKU IN THE DEPTHS OF
THE SACRED MOUNTAIN BEYOND THIS
BARRIER?
EVERYONE IS GATHERED AT
MOUNT HAKUREI, WHERE OUR
DRAMATIC SCENE IS ABOUT TO
UNFOLD.
[PANTING]
>> THE DEMONIC AURA IS GETTING
EVEN STRONGER, AS I HAD
SURMISED.
THE BARRIER AROUND THE SACRED
MOUNTAIN HAS BEEN HIDING THE
SOURCE OF THIS EVIL IN ITS
DEPTHS.
HUH?
CLOISTERS?
>> THE DEMONIC AURA IS THICK
IN HERE.
[SNARLING]
NARAKU'S DEMONS!
>> I GUESS HE DOESN'T INTEND TO
HIDE HIMSELF ANY LONGER.
>> UP THERE.
NARAKU'S POISONOUS INSECTS.
MIROKU, DON'T USE THE WIND
TUNNEL.
IF YOU SUCK THEM IN, THE POISON
WILL GET YOU.
>> HIRAIKOTSU!
>> SACRED SUTRAS!
>> HMM.
WELL, WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT?
YOU TWO MORTALS HAVE MADE IT
THIS FAR INSIDE ALL BY
YOURSELVES?
THEN AGAIN, YOUR FRIEND
INUYASHA CAN'T COME IN BEYOND
THE BARRIER, CAN HE?
>> KAGURA!
>> YOU CERTAINLY HAVE GUTS.
THAT MUCH I'LL GRANT YOU.
BUT YOU WON'T MAKE IT OUT OF
HERE ALIVE.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE THEY DON'T
WANT US TO GO IN ANY DEEPER.
>> YEAH, SO WE MUST BE CLOSING
IN ON NARAKU.
YAH!
SANGO, THIS WAY!
>> FALL, SANGO!
>> SANGO!
>> AH!
MIROKU, YOU GO ON WITHOUT ME.
>> I CAN'T LEAVE YOU.
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
FINDING WHERE NARAKU IS HIDING
IS OUR FIRST PRIORITY, RIGHT?
KAGURA.
HIRAIKOTSU!
>> ARE YOU THROWING THAT WEAPON
AT ME?
I AM THE WIND, REMEMBER?
>> HUH?
KOHAKU.
>> FOOL, PAY ATTENTION!
>> UNH!
UHH!
SANGO!
SANGO.
SAY SOMETHING TO ME.
SANGO!
>> HOW VERY TOUCHING, MONK.
UNFORTUNATELY, YOU MIGHT HAVE
LIVED A LITTLE LONGER IF YOU'D
ONLY GONE ON AHEAD WITHOUT HER.
YOU CAN'T USE YOUR WIND TUNNEL,
THOUGH, FOR FEAR OF THE INSECTS'
POISON.
>> YOU DON'T KNOW WHO YOU'RE
DEALING WITH.
WHAT MEANING DOES MY LIFE HAVE
WITHOUT THE WOMAN I DEEPLY
CARE FOR?
I WOULD SACRIFICE MY LIFE
FOR HERS.
WIND TUNNEL!
>> HE USED THE WIND TUNNEL,
ENDANGERING HIMSELF.
>> THE INSECT POISON IS
SPREADING THROUGH MY BODY.
>> MIROKU AND SANGO STILL
AREN'T BACK.
THEY'VE BEEN GONE WAY TOO LONG.
I HOPE THEY'RE NOT IN ANY KIND
OF TROUBLE.
>> KAGOME, YOU WAIT HERE.
>> HUH?
>> I'M GOING UP THE MOUNTAIN TO
SEE FOR MYSELF WHAT'S GOING ON.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU KNOW YOU CAN'T GO PAST THAT
SACRED BARRIER.
>> I'M ONLY HALF DEMON.
I'M NOT GOING TO LET ANY DUMB
SACRED GROUNDS PURIFY ME.
>> THAT'S CRAZY, INUYASHA.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA WHAT'LL HAPPEN
IF YOU GO IN THERE.
>> YOU JUST STAY HERE AND WAIT
TILL I COME BACK.
WE DON'T HAVE TIME TO STAND
HERE ARGUING ABOUT IT ALL DAY.
HEY, YOU SCRAWNY WOLVES, YOU'RE
THERE, AREN'T YOU?
>> OOPS, BUSTED.
>> YEAH, MUTT, WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> YOU STAY HERE AND MAKE SURE
KAGOME IS SAFE.
>> WHY?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> MIROKU AND SANGO HAVE GONE
ON THEIR OWN THROUGH THE BARRIER
OF MOUNT HAKUREI, BUT THEY
HAVEN'T COME OUT YET.
>> IT MAKES SENSE FOR ME TO GO
BECAUSE THE SACRED GROUNDS
WON'T BE AS ROUGH FOR ME AS
THEY WOULD BE FOR A
FULL-FLEDGED DEMON.
>> SOUNDS FINE BY ME, MUTT.
GOOD RIDDANCE.
>> KEEP YOUR HANDS OFF!
AND DON'T TALK TO HER.
I'M WARNING YOU, IF ANYTHING
HAPPENS TO KAGOME, I'LL KILL
YOU.
GOT THAT?
>> INUYASHA!
>> THINK HE'S GOING TO BE
ALL RIGHT?
>> WELL, HE IS A HALF-DEMON,
SO HE MIGHT BE OK.
>> INUYASHA...
PLEASE DON'T PUSH YOURSELF
TOO FAR.
>> THIS IS A LOT WORSE THAN
I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE.
>> IF YOU WANT TO THROW YOUR
MISERABLE LIVES AWAY, THEN
COME ON.
YOU'LL FALL PREY TO MY
WIND TUNNEL!
>> [GROWLING]
>> I FIGURED AS MUCH.
EVEN YOU DEMONS PLACE SOME
VALUE ON YOUR MISERABLE LIVES.
>> THE MONK DOESN'T SEEM TO BE
AFFECTED AT ALL, AND YET HE
MUST HAVE GOTTEN A HUGE DOSE OF
THE SAIMYOSHO'S POISON.
>> WIND TUNNEL!
>> THAT MONK MUST BE REALLY
DESPERATE.
I DON'T WANT TO BE SUCKED UP
IN HIS WIND TUNNEL.
I'LL HAVE TO LET HIM GO.
AND BESIDES, UNFORTUNATELY FOR
YOU, MONK, THAT'S NOT WHERE
NARAKU IS.
>> PLEASE, DON'T COME AFTER
ME AGAIN.
IF I OPEN THE WIND TUNNEL ONE
MORE TIME, IT'LL ALL BE OVER
FOR ME.
>> SANGO, LOOK AT ME.
>> AH-CHOO!
OH, MAN, IS IT COLD.
I'VE GOT TO FIND SOME CLOTHES
SOMEWHERE BEFORE I FREEZE.
[HORSE NEIGHS]
>> HELLO, WARDROBE.
>> WHO GOES THERE?
>> WRETCH, OUT OF OUR WAY!
>> AND WHAT'LL YOU DO IF
I DON'T MOVE?
>> [YELLING]
>> MMM, LET'S SEE, NOW.
I GUESS THIS'LL HAVE TO DO.
>> JAKOTSU!
>> HUH?
>> HEY, I'VE BEEN LOOKING
FOR YOU.
I GOT THE NEWS FROM THE
SAIMYOSHO.
SO SUIKOTSU DIDN'T MAKE IT, HUH?
>> NO.
IT WAS A PRETTY SAD ENDING
FOR HIM.
OOH, THAT REMINDS ME, I'VE GOT
SOMETHING FOR YOU HERE,
BANKOTSU.
THIS IS A MEMENTO FROM
SUIKOTSU, A SHARD OF THE
SACRED JEWEL.
HERE.
>> HUH?
IT'S FOR ME?
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO SAID TO HAND
IT OVER IF WE GOT ONE.
>> JAKOTSU, WHY, YOU...
YOU'RE SUCH A GOOD FRIEND!
YOU'RE REALLY SOMETHING,
JAKOTSU, AND THE ONLY PERSON IN
THE WHOLE WORLD I CAN TRUST!
REALLY WEIRD, BUT LOYAL.
>> YOU REALLY THINK SO?
>> [LAUGHING]
>> [GROANING]
SEE?
I KNEW IT.
I'M NOT BEING PURIFIED.
I'M GOING TO MAKE IT.
DAMN IT.
NOW I CAN'T MOVE.
DOES THAT MEAN IT'S TOO
DANGEROUS TO GO ANY FURTHER?
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
>> WELL, WELL, INUYASHA.
CAN'T GO ANY FURTHER?
YOU LOOK QUITE WEAKENED BY
THE BARRIER.
>> RENKOTSU.
>> I'M SURPRISED.
IT'S UNLIKE YOU TO NOT NOTICE
THAT I WAS FOLLOWING.
>> YOU AGAIN, HUH?
THE BAND OF 7 MUST BE REALLY
SHORT-HANDED.
>> [LAUGHING]
YOUR MOUTH IS AS SHARP AS EVER.
ONE THING'S OBVIOUS, INUYASHA.
YOU'RE IN A HURRY TO GET IN
THERE, AREN'T YOU?
PROBLEM IS, IF YOU GO ANY
FURTHER, EVEN A HALF-DEMON LIKE
YOURSELF WILL BE PURIFIED.
GET GOING!
>> OH, NO!
[SCREAMING]
>> [SCREAMING]
>> HMM.
SO MUCH FOR HIM.
WHAT THE..?
>> SEE?
I'M STILL...
HUH?
MY DEMONIC POWERS ARE GONE, AND
IT'S NOT EVEN THE NIGHT OF THE
NEW MOON.
DAMN IT!
IT'S THIS BARRIER'S FAULT.
>> [CHUCKLING]
WELL, WELL, ISN'T THIS A
SURPRISE?
I THOUGHT THE SACRED GROUNDS
WOULD PURIFY YOU, BUT ONLY YOUR
DEMONIC POWERS HAVE DISAPPEARED.
HOW CONVENIENT FOR YOU THAT
YOU'RE ONLY A HALF-DEMON.
>> EXACTLY.
I'M FEELING WAY BETTER THAN
I WAS.
>> YOU'RE NEVER AT A LOSS FOR
WORDS, ARE YOU?
NOT THAT IT MATTERS, THOUGH.
YOU'RE NOTHING BUT A MORTAL NOW!
DAMN IT!
YOU WON'T ESCAPE ME!
>> I DON'T HAVE TIME TO WASTE
WITH THAT RENKOTSU.
I'VE GOT TO KEEP RUNNING ALL
THE WAY INTO THE MOUNTAIN.
>> HUH?
HMM?
MIROKU?
AH!
THAT'S RIGHT.
I WAS HIT BY THE HIRAIKOTSU.
MIROKU.
HE OPENED THE WIND TUNNEL AND
SUCKED IN THE POISONOUS INSECTS?
MIROKU, COME ON, WAKE UP,
PLEASE!
THIS IS TERRIBLE.
IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
MIROKU, MIROKU, PLEASE OPEN
YOUR EYES!
MIROKU!
>> HUH?
>> MIROKU!
>> SANGO?
THANK GOODNESS YOU'RE CONSCIOUS
AGAIN.
SANGO, DON'T STAY HERE.
GO ON WITHOUT ME.
>> NO, NOT UNLESS YOU'RE
WITH ME.
>> I THINK I MIGHT HAVE PUSHED
MYSELF TOO FAR THIS TIME.
YOU, AT LEAST, HAVE TO MAKE IT
OUT OF THIS ALIVE FOR ME, OK?
>> NO!
IF YOU CAN'T GO ON...THEN WE'LL
DIE HERE TOGETHER.
>> SANGO...
>> HMM?
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO ME?
IT FEELS LIKE I'M GETTING
BETTER.
>> MIROKU, WHAT IS IT?
>> WHY AREN'T THOSE DEMONS
ATTACKING US?
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT'S STRANGE.
>> IT WAS PURIFIED.
>> THEY CAN'T COME ANY CLOSER
TO US.
RIGHT.
THIS IS STILL SACRED GROUND.
IT'S EVEN POWERFUL ENOUGH TO
PURIFY THE POISON IN MY BODY.
LET'S GO, SANGO.
THERE'S DEFINITELY SOMETHING
UP AHEAD.
>> MIROKU, ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE
ALL RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
I GUESS WE WON'T HAVE TO DIE
TOGETHER AFTER ALL.
>> OH, NO.
WHAT DID I SAY?
>> SHE DOESN'T REMEMBER.
HUH.
>> [PANTING]
>> [LAUGHING]
HOW LONG DO YOU THINK YOU CAN
ESCAPE ME?
GOTCHA!
>> AAH!
>> YOU'VE NOWHERE TO RUN.
I GUESS THIS IS AS FAR AS
YOU GO.
>> DAMN YOU.
HUH?
WHAT'S THAT?
>> DIE!
>> AAH!
>> GOT HIM.
HUH?
WHERE'S HIS BODY?
HE MUST HAVE SLIPPED THROUGH
THAT CRACK BEFORE THE BLAST.
>> HEY, OVER HERE, RENKOTSU.
>> JAKOTSU.
>> HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN
A PLACE LIKE THIS?
>> SO I GUESS WE'RE ALL THAT'S
LEFT OF THE BAND OF 7.
>> EXACTLY, AND THAT'S WHAT
THE PROBLEM IS.
>> HMM?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> HOW CAN WE POSSIBLY BE THE
BAND OF 7 WHEN THERE'S ONLY 3
OF US LEFT?
WE'VE GOT TO TRY AND COME UP
WITH A NEW NAME.
>> OH, BY THE WAY, YOU DON'T
KNOW WHAT HAPPENED TO
SUIKOTSU'S JEWEL SHARD, DO YOU?
>> OH, THAT?
WELL, I TOOK IT AND HANDED IT
OVER TO BANKOTSU, OF COURSE.
>> YEAH?
HE DOESN'T HAVE A SHRED OF
GREED IN HIM.
STILL, IT'S BAD NEWS FOR ME.
BANKOTSU IS GETTING ALL THE
SHARDS.
EVENTUALLY HE'LL WANT JAKOTSU'S
SHARD, TOO.
>> ...REMEMBER, LIKE THE
3 RAVENS...
>> AND I CAN'T LET THAT HAPPEN.
JAKOTSU, I MEANT TO TELL YOU,
SOMETHING INTERESTING HAS
HAPPENED RECENTLY.
>> HMM?
INTERESTING?
>> [PANTING]
>> MIROKU.
>> RIGHT, LET'S DO IT.
>> THIS HOLE IS REALLY DEEP.
I WONDER IF IT GOES ALL THE
WAY DOWN.
HUH?
AAH!
>> SO RENKOTSU WAS RIGHT.
IS THAT REALLY YOU AS A MORTAL?
YOU'RE AS CUTE A HUMAN AS YOU
ARE A HALF-DEMON.
>> JAKOTSU.
>> HA HA.
WHAT A PLEASANT SURPRISE.
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR THE TIME
WHEN I CAN FIGHT YOU AGAIN,
INUYASHA.
WELL?
COME ON.
[LAUGHING]
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> THIS MUMMY IS SAINT HOKUSHIN?
>> SAINT HOKUSHIN, IN LIFE YOU
WERE A MAN OF HIGH MORALS AND
YOU SAVED MANY PEOPLE.
WHY ON EARTH ARE YOU WORKING TO
HELP NARAKU?
>> I WAS ENSHRINED AND BECAME A
LIVING BUDDHA, BUT MY SOUL WAS
LEFT IN THE DARKNESS, AND HENCE
I COULD NOT BE SAVED.
THAT'S WHEN THE MAN'S VOICE
CALLED OUT TO ME.
>> I HAVE NO INTENTION OF
JUDGING YOU.
>> NEXT TIME, DIVINE MALICE OF
THE SAINT.
>> BUT I CANNOT IGNORE THE
BARRIER WHICH PROTECTS NARAKU.