- HUH?
SEE YOU LATER, SHIPPO.
I'M OFF NOW.
- BYE, COME BACK SOON.
AND MAKE SURE YOU DON'T
FORGET OUR YUMMY NINJA TREATS,
OK, KAGOME?
- HEY, DID YOU SEE INUYASHA?
- YEAH, HE TOOK KILALA
AND LEFT
FIRST THING THIS MORNING.
- I THINK HE WAS
GOING SOMEWHERE FAR AWAY.
- HMM, THERE'S ONLY ONE PLACE
HE COULD'VE BEEN HEADED.
- YEAH, AND THAT'D BE?
- THERE IS JUST ONE PERSON
WHO UNDERSTANDS
TETSUSAIGA'S TRUE POWER,
AND THAT IS
THE MAN WHO FORGED IT.
- OH, YOU MEAN TOTOSAI?
INUYASHA MUST BE PLANNING
TO BREAK THROUGH
NARAKU'S BARRIER.
- SO, HE'S GONE
TO SEE THE OLD MAN.
HMM.
[METAL CLANGING]
- TOTOSAI, YOU MUST A KNOW A WAY
THAT I CAN BREAK THROUGH
ANY BARRIER, NO MATTER
HOW STRONG IT IS.
[CLANG]
- THE TECHNIQUE TO BREAK THROUGH
A BARRIER OF ANY STRENGTH.
IT'S NOT LIKE THERE ISN'T A WAY
OR LIKE THERE IS A WAY.
- WHICH IS IT?
I HAVE TO GET STRONGER
WHILE NARAKU'S LAID UP
AND OUT OF COMMISSION.
- HMM...OOH, IT ITCHES.
THAT'S RIGHT,
I HAVEN'T BATHED
IN OVER A WEEK.
- KNOWING THIS OLD FART,
HE WON'T JUST COME OUT
AND TELL ME THE ANSWER.
I HAVE TO BE PATIENT
AND TRY TO PRY IT OUT OF HIM.
YOU GOTTA HELP!
- MMMM...OH, DEAR, I'M ITCHY.
MY BACK IS ITCHY, TOO.
- TOTOSAI,
I NEED YOU TO TEACH ME
HOW TO BUST THROUGH
NARAKU'S BARRIER.
- OH, THE ITCH!
I SURE COULD USE A BATH.
- ISN'T THERE SOME WAY,
SOMETHING I CAN DO AS TRAINING?
- A BATH.
I'LL NEED
A FEW THINGS TO GET READY.
OH, BUT WE'LL NEED
SO MUCH WATER.
- WATER?
- IT'S SUCH HARD WORK.
- HMM.
- THERE NEEDS TO BE
ENOUGH WATER FROM THE RIVER
AT THE BOTTOM
OF THE VALLEY
TO FILL THE TUB.
THEN ALL THE WOOD OUT BACK
HAS TO BE CUT INTO
SMALL PIECES OF KINDLING
FOR THE FIRE.
AH, HUMBUG, PREPARING A BATH
IS SO MUCH WORK FOR ONE PERSON.
- CUT THE WOOD?
IS THAT MY TRAINING?
- TRAINING?
- MASTER!
- YOU AGAIN!
WHAT IS IT THIS TIME?
- I'M NOT GOIN' AWAY
TILL YOU HELP ME.
- HEY,
WHO'S THE LITTLE FOX DEMON?
- I'M NO FOX!
I'M A LYNX!
AND I'VE ASKED MASTER TOTOSAI
TO TRAIN ME.
- OH, YEAH?
- HE'S GONNA TEACH ME
THE TECHNIQUES I NEED
TO BREAK THROUGH
A DEMONIC BARRIER.
- IT'S REALLY ITCHY.
WAIT, I SHOULDN'T LOOK
A GIFT HORSE IN THE MOUTH.
AHEM, I WANT YOU TWO
TO FETCH SOME WATER
AND CHOP THE FIREWOOD.
- I KNEW IT.
THAT'S MY SPECIAL TRAINING.
- AWW, DON'T YOU KNOW ANYTHING?
- HMM?
- THE FETCHING OF WATER
BUILDS UP ESSENTIAL MUSCLES
AND THE CUTTING
OF THE WOOD IMPROVES
YOUR SWING WHILE FIGHTING.
EVERY SINGLE TASK
HAS SPECIAL SIGNIFICANCE.
FATHER TOLD ME THAT'S BEEN
A TRADITION ON THE CONTINENT
FOR 4,000 YEARS.
- OH, YEAH?
SO, I'VE FINALLY WORN YOU DOWN,
AND YOU'RE GONNA TEACH ME
HOW TO BREAK THROUGH
THE BARRIER.
- NO, I SIMPLY
WANTED YOU TO HELP ME--OWW!
- WHY DIDN'T YOU COME OUT
AND TELL ME FROM THE START?
- HUH?
- OH, I GUESS IN ORDER TO LEARN
THIS SPECIAL TECHNIQUE OF YOURS,
I GOTTA BUILD UP
MY STRENGTH FIRST.
FINE, I'LL STAY HERE
AND TRAIN WITH YOU.
- HOLD ON!
I'VE BEEN STAYING
IN THAT HUT FOR 10 DAYS,
WAITING FOR HIM TO TEACH ME,
MAKING ME SENIOR APPRENTICE.
- YOU SENIOR?
- DON'T YOU KNOW ANYTHING?
IN THE WORLD OF HUMANS,
THERE'S A WHOLE SYSTEM
FOR APPRENTICES.
THE ONE WHO CAME FIRST
IS THE SENIOR BROTHER.
NOW, QUIT YOUR DAWDLING,
AND FOLLOW ME, JUNIOR.
- JUNIOR?
- NOW, HURRY UP, LITTLE BROTHER.
- THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
- WHAT'S TAKIN' YA?
- I'M COMING, YOU LITTLE PEST.
- THEY SEEM TO BE
UNDER THE WRONG IMPRESSION.
BUT I'M GONNA GET MY BATH!
- I TOOK OFF
WITHOUT SAYING A WORD
TO KAGOME AND THE OTHERS.
AND LEARNING THIS SKILL
FROM TOTOSAI MIGHT TAKE
LONGER THAN I THOUGHT.
- RRRRRR...
- HEY, KITTY, THAT'S TO HEAVY
FOR A LITTLE GUY LIKE YOU.
DON'T CALL ME KITTY.
THE NAME'S BONZA.
- CAREFUL YOU DON'T
HURT YOURSELF, BONZA.
- MIND YOUR OWN BUSINESS.
I'M GOING TO
TRAIN HARDER THAN YOU,
AND MASTER TOTOSAI
WILL TEACH ME THE METHOD FIRST.
- YEAH, WHATEVER YOU SAY.
HOW COME YOU'RE
SO DESPERATE, ANYWAY?
- [GRUNTING]
[CRYING]
HEY! LET ME DOWN!
LET ME DOWN RIGHT NOW, JUNIOR!
ARE YOU LISTENING?
THIS WON'T GET ME ANYWHERE.
PUT ME DOWN AT ONCE.
DON'T YOU MAKE ME ANGRY!
ARE YOU EVEN LISTENING?
[GRUNTING]
- LOOK, I TOLD YOU,
YOU'RE GONNA HURT YOURSELF.
- WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO LEARN THE SKILL.
[GRUNTING]
WHOA!
- AAH!
WATCH WHAT
YOU'RE DOING, YOU FOOL!
- [PANTING]
- UGH, GO SIT
SOMEWHERE OUT OF TROUBLE.
- NO, I GOTTA KEEP TRAINING.
AHH, AHH, AHH...
AAAAAHHHH!
AAAHHH!
- OH, NO!
- AAAHHH...
- HOW MANY TIMES
DO I GOTTA TELL YOU?
YOU'RE GONNA GET HURT.
HMM?
HEY, KID, YOU'RE BURNING UP.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
YOU MEAN TO TELL ME
YOU HAVEN'T EATEN FOR DAYS?
- THANKS.
SORRY ABOUT THIS.
- HMM. AND YOU STAYED
IN THIS DRAFTY OLD HUT
FOR 10 DAYS, HUH?
WELL, IT'S NO WONDER
YOU'VE COME DOWN WITH A FEVER.
- BUT I DIDN'T HAVE ANY CHOICE.
I HAVE TO LEARN
HOW TO BREAK THE BARRIER.
- FIRST YOU HAVE TO
GET YOURSELF BETTER.
YOU REST, AND I'LL BRING YOU
SOMETHING GOOD TO EAT LATER.
OK?
- I DON'T GET IT.
SO, HOW COME
YOU'RE BEING SO NICE TO ME?
- WHO KNOWS?
MAYBE IT'S BECAUSE
ONE OF MY FRIENDS
IS ABOUT
THE SAME AGE AS YOU ARE.
- AHH-AHH-AAH-CHOO!
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, SHIPPO?
- I THINK I'M GETTING A COLD.
- EITHER THAT
OR SOMEONE IS TALKING ABOUT YOU
BEHIND YOUR BACK.
- HMM?
- GREAT IDEA, TOTOSAI.
THIS'LL BUILD UP
THE STRENGTH OF MY LUNGS.
- AHHH, WHAT A FINE BATH.
- OLD MAN, JUST HOLLER
IF THERE'S ANYTHING ELSE
I CAN DO FOR MY TRAINING.
THE SOONER
I MASTER THIS TECHNIQUE,
THE BETTER.
- TRAINING?
- HEY! HOLD ON, HERE.
- HMMM?
- I HEAR YOU'RE
MAKING MASTER INUYASHA TRAIN.
IS IT TRUE?
- WELL, ACTUALLY,
I ONLY WISHED FOR SOME HELP
TO PREPARE MY BATH.
FETCHING WATER
IS SUCH A CHORE FOR AN OLD MAN.
IT'S NOT MY FAULT IF HE THINKS
THIS IS SOME KIND OF TRAINING.
HE'S THE ONE WHO'S JUMPING
TO ALL THE WRONG CONCLUSIONS.
- I'VE NEVER SEEN
MASTER INUYASHA WORKING SO HARD.
DO YOU HAVE
ANY IDEA WHAT'LL HAPPEN
WHEN HE LEARNS THE TRUTH?
- UHHH...
- WHAT? YOU WANTED ME
TO PREPARE YOUR BATH?
- THE MERE THOUGHT OF IT
IS MAKING ME SHAKE WITH FEAR.
- OH, AND IT'S
GIVING ME GOOSEBUMPS.
- I CAME TO SCRUB YOUR BACK,
BUT YOU LOOK COLD.
I'LL GO BACK DOWN
AND STOKE THE FIRE.
- [GULPING, SLURPING]
- HERE.
HAVE MINE, TOO.
- HMM? YOU SURE?
- YOU'RE SICK.
JUST TAKE IT, OK?
- THANKS.
- HOW COME
YOU WANT TO TRAIN SO BAD?
AH, FORGET IT,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO TALK
IF IT'S THAT HARD FOR YOU.
- A DEMON NAMED NONAFUSHI
TOOK OVER THE MOUNTAIN
WHERE ME
AND MY LYNX TRIBE LIVED.
- [SCREAMING]
HE BLOCKED OFF THE MOUNTAIN
WITH A DEMONIC BARRIER
SO WE COULDN'T GATHER FOOD.
OUR LIVES
WERE TOTALLY DISRUPTED.
MY FATHER'S THE TRIBE LEADER,
AND HE SAYS THAT
TOTOSAI IS THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN MAKE
A WEAPON STRONG ENOUGH
TO BREAK THE BARRIER.
AND THAT TOTOSAI
WOULD KNOW THE TECHNIQUE TO USE.
BUT THE OLD MAN'S ECCENTRIC
AND REFUSES
TO TEACH JUST ANYONE.
WELL, THAT'S
WHAT FATHER TOLD US.
PEOPLE IN MY TRIBE
ARE STARTING TO DOUBT
AND TURN THEIR BACKS ON HIM.
IT'S MADDENING.
I WANT EVERYONE
TO LOOK TO MY FATHER
AS THEIR LEADER AGAIN.
AND THAT'S WHY I HAVE TO LEARN
HOW TO BREAK DOWN THE BARRIER.
FOR MY FATHER'S SAKE.
- [MEOWING]
- HMM? WHO'S THAT?
HUH?
TORAKO!
TORAKO, IS THAT YOU?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
WAY OUT HERE, TORAKO?
- MEOW MEOW MEOW.
MEOWWW.
- THAT'S TERRIBLE!
- WHAT'D SHE SAY, BONZA?
- MY FATHER'S GONE
TO ATTACK NONAFUSHI.
- HUH?
EVEN THOUGH HE DOESN'T KNOW
HOW TO BREAK THE BARRIER,
HE WENT INSIDE IT
TO TAKE BACK THE MOUNTAIN
FOR THE LYNX TRIBE.
[GROWLING]
- WAIT! BONZA!
- MEOWWWW...
- FATHER. FATHER!
HUH?
AHH...
- [SNORING]
I COULD HAVE SWORN
I SENSED SOMETHING JUST NOW.
-YOU DID?
LIKE WHAT?
- OLD MAN,
DID BONZA COME AROUND THIS WAY?
- HUH...
OH, MAYBE THAT'S WHO IT WAS.
- WHICH WAY DID HE GO?
- UHH, THAT WAY.
- CRAZY KID.
- AHH, THAT FEELS MUCH BETTER.
- IS THIS THE WAY?
- MEOW.
- [PANTING]
- HUH? THERE HE IS.
- BONZA!!
BONZA.
- AAH!
INUYASHA!
- I'LL HELP YOU
SAVE YOUR FATHER.
- NO, THANKS.
- HOW COME?
- HE'S MY FATHER.
I'LL RESCUE HIM.
IT'S GOT NOTHIN' TO DO WITH YOU.
IT'S NOT YOUR RESPONSIBILITY.
- SPARE ME.
YOU WERE THE ONE WHO SAID
WE WERE LIKE BROTHERS.
SENIOR AND JUNIOR BROTHERS.
ISN'T THAT REASON ENOUGH?
- HMM.
- I'M STILL WAITING!
- MMM-HMM, MMM-HMM.
HUH?
FATHER!
- NO, WAIT.
HE'S TRAPPED INSIDE THE BARRIER.
- HUH? YOU'RE RIGHT.
STILL, HOW DO YOU
GET INSIDE THERE?
- [MEOWING]
- HUH? NONAFUSHI
WANTED TO KILL FATHER.
AND SO HE OPENED THE BARRIER
TO LET HIM INSIDE.
- HUH?
- FATHER KNEW IT WAS A TRAP.
BUT HE WENT INSIDE
IN ORDER TO SAVE
THE REST OF THE TRIBE.
MY FATHER
PUT HIS LIFE IN JEOPARDY,
AND HE CHOSE TO FIGHT
AS THE BRAVE LEADER
OF THE LYNX TRIBE!
[GRUNTING]
- HOLD IT.
I'M GONNA GO IN.
- NO, YOU CAN'T!
HE'S MY FATHER,
AND IT'S A SON'S DUTY
TO SAVE HIS OWN FATHER!
- THEN I'M GOING IN
AS YOUR JUNIOR.
IS THAT ALL RIGHT, BIG BROTHER?
- SURE THING, JUNIOR.
- [GROANING]
- YOUR FATHER
IS GOING TO BE ALL RIGHT.
I'M SURE WE CAN MAKE IT
IN TIME TO SAVE HIM.
- YAAAHHH!
- STOP! BONZA!!
- YAAAAHHH! YAH!
- [GASP]
- AAAAHHHH!
- ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR MIND?
- IT DIDN'T WORK.
I COULDN'T DO IT.
I WASN'T ABLE TO SAVE MY FATHER.
- DON'T BE SO SURE OF THAT.
I THINK YOUR ATTACK
SEEMS TO HAVE GOTTEN
NONAFUSHI PRETTY WORRIED.
[RUSTLING, LIMBS BREAKING]
- THAT'S HIM.
HERE HE COMES.
- YEAH.
THAT'S RIGHT.
- [GROWLING]
- WHY DON'T YOU QUIT HIDING
LIKE A COWARD
AND COME OUT AND FIGHT US?
- [ROARING]
- THAT'S MORE LIKE IT, MANTIS.
- [GRUNTING]
SOME NERVE,
FIGHTING FROM BEHIND A BARRIER.
YOU'RE THROUGH, COWARD!
- WHOAH!
LOOK AT THAT.
- [ROARING]
- WE WEREN'T IN TRAINING
WITH TOTOSAI FOR LONG,
BUT NOW'S AS GOOD A TIME AS ANY
TO START REAPING THE REWARDS.
THIS GUY'S
GONNA BE MY GUINEA PIG.
WE ONLY TRAINED FOR ONE DAY,
I'M PUTTING EVERYTHING
WE LEARNED INTO THIS SWORD.
- YEAH!
YOU SHOW HIM, JUNIOR!
- WATCH THIS.
WIND STAR! YAAAAHH!
- YEAH! HA HA!
- [GROWLING]
- AH AH AH AH! AAH!
AAAHHH!
- HUH? AAH!
HUH, YOU WANT ANOTHER GO AT ME?
FINE!
YAAAAHHH!
- THAT WAS AMAZING.
HEY, JUNIOR, MASTER TOTOSAI
TAUGHT US MORE THAN I REALIZED.
- LOOKS LIKE.
YOU KNOW, BONZA,
I REALLY DO FEEL
AN AWFUL LOT STRONGER
THAN I DID BEFORE.
- KEEP UP WITH YOUR TRAINING.
- YOU BET.
SAME WITH YOU, BONZA.
YOU SAVED YOUR FATHER.
NOW YOU MUST BECOME
THE TRIBE LEADER ONE DAY.
- I'LL SEE YOU AGAIN, RIGHT?
- DEFINITELY.
- COME BACK AND SEE ME SOMETIME!
OK, BROTHER?
- WHERE'VE YOU BEEN, INUYASHA?
- UH, JUST OUT.
I HAVE TO THANK YOU, THOUGH.
THAT TRAINING OF YOURS
WAS GREAT.
I'M A LOT STRONGER
THAN I WAS BEFORE I CAME.
- HUH?
STRONGER, HMM.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE
MADE YOU DO THOSE THINGS.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- MMM, THIS IS HARD TO ADMIT.
YOU THOUGHT
THAT YOU'D BECOME STRONGER,
AND I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'D HAVE DONE
IF YOU'D HAVE BEEN HURT
WHILE CONFRONTING
NARAKU'S BARRIER.
OH, THANK GOODNESS YOU'RE OK.
- I STILL DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- OH, THERE'S NO WAY
YOU COULD'VE GOTTEN
ANY STRONGER.
- YOU MEAN THAT TRAINING WAS...
- WHAT TRAINING?
I SIMPLY WANTED TO TAKE A BATH.
- WHAT A SURPRISE.
YOU JUMPED
TO THE WRONG CONCLUSION.
- YOU SEE, I HADN'T BATHED
IN SUCH A LONG TIME, HA HA...
OLD MAN,
YOU'RE SAYING
THERE'S NO METHOD
FOR BREAKING THROUGH
NARAKU'S BARRIER?
- UHH, IT'S NOT
AS THOUGH THERE ISN'T.
B-B-BUT IT'S NOT
AS THOUGH THERE IS.
OHH! OWW!
- THAT'LL TEACH YOU.
USELESS OLD MAN.
ALL THAT WORK FOR NOTHING?
- HE'S SUCH A RASH YOUNG MAN.
AND HE LEFT
JUST WHEN I WAS
GOING TO TELL HIM.
- TELL HIM WHAT?
- HE LABORED SO HARD
AND PERSEVERED,
SO I THOUGHT I SHOULD TEACH HIM
THE METHOD TO BECOME STRONGER,
AND THUS ENABLE HIM
TO BREAK THE BARRIER.
- IS IT THE METHOD
THAT I'M THINKING OF?
- YES.
YOU TELL HIM FOR ME, WOULD YOU?
- COUNT ON IT.
BY THE WAY, YOU'RE LUCKY
YOU GOT AWAY WITH JUST ONE LUMP.
- I WAS AWAY THE WHOLE NIGHT
WITHOUT TELLING EVERYONE.
THEY MUST BE WORRIED.
DRY YOUR TEARS,
EVERYONE, BECAUSE I'M BACK.
HUH?
- NINJA FOOD
IS ALWAYS SO DELICIOUS.
- THERE'S NOTHING THAT EVEN
COMPETES WITH THIS FLAVOR.
- YEAH, WHERE'S MINE?
- YOU WEREN'T HERE,
SO I ATE IT.
- YOU WHAT?!
GIVE IT BACK, YOU LITTLE CREEP!
- LET GO INUYASHA!
- HAND IT OVER!
IT'S MINE!
I WANT IT!
- SIT, BOY.
FIGURES.
TRUST YOU
TO TURN THIS INTO A BRAWL.
YOU SNOOZE, YOU LOSE.
WEREN'T YOU WORRIED?
I WAS GONE FOR A WHOLE DAY.
- I GUESS I COULD
SHARE MY SOUP WITH YOU.
NOT THAT YOU DESERVER IT.
- HOW CHARITABLE OF YOU.
- [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
♪ EVERY HEART... ♪
- SO, THERE'S
A TRIBE OF BAT DEMONS
WHO HUNT DOWN HUMANS?
- YES,
AND IF INUYASHA DESTROYS IT,
THE TETSUSAIGA
WILL BE ABLE TO BREAK THROUGH
NARAKU'S BARRIER.
THERE'S JUST ONE PROBLEM.
- A LITTLE HALF DEMON GIRL
IS PROTECTING THEM
WITH THE BARRIER.
- I'M NOT SO SURE
INUYASHA WILL BE
WILLING TO KILL HER.
- NEXT TIME, "SHIORI'S FAMILY
AND INUYASHA'S FEELINGS."
- DID I MENTION HOW GOOD
THAT BATH FELT?