- NOW, THEN,
LET'S SEE WHAT STATE
THE WORLD IS IN TODAY.
HMM. HMM. WHAT'S THIS?
FOOT-AND-MOUTH DISEASE
ONLY AFFECTS YOUNGER CHILDREN?
I CAN'T USE IT THEN.
HMM.
I'M RUNNING OUT OF DISEASES
TO USE AS AN EXCUSE
FOR KAGOME'S ABSENCE FROM SCHOOL
WHILE SHE'S
IN THE WARRING STATES ERA.
- HELLO, GRAMPS!
- HI.
-AH-AH-CHOO!
- BLESS YOU, MOMMY.
ARE YOU SICK?
- OHH. THE COLDS GOING AROUND
THIS YEAR ARE NASTY.
I SHOULD HAVE WORN
A SCARF TODAY.
- HUH? SHE COULD HAVE A COLD!
- BYE, GRAMPS.
- OKEY-DOKEY, MY DEAR.
WATCH OUT FOR CARS, WILL YOU?
WAIT, KAGOME, COME BACK!
WHERE ARE YOU HEADED OFF TO?
- SHE'S GOING TO SCHOOL
OF COURSE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- SHE CAN'T JUST
RUSH OFF TO SCHOOL.
I THOUGHT UP
A REALLY GOOD ILLNESS.
KAGOME'S SUCH
AN IMPERTINENT CHILD.
- WHAT IS GRANDPA TALKING ABOUT?
HE'S LOSING IT.
[BELL RINGING]
- OH, NO! I FORGOT
MY MATH BOOK. OHH.
- WHAT ARE YOU
LOOKING FOR, KAGOME?
- YOU COULD RUN OUT QUICKLY
AND BORROW A BOOK
FROM THE CLASSROOM NEXT DOOR.
- OHH. I FORGOT MY ENGLISH,
SCIENCE, AND SOCIAL STUDIES
BOOKS, AS WELL.
- OHH. YOU FINALLY
SHOW UP FOR CLASS,
AND YOU'RE TOTALLY UNPREPARED.
- I BROUGHT MY QUILL PEN
INSTEAD OF MY BALLPOINT.
- STUDENTS, IS KAGOME HERE?
- THOSE ARE ALL
THE BOOKS YOU FORGOT?
- YOUR YOUNGER BROTHER
DROPPED THEM OFF
AND ASKED ME TO FORGIVE YOU
FOR BEING SUCH A SCATTERBRAIN.
[STUDENTS LAUGHING]
- AT LEAST SOMEONE
IN KAGOME'S FAMILY
HAS THEIR ACT TOGETHER.
- IT'S BEEN A WHILE NOW
SINCE THIS EVERYDAY,
AVERAGE SCHOOLGIRL
HAS BEEN CROSSING BACK AND FORTH
FROM THE WARRING STATES ERA
TO MODERN TIMES.
IN THE OTHER DIMENSION,
I HAVE INUYASHA, MIROKU,
AND OLD KAEDE TO HELP ME OUT,
BUT IN THE REAL WORLD
WITH HIGH-SCHOOL EXAMS
LOOMING OVER MY HEAD,
I HAVE TO MANAGE ALL BY MYSELF.
HMM. WELL, NOT QUITE.
I'VE BEEN GETTING HELP
IN THIS WORLD, TOO.
ERI, THANKS FOR THE NOTES.
THEY WERE A BIG HELP.
- THANK YOUR BROTHER SOTA.
HE ASKED ME TO WRITE THEM.
HE SAID YOU TEND TO FALL BEHIND
A LITTLE IN MATH CLASS.
- WHAT? MY LITTLE BROTHER
SAID THAT?
- MY SISTER FORGOT
HER SCHOOLBOOKS AT HOME.
DO YOU THINK YOU COULD
GIVE THESE TO HER
BEFORE CLASS STARTS?
WHAT? THERE'S A BIG TEST
COMING UP?
OH, NO. I BETTER GO
TELL MY SISTER.
WELL, THANKS.
PLEASE KEEP ME UPDATED.
- SOTA--THAT LITTLE BRAT.
BUT A HELPFUL LITTLE BROTHER.
[ROARING]
- AAH!
[SCREECHING]
[BUZZING]
- I SEE. SO INUYASHA
WIPED THEM OUT
WITH A SINGLE SWING.
HMM. RATHER THAN SENDING
NUMEROUS DEMONS TO THEIR DEATHS,
IT WOULD SEEM BETTER TO SEND ONE
THAT HE CANNOT KILL.
WELL, KILLING OR NOT,
IT WOULD SERVE ME EITHER WAY.
I INTEND TO USE YOU AGAIN
IN MY SERVICE.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
ARE YOU ABLE
TO MOVE YOUR BODY NOW?
- YES, MASTER NARAKU.
- GOOD. CAN YOU KILL THEM?
- CAN YOU KILL INUYASHA,
MIROKU, AND SANGO?
- YES, MASTER NARAKU.
- READY AND AARGH!
HUH? DAMN IT!
HOW THE HECK DO I ENGAGE
THE TETSUSAIGA'S ULTIMATE POWER?
- DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT, INUYASHA.
EVEN IF IT WAS LUCK,
YOU SAVED US.
JUST GET LUCKY AGAIN NEXT THEM.
- HMM. HMM. TETSUSAIGA!
- OHH! INUYASHA, ARE YOU
TRYING TO KILL ME OR WHAT?
- I THOUGHT YOU SAID
IT WAS ALL LUCK.
- LISTEN. YOU'RE REALLY
PUSHING YOUR LUCK
WITH ME TODAY.
GO TEST THOSE SWORD POWERS
OF YOURS SOMEWHERE ELSE, OK?
- BE QUIET AND STOP
CALLING IT LUCK.
IT'S SKILL.
[ANIMAL HOWLING]
- NARAKU TOOK THE OFFENSIVE
WITH THOSE DEMONS.
HE'S PROBABLY KEEPING A WATCH
ON US FROM SOMEWHERE.
IT WILL BE VERY HARD
TO MAKE A MOVE.
- IT WILL SAVE US TIME
LOOKING FOR HIM, THE CREEP.
JUST TRY TO ATTACK US
ANYTIME, ANYWHERE.
- HA HA HA!
- AND WHAT ARE YOU
LAUGHING AT, MIROKU?
- I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT.
MY WIND TUNNEL
CAN'T BE USED FOR A WHILE.
I'M FEELING VULNERABLE,
AND HEARING YOU TALK
WITH SUCH CONFIDENCE
IS ENCOURAGING.
- HA! CHILL OUT, MONK.
I GOT YOU COVERED.
IF NARAKU COMES SLINKING AROUND,
I'LL TAKE CARE OF HIM
WITH THE TETSUSAIGA.
EVEN IF IT IS LUCK,
IF I CAN ENGAGE
THE TETSUSAIGA'S
TRUE POWER AGAIN,
I KNOW I CAN BEAT NARAKU.
I VOW I WILL MASTER THIS SWORD.
THE TETSUSAIGA IS MINE.
- WELL, SHIPPO?
- THEY'RE STILL
IN DEEP CONVERSATION.
- REALLY? NOW'S OUR CHANCE TO GO
FOR A DIP IN THE HOT SPRINGS.
- I KNOW THE MONK WOULD
TRY TO PEEK AT US,
BUT DO YOU THINK INUYASHA WOULD?
- NO WAY. HE'S SUCH A COLD FISH.
- DO YOU WANT HIM TO LOOK?
- OHH! THAT'S A BAD SCAR.
- YES. IT DIDN'T HEAL WELL.
- WHO HURT YOU, THE DEMONS?
- NO. I GOT THIS SCAR
FROM MY YOUNGER BROTHER.
IF ONLY I'D REALIZED
SOME THINGS EARLIER,
I COULD HAVE
PREVENTED HIS DEATH.
KOHAKU WAS TENDERHEARTED.
HE WAS ALWAYS A VERY GENTLE BOY.
PERHAPS HE WASN'T SUITED
FOR THE LIFE OF A DEMON SLAYER.
- I'M SORRY TO BRING UP
SUCH PAINFUL MEMORIES.
IT MUST BE HARD FOR YOU
TO TALK ABOUT IT.
- NO. IT'S ALL RIGHT.
BEFORE HE DIED,
KOHAKU REVERTED BACK
TO HIS OLD SELF.
I STILL MOURN FOR HIM,
BUT THAT THOUGHT HELPS EASE
THE PAIN OF HIS LOSS.
WE WERE BOTH
STRONG DEMON SLAYERS.
I'M PROUD OF THAT.
WE ALL HAVE OUR REASONS
FOR BEING HERE, DON'T WE?
WHY ARE YOU GATHERING
THE SACRED SHIKON JEWEL SHARDS.
- UH, UM, UH,
I FIGURED IT WAS
THE LEAST I COULD DO
AFTER WHAT HAPPENED.
- SO YOU BROKE THE JEWEL?
- I'M SORRY. I KNOW.
I REALLY BLEW IT.
- I'M SURE YOU WERE JUST TRYING
TO RETRIEVE IT FROM A DEMON,
SO IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
WHAT'S AMAZING IS,
YOU'RE THE REINCARNATION
OF A PRIESTESS.
- THAT'S THE PART I DON'T GET,
BUT I DO UNDERSTAND,
WE NEED TO GATHER
THE JEWEL SHARDS,
AND WE DO THAT BEST
BY JOINING FORCES.
WITH NARAKU'S APPEARANCE,
THINGS HAVE GOTTEN
A LOT MORE COMPLICATED.
- IN ORDER TO BREAK THE CURSE
OF THE SHIKON JEWEL,
WE MUST DESTROY NARAKU FIRST.
- MM-HMM.
- DID YOU FOLLOW
THE DEEPER POINTS
OF OUR CONVERSATION,
YOU PEEPING TOMS?!
[YELPING]
- HUH?
- A MONKEY.
- UH, HEY, WHAT'S
WITH ALL THE RUCKUS?
[PUNCHING]
OW!
- HMM.
- HMPH.
- THIS TIME, YOU ACTUALLY WERE
IN DEEP CONVERSATION
AND RUSHED TO HELP.
- WHY DO THEY HAVE TO
SUSPECT ME, TOO?
- IT WAS WORTH THE PAIN.
THAT WAS A WONDERFUL SIGHT
WE JUST SAW.
- EVERYONE HAS BEEN DRAWN
INTO THE CURSED WEB
OF THE SACRED SHIKON JEWEL,
BUT I FEEL SORRY
FOR SANGO THE MOST.
SHE SAW HER FATHER
AND HER YOUNGER BROTHER
BEING KILLED.
- ALL RIGHT. TIME TO GO.
[GRUNTING]
KAGOME, WHAT DO YOU HAVE
IN YOUR BAG, ROCKS?
IT'S WAY HEAVIER
THAN IT WAS BEFORE.
- I HAVE A TEST NEXT WEEK,
SO I BROUGHT AS MANY BOOKS
AS I COULD CARRY.
- IT MUST BE HARD FOR YOU.
- MIROKU SAYS YOU SHOULD JUST
GIVE UP ON SCHOOL THIS YEAR
AND FLUNK A GRADE.
- DON'T TELL ME MIROKU
THINKS SO, TOO.
MY BROTHER SOTA'S
ONLY IN ELEMENTARY,
AND HE SAYS THINGS LIKE,
"IF YOU FLUNK 6 TIMES,
"THEN I'LL BE
IN THE SAME GRADE AS YOU,
AND I CAN HELP YOU STUDY,
AND WE CAN GRADUATE TOGETHER."
HE'S SUCH A LITTLE GEEK.
HE THINKS HE'S SO HOT.
OHH!
- I BET HE ACTS TOUGH
AND PRETENDS TO BE COCKY,
BUT HE HATES TO BE LONELY,
AND HE CRIES EASILY.
HE'S A VERY GOOD BOY,
THIS LITTLE BROTHER OF YOURS.
- [SIGHS]
HMM.
- [GRUNTS]
HEY. LOOK. SOMEBODY'S COMING.
- HUH?
- [GRUNTING]
- INUYASHA, HURRY!
- HE'S NOT BREATHING.
HE SEEMS NOTHING MORE
THAN A SIMPLE VILLAGER.
- THOSE WOUNDS WEREN'T
MADE BY A SWORD.
- HE'S NOT THE ONLY ONE
WHO'S BEEN KILLED AROUND HERE.
- HUH?
THE AIR IS FILLED
WITH THE THICK SMELL OF BLOOD,
AND THE BLOOD IS FRESH.
THERE'S BEEN A SLAUGHTER.
- A MASSACRE.
- IS ANYONE LEFT ALIVE?
- LET'S FIND OUT WHAT HAPPENED.
WE'LL SPLIT UP AND SEARCH.
- GOOD IDEA.
- HOLD IT.
HMM.
[ALL MOANING]
DON'T MOVE AN INCH.
TRAPS ARE SET EVERYWHERE.
ONE STEP, AND YOUR LEG
MIGHT BE BLOWN OFF.
- W-W-WHAT?
TRAPS ARE BURIED UNDERGROUND?
- BESIDE ALL THE DEAD BODIES?
- PROBABLY.
- I'VE NEVER HEARD
OF ANYTHING SO CRUEL.
- IF YOU TRY TO HELP
OR BURY THE DEAD,
YOU GET BLOWN UP, TOO.
- THIS HEARTLESS BASTARD
DOESN'T DESERVE TO LIVE!
LET'S FIND HIM
BEFORE HE MAKES ANOTHER MOVE.
- INUYASHA,
IT'S DANGEROUS TO WALK.
- HUH! IF HE THINKS
I'M THE KIND OF GUY
WHO'S JUST GONNA
STAND STILL AND TAKE IT,
HE'S GOT ANOTHER THING COMING.
HUH! AAH!
UNH!
IS HE THE ONE?
- HE COULDN'T HAVE KILLED
ALL THE VILLAGERS.
HE'S JUST A YOUNG BOY.
- IMPOSSIBLE.
- LOOK AT THE CHAIN HE'S GOT
AND ALL THE BLOOD ON HIS BODY.
HE'S COVERED IN IT.
THE KID'S GONE INSANE!
YOU MASSACRED A VILLAGE.
WHY DID YOU DO THIS?
WHAT ARE YOU AFTER? HEY!
- KOHAKU?
- HIS OUTFIT IS LIKE SANGO'S.
HE'S A DEMON SLAYER.
[MEOW]
- KIRARA RECOGNIZES HIM,
BUT HOW?
IT CAN'T BE KOHAKU.
- WHAT DID SANGO JUST SAY?
- HUH? GET BACK HERE!
UNH! AAH!
DAMN IT!
- KIRARA!
[ROARS]
GO!
- WHAT? A SPIRIT SHIELD.
- KOHAKU, I THOUGHT
YOU WERE DEAD.
- ALL RIGHT. WE'RE HERE.
GET OFF MY BACK.
- SO YOU SAW BOTH OF THEM
ENTER THE SPIRIT SHIELD
AND PASS THROUGH?
- YEAH.
KAGOME, ARE YOU SURE?
MAYBE SHE MUMBLED
SOMETHING ELSE BACK THERE.
- I'M ABSOLUTELY POSITIVE.
SANGO CALLED OUT THE NAME
OF HER BROTHER--KOHAKU.
SHE TOLD ME EARLIER
THAT KOHAKU HAD BEEN KILLED
IN THE CASTLE OCCUPIED
BY NARAKU.
- DID YOU NOTICE HE HAD
A SACRED SHIKON JEWEL SHARD
IMBEDDED IN HIS BACK?
WE'VE EXPERIENCED
THAT ONE BEFORE.
- IT'S NARAKU'S SAME OLD TRICK.
HE FORCED SANGO TO FIGHT
AGAINST HER WILL
IN THE SAME MANNER.
- DO YOU THINK NARAKU
IS MANIPULATING KOHAKU
THE SAME WAY?
- SANGO'S PROBABLY AWARE
OF WHAT'S GOING ON,
BUT THEN WHY DID THE SHIELD
ALLOW HER TO PASS THROUGH?
I'VE GOT A BAD FEELING
ABOUT THIS.
[PURRING]
- LET ME SEE YOUR FACE.
[GASPS]
KOHAKU. YOU'RE ALIVE, KOHAKU!
- ARE YOU HAPPY TO SEE
YOUR BROTHER ALIVE?
- HUH?
- IT HAS BEEN SUCH
A LONG TIME, SANGO.
- NARAKU!
- HA HA HA!
AREN'T YOU GOING TO THANK ME?
- HA! FOR WHAT?
- I SALVAGED YOUR BROTHER'S LIFE
AFTER HE WAS FELLED
BY THOSE ARROWS
AT THE CASTLE.
KOHAKU'S LIFE SHOULD HAVE
ENDED RIGHT THEN AND THERE
AS HE LAY BLEEDING,
BUT I SAVED HIM.
YOU HAVE ALREADY
PERSONALLY EXPERIENCED
THIS KIND OF SALVATION.
IT IS THROUGH THE POWER
OF THE SHIKON JEWEL.
WHEN YOU HAD THE SHARD
INSIDE YOUR BACK,
YOU WERE ABLE TO FIGHT INUYASHA,
AND YOU WERE
HIS EQUAL IN BATTLE.
- SILENCE!
- NOW KOHAKU POSSESSES
THAT SAME POWER.
HE STANDS BEFORE YOU
AS AN EQUAL WARRIOR
BECAUSE OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
IF IT IS EXTRACTED FROM HIM,
HE WILL SURELY DIE.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND, SANGO?
THINK THROUGH YOUR ACTIONS.
KOHAKU'S LIFE IS IN YOUR HANDS.
BRING ME THE TETSUSAIGA,
INUYASHA'S PRECIOUS SWORD.
ONLY THEN SHALL I LET
KOHAKU HAVE ETERNAL LIFE.
HA HA HA!
- I WON'T BE BRIBED!
UNH!
KOHAKU, WHY ARE YOU PROTECTING
THAT DEMON--NARAKU?
- I'VE ERASED ALL
OF KOHAKU'S MEMORIES OF YOU
AND HIS FORMER LIFE
IN THE VILLAGE.
A FIGHTING MACHINE HAS
NO NEED FOR FEELINGS.
THEY WOULD ONLY GET IN THE WAY.
HE SLAUGHTERED
AN ENTIRE VILLAGE BY HIMSELF.
YOU SHOULD BE PROUD
OF YOUR LITTLE BROTHER.
HE HAS BECOME A VERY FINE
DEMON SLAYER.
- DAMN YOU!
POISON GAS! UNH!
- YOU WILL BRING ME
THE TETSUSAIGA.
- UNH!
- I WILL BE WAITING
FOR YOU, SANGO.
- [SIGHS]
- HUH?
- IT'S SANGO.
SANGO, WAS THAT BOY
YOU WERE CHASING
YOUR LITTLE BROTHER?
DID YOU GET A CHANCE
TO TALK WITH HIM?
- THAT BOY WAS NOT MY BROTHER!
- SORRY, SANGO.
- WELL, THE MAIN THING IS,
YOU'VE RETURNED UNHARMED.
SANGO, THIS WHOLE INCIDENT
WITH THE TRAPS AND BARRIER--
TELL ME, WAS IT NARAKU
WHO WAS BEHIND IT ALL?
- MM-HMM.
- I SEE.
THEN YOU MUST BE EXHAUSTED
FROM THE ENCOUNTER.
LET'S RETURN TO THE VILLAGE
AND GET SOME REST, OK?
- WAIT, MIROKU.
I BEG YOU,
PLEASE PERFORM A SERVICE
TO HONOR AND COMMEMORATE
THE DEAD.
- HMM.
- THAT'S THE LAST ONE.
YOU'RE AMAZING KIRARA.
GROWING UP IN THE SLAYERS'
VILLAGE PAID OFF.
YOU MANAGED TO SNIFF OUT
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF THE TRAPS.
WE'LL GET SANGO TO SAFELY
DESTROY THESE SOMEWHERE LATER.
NOW THEN, I'LL GO TELL EVERYBODY
ABOUT WHAT YOU MANAGED TO DO.
HUH? HEY, KIRARA,
WHERE DID YOU GO?
KIRARA? KIRARA?
- SO WHAT DO YOU MAKE
OF IT ALL, MIROKU?
- WHAT'S THAT?
- ABOUT HER MEETING UP
WITH NARAKU.
I WONDER WHAT SANGO AND NARAKU
ENDED UP TALKING ABOUT.
- HE PROBABLY TOLD SANGO
THAT HE WAS MANIPULATING
HER BROTHER LIKE A PUPPET.
- HE TRIED TO GET SANGO
TO FIGHT KOHAKU!
NARAKU IS UNFORGIVABLY CRUEL!
- SANGO CAN'T SLAY
HER OWN BROTHER.
LET'S LEAVE HER ALONE
FOR A WHILE,
LEAVE HER WITH HER THOUGHTS
UNTIL SHE'S READY
TO TALK TO US ABOUT IT.
- WELL, YOU CAN'T JUST
LET HIM OFF THE HOOK.
SO WHAT IF HE'S NARAKU'S PUPPET
WITH A JEWEL SHARD IN HIS BACK?
KOHAKU'S RESPONSIBLE
FOR SLAUGHTERING AN ENTIRE TOWN.
IF SANGO CAN'T KILL HIM,
THEN I'M GONNA HAVE TO
TAKE HIM DOWN.
HEY, SANGO, YOU GOT
A PROBLEM WITH THAT?
- UH, INUYASHA, I CAN'T BELIEVE
HOW UTTERLY INSENSITIVE
YOU CAN BE.
SANGO, WAIT UP!
- DON'T KNOW WHAT WE'RE
GOING TO DO ABOUT HIM.
DO WE KILL HIM?
- OF COURSE!
- NO MATTER WHAT?
- YEAH. THINK ABOUT IT.
NARAKU SENT SANGO'S
ZOMBIE-SHARD-PUPPET BROTHER
BECAUSE HE THOUGHT
WE'D BE TOO SENTIMENTAL
AND TOO WIMPY ABOUT IT
TO KILL HIM OFF,
AND THERE'S NO WAY
I'M GONNA FALL FOR THAT!
- HMM. I CAN SEE YOU'RE
REALLY TORN UP ABOUT IT.
- SHUT UP, MIROKU! GET LOST!
I'M IN A LOUSY POSITION.
NOBODY ELSE WILL TAKE
CARE OF THIS EXCEPT ME,
BUT I FEEL BAD FOR SANGO.
- UNH!
DID IT! UNH!
- KOHAKU, YOU'RE NOT
TRYING HARD ENOUGH.
- HUH? HEY, KIRARA.
COME ON NOW. CUT THAT OUT.
- HOW'S THE WOUND?
- HEY, SANGO.
- ROUGH TRAINING.
- ROUGH FOR ME, THAT IS.
I HAVE SUCH A LONG WAY TO GO.
- FATHER TOLD ME HE'S
BEEN WATCHING YOU,
AND HE THINKS YOU'RE GETTING
BETTER EVERY DAY, KOHAKU.
- REALLY?
- REALLY.
- THAT'S THE FIRST TIME
I'VE EVER HEARD
OF FATHER PRAISING ME.
HA HA! MAKES ME FEEL
KIND OF EMBARRASSED.
HA HA HA!
- I MADE HIM FORGET.
I ERASED ALL THE MEMORIES
OF HIS LIFE.
- KOHAKU DIDN'T REACT AT ALL
WHEN HE SAW ME.
HAS HE TRULY FORGOTTEN
EVERYTHING ABOUT ME,
ABOUT HIMSELF?
NO. HE DOESN'T EVEN KNOW
THAT NARAKU IS OUR SWORN ENEMY.
I WON'T ALLOW NARAKU
TO MANIPULATE KOHAKU.
I MUST RESCUE HIM
FROM NARAKU'S EVIL GRIP.
- BRING ME THE TETSUSAIGA,
INUYASHA'S PRECIOUS SWORD.
ONLY THEN SHALL I LET
KOHAKU HAVE ETERNAL LIFE.
- I MUST STEAL THE TETSUSAIGA
IN ORDER TO SAVE
MY BROTHER--KOHAKU.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- NARAKU TOLD SANGO TO STEAL
INUYASHA'S SWORD IN EXCHANGE
FOR HER BROTHER'S LIFE?
NARAKU IS THE ABSOLUTE
WORST SCUM OF THE EARTH.
KOHAKU IS BEING USED
IN THE WORST WAY,
BUT WE CAN'T FIGHT HIM
AND RISK KILLING HIM.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO
ATTACK THE CASTLE
AND DESTROY NARAKU
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
EVEN I'M ANGRY ENOUGH
TO DO IT NOW.
NEXT TIME:
"TETSUSAIGA IS STOLEN!
SHOWDOWN AT NARAKU'S CASTLE!"
SEE YOU SOON!