>> HERE WE COME.
IT'S THE START OF "INUYASHA."
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL
THE SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY NARAKU
WITH MY TETSUSAIGA.
>> INUYASHA DEFEATS BANKOTSU,
ENDING THE LONG BATTLE WITH
THE BAND OF 7.
NARAKU USES THE SACRED JEWEL
SHARDS AND FINALLY REVEALS HIS
NEW FORM.
>> IT'S UP TO ALL OF US.
>> TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FEUDAL FAIRY TALE.
>> "INUYASHA."
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> AAH!
>> [SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
AAH!
>> [CHUCKLING]
>> [GRUNTING]
>> [SCREAMING]
>> THANK YOU, KIRARA.
>> DON'T WORRY.
I'VE GOT YOU, KAGOME.
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> INUYASHA!
INUYASHA!
[THINKING] INUYASHA, WHAT
HAPPENED TO YOU?
[ALOUD] INUYASHA!
INUYASHA!
>> [GROANING]
KAGOME?
>> THANK GOODNESS.
>> AH, YOU IDIOT!
WHY DID YOU COME IN HERE AND PUT
YOUR LIVES IN DANGER?
>> CAN YOU BLAME ME?
>> I TOLD YOU TO WAIT OUTSIDE
FOR ME.
YOU SHOULD'VE LISTENED.
>> HMPH.
[STRAINING]
DON'T BE MAD AT ME.
I WAS WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
>> HUH?
HA, I CAN TAKE CARE OF MYSELF
JUST FINE.
WHAT'S YOUR STORY, WOLF?
I KNEW I COULDN'T TRUST YOU.
HUH?
WHAT HAPPENED TO THAT MANGY
WOLF?
WHERE IS HE?
>> UH, KOGA WAS SWALLOWED INTO
THESE WALLS OF FLESH.
>> [THINKING] WHAT?
HE WAS DEVOURED?
THAT'S WHY YOU HAVE TO GET OUT
OF HERE.
THE SOONER THE BETTER.
>> YEAH.
[STRAINING]
DAMN, I CAN'T BUDGE.
HUH?
GET OUT OF HERE, KAGOME.
>> HUH?
>> [CHUCKLING]
>> I KNOW THAT VOICE.
>> NARAKU!
>> [LAUGHING]
>> DID HE SAY NARAKU?
>> IMPOSSIBLE!
[THINKING] WHAT AN UNBELIEVABLY
EVIL AURA.
HOW COULD IT POSSIBLY COME FROM
NARAKU?
>> [STRAINING]
>> INUYASHA!
>> HAVING TROUBLE MOVING,
ARE YOU, INUYASHA?
>> NARAKU, YOU BASTARD!
>> [GASPING]
>> [GROWLING]
>> YOU'VE DONE WELL TO SUCCEED
IN GETTING HERE.
OR SO I'D SAY UNDER DIFFERENT
CIRCUMSTANCES.
BUT IT'S ALREADY TOO LATE.
YOU ARE ALREADY HOPELESSLY
ENTANGLED IN MY INTESTINES.
IT'S ALL OVER FOR YOU.
>> YOU THINK SO?
THEN YOU MUST BE DREAMING.
I'LL TELL YOU WHEN IT'S OVER.
IT'S OVER WHEN I RIP OUT YOUR
DAMN THROAT!
>> GOT THAT RIGHT!
TODAY'S THE DAY WE DESTROY YOU
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
NARAKU, YOU'RE DEAD.
>> SANGO, STAY AWAY FROM IT!
>> UNH!
THIS STUFF IS LIKE ACID.
WE'RE IN TROUBLE.
IT'LL DISSOLVE US IN NO TIME.
[GRUNTING]
>> SANGO!
>> [GRUNTING]
>> SHIPPO!
>> KAGOME!
>> AAH!
>> KAGOME! SHIPPO!
>> [SCREAMING]
>> FOOLS.
YOU STILL DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THE HOME OF MOUNT HAKUREI HAS
BECOME PART OF MY BODY.
IN OTHER WORDS, YOU ARE ALL
TRAPPED INSIDE ME.
HEH HEH HEH!
>> THESE FLESHY WALLS ARE PART
OF NARAKU?
>> KAGOME, ARE WE GOING TO BE
DEVOURED JUST LIKE KOGA WAS?
>> HEH HEH HEH.
DON'T BE SO CONCEITED.
THERE'S NO VALUE IN ABSORBING
THE LIKES OF YOU.
ESPECIALLY, A WEAK LITTLE DEMON.
>> HEY, DOES HE MEAN ME?
>> [GROWL]
>> NOT TO MENTION A HALF-DEMON
LIKE INUYASHA.
EVEN MORE SO A HANDFUL OF MERE
HUMANS.
DEVOURING YOU WOULD ONLY SERVE
TO WEAKEN MY BODY.
>> BANKOTSU!
>> BANKOTSU'S DEAD?
>> HA HA HA.
THE STUPIDITY OF HUMANS MAKES ME
UTTERLY SICK TO MY STOMACH.
EVEN VILLAINS LIKE BANKOTSU.
HE ARRIVED HERE DETERMINED TO
AVENGE HIS COMRADE'S DEATH.
AND HE FOUGHT WITH YOU,
INUYASHA.
I GAVE EACH MEMBER OF THE
BAND OF 7 A SINGLE SACRED JEWEL
SHARD.
WHEN BANKOTSU POSSESSED THEM
ALL, HE SHOULD'VE FORGOTTEN
ABOUT GETTING REVENGE AND FLED
WITH THEM.
YET HE DIDN'T.
>> [GROWL]
>> HA HA HA!
THEY PROVE THEMSELVES TO BE SUCH
FOOLS EVERY TIME, THESE MORTALS
CALLED HUMANS.
>> [GASP]
>> HA HA HA.
>> NARAKU, DAMN YOU TO HELL!
SURE, BANKOTSU MAY HAVE BEEN A
VILLAIN.
>> YOU KILLED ALL MY BAND OF 7
BROTHERS, SO NOW I'M GOING TO
AVENGE THEIR DEATHS.
>> HUH?
[GRUNTING]
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER, INUYASHA?
I'M GOING OUT OF MY WAY TO PUNCH
WITH THIS HAND TO MAKE IT EASIER
FOR YOU TO TAKE MY JEWEL SHARDS.
>> HE WAS EVIL, ALL RIGHT, BUT
HE WAS HUNDREDS OF TIMES MORE
DECENT THAN YOU, NARAKU!
AAH!
WIND SCAR!
BUT NARAKU, COMPARED TO HIM,
YOU'RE...
>> HA HA HA.
WHY ARE YOU SO RILED UP,
INUYASHA?
ULTIMATELY, YOU WERE THE ONE WHO
DEFEATED BANKOTSU.
>> SPARE ME THE LECTURES.
[GRUNT]
>> INUYASHA!
>> [GRUNTING]
>> HEH HEH HEH.
AT LONG LAST, I HAVE THEM.
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS BELONG
TO ME.
>> HMM.
[THINKING] THE SACRED JEWEL
SHARDS ARE MERGING INTO ONE.
SO, YOU FINALLY MADE YOUR MOVE,
NARAKU.
>> THERE'S NO MISTAKE.
IT'S HIS DEMONIC AURA.
>> PAGEN, UH, DID YOU SAY,
SOMETHING, LORD SESSHOMARU?
HMM?
>> [THINKING] NARAKU, HMM.
YOU FINALLY REAPPEARED.
>> HUH?
[THINKING] I'VE NEVER FELT SUCH
A STRONG DEMONIC AURA OTHER THAN
THAT AROUND LORD SESSHOMARU.
IF I CONTINUE TO GO WITH HIM,
I MAY WIND UP DEAD!
[ALOUD] LORD SESSHOMARU!
GOOD LUCK, MILORD.
[SLAP]
>> LET'S GO, JAKEN.
>> YES, MILORD.
>> IT HAS BEGUN.
>> WHAT'S BEGUN?
>> HOWEVER IT WILL SOON END.
>> HUH?
ARE YOU SURE WE DON'T NEED TO
WAIT?
>> KAGURA IS NO LONGER HERE.
>> HMM.
GOOD-BYE, MISS.
>> THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS ARE
JOINING TO FORM ONE BIG CLUMP.
>> [GROWL]
>> [GASP]
>> HUH?
>> [GRUNTING]
>> [GASPING]
>> [GROWL]
>> WHAT IS THAT?
>> NARAKU'S NEWLY FORMED BODY.
>> [SHIVERING]
>> NO, NO WAY.
>> HEH HEH HEH.
SUCH A PITY.
LOOK AT YOU.
EACH AND EVERY ONE OF YOU
DESPISES ME SO MUCH.
AND NOW THAT YOU'VE FINALLY
TRACKED ME DOWN, YOU CAN'T EVEN
LAY A FINGER ON ME.
>> YEAH, LIKE I'M TREMBLING IN
FEAR.
YOU WENT TO SO MUCH TROUBLE TO
HIDE YOURSELF IN SACRED GROUNDS,
I WAS EXPECTING YOU TO BE SOME
BIG SCARY MONSTER!
>> [THINKING] YOU'RE WRONG,
INUYASHA.
YOU SHOULD BE AFRAID OF HIM.
[ALOUD] INUYASHA!
NARAKU'S DEMONIC AURA HAS
CHANGED!
IT'S MUCH STRONGER THAN IT USED
TO BE!
>> DEMONIC AURA!
DON'T MAKE ME LAUGH!
>> AHH....
>> HA! AS IF.
HE'S JUST BECOME MORE WARPED
THAN BEFORE.
THAT'S THE ONLY THING THAT'S
DIFFERENT ABOUT THIS LOSER.
[GRUNTING]
>> INUYASHA!
>> [GRUNTING]
IRON REAPER SOUL STEALER!
[GRUNTING]
>> HA.
PATHETIC.
ONLY A FOOL WOULD DARE TO ATTACK
ME WITH BARE FISTS.
>> HA, YOU THINK SO?
IF IT'S A SWORD YOU WANT, I'LL
GLADLY CUT YOU TO SHREDS.
HMM.
COME, TETSUSAIGA.
NOW, PREPARE TO DIE.
[GRUNT]
IT'S OVER.
WIND SCAR!
UNH.
>> HA, ALWAYS THE FOOL.
>> HUH?
[THINKING] HE DEFLECTED THE
WIND SCAR.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> KAGOME!
>> AAH!
>> HOW COME MY WIND SCAR WON'T
SUBSIDE?
>> MIROKU, STAY BEHIND MY
HIRAIKOTSU.
>> WHAT IS GOING ON?
>> [CHUCKLING]
INUYASHA, I'VE TRAPPED YOUR
WIND SCAR IN THE FLOW OF MY OWN
DEMONIC AURA.
>> KAGOME, ARE YOU TWO OK?
>> MM-HMM.
>> STUPID INUYASHA!
YOU LET NARAKU GOAD YOU INTO
UNLEASHING THE WIND SCAR AND NOW
HE'LL TURN IT ON US.
>> SHUT UP.
>> AAH!
IT'S COMING AGAIN.
>> THE WIND SCAR WILL CONTINUE
TO CIRCLE IN HERE.
AT LEAST UNTIL YOU ARE ALL
SLICED TO PIECES.
IRONIC, ISN'T IT, INUYASHA?
TO THINK THAT THE UNLEASHING OF
YOUR OWN WIND SCAR IS WHAT WILL
CAUSE THE DEATH OF ALL YOUR
PRECIOUS FRIENDS.
HA!
>> [THINKING] A DEMONIC AURA IS
WHIRLING AROUND INSIDE MOUNT
HAKUREI.
HMM?
>> THAT'S KAGURA,
NARAKU'S INCARNATION.
SHE'S HOLDING SOMETHING.
>> HUH?
HMM.
WELL, IF IT ISN'T KIKYO.
>> STOP, KAGURA.
YOU WILL NOT BE THE ONE TO
DESTROY KIKYO.
>> [THINKING] WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
IT TALKS.
[ALOUD] AS YOU WISH.
HMM.
>> [THINKING] NARAKU, WHAT HAVE
YOU UNLEASHED?
>> [THINKING] KIKYO.
>> ]GRUNTING]
>> KAGOME, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> YEAH, MM-HMM.
>> [GRUNT]
[THINKING] WE'VE GOTTA
DO SOMETHING.
ANYTHING TO STOP THIS WIND.
>> [THINKING] HA, INUYASHA AND
HIS COMPANIONS SHALL DIE HERE.
AND AT LAST, I POSSESS A NEW
BODY.
THERE IS ONLY ONE THING LEFT TO
DEAL WITH.
>> NARAKU, ARE YOU TRYING TO RUN
AWAY FROM ME?
>> [THINKING] HUH?
THAT'S--
[ALOUD] GO AFTER HIM, INUYASHA!
>> KAGOME?
>> GO AFTER NARAKU.
>> YEAH, SURE.
WHAT ABOUT YOU, THOUGH?
>> I'M COMING ALONG WITH YOU.
>> HUH?
>> IF THIS WIND IS COMING FROM
NARAKU'S DEMONIC AURA, I MIGHT
BE ABLE TO DISPERSE IT.
AND ALSO, I SEE SOMETHING.
THERE ARE TWO SHIKON JEWEL
SHARDS AT NARAKU'S FEET.
>> TWO?
YOU MEAN THE WOLF'S?
>> I'M ALMOST POSITIVE.
KOGA IS A DEMON, SO NARAKU MIGHT
TRY TO ABSORB HIM INTO HIS BODY
TO GET THE JEWEL SHARDS.
>> [GROWL]
>> WE'VE GOT TO SAVE HIM.
>> HA, THAT'S ASSUMING THE GUY'S
STILL ALIVE.
>> [GRUNTING]
[SIGH]
HMM.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> HA, THEY MUST BE INSANE,
LEAVING DIRECTLY INTO THE WIND
SCAR.
HUH?
>> KAGOME, THE WHIRLWIND OF THE
DEMONIC AURA IS CENTERED AROUND
NARAKU.
>> HMM?
>> STAY FOCUSED.
AIM YOUR ARROW STRAIGHT FOR
NARAKU AND TAKE HIM DOWN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
TAKE THIS!
>> HUH?
>> I HIT HIM.
OH, LOOK, IT'S KOGA!
>> HEH HEH HEH.
YOU BOTHER TO WORRY ABOUT A
FRIEND AT A TIME LIKE THIS?
YOUR UNFAILING STUPIDITY
THOROUGHLY DISGUSTS ME.
>> THE WIND SCAR HAS FINALLY
BEEN DISPERSED.
>> KAGOME DID IT.
>> IF YOUR COMRADES ARE SO
PRECIOUS TO YOU...
>> [GRUNTING]
>> WHAT NOW?
>> IT'S BREAKING UP.
>> [GRUNT]
OH, NO, A MIASMA!
>> HMM, I'LL SHOW YOU ALL
COMPASSION.
YOU CAN ALL REST TOGETHER IN
THE SAME GRAVE.
>> AAH!
>> HEH HEH HEH!
KIKYO, I SHALL BE SEEING YOU
SOON.
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> DON'T WORRY, KAGOME.
I'LL GET THAT SCRAWNY WOLF BACK
FOR YOU, I PROMISE.
>> INUYASHA GOES TO RESCUE KOGA,
AND AT THE SAME TIME, NARAKU
GOES AFTER KIKYO.
>> NARAKU, WHAT IS YOUR TRUE
OBJECTIVE?
>> THE BOTTOM OF THIS FISSURE IS
FILLED WITH MY MIASMA.
YOUR IMITATION BODY WILL NOT BE
ABLE TO ENDURE IT.
KIKYO, THIS WILL BE YOUR GRAVE.
>> NEXT TIME, "FAREWELL KIKYO,
MY BELOVED."
>> INUYASHA, YOU WERE THE ONE
WHO COULD NOT SAVE HER.