- THEY CALL ME SHIPPO,
THE FOX-DEMON OF JUSTICE.
FOLLOWED BY MY VASSALS,
INUYASHA AND OTHERS,
I ROAM THE COUNTRYSIDE,
CONQUERING EVIL DEMONS.
STRONG AS I AM,
EVEN I HAVE TO TAKE A BREAK
FROM TIME TO TIME
TO REST MY WEARY BODY.
BUT NOT FOR LONG,
BECAUSE TROUBLE ALWAYS BECKONS.
HMM?
[THUNDER]
[SHOUTING]
OH...A MESSAGE.
WHAT?
A CHALLENGE TO A DUEL?
"THUNDER-DEMON SOTAN"?
I HAVE BEEN CHALLENGED
TO A DUEL TO THE DEATH.
YES, IT WAS
JUST ANOTHER DAY
IN MY LIFE
AS A BRAVE WARRIOR.
[THUNDER]
- SOTAN, I HAVE DELIVERED
THE LETTER.
THE TIME HAS COME,
THE DAY FOR WHICH
I HAVE WAITED SO LONG.
SOTAN, I BEG YOU
TO DO YOUR UTMOST
AS THE SOUL SURVIVOR
OF THE THUNDER-DEMON TRIBE.
HEH HEH HEH!
- HMM...LET'S SEE.
"TO FOX-DEMON SHIPPO.
"TO UPHOLD
THE THUNDER-DEMON TRIBE'S HONOR,
"I CHALLENGE YOU
TO A DUEL TO THE DEATH.
"I WILL WAIT FOR YOU AT
RIMAI VALLEY TODAY AT SUNDOWN.
IF YOU FLEE, YOUR FRIENDS
WILL PAY WITH THEIR LIVES."
- IS THAT A CHALLENGE
TO A DUEL?
- UH! HMM?
- YOU KNOW, RIMAI VALLEY ISN'T
VERY FAR FROM HERE, SHIPPO.
- HEY, ISN'T THAT
THE SAME PLACE
THAT THE THUNDER BROTHERS
USED TO LIVE?
MAYBE THEIR RELATIVES.
- THEY'VE GOT GUTS,
SENDING A CHALLENGE LIKE THAT.
- HEY, WHO SAID YOU COULD
READ MY LETTER? HUH?
- DON'T YOU THINK
IT'S STRANGE, THOUGH?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- IF THE THUNDER-DEMON TRIBE
WANTED REVENGE,
THEIR ENEMY SHOULDN'T
BE YOU, SHIPPO.
IT SHOULD BE
INUYASHA THEY'RE AFTER.
HE'S THE ONE
WHO FOUGHT THE BROTHERS.
- YEAH. GOOD POINT.
- INUYASHA
IS A HALF-DEMON.
THEY PROBABLY FIGURE
HE'S NOT GOOD ENOUGH FOR THEM.
- WHAT?
- OW! OH...
- SO, WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
ARE YOU GONNA ACCEPT
THIS SOTAN PERSON'S CHALLENGE
TO A DUEL?
- THERE'S NO CHOICE.
I AVENGED MY FATHER'S DEATH.
SO IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE SOMEONE COMES AFTER ME.
THIS IS MY DESTINY
AS A BRAVE WARRIOR.
- HMM! LISTEN
TO THE BIG TALKER.
- YOU'RE JUST JEALOUS BECAUSE
I'M WAY BETTER THAN YOU ARE!
- AH...
- DO YOU WANT US
TO HELP YOU OUT, SHIPPO?
WE COULD MAKE IT
AFFORDABLE FOR YOU.
- JUST SAY THE WORD,
AND WE'LL BE THERE.
ALL I WANT IN RETURN
IS A LITTLE INTRODUCTION
TO A PRETTY GIRL.
- YOU TWO.
- HMM. I WON'T LIFT A FINGER,
EVEN IF YOU BEG ME.
- DON'T WORRY. I CAN HANDLE
THE THUNDER-DEMON TRIBE.
[THUNDER]
[WHIMPERING]
- THERE'S THE VALLEY WHERE
THE THUNDER BROTHERS LIVED.
- THAT'S ONE STRONG
DEMONIC AURA.
- YEAH. THERE'S NO SHORTAGE
OF LIGHTNING, THAT'S FOR SURE.
- DON'T BE SO PROUD.
JUST ASK THEM BOTH
FOR HELP, SHIPPO.
- I CAN'T DO THAT.
IF I DID, MY HONOR
AS A RECIPIENT OF THE CHALLENGE
WOULD BE DISGRACED.
- BOO!
- AAH!
- WHAT HONOR? YOU'RE ALREADY
SCARED OUT OF YOUR HEAD.
HUH?
- THIS ISN'T LOOKING GOOD.
- I AGREE.
- ME, TOO.
- SOTAN, WHAT
ARE YOU WRITING?
[SIGHS]
- KORYU, STOP FLOATING AROUND
AND COME HERE.
- OK.
[GROANING]
- THIS IS OUR STRATEGY
FOR DEFEATING SHIPPO.
I WANT YOU TO MEMORIZE IT
REALLY WELL.
- OUR STRATEGY?
DOES THAT MEAN
YOU AREN'T GOING TO FIGHT
FAIR AND SQUARE, SOTAN?
- AAH!
DO YOU HONESTLY THINK
THAT A LITTLE CHILD LIKE ME
HAS A CHANCE AGAINST
THOSE RUFFIANS?
- GOOD POINT.
- THIS MONK, NAMED MIROKU,
HAS A WIND TUNNEL
THAT SUCKS UP
EVERYTHING IN ITS PATH.
SANGO IS
AN EXPERT DEMON-SLAYER.
AND SHE HAS A DEMON FELINE
NAMED KILALA.
- I KNOW. I'M THE ONE
THAT DID ALL THE RESEARCH.
- ON TOP OF THAT, INUYASHA
AND KAGOME ARE EVEN WORSE.
HOW MANY DEMONS DO YOU THINK
HAVE FALLEN AT THEIR FEET?
I COULDN'T POSSIBLY SURVIVE
A BATTLE IF I FOUGHT FAIR.
AND THAT WOULD MEAN
THE ABSOLUTE EXTINCTION
OF THE THUNDER-DEMON TRIBE.
- IF YOU FEEL THAT WAY,
SHOULDN'T YOU JUST FORGET
THE DUEL AND LIVE IN PEACE?
- NO CHANCE!
THEY'RE MY WORST ENEMIES.
I MUST GET SHIPPO,
AT THE VERY LEAST.
- OH, BOY.
- STOP YOUR COMPLAINING
AND PUT THIS PLAN INTO ACTION,
BECAUSE THEY'RE ALREADY
CLOSING IN ON US.
- ALL RIGHT!
[TREMBLING]
- SHIPPO, SPEED IT UP.
JUST QUIT STALLING,
WOULD YOU?
- HEY, CALM DOWN,
INUYASHA.
HE'S RIGHT, SHIPPO.
YOU'D BETTER MOVE IT ALONG,
OR YOU WON'T MAKE IT THERE
BY SUNDOWN.
I MEAN, ISN'T THAT WHEN YOU'RE
SUPPOSED TO BE THERE?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
THE LETTER.
SAY, UH, KAGOME?
- HMM? WHAT IS IT?
- ARE YOU SURE
THIS SAYS SHIPPO?
- YEAH. WHY?
- LOOK AGAIN.
IT'S PRETTY SQUIGGLY.
IT DOESN'T SAY
INUYASHA?
- HUH?
- ARE YOU SAYING YOU CAN'T EVEN
READ YOUR OWN NAME?
- SURE, I CAN!
I WAS JUST DOUBLE-CHECKING, OK?
IT'S ME THEY WANT!
THEY'RE CHALLENGING ME!
[TREMBLING]
JUST WAIT, SOTAN.
I'M COMING.
- SHIPPO, YOU'RE NOT
GETTING ANYWHERE.
- GRR...
I CAN'T STAND IT!
- INUYASHA.
[SHIPPO STRUGGLING]
- GO AWAY, EVERYONE!
I DON'T NEED ANYONE'S HELP
THIS TIME, SO LAY OFF!
- EXCEPT TO GET THERE.
NOW KEEP IT MOVING, WOULD YOU?
- DON'T BE SO HARSH.
- KAGOME, YOU BETTER
TAKE COVER SOMEWHERE SAFE.
I'LL BE BATTLING SOMEONE FROM
THE DREADED THUNDER-DEMON TRIBE.
- ALL RIGHT.
- THE SAME GOES
FOR YOU TWO.
- HE'S PRACTICALLY BEGGING US
TO HELP HIM, MIROKU.
- YEAH. THAT'S OBVIOUS.
- WHY DOESN'T HE
JUST COME OUT AND ASK?
[STRAINING]
- FIRST, WE'RE GOING TO
SEPARATE SHIPPO FROM THE OTHERS
WITH A LARGE BOULDER.
[RUMBLING]
- HUH?
- KAGOME!
- LOOK OUT!
- SHIPPO!
- WHAT IS
THAT IDIOT DOING?
[SCREAMING]
- EXCELLENT. THINGS ARE GOING
JUST AS PLANNED.
- AAH! HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT AM I THINKING? TRANSFORM!
WHOA!
- OOH! SOMEBODY HELP ME!
- SHIPPO!
- OH, THAT KLUTZ.
- HE'S DONE FOR.
- DAMN, SHIPPO'S HOPELESS.
- HEY! LET ME
OUT OF HERE!
- HA HA HA!
WELCOME, SHIPPO.
[SHIPPO LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
- I'M NOT WASTING MY BREATH
ON SMALL FRY LIKE YOU.
WHO'S THE LEADER
AROUND HERE?
GET THE LEADER OF THE
THUNDER-DEMON TRIBE RIGHT NOW.
- THAT'S ME.
- WHAT?
YOU MUST BE KIDDING.
- I'M OBVIOUSLY THE LEADER.
CAN'T YOU TELL?
- UH, NO. THAT'S WHY I ASKED
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
THIS IS SO STUPID.
I DON'T HAVE TIME TO WASTE
ON A LITTLE KID LIKE YOU.
- SHUT UP! DON'T YOU
TREAT ME LIKE A CHILD!
- OH, YEAH?
[AHEM]
- WOW. THAT'S A VERY NICE
PLAYTHING YOU HAVE THERE.
CAN I PLAY WITH IT?
- SEE? I KNEW
YOU WERE A KID.
- OH, I AM NOT A KID!
AND BESIDES, YOU'RE ONE TO TALK!
- WHAT? I'M
A FULL-FLEDGED DEMON.
- SO AM I.
NOW GIVE THAT TO ME.
- NO WAY.
- GIVE IT TO ME.
- NO WAY!
- THEY'RE BOTH CHILDISH,
IF YOU ASK ME. AY!
- MOVE, KORYU. DON'T YOU HAVE
SOME THINGS TO DO?
- YES, I GOT
THINGS TO DO.
- HMM?
- WHERE'S THAT SMOKE
COMING FROM?
- NEXT, WE TAKE
THAT FELINE KILALA.
BIG OR SMALL,
SHE'S STILL A CAT.
SO SHE SHOULD GET INTOXICATED
ON THIS CATNIP.
- IT'S HARD WORK,
BEING THE BAD GUY ALL THE TIME.
[SNARL]
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, KILALA?
- YOU SMELL THAT?
IT'S CATNIP.
- YOU'RE NOT SERIOUS.
- WHOA!
- AAH!
[SNORES]
- LOOKS LIKE WE'VE FALLEN
INTO ANOTHER TRAP.
- WE'LL JUST HAVE TO
WALK FROM HERE.
[CRYING]
- HMM?
- WHAT SEEMS TO BE
THE TROUBLE, MISS?
- PLEASE FIND IT
IN YOUR HEART TO HELP ME.
- YOU'D BETTER
BE CAREFUL, MIROKU.
THIS IS PROBABLY
JUST ANOTHER TRAP.
- NOW, SANGO,
YOU KNOW I LIVE MY LIFE
ACCORDING TO
SACRED TEACHINGS,
AND I WILL NEVER TURN MY BACK
ON ANY PERSON IN NEED.
IF THIS IS INDEED A TRAP,
I WILL GLADLY FALL INTO IT.
- HOW INCREDIBLY SELFLESS
OF YOU, MIROKU.
- MIROKU'S WEAKNESS
IS WOMEN,
AND BECAUSE OF THAT,
SANGO NEVER LEAVES HIM ALONE.
THIS IS HOW WE'LL KILL
2 BIRDS WITH ONE STONE.
- OH, PLEASE, WON'T YOU
COME A LITTLE CLOSER?
- YES, OF COURSE.
IT WOULD BE MY HONOR.
- LISTEN TO ME, MIROKU.
PLEASE, STOP.
- NOW, REVEAL EVERYTHING--
- AAH!
[THUD]
- HEE HEE HEE! OOPSIE.
THEY FELL FOR IT.
- I TOLD YOU
IT WAS A TRICK.
THIS IS ALL
YOUR FAULT, MIROKU.
- MY APOLOGIES.
- LET ME OUT! I THOUGHT YOU SAID
YOU WANTED TO DUEL WITH ME!
- DON'T EVEN BOTHER
TRYING TO WASTE MY TIME, SHIPPO.
- WHAT'S THAT?
WASN'T IT YOU
WHO SENT ME THIS LETTER?
- YOU FOOL. THAT WAS JUST A TRAP
TO LURE YOU HERE.
- A TRAP?
SO, WHAT ARE YOU PLANNING
TO DO WITH ME?
- HEH HEH HEH. I'M GONNA
KILL YOU NICE AND SLOW.
- WHAT?
- HA HA HA!
GO AHEAD AND SCREAM.
THE LOUDER, THE BETTER.
- THE CREEP. GRR...
OH, I GET IT.
YOU'RE WEAK.
THAT'S WHY
YOU DON'T WANT TO FIGHT.
- I'LL HAVE TO ADMIT,
YOU'RE PRETTY SHREWD,
BUT I'M A GENIUS!
I'VE COME UP WITH
SOME BRILLIANT STRATEGIES
TO COMPENSATE
FOR MY DIMINUTIVE SIZE.
- THAT'S PLAYING DIRTY,
YOU COWARD!
- YOU'RE THE COWARD,
LOOKING TO YOUR FRIENDS FOR HELP
INSTEAD OF STANDING UP
FOR YOURSELF.
- I DID NOT ASK THEM FOR HELP.
THEY JUST CAME ALONG.
- SAVE THE EXCUSES,
WEAKLING.
- I'M NOT
A WEAKLING, COWARD.
- WEAKLING, WEAKLING,
WEAKLING, WEAKLING!
- COWARD! COWARD! COWARD!
COWARD! COWARD! COWARD! COWARD!
- WHAT ARE MIROKU
AND SANGO DOING?
- THEY'RE SURE
TAKING THEIR TIME.
- ALL RIGHT.
HERE THEY COME.
- INUYASHA IS HELPLESS
AGAINST KAGOME.
WE'LL GET HIM TO SIT.
- INUYASHA...
SIT!
- HMM?
- SIT! SIT! SIT!
SIT! SIT!
- HEY.
- OH, COME ON. WHY DOESN'T
KAGOME'S "SIT" WORK?
- DON'T TELL ME
THAT'S SUPPOSED TO BE ME?
- SHE'S IDENTICAL.
- HUH? SHE'S NOT IDENTICAL!
- I HOPE YOU'RE PREPARED
TO MEET YOUR MAKER.
[WHIMPERS]
- WELL, I SHOULD PROBABLY
BE GETTING BACK NOW.
- STOP! YOU'RE STAYING.
- I'D LOVE TO.
- WELL, DO YOU GIVE UP?
- HARDLY. YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S
GONNA HAVE TO SURRENDER HERE.
- I HAVE TO SAY,
YOU SURE HAVE BROUGHT ALONG
STRANGE WRITING TOOLS.
- THESE? KAGOME GAVE ME
THESE THINGS.
THEY'RE CALLED CRAYONS.
- WOW! I LOVE THEM.
GIVE THEM TO ME, WOULD YOU?
- NO WAY.
NOT A CHANCE.
- GIVE THEM TO ME, STINGY!
- LET'S SEE...IF YOU
LET ME OUT OF THIS PLACE,
I MIGHT RECONSIDER.
- HUH?
[HUMMING]
- SEE? ISN'T THIS BEAUTIFUL?
- I WANT! I WANT! I WANT!
I WANT! I WANT! I WANT! I WANT!
- THEN ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS LET ME OUT.
- YOU DON'T THINK I'M GONNA FALL
FOR THAT OLD TRICK, DO YOU?
I'M JUST GONNA KILL YOU
NICE AND SLOW.
- THEN HOW ABOUT WE DUEL,
AND THE WINNER
CAN HAVE THE CRAYONS?
- OH, YEAH.
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA!
- HA HA HA. THIS SOTAN
MIGHT BE A REAL DOOFUS.
- THAT'S WEIRD.
A FLYING SNAKE?
- DRAGON!
- DON'T FLATTER YOURSELF.
- OW.
- YOU'RE THE THUNDER-DEMON
FAMILIAR, AREN'T YOU?
- I BELONG TO THE HONORABLE
DRAGON CLAN! OW!
- QUIT TALKING SO BIG,
YOU SLIMY WORM.
- JUST ONE MORE TIME.
HEY, WHAT DO YOU THINK
MY HEAD IS MADE OF, ANYWAY?
- SHUT UP!
- EXCELLENT.
NOW I'LL MAKE MY ESCAPE.
- NOW, THAT'S ENOUGH HITTING
ALREADY, INUYASHA.
QUIT HURTING THE THING.
- STAY OUT OF THIS, KAGOME.
I DON'T NEED
YOUR STINKING PITY!
I BELONG
TO THE DRAGON CLAN!
SO GO AHEAD
AND HIT ME ALL YOU WANT!
- YOU KNOW, YOU'RE PRETTY BRAVE
FOR A LITTLE DRAGON.
- OOPS. I SHOULD HAVE SAID
I WAS A SNAKE.
- TELL US WHERE SOTAN IS.
WE KNOW SHIPPO'S
WITH HIM, ISN'T HE?
- OH, YEAH.
LIKE I'D TELL YOU PEOPLE.
- AH! WHY, YOU...
- OW! THAT'S IT.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- HA HA HA! SHOCKED?
WHEN MY HEAD IS STRUCK 3 TIMES,
I TRANSFORM
INTO A LIGHTNING CLOUD.
TAKE THIS, YOU FOOLS!
AND THIS! AND THIS!
AND THIS!
HA HA HA HA!
- WHY DIDN'T YOU
COME AT US FROM THE START?
HYAH!
- HA HA HA! IT'S USELESS.
IT'S USELESS.
- HUH?
- THE WIND STAR
WON'T WORK ON HIM.
- HA HA HA!
FAREWELL, INUYASHA.
YOUR TIME IS UP.
- THIS IS THE END
FOR YOU, SHIPPO.
- JUST WHAT I WAS
GONNA TELL YOU.
EN GARDE!
- TAKE THAT! AND THAT!
AND THAT!
- DAMN! WHAT NOW?
- THE WIND STAR
WON'T WORK ON A CLOUD.
- AAH!
- KAGOME!
- I'LL TAKE CARE
OF THE GIRL FIRST.
- AH!
- KAGOME!
UH!
OH, NO.
- INUYASHA!
INUYASHA!
- TAKE THIS!
- LIGHTNING ATTACK! AAH!
- WOW. YOU'RE
AN AWFUL LOT STRONGER
THAN I WOULD HAVE FIGURED.
- OF COURSE. I MEAN,
WHO DID YOU THINK
YOU WERE DEALING WITH HERE?
- ALL RIGHT, I'M GONNA
HAVE TO GET SERIOUS.
- HMM. SO AM I.
- HA HA HA. EVEN INUYASHA
IS HELPLESS AGAINST MY ARROWS.
[PANTING]
- INUYASHA,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- HMM?
- YOU'RE OK?
- SURE, I'M OK.
THOSE ARROWS ARE RIDICULOUS.
THEY DON'T EVEN HURT.
- HUH?
- WHAT? THAT'S ABSURD!
TAKE THAT!
- UH. HERE. JUST GIVE YOURSELF
A LITTLE POKE IN THE HAND.
- MMM...
- MMM! HA HA.
HEY, THAT FEELS GOOD.
THAT WOULD BE GREAT
ON MY STIFF SHOULDERS.
- I'M NOT GONNA STAY HERE
AND BE INSULTED.
- OH, NO. YOU'RE NOT
GOING ANYWHERE. UH!
- YOU CHANGE BACK
IF YOU'RE HIT 3 TIMES, RIGHT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- DON'T PLAY DUMB.
- OW! OW! OW!
OH, HOW CRUEL-HEARTED.
OH...AH!
- NOW, YOU LITTLE WORM,
YOU'RE GONNA TAKE US
TO THIS SOTAN PERSON.
- AAH!
- OH!
[RIP]
- YOU'RE GOOD.
- SO ARE YOU.
- FOX MAGIC,
SMASH IT ALL!
THUNDER MAGIC!
- JUST TRY AND STAVE OFF
MY WEEPING MUSHROOMS!
- YOU JUST TRY AND FIGHT OFF
MY LAUGHING ACORNS!
- HEY, SOTAN, ISN'T IT
ABOUT TIME YOU GAVE UP?
- YEAH, YOU'RE ONE
TO TALK.
WHICH MEANS MORE TO YOU--
YOUR LIFE OR YOUR CRAYONS?
- SHIPPO!
- OH, INUYASHA!
YOU'RE ALIVE!
- INUYASHA!
- KORYU, DID YOU FAIL
IN YOUR MISSION?
- PLEASE FIND SOME WAY
TO FORGIVE ME, SOTAN.
- HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
DON'T TELL ME THIS IS--
- YEAH, THIS IS SOTAN,
THE ONE WHO SENT ME
THE CHALLENGE.
- HE'S ADORABLE!
HA HA HA!
- HEY! WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I--AAH!
- THAT'S A GOOD BOY.
- DON'T TREAT ME
LIKE A CHILD!
I'M THE LEADER
OF THE THUNDER-DEMON TRIBE!
- SURE YOU ARE.
- DON'T TOUCH THE HAIR, OK?
DON'T TOUCH THE HAIR.
- YOU MEAN TO TELL ME THAT WE'VE
BEEN RUNNING AROUND IN A PANIC
BECAUSE OF SOME
LITTLE KID?
- I TOLD YOU GUYS
I DIDN'T NEED ANY HELP.
- SUCH A CUTE BOY.
- DON'T INSULT ME!
I'M NOT A BOY! I'M A GIRL!
- HUH?
- YOU'RE A GIRL?
THAT'S EVEN CUTER.
- OH! DON'T MESS
WITH MY HAIR, I SAID.
CUT IT OUT! LET ME GO!
- A GIRL?
THAT'S A GIRL? NO WAY!
OH, THIS IS STUPID.
I'M GOING HOME.
- HEY, WAIT, SHIPPO.
ARE YOU RUNNING AWAY FROM ME?
IF YOU LEAVE,
YOU'RE ADMITTING DEFEAT.
- OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
HERE. YOU CAN HAVE THESE.
- HUH?
- HMM? AH.
- BE A GOOD KID
AND BEHAVE YOURSELF, OK?
AND DON'T YOU EVEN THINK
ABOUT VENGEANCE ANYMORE.
AND SO, MY BATTLE
HAD ENDED.
I HAD SUCCEEDED
IN OVERCOMING A VENDETTA,
AND THAT EVIL, CONNIVING DUO--
SOTAN AND KATYU--
LEARNED THEIR LESSON
AND WOULD NEVER
CHALLENGE ME TO A DUEL AGAIN.
[HUMMING]
- HMM...HMM...
HA HA HA.
- WITH THIS EXPERIENCE,
I HAVE GROWN EVEN MORE MATURE.
MANY ENEMIES
STILL LAY AHEAD,
WAITING TO TEST
MY STRENGTH.
I COULD NOT STAND IDLE
OR LOOK BACK.
YES, THIS WAS THE PATH
OF A WARRIOR LIKE MYSELF,
WHOSE DESTINY
WAS TO FIGHT.
- QUIT PUTTING ON THE ACT.
- OW! KAGOME,
INUYASHA'S PICKING ON ME!
- INUYASHA!
- WAIT! KAGOME, DON'T!
[SHIPPO CRYING]
- SIT!
- SERVES HIM RIGHT.
- WHAT'S WITH THIS GUY?
- SORRY, INUYASHA.
I TOLD EVERYONE ABOUT YOU,
AND THERE'S BEEN
A HUGE MISUNDERSTANDING.
- THERE'S NO TIME
FOR THAT.
ANOTHER NARAKU INCARNATION
HAS SHOWN UP.
- WITH ALL THE CONFUSION
ABOUT YOU, THOUGH,
NOW THEY THINK YOU'RE
SOME DELINQUENT BIKER THUG.
- THIS GUY GOES AROUND KILLING
PEOPLE AND STEALING THEIR FACES.
NEXT TIME...
TERROR OF THE FACELESS MAN.
BY THE WAY, KAGOME,
WHAT'S A BIKER?