>> HERE WE COME.
IT'S THE START OF "INUYASHA."
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL THE
SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY NARAKU WITH
MY TETSAIGU.
>> EVENTS WHICH OCCUR AT MOUNT
HAKUREI CAUSE THE SACRED
MOUNTAIN'S BARRIER TO COLLAPSE
AND RETURN INUYASHA'S DEMONIC
POWERS.
THE TIME FOR THE FINAL SHOWDOWN
BETWEEN INUYASHA AND JAKOTSU HAS
COME.
>> IT'S UP TO ALL OF US.
>> TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FEUDAL FAIRY TALE.
>> "INUYASHA."
♪♪
>> I'LL TAKE THOSE DOG EARS OF
YOURS AS A SOUVENIR, THOUGH.
>> YEAH, RIGHT.
UH!
UHH! UH!
>> HA HA HA!
ONCE I PULL ON THIS SWORD,
YOU'LL BE SLASHED INTO PIECES.
>> GRR.
>> BYE-BYE, INUYASHA.
OF ALL THE MEN WHO HAVE DIED BY
MY SWORD, I HAVE TO SAY, I LIKE
YOU THE BEST.
>> GRR! YOU FOOL!
IT'S A LITTLE TOO SOON TO PULL,
JAKOTSU!
>> [GASP]
>> WINDSCAR!
>> UH!
>> GRR!
AHH, IT'S OVER.
>> [COUGHING]
>> HUH?
YOU STILL NOT DEAD, JAKOTSU?
>> INUYASHA, WHAT ARE YOU
WAITING FOR?
JUST FINISH ME.
I DON'T MIND DYING BY YOUR HAND,
INUYASHA.
[COUGHS]
>> NO.
>> ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
IF YOU DON'T KILL ME NOW, I'LL
JUST COME AFTER YOU AGAIN.
YOU SHOULD KNOW BY NOW HOW
STUBBORN I CAN BE.
>> FINE, THEN.
I'LL JUST KILL YOU WHEN I SEE
YOU NEXT.
>> [SOBS]
>> THIS IS NARAKU'S SCENT, AND
IT'S COMING FROM THE SAME
DIRECTION AS THESE DEMONS.
NARAKU IS IN THE CORE OF THIS
MOUNTAIN.
>> OH, THAT INUYASHA--SUCH A MAN
OF PRINCIPLES.
SO CUTE, THOUGH.
NNGH. NNGH!
[CHUCKLES]
I GUESS THIS IS IT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF JAKOTSU OF
THE BAND OF SEVEN, HUH?
>> NOT TOO MUCH.
>> OK. THIS IS IT, MEN.
>> [GASP]
YOU REALLY THINK SO?
HA HA HA!
>> AAH!
>> IS THAT REALLY YOU AS A
MORTAL?
YOU'RE AS CUTE A HUMAN AS YOU
ARE A HALF-DEMON.
WHAT THE HECK?
I DID HAVE A LOT OF FUN.
>> FORGIVE ME, JAKOTSU.
>> MM.
>> THOUGH IT IS ONLY ONE MORE, I
STILL NEED YOUR SHIKON JEWEL
SHARD, JAKOTSU.
I WILL USE WHATEVER MEANS ARE
NECESSARY TO ENSURE THAT I
REMAIN ALIVE.
[INSECT FLAPPING AND BUZZING]
>> IT'S CLOSE.
WHATEVER IT WAS, IT ESCAPED
MOUNT HAKUREI.
HUH? A BARRIER?
AND IT'S PURE BARRIER, THE SAME
KIND THAT SURROUNDS MOUNT
HAKUREI.
SO THEN IS THIS THE PERSON WHO
CREATED THE BARRIER?
HUH?
DEMONIC AURA IS SEEPING OUT OF
THE BROKEN BARRIER, AND IT'S
NARAKU'S DEMONIC ENERGY.
YOU SEEM TO BE ONE WHO WAS MOST
VIRTUOUS DURING HIS LIFETIME.
>> FIRST A MONK, NOW A
PRIESTESS.
SO DO YOU ALSO PURSUE NARAKU?
>> TELL ME, DID NARAKU HIDE
HIMSELF DEEP INSIDE THE BARRIER
YOU CREATED?
>> YOUR GAZE IS INTENSE,
PRIESTESS.
ARE YOU ATTEMPTING TO LOOK DEEP
WITHIN MY HEART?
>> I DO NOT EVEN HAVE TO TRY.
YOUR HEART IS PLAIN FOR ME TO
SEE.
>> IT IS ALL RIGHT FOR YOU TO
HATE THEM.
WHAT DID THEY DO?
THEY REVERED YOU AS A SAINT AND
CALLED YOU HOLY AND MADE YOU
PROMISE TO BECOME A LIVING
BUDDHA, THE FOOLS.
THEN THEY BURIED YOU ALIVE IN
SOLITARY DARKNESS.
HATE THEM.
HATE THEM ALL, THE HUMANS OF
THIS WORLD.
>> DO YOU SCORN ME?
I, A SAINT WHO SAVED PEOPLE AND
FORGAVE THEIR SINS, BECAME THE
ONE WHO WAS LOST AND DIED
SUFFERING.
THEN NARAKU, A DEMON, CAME TO ME
AND SAVED MY SOUL.
>> YOUR SOUL WAS SAVED?
IF SO, THEN WHAT IS THIS
SADNESS, THIS GREAT SADNESS
WHICH PERMEATES THE BARRIER?
>> I WAS NOT TRULY A SAINT.
WHILE ON THE BRINK OF DEATH, I
CAME TO THAT REALIZATION.
>> AND AT THAT MOMENT, HIS SOUL
BECAME LOST.
THEN NARAKU CAME TO THE SOUL
WHICH WAS LOST IN THE DARKNESS
AND GAVE IT PURPOSE, BUT HATING
PEOPLE AND PROTECTING THE EVIL
DEMON NARAKU--WAS THAT REALLY
WHAT YOUR HEART DESIRED?
YOUR SOUL WILL NOT FIND
SALVATION BY KEEPING THIS
TAINTED BARRIER AROUND YOU AT
THE BEHEST OF NARAKU.
IS THERE TRULY ANYONE IN THIS
WORLD WHO HAS NOT DOUBTED OR WHO
HAS NEVER SINNED AT ALL?
>> THE PEOPLE ALL REVERED ME AS
A SAINT, SO I WAS RESOLVED TO BE
ONE.
>> I WAS LIKE YOU WHEN I WAS
STILL ALIVE.
I TRIED TO LIVE WITHOUT DOUBT,
WITHOUT MISTAKES.
>> AH, SO I WAS RIGHT.
YOU, TOO, ARE DEAD.
>> IT IS TRUE, AND THAT IS WHY I
CAN UNDERSTAND THE PAIN YOU ARE
FEELING.
TO DOUBT IS TO BE HUMAN.
HUMANS TRY TO BE DIVINE, TO BE
FREE OF DOUBT.
>> I COULD NOT BECOME A LIVING
BUDDHA.
MY ATTACHMENT TO CORPOREAL LIFE
SENT MY SOUL TO HELL.
>> DO NOT BE ASHAMED THAT YOU
YEARNED FOR LIFE.
IT IS NO CAUSE FOR DAMNATION,
AND SO I ASK YOU TO PLEASE
DISSOLVE THIS BARRIER.
>> WHY ARE YOU ASKING THIS OF
ME?
>> BECAUSE I HOPE THAT YOU WILL
ALLOW ME TO TOUCH YOUR SOUL.
>> AND THEN YOU WISH TO LAY ME
TO REST, YOU WHO ARE A DEAD
PRIESTESS.
>> WHAT ARE THESE VIBRATIONS?
THEY'RE ALMOST LIKE HEARTBEATS.
HMM?
WITH EACH PULSE, NARAKU'S SCENT
BECOMES STRONGER.
YOU'RE HERE, AREN'T YOU, NARAKU?
I FINALLY FOUND YOU.
>> DOES THIS MEAN NARAKU IS
STARTING TO MOVE?
JAKOTSU'S SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
SHALL I USE IT?
WHETHER I RUN AWAY OR STAY TO
FIGHT...
I INTEND TO SURVIVE.
>> THERE'S SOMETHING STRANGE
ABOUT MOUNT HAKUREI.
THE BARRIER IS BECOMING
UNSTABLE.
COULD SOMETHING HAVE HAPPENED TO
INUYASHA AND THE OTHERS?
>> WHAT IS IT, KAGOME?
>> IT'S NOTHING.
>> LISTEN, KAGOME.
IF THERE'S ANYTHING I CAN DO,
THEN PLEASE TELL ME.
>> KOGA IS FINALLY MAKING HIS
MOVE.
>> OH, BOY, I'VE REALLY GOT TO
SEE THIS.
>> INUYASHA IS INSIDE THE
BARRIER.
>> AND KAGOME IS ALL ALONE.
>> NOT QUITE SPORTING, BUT IF
HE'S GONNA WOO HER, THIS IS THE
PERFECT TIME.
>> GO FOR IT, KOGA.
>> WELL, THEN...
>> KAGOME...
>> HUH?
>> PLEASE TAKE CARE OF SHIPPOU
AND KILALA.
>> HMM?
>> SOMETHING IS WRONG.
I HAVE TO GO CHECK OUT THE
BARRIER.
>> KAGOME? HEY, WAIT A SECOND!
>> HA HA HA!
>> KAGOME.
>> INUYASHA, MIROKU, SANGO,
PLEASE BE SAFE.
>> GET OUT OF MY WAY!
YOU, TOO!
>> HUH?
BANKOTSU.
>> OH, SO YOU'RE STILL ALIVE,
RENKOTSU.
>> YES.
DAMN THAT BANKOTSU.
HE HAS THE SHARDS FROM KYOKOTSU,
MUKOTSU, AND SUIKOTSU.
THAT MAKES 4 IN ALL.
THE SHARDS I TOOK FROM KAGOME
ARE EMBEDDED IN HIS HALBERT
BANRYUU.
I HAVE 3 SHARDS WITH THE ONES
FROM KINKOTSU AND JAKOTSU.
IF I CAN KEEP BANKOTSU FROM
USING HIS HALBERT, WE'LL BE JUST
ABOUT EVEN.
IF I'M GOING TO DO IT, IT HAS TO
BE NOW.
UGH.
UHH...
>> THAT'S TWO.
SO RIGHT, RIGHT.
YOU STILL HAVE ONE MORE, DON'T
YOU?
>> DAMN YOU!
>> YOU KNOW, FOR A SMART GUY,
YOU SURE CAN BE STUPID.
YOU KEPT PLOTTING AND PLANNING,
BUT YOU WAITED TOO LONG TO ACT.
>> WILL YOU KILL ME?
>> WELL, WHAT SHOULD I DO?
AFTER ALL, YOU KILLED JAKOTSU
FOR A SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
>> WHO THE HELL ARE YOU TO TALK?
IN THE END, ALL THAT COUNTS IS
POWER, AND THE MORE SHARDS YOU
HAVE, THE STRONGER YOU BECOME.
>> [CHUCKLES]
>> WHAT'S SO FUNNY ABOUT THAT?
DON'T FORGET THAT YOU HAVE
SACRED JEWEL SHARDS IN YOUR
BODY, TOO, BIG BROTHER, AND YOU
USED US TO GET THEM FOR YOU.
>> LET'S PUT YOUR THEORY TO THE
TEST.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> HERE.
>> HUH?
>> TAKE THEM.
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
>> UH...UH...
>> HMM?
AW, DON'T WORRY.
I WON'T EVEN USE BANRYUU.
>> HUH?
>> NOW I WILL DEMONSTRATE JUST
HOW DIFFERENT YOU AND I ACTUALLY
ARE.
WELL, WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
LET'S DO IT.
IF YOU WON'T ATTACK, THEN I'LL
COME AT YOU FIRST.
>> AAH!
>> AAH! DIE!
UH! GAH! GAH! GAH!
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER, RENKOTSU?
YOUR AIM IS NOT SO GOOD.
>> UH...UH...AAH!
>> NOW WHAT?
YOUR BALANCE ISN'T SO GOOD,
EITHER?
GET ON YOUR FEET SO THAT I CAN
KILL YOU.
>> DAMN IT!
>> HA! I THINK I GOT HIM.
>> OH, YEAH?
WELL, THINK AGAIN.
>> AAH!
UHH...
WHA--
WHAT IS THE DIFFERENCE?
UGH...WHAT IS IT?
TELL ME.
HOW IS WHAT I'VE DONE ANY
DIFFERENT THAN WHAT YOU ARE
DOING NOW?
>> THE DIFFERENCE IS, I WOULD
NEVER BETRAY MY FRIENDS.
HOW SAD.
IT SEEMS NOW THAT I'M THE ONLY
ONE LEFT.
[FLAPPING AND BUZZING]
I KNOW.
I'VE GOT THINGS TO FINISH.
THIS WILL BE THE FINAL BATTLE
FOR THE BAND OF SEVEN.
>> THERE.
I'VE DISSOLVED THE BARRIER AS
YOU ASKED OF ME, PRIESTESS.
YOU SAID YOU WANTED TO LAY ME TO
REST AND DISSOLVE THE BARRIER
AROUND MOUNT HAKUREI, DID YOU
NOT?
HOWEVER, I WAS BURIED ALIVE, AND
NOW MY SOUL IS FILLED WITH ANGER
AND HATRED.
I FEAR THAT IT CANNOT BE SAVED.
>> YOU WERE WRONG.
I NEVER SAID THAT I HAD THE
ABILITY TO SAVE YOUR SOUL FROM
THE DARKNESS.
>> HUH?
>> BUT I DO WANT YOU TO TELL ME,
WHAT IS IT THAT MAKES YOU SO
UNBEARABLY SAD?
>> SAD, YOU SAY?
[SOBBING]
>> EVEN THOUGH I TOUCH YOUR VERY
SOUL, I CANNOT FEEL THE HATRED
AND BITTERNESS YOU SPEAK OF.
>> HATE THEM.
IT'S ALL RIGHT FOR YOU TO HATE
THEM.
HATE THEM ALL, THE HUMANS OF
THIS WORLD.
>> BUT I--
>> THE TEARS YOU SHED WERE NOT
TEARS OF HATRED TOWARD HUMANS
AND THEIR WORLD.
>> YES. YOU'RE RIGHT.
I WANTED TO DIE AN ADMIRABLE
DEATH AS A SAINT, BUT IT WAS NOT
TO BE.
I DID NOT WANT TO ADMIT MY OWN
WEAKNESS.
SO I CRIED IN DESPAIR, ALL FOR
THE WEAKNESS OF MY OWN HEART.
>> HOW PAINFUL IT MUST HAVE
BEEN.
>> YES. IT WAS PAINFUL.
>> YOU HAVE DONE MORE THAN
ENOUGH GOOD IN THIS WORLD, SO
PLEASE LET YOUR SOUL BECOME
FREE.
>> IS THAT ALL RIGHT?
>> YES. IT'S ALL RIGHT.
>> OHH...
>> THERE IS NOT ONE PERSON IN
THIS WORLD WHO NEVER FEELS LOST,
WHO HAS NEVER SINNED IN LIFE.
THOSE WHO TRY TO BE FOREVER
DIVINE, THOSE WHO TRY TO BE
FOREVER KIND, AND EVEN THOSE WHO
ARE TAINTED BY EVIL--EVERYONE
WISHES TO BE SAVED.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, KANUSKE?
HE HAS FOUND PEACE.
[RUMBLING]
MOUNT HAKUREI.
THE BARRIER.
IT'S BEEN DISSOLVED?
>> OH, NO.
THOUSANDS OF DEMONS ARE SWARMING
OUT OF MOUNT HAKUREI.
>> LORD SESSHOMARU.
LORD SESSHOMARU.
THE MOUNTAIN!
>> THEY'RE COMING!
AAH!
>> RRGH...UH!
>> KOGA!
>> IF ANYTHING WERE TO HAPPEN TO
YOU, THAT GOOD-FOR-NOTHING MUTT
WOULD NEVER LET ME HEAR THE END
OF IT, HMM?
>> HA!
>> ALL RIGHT. COME ON.
>> COME ON OUT AND SHOW
YOURSELF, NARAKU!
AAH!
>> INUYASHA, YOU WON'T ACTUALLY
BE MEETING NARAKU...
>> GRR.
BECAUSE YOU AND I HAVE A SCORE
TO SETTLE.
>> GRR. BANKOTSU. GRR.
♪♪
>> ALL THOSE PURSUING NARAKU ARE
GATHERING IN MOUNT HAKUREI, BUT
BEFORE THAT, INUYASHA HAS ONE
MORE BATTLE TO FIGHT.
>> BANKOTSU, ARE YOU TRYING TO
GET IN MY WAY?
>> OF COURSE.
YOU KILLED MY BROTHERS IN THE
BAND OF SEVEN.
I'M GOING TO AVENGE THEM.
>> CAN'T YOU SEE THAT NARAKU IS
JUST USING YOU?
>> NEXT TIME: "FINAL BATTLE:
THE LAST AND STRONGEST OF THE
BAND OF SEVEN."
>> I DON'T CARE ABOUT ORDERS.
SETTLING MY SCORE WITH YOU COMES
FIRST.