[COW MOOS]
- MYOGA, MY FRIEND, YOU'D
BETTER NOT BE DECEIVING ME.
HAS THIS INU-SOMETHING-OR-OTHER
REALLY MANAGED TO MASTER
THE TETSUSAIGA?
- HIS NAME IS INUYASHA.
- OH, THAT'S RIGHT! INUYASHA.
HE'S THE SON OF THE GREAT
DOG DEMON WHO GAVE ME HIS FANG
SO THAT I COULD FORGE
A SWORD FROM IT.
HE'S THE RUNT OF THE LITTER,
CORRECT?
- YES. HE'S THE YOUNGER BROTHER,
AND YOU'D BETTER
LEARN SOME RESPECT.
I'VE SEEN HIM KILL 100 DEMONS
WITH ONE SWING OF HIS SWORD.
- I WON'T BE ACCUSED
OF ABANDONING YOU.
I DON'T WANT NO GUILT TRIP.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA LAY
THAT RESPONSIBILITY ON ME!
AAH!
- MIND YOU,
I'VE ONLY SEE HIM DO IT ONCE,
AND HE HASN'T BEEN ABLE
TO WIELD THAT POWER SINCE.
- PERHAPS IT IS BECAUSE HE DOES
NOT DESERVE TO USE THE FAMOUS
TETSUSAIGA THAT I FORGED.
I SUPPOSE I WILL HAVE TO TEST
HIS WORTH SOMEHOW.
[WOLF HOWLS]
- HH-HOT! OOH OOH! OH OH! YAII!
- WHAT KIND OF HELLHOLE
IS THIS PLACE?
THE ROCKS UNDER MY FEET ARE RED.
MM! I SMELL
ROASTING MEAT SOMEWHERE.
HMM? OOH! EEH!
[WHIMPERING]
[SIZZLES]
- WHOA! OW!
[PANTING]
HUH?
HMM. THIS MUST BE IT.
ARE YOU HERE TOTO-SAI?
I HOPE YOU FINISHED THE SWORD
YOU WERE COMMISSIONED TO FORGE.
THIS IS THE PROMISED
DATE OF DELIVERY.
HMM. HEY, COME ON OUT!
I'M TALKING TO YOU.
HUH? OH!
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
YOU'VE MOVED?
DAMN THAT SNEAKY BADGER.
WHERE'D HE GO?
WHOA...
- SO, TOTO-SAI IS GONE.
- PLEASE FORGIVE ME,
MASTER SESSHO-MARU,
BUT THAT ERICAN SWORDSMITH IS
KNOWN TO BE VERY TEMPERAMENTAL,
AND HE ONLY FORGES SWORDS
IF HE TAKES A PERSONAL LIKING
TO THE CUSTOMER WHO ORDERED IT.
- I SEE.
HE HAS NO INTENTION OF FORGING
A SWORD THAT SUITS MY PURPOSE,
AND SO HE HAS ESCAPED.
- YOU CAN'T BLAME HIM
FOR NOT LIKING YOU.
YOUR RESUME IS ONE LONG
DEATH WISH. UHH! HUHH!
AAH! YOU'RE SMILING.
OH, DON'T SMILE AT ME,
MASTER SESSHO-MARU.
PLEASE GET ANGRY.
YOU'RE ALWAYS MUCH HARDER
ON ME WHEN YOU'RE BEING
PASSIVE-AGGRESSIVE.
PLEASE BE STRAIGHT
WITH ME, PLEASE!
HMM?
I THINK I'VE JUST SHORTENED
MY LIFE BY 100 YEARS.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
MY JEWEL SHARDS WERE TAKEN.
[GASPS]
- STOP WORRYING
ABOUT IT, KAGOME.
- BUT...
- IT'S NOT LIKE SHE STOLE
ALL THE PIECES OR NOTHING.
WE'LL JUST HAVE TO GO OUT
AND FIND SOME MORE.
NO BIG DEAL.
- HMM.
- WHY IS INUYASHA BEING
SO UNDERSTANDING?
IT'S SO UNLIKE HIM.
- I SUSPECT IT IS BECAUSE
KIKYO WAS THE ONE WHO STOLE
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
- OH, WHAT CAN HE DO
WHEN THE CULPRIT IS A WOMAN
HE'S BEEN IN LOVE WITH?
- LISTEN, YOU MORONS, IF YOU
THINK I'M PROTECTING KIKYO,
YOU'VE GOT ANOTHER THING COMING!
OK?!
YOU THINK I'M GOING
SOFT ON HER, TOO, DON'T YOU?
THEN SPEAK UP!
[GROWLS]
YOU GOT SOMETHING TO SAY,
THEN SAY IT TO MY FACE!
[COW MOOS]
- HUH?
- A COW?
- WHERE IS IT?
I DON'T SEE ANY CATTLE
AROUND HERE.
[MOOING]
- HUH?
[GASP]
- IN THE SKY?!
- AAH!
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- INUYASHA!
- WHO THE HECK ARE YOU?
- MY NAME IS TOTO-SAI.
DRAW YOUR SWORD, INUYASHA.
- HOW DOES THAT OLD GEEZER
KNOW MY NAME?
- I'M COMING AT YOU WHETHER
YOU PUT UP YOUR SWORD OR NOT!
HAAH!
- GET BACK, KAGOME.
- OK.
- UHH!
[GRUNTING]
HUH?
- HE THWARTED THE TETSUSAIGA
USING A HAMMER?
- OOH! THAT SWORD IS SINGING
LIKE AN OLD SAW--
DULL RESONANCE--THIS KID CAN'T
BE THE RIGHT ONE TO USE IT!
- TELL ME WHO THE HELL YOU ARE!
AAH!
HUH?
- HE STOPPED THE SWORD.
- THAT'S A PIECE OF LEATHER.
- YOU'VE BEEN TOO ROUGH
WITH HER; THIS BLADE IS
ALL NICKED UP.
HAVE YOU BEEN
CHOPPING DOWN TREES? HMM.
- WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT IT?
WHO ARE YOU?
- I THINK THAT'S ENOUGH,
TOTO-SAI.
- HUH? MYOGA?
SO YOU'RE THE SWORDSMITH
WHO FORGED TETSUSAIGA?
- PRECISELY!
I'M THE MAN WHO FORGED
TETSUSAIGA FROM A FANG
THAT YOUR FATHER GAVE TO ME.
ONLY CERTAIN CIRCLES OF THE
FINEST BLADE-SWINGING DEMONS
ARE ACQUAINTED WITH MY WORK.
- HUH? CERTAIN CIRCLES?
- I THINK THAT'S A POLITE WAY
OF SAYING HE'S NOT VERY FAMOUS.
- I DON'T GIVE A RAT'S ASS IF
YOU'RE FAMOUS OR NOT, OLD MAN!
- WELL, NOW THAT I'VE SEEN
THE TETSUSAIGA IN ACTION,
I HAVE TO SAY THE SWORD IS BEING
BADLY MISUSED AND ABUSED.
IT SINGS A SAD SONG INDEED.
TO SEE MY WORK LIKE THIS,
OH, IT SIMPLY BREAKS MY HEART.
- IF YOU'VE COME TO PICK A FIGHT
WITH ME, JUST SAY SO.
- INUYASHA!
- OH, THIS IS USELESS, MYOGA.
THE TETSUSAIGA CAN'T BE
ENTRUSTED TO SOMEONE
AS SHORT-TEMPERED
AS THIS ARROGANT WHELP.
- I SEE WHAT YOU MEAN.
IT WOULD PROBABLY BE BETTER
IF HE JUST GAVE UP THE SWORD,
THAN RECKLESSLY GOING
INTO BATTLE WITH IT,
BLINDLY TRYING TO RELY
ON A STRENGTH HE DOESN'T HAVE
THE SELF-DISCIPLINE TO YIELD.
- YES, THERE'S NO USE STALLING.
I'LL HAVE TO TAKE
THE TETSUSAIGA BACK IMMEDIATELY
AND BREAK IT IN HALF.
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
I DON'T CARE WHO MADE
THIS SWORD, YOU DRIED-UP
METAL BENDER.
IT'S MINE, AND I'LL RUN YOU
THROUGH WITH IT IF YOU EVEN
TRY TO BREAK IT!
- I DON'T HAVE TO BREAK IT.
IT WAS ONLY A THOUGHT.
[SIGHS]
- SORRY. I FORGOT TO
WARN YOU ABOUT HIS TEMPER.
- DON'T WORRY.
I'LL SNEAK IT AWAY
WHEN HE'S NOT LOOKING
AND MELT IT INTO CUTLERY.
AAH! I--I'M ONLY JOKING.
- MASTER INUYASHA, YOU HAVEN'T
BEEN ABLE TO UNRAVEL THE MYSTERY
OF THE TETSUSAIGA ON YOUR OWN.
YOU'VE TRIED, BUT YOU CAN'T
FIGURE OUT HOW TO TAP INTO
THE POWER THAT KILLED
THE 100 DEMONS IN ONE SWEEP.
BUT TOTO-SAI KNOWS ITS SECRET.
I THINK IF YOU BOTH TOOK
THE TIME TO GET TO KNOW
ONE ANOTHER AND COOPERATE,
YOU COULD AWAKEN AND HARNESS
TETSUSAIGA'S FULL STRENGTH.
- THERE'S NO MYSTERY.
I'LL GET THE HANG OF IT.
I JUST NEED PRACTICE.
- I UNDERSTAND YOU'VE BEEN
COLLECTING THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARDS FOR A WHILE.
WHO KNOWS HOW MANY DEMONS
HAVE MULTIPLE PIECES
OF THE JEWEL?
YOU KNOW HOW DIFFICULT
IT'S BEEN TO BATTLE DEMONS
WITH MORE THAN ONE.
DON'T YOU WANT TO AWAKEN
THE TETSUSAIGA'S FULL POTENTIAL
IN ORDER TO DESTROY DEMONS
WITH THAT ENHANCED STRENGTH?
- HE DOES HAVE A POINT,
INUYASHA.
- I THINK YOU SHOULD AT LEAST
HEAR WHAT HE HAS TO SAY.
- I GUESS IT CAN'T HURT.
[GRUNTS]
SO, TELL ME, WHAT DO
I HAVE TO DO, TOTO-SAI?
- FIRST, I HAVE TO TELL YOU
THAT SOMEONE SEEKS MY LIFE.
- HUH?
- A FOOL BARGED INTO MY FORGE
AND ORDERED A SWORD THAT WOULD
RIVAL THE POWER OF TETSUSAIGA.
HE TOLD ME HE'D KILL ME
IF I REFUSED.
I WANT YOU TO PROTECT ME
FROM HIM.
- SAY PLEASE BEFORE
ASKING FOR FAVORS.
- YOU NEVER TOLD ME
ABOUT THIS.
WHAT DID HE LOOK LIKE?
- HE HAS LONG, WHITE HAIR,
AND HE WEARS A CLOAK MADE OF
SOMETHING WHITE AND FURRY.
- WHAT? ANOTHER OLD GEEZER?
[RASPBERRY]
- GUESS AGAIN!
- WAIT A MINUTE.
IF HE'S YOUNG, DRESSED
IN FUR, AND WANTS A SWORD
STRONGER THAN TETSUSAIGA,
COULD HE BE...?
- HE--HE--HE'S HERE.
- HUH?
SESSHO-MARU.
- WHO IS THAT?
- INUYASHA'S OLDER BROTHER.
- I WAS RIGHT.
HE IS THE ONE WHO'S AFTER YOU.
- EXACTLY!
SO PROTECT ME!
- INUYASHA, WHY HAVE YOU
CONSPIRED WITH TOTO-SAI
TO PLOT AGAINST ME?
- BECAUSE YOU HAPPEN
TO BE EVIL INCARNATE?
- TOTO-SAI, IT SOUNDS LIKE
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR AN EARLY
RETIREMENT INTO YOUR GRAVE.
- I--I NEVER SAID I WAS
TALKING ABOUT YOU, SESSHO-MARU!
WHY DON'T WE DISCUSS
YOUR SWORD AFTER YOU BATTLE
IT OUT WITH INUYASHA?
- YOU SURE CHANGED YOUR TUNE
PRETTY QUICK.
YOU'RE NOT BIG ON LOYALTY.
- DID I? I DON'T REMEMBER.
- UHH!
- TOTO-SAI, YOUR WORD IS AS GOOD
AS A BLOOD VOW TO ME.
DID YOU HEAR THAT,
INUYASHA?
HE WILL FORGE MY NEW SWORD
AFTER I KILL YOU OFF.
- KAGOME, RUN FOR COVER.
[GASPING]
- OH, YEAH?
WE'LL SEE WHO KILLS WHO!
YAAAH!
- YOU CAN TELL BY THEIR TEMPERS
THEY'RE RELATED.
- YOU'RE THE ONE WHO STARTED
THIS WHOLE THING.
[GASPS]
- DID I, REALLY?
- HUH!
NO WONDER HE'S PALS
WITH MYOGA.
THEY'RE BOTH REAL PROS
WITH THE INNOCENT BYSTANDER ACT.
WHERE IS MYOGA?
MYOGA, ARE YOU HERE?
- KAGOME, HE'S
ON MIROKU'S SHOULDER.
HE ALWAYS GOES
WHERE IT'S SAFEST.
THAT MEANS IT'S DANGEROUS
OVER THERE.
- WHAT? OH, NO!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING? LET GO!
[GASPS]
HEY! YOU COWARD!
[GRUNTING]
- HUH?
- TOO SLOW.
[GRUNTING]
[COUGHS]
[ALL GASP]
- INUYASHA'S SO SLOW.
HE'S PATHETIC.
MYOGA, WHY DID YOU LIE TO ME
ABOUT HIS ABILITY TO USE
TETSUSAIGA'S FULL POWER?
- HE USED IT ONCE.
I PROMISE.
- MYOGA DIDN'T LIE.
INUYASHA ALWAYS ENDS UP
SENDING SESSHO-MARU HOME
WITH HIS TAIL BETWEEN HIS LEGS.
- ARE YOU SURE YOU WEREN'T
DREAMING WHEN YOU SAW HIM
DO THIS, YOUNG LADY?
- HAH!
- UHH! OOH.
- I'M NOT DREAMING IT UP.
IT'S TRUE!
- MY APOLOGIES.
- WELL, TOTO-SAI...
DON'T YOU FEEL SORRY
FOR TETSUSAIGA?
THAT FAMOUS SWORD IS NO BETTER
THAN A WOODEN CLUB
THE WAY INUYASHA SWINGS IT
AROUND LIKE A NEANDERTHAL.
A SWORD CAN LIVE OR DIE
DEPENDING ON ITS MASTER.
- MM-HMM.
A WISE OBSERVATION, I AGREE.
- STOP AGREEING WITH HIM!
- DON'T GIVE ME THAT,
SWORDSMITH,
OR YOU'LL REALLY HAVE
SOMETHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
I'M ONLY WARMING UP.
DON'T BE TOO SHOCKED
WHEN YOU SEE WHAT KIND
OF POWER I REALLY GOT!
HYAH!
[GRUNTING]
- OH, GREAT.
THE BLOOD'S RUSHED TO HIS HEAD.
THAT'S ALWAYS BAD NEWS.
- WELL, TOTO-SAI, TELL ME,
DO YOU STILL REFUSE
TO MAKE ME A SWORD?
- HMM...NO WAY!
- YAAH!
- THAT WAS A BIG HELP! HUH?
- SO, YOU ABSOLUTELY REFUSE?
- HMM! BE QUIET,
YOU UNGRATEFUL MONGREL!
YOU KNOW AS WELL AS I DO
I'VE ALREADY MADE YOU
AN EXCELLENT SWORD.
- HUH?
- THE FAMOUS SWORD THAT
YOU NOW WEAR--THE TENSEIGA.
I ALSO FORGED IT FROM A FANG
GIVEN TO ME BY YOUR FATHER.
HE CLEARLY INSTRUCTED
THAT THE ELDEST BROTHER
WOULD HAVE THE TENSEIGA,
AND THE YOUNGEST BROTHER
WOULD HAVE THE TETSUSAIGA.
THAT WAS YOUR FATHER'S
LAST WISH.
IT IS A GREAT SWORD OF SWORDS,
NO BETTER AND NO WORSE
THAN THE TETSUSAIGA.
YOU SHOULD LEARN
TO RESPECT AND LOVE IT.
- SO THAT OLD MAN ALSO MADE
SESSHO-MARU'S SWORD?
- THOUGH, COME TO THINK OF IT,
I'VE NEVER SEEN SESSHO-MARU
UNSHEATHE HIS SWORD
IN ANY OF THEIR BATTLES YET.
HAVE YOU?
- NO. YOU'RE RIGHT.
- DO YOU DARE IMPLY THAT THIS
USELESS SWORD IS WORTHY OF ME?
- OHH! I'VE MADE YOU ANGRY,
HAVE I? HA HA HA!
TIME TO TAKE OUR LEAVE.
AAH!
- THEY'VE ESCAPED.
- WOW! I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU HAD THAT KIND OF POWER.
- I'LL SAY.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
INUYASHA SHOULD BE
ASKING YOU FOR PROTECTION,
NOT THE OTHER WAY AROUND.
- YOU TRYING TO SAY
THAT I'M A WEAKLING?!
[SIGHS]
- HMM?
- SESSHO-MARU CALLS
HIS GREAT SWORD USELESS,
AND INUYASHA IS USELESS
WITH HIS GREAT SWORD.
HOW I OVERESTIMATED
BOTH OF THEM.
- WHAT'S THAT?!
[PUNCHES LAND]
- UHH...
- I AM NOT USELESS!
- TOTO-SAI, I'VE BEEN THINKING
ABOUT SESSHO-MARU'S SWORD.
IS IT REALLY AS POWERFUL AS
THE TETSUSAIGA, LIKE YOU SAID?
- THE TENSEIGA?
ITS ABILITIES ARE UNLIKE
ANYTHING I'VE HEARD OF BEFORE.
WHEN YOUR FATHER FIRST
COMMISSIONED ME TO MAKE IT,
I SHUDDERED AT THE VERY THOUGHT
OF ITS IMMENSE POWERS.
- IT'S A BLADE THAT DOESN'T CUT?
SO HOW ARE YOU SUPPOSED
TO FIGHT WITH A SWORD LIKE THAT?
- THE TENSEIGA IS NOT A SWORD
USED AGAINST FOES.
TO PUT IT SIMPLY:
IT IS A SWORD OF HEALING.
- HEALING?
- THE TETSUSAIGA IS A SWORD
THAT DEFEATS THE POWERFUL,
AND THE TENSEIGA IS A SWORD
THAT HAS THE ABILITY TO SAVE
THE LIVES OF THE WEAK.
- IT SAVES LIVES?
- IF THE BEARER TRULY
HAS KINDNESS OF HEART
TOWARDS HUMANITY,
THEN THE TENSEIGA HAS THE POWER
TO SAVE 100 PEOPLE IN ONE SWEEP.
- KINDNESS OF HEART?
- SO, THE TETSUSAIGA CAN SLAY
100 DEMONS IN ONE SWEEP,
AND THE TENSEIGA CAN SAVE
100 PEOPLE IN ONE SWEEP?
- BUT HOW ARE YOU ABLE
TO USE THIS SWORD AS A WEAPON?
- IT MUST HAVE THE ABILITY
TO BRING BACK DEAD SOULS.
SUCH A POWER COULD BE
VERY USEFUL DURING
THESE FEUDAL TIMES.
- I ALMOST CALLED THE SWORD
THE COFFIN-CHEATER,
BUT I OPTED FOR
TENSEIGA INSTEAD.
IT WAS A LITTLE MORE CLASSY.
ACTUALLY, IT WAS YOUR FATHER
WHO SUGGESTED THE NAME.
- I GET IT NOW.
NO WONDER SESSHO-MARU
WANTS A NEW SWORD.
HE CAN'T USE HIS.
HE'S INCAPABLE OF FEELING
KINDNESS FOR PEOPLE,
LET ALONE SAVING LIVES.
- TOO BAD THIS ISN'T WORKING.
IT WAS YOUR FATHER'S
LAST WISH, AFTER ALL.
- YOUR BROTHER'S
SO BLACK-HEARTED.
- HE WOULDN'T BE HAPPY
WITH THE SWORD EVEN
IF HE COULD USE IT.
- THAT SMELLS GOOD.
- OH, WELL, ROASTED PIG, INDEED!
LET'S DIG IN, FOLKS.
[ALL GASP]
- HEY! DON'T EAT
THE WHOLE THING, PIG!
- HUH? WHERE'D THE ROAST GO?
- IT'S IN YOUR GREEDY GUT!
- WHERE AM I RIGHT NOW?
WHO ARE YOU PEOPLE?
[CRASH]
- OOMPH!
[HOOTING]
- I DIDN'T REALIZE THAT
YOUR SWORD WAS ALSO YOUR
INHERITANCE FROM YOUR FATHER.
WHY DON'T YOU USE IT, MASTER?
WHAT KIND OF POWER DOES IT HAVE?
OOH, IT MUST BE
SOMETHING REMARKABLE!
- YOU WANT TO KNOW, JAKEN?
- THE IDEA OF 2 SWORDS FORGED
FROM YOUR FATHER'S FANGS
IS EXTREMELY INTRIGUING.
IT'S LIKE THE SWORDS
ARE 2 BROTHERS BORN
FROM THE SAME FATHER,
YET ONE IS POWERFUL
AND ONE IS USELESS.
AAH! I DON'T MEAN YOU'RE
USELESS, MASTER SESSHO-MARU!
I MEAN YOUR SWORD WAS,
OR AT LEAST I DON'T
SEE YOU USING IT,
AND YET THAT HALF-BREED BROTHER
OF YOURS CAN USE HIS,
WHICH MAKES HIM MORE POWERFUL.
OH, BUT DON'T TAKE THAT
PERSONALLY!
I'M SURE--
- JAKEN.
- YES, SIR?
[WHIMPERING]
MASTER SESSHO-MARU, WHY?
- GET UP, JAKEN.
YOU'RE FINE.
- HUH?
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
YOU JUST CUT ME IN HALF.
HOW CAN I BE ALIVE?
- YOU SEE NOW.
THIS USELESS TENSEIGA
CANNOT KILL.
- WHAT'S IT GOOD FOR, THEN?
[WHIMPERING]
WHAT'S GOING ON?
[GROWLS]
- AAH! A DRAGON!
- WHY DID MY FATHER BESTOW
THIS USELESS TENSEIGA ON ME,
AND YET BLESS INUYASHA
WITH THE TETSUSAIGA?
[GROWLS]
[JAKEN WHIMPERS]
- THIS DRAGON
HAS GIVEN ME A GIFT.
NOW I CAN GO BACK
AND CLAIM WHAT IS OWING TO ME.
TETSUSAIGA.
[GROANING]
- FAREWELL!
- YOU'RE LEAVING US?
YOU'RE HEADING OUT ALONE?
- WELL, INUYASHA'S
NOT MUCH PROTECTION FOR ME.
- COME ON.
- LET HIM GO.
WHO NEEDS HIM?
THE OLD GEEZER WOULD ONLY
SLOW US DOWN ANYWAY.
- HMM!
GIVE IT BACK.
THE TETSUSAIGA IS USELESS
IN YOUR HANDS.
IT WOULD BE BETTER OFF
AS SCRAP METAL.
- I TOLD YA,
DON'T TOUCH MY SWORD.
- INUYASHA!
- DON'T SAY I DIDN'T WARN YOU.
- HE'S NOT AFRAID
TO SPEAK HIS MIND.
- EITHER TOTO-SAI IS EXTREMELY
BRAVE OR HE'S EXTREMELY SENILE.
- THAT POOR LITTLE RUNT
OF THE DOG DEMON
IS GONNA GET HIMSELF KILLED
BY SESSHO-MARU.
HE HASN'T EVEN BEEN ABLE
TO SEE THE WIND SCAR THAT
AWAKENS TETSUSAIGA'S POWER.
- AREN'T YOU GONNA GO
AFTER HIM, INUYASHA?
AFTER ALL, HE IS THE ONE
WHO MADE TETSUSAIGA.
- HUH! YEAH, WELL,
THAT OLD FART IS FULL OF IT.
- HUH?
- HE'S BACK.
- AAAH! OOMPH!
- SESSHO-MARU!
- STAY WHERE YOU ARE,
OR I'LL TEAR YOU BOTH TO SHREDS.
[WHIMPERING]
DID YOU HEAR THAT?
I THINK WE'RE IN
BIG TROUBLE NOW.
- LISTEN, OLD MAN,
YOU'VE GOT NO INTENTION
OF MAKING SESSHO-MARU
A NEW SWORD, NOW, DO YA?
- NO.
- YOU HEAR THAT?
I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF THIS
BAD RAP OVER TETSUSAIGA,
AND NOW I'M ITCHIN'
TO USE IT AND FIGHT.
SO, LET'S SETTLE THIS
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
- HAVE NO FEAR.
- UHH!
- IT WILL ALL END TODAY.
YOU'LL NEVER HAVE
THE POWER TO BEAT ME,
NOT WITHOUT THE WIND SCAR.
[WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- INUYASHA'S FATHER HAS GIVEN
EACH OF HIS TWO SONS A SWORD.
BUT THE OLDER BROTHER,
SESSHO-MARU,
DOESN'T LIKE THE FACT
THAT INUYASHA HAS BEEN
GIVEN THE TETSUSAIGA.
THE MYSTERY OF THE WIND SCAR
IS FINALLY REVEALED TO INUYASHA
IN BATTLE WITH HIS BROTHER.
BUT SESSHO-MARU DRAWS
HIS SWORD, THE TENSEIGA.
IT'S THE SWORD OF LIFE.
SO, THEN, WHAT HAPPENS
TO SESSHO-MARU?
NEXT ON "INUYASHA..."
SEE YA SOON!