>> MY NAME IS KAEDE.
I AM AN ELDERLY PRIESTESS
WHO HAS SURVIVED A VIOLENT AGE
OF ENDLESS BATTLES.
KIKYO!
SISTER KIKYO, WHERE ARE YOU?
BACK THEN, I WAS AN INNOCENT
GIRL WHO KNEW NOTHING OF
FIGHTING OR WAR.
[PANTING]
KIKYO!
SISTER KIKYO!
>> STAND BACK, KAEDE.
>> HUH?
OH.
THAT WOMAN.
ISN'T SHE...
THE PRIESTESS NAMED TSUBAKI?
>> HMM. THAT YOUNG GIRL.
I ASSUME SHE MUST BE
YOUR LITTLE SISTER.
>> HMM.
>> YOU MIGHT WANT TO THINK
TWICE ABOUT THIS.
I AM PERFECTLY CAPABLE OF
HANDLING IT ALONE.
GO WITH YOUR SISTER
AND TAKE COVER.
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT US.
>> HOW TYPICAL OF YOU.
YOUR OWN SISTER MAY BE
IN DANGER.
YET, YOU REFUSE TO BACK DOWN
AND TAKE PROTECTION.
>> DEMONS!
>> YAH!
>> INCREDIBLE.
>> YOU'RE A COLD WOMAN, INDEED,
KIKYO.
NO. YOU ARE NOT A WOMAN.
YOU ARE A PRIESTESS.
>> YES, I AM A PRIESTESS.
THAT IS MY DESTINY.
>> [SNARLS]
>> SHE WAS A STRONG, PROUD,
BEAUTIFUL PRIESTESS.
IN MY YOUTHFUL EYES,
MY SISTER KIKYO WAS EVERYTHING.
OF COURSE, I WAS COMPLETELY
UNAWARE OF THE SAD FATE
THAT AWAITED MY SISTER.
>> CURSE YOU!
THIS IS NOT OVER!
NOT BY A LONG SHOT!
>> WHERE DID YOU GO?
WHERE ARE YOU, HALF-DEMON?
HUH?
>> RIGHT HERE.
IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
THAT'LL TEACH HIM A LESSON.
NO ONE DARES TO CALL ME
A HALF-DEMON AND LIVES
TO TELL THE WORLD ABOUT IT.
>> [HORSES NEIGHING]
>> PUSH HARDER.
>> GIVE ME A HAND WITH THIS.
[MEW]
>> NO. NO. THE OTHER SIDE.
>> CHIEF!
>> YES? WHAT IS IT?
IS SOMETHING THE MATTER?
>> IT'S THE LIMESTONE CAVE.
COME AND SEE FOR YOURSELF.
THERE'S SOMETHING WRONG
AT THE LIMESTONE CAVE.
>> OH?
>> CHIEF, YOU'RE HERE.
>> HAVE YOU SEEN ANYTHING
LIKE IT BEFORE?
>> HUH.
THIS IS ABSOLUTELY INCREDIBLE.
>> ANY IDEA WHAT'S CAUSING THIS,
CHIEF?
>> THERE'S NO MISTAKE.
IT HAS TO BE MIDORIKO.
>> MIDORIKO?
YOU MEAN, THE LEGENDARY
PRIESTESS WHO CREATED
THE SACRED JEWEL?
>> THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
SHE'S BEEN DEAD FOR HUNDREDS
OF YEARS.
>> WHERE'D THIS CORPSE
COME FROM?
>> THAT'S THE DEMON WE SLEW
2 DAYS AGO.
I THINK IT CALLED ITSELF
MISTRESS CENTIPEDE.
>> IT PUT UP QUITE THE FIGHT,
BUT WE SMASHED ITS HEAD IN.
SO IT SHOULD BE GOOD AND DEAD.
>> [MEW]
>> [GRUNTS]
>> CAREFUL, CHIEF.
WHAT IS IT?
>> A JEWEL.
THIS JEWEL MUST BE WHAT
MIDORIKO'S SOUL IS REACTING TO.
>> CHIEF, YOU DON'T THINK
THAT'S THE CRYSTAL?
>> YES.
I'M SEEING IT FOR THE FIRST
TIME, TOO.
THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> [MEW, GROWL]
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER, KILALA?
>> GIVE IT BACK!
>> RUN, MEN!
>> THAT BELONGS TO ME!
>> AAH!
>> NO! CHIEF!
>> GIVE BACK THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AAH!
>> CHIEF!
>> [SHOUTS IN JAPANESE]
>> CHIEF.
CHIEF, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> IT'S THE POWER OF
THE SACRED JEWEL.
AS LONG AS THIS JEWEL IS
SOMEWHERE NEARBY,
SHE'LL SENSE IT AND KEEP ON
REVIVING.
>> QUICK!
DON'T LET IT GET AWAY, KILALA!
>> [SNARLS]
>> DAMN IT!
WE CAN'T DO ANYTHING ABOUT
THIS TAINTED JEWEL WITHOUT
SOME KIND OF HELP--
A PRIESTESS.
UHH!
>> CHIEF, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> YOU OK?
>> FIND A PRIESTESS WITH
THE SPIRITUAL POWER TO PURIFY
THIS SACRED JEWEL.
>> MY SISTER KIKYO AND I
WANDERED THE COUNTRYSIDE
AS A PART OF OUR TRAINING
TO BE PRIESTESSES.
AND WE SLEW MANY TROUBLESOME
DEMONS.
>> ARE YOU CERTAIN YOU DON'T
WANT A REWARD FOR YOUR TROUBLES?
>> YES.
KEEP IT FOR YOURSELF, TSUBAKI.
>> VERY WELL, THEN.
I ACCEPT YOUR KINDNESS.
>> KIKYO, LET ME GIVE YOU
A PIECE OF ADVICE FROM ONE
PRIESTESS TO ANOTHER.
WHEN A PRIESTESS ABANDONS
ALL HUMAN FEELINGS, HER TRUE
POWER COMES ALIVE.
THEN AGAIN, FOR A WOMAN,
IT'S ONLY NATURAL TO FALL
IN LOVE.
>> FALL IN LOVE?
YOU THINK I WOULD FALL IN LOVE?
>> MARK MY WORDS.
YOU MUST NOT FALL IN LOVE.
NEVER ALLOW ANY MAN
TO DESIRE YOU.
FOR, IF YOU DO MEET SUCH A MAN,
YOU WILL DIE A VIOLENT DEATH.
>> [CHUCKLES]
I'LL KEEP THAT IN MIND.
>> HMM.
>> TSUBAKI IS UNSCRUPULOUS,
I'LL SAY THAT MUCH OF THE WOMAN.
>> HMM?
>> THAT WAS A CURSE
SHE JUST PLACED ON ME, KAEDE.
>> A CURSE?
>> IT'S OK.
THERE'S NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
IF THERE'S ONE THING I'M SURE OF
IT'S THAT I'LL NEVER
FALL IN LOVE.
>> YOU WON'T GET AWAY,
HALF-DEMON.
>> WE'LL AVENGE OUR OLDER
BROTHER'S DEATH.
>> [GRUNTS]
I WISH I'D KNOWN HE HAD
2 BROTHERS.
>> SO THAT'S WHERE YOU'RE
HIDING.
UHH!
YOU WON'T ESCAPE!
>> WE'LL SEE ABOUT THAT.
BLADES OF BLOOD!
>> AAH!
>> YAAR!
CURSE YOU, HALF-DEMON.
>> YOU GOT SOMETHING AGAINST
HALF-DEMONS?
>> HUH?
>> IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
>> AAAR!
>> [GRUNTING]
DAMN IT ALL!
HOW COULD I HAVE LET
THESE 2 WEAKLINGS GET TO ME.
I HAVE TO BECOME STRONGER.
I NEED TO BECOME WAY STRONGER.
>> [WHISPERING]
SHE'S COME BACK.
>> WELCOME HOME, LADY KIKYO.
>> LADY KIKYO, A DEMON SLAYER
CAME TO THE VILLAGE LOOKING
FOR YOU THIS MORNING.
WHEN I EXPLAINED THAT YOU
WERE AWAY, HE SAID HE'D RETURN
TONIGHT.
>> A DEMON SLAYER?
I WONDER WHAT HE WANTS WITH ME.
>> KIKYO, WE'D BETTER HURRY
INSIDE.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER, KIKYO?
WHAT IS THAT?
>> IT IS KNOWN AS THE JEWEL
OF FOUR SOULS.
I'VE BEEN GIVEN THE DUTY
OF PURIFYING IT.
>> THAT WAS THE FIRST TIME
I HAD LAID EYES ON THE SACRED
JEWEL.
AFTER SHE TOOK CUSTODY
OF THE JEWEL, MY SISTER KIKYO'S
DESTINY CHANGED DRASTICALLY.
OTHER GIRLS HER AGE
WERE BURNING PERFUMED INCENSE,
COLORING THEIR LIPS AND CHEEKS,
AND ENJOYING THEIR YOUTH.
>> [GRUNTS]
I HAVE TO HURRY, 'CAUSE
TONIGHT'S THE NIGHT.
[EXPLOSION]
HUH?
WHAT?
IT REEKS OF BLOOD.
>> [PANTING]
HMM.
>> A HUMAN.
IS THAT REALLY A WOMAN?
OH, NO. IT'S STARTING.
>> HOW LONG DO YOU INTEND
TO HIDE FROM ME UP THERE?
[THUNDER]
ARE YOU AFTER THE SACRED
JEWEL, TOO?
>> SACRED JEWEL?
NEVER HEARD OF IT.
>> IF YOU DON'T KNOW ABOUT IT,
THEN NEVER MIND.
IF YOU VALUE YOUR LIFE AT ALL,
I WARN YOU TO STAY AWAY FROM ME.
[THUNDER]
[GROANS]
>> SHE'S SOME PRIESTESS.
>> LADY KIKYO!
LADY KIKYO!
>> KIKYO!
>> SISTER KIKYO!
THERE SHE IS.
KIKYO!
>> LADY KIKYO!
>> KAEDE.
>> ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> YES.
[THUNDER]
HE DECIDED NOT TO KILL ME.
MUST BE MY LUCKY NIGHT.
>> IT'S AROUND HERE.
I KNEW IT.
THE SACRED JEWEL IS NEARBY.
I MUST FIND IT AND INCREASE
MY DEMONIC POWER BEFORE MY BODY
FAILS ME.
>> I GET IT NOW.
SO THAT'S WHAT IT'S ABOUT.
THE SACRED JEWEL, HUH?
IT'S WORTH LOOKING INTO.
THAT PRIESTESS'S NAME WAS KIKYO.
>> HEY, KIKYO.
>> HUH?
>> I HEAR THIS SO-CALLED
SACRED JEWEL IS A MYSTERIOUS
CRYSTAL THAT INCREASES
THE POWER OF A DEMON.
>> THAT VOICE.
I'VE HEARD IT BEFORE.
I REMEMBER.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO WAS HIDING
IN THE SHADOWS THE OTHER NIGHT.
>> SHUT UP!
JUST HAND OVER THAT SACRED
JEWEL.
HUH?
[GRUNTING]
>> I UNDERSTAND.
I THOUGHT I SENSED A DIFFERENT
AURA FROM YOU.
SO YOU ARE A MERE HALF-DEMON.
>> [GRUNTS]
>> WITH THE SACRED JEWEL,
YOU COULD BECOME A FULL-BLOODED
DEMON.
WOULD YOU GO THAT FAR TO FIND
YOUR PLACE IN THE WORLD,
HALF-DEMON?
DO YOU BELIEVE THAT IS
TRUE POWER?
>> I TOLD YOU TO SHUT UP.
I'LL BECOME THE STRONGEST
DEMON AROUND.
I'VE ALREADY MADE UP MY MIND.
AND WHEN I DO BECOME
A FULL-FLEDGED DEMON,
I'M GONNA PUT YOU OUT OF YOUR
MISERY.
>> HMM. TAKE MY WORD FOR IT.
THAT'S NEVER GOING TO HAPPEN.
NOT AS LONG AS I PURIFY
AND PROTECT IT.
>> DON'T MAKE ME LAUGH.
YOU TOTALLY REEK WITH THE STENCH
OF DEMON BLOOD.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
DID I TOUCH A NERVE,
HUH, KIKYO?
>> YOU'D BETTER STAY AWAY
FROM ME IF YOU DON'T WANT
TO BE KILLED.
THERE WILL BE NO THIRD CHANCE.
>> HA!
I'M NOT GIVING UP THAT EASILY.
GO AHEAD AND RUN.
YOU WON'T GET AWAY FROM ME.
WITH THAT BLOODY DEMON SMELL
ON YOU, YOU'LL BE EASY ENOUGH
TO FIND.
>> THE SMELL ON ME.
HUH.
YOU CAN COME OUT.
>> ARE YOU OK, KIKYO?
>> COME ON.
LET'S GO HOME, KAEDE.
>> OK.
>> HUH?
IT'S YOU AGAIN.
>> KIKYO, HAND OVER THE SACRED
JEWEL.
>> I WARNED YOU TO STAY AWAY
FROM ME.
>> AND I TOLD YOU THAT I WASN'T
GONNA GIVE UP SO EASILY.
WE ARE GONNA SETTLE THIS TODAY.
NOW, GET THAT KID
OUT OF THE WAY.
>> KAEDE, TAKE COVER
IN THE TREES.
>> ALL RIGHT, KIKYO.
>> A PRIESTESS THAT WALKS
A PATH TAINTED WITH BLOOD.
>> A BEING THAT IS NEITHER
HUMAN NOR DEMON,
A PITIFUL HALF-DEMON LOOKING
FOR HIS PLACE IN THIS WORLD.
>> HMM!
>> THERE IS SOMETHING
I WISH TO ASK YOU.
WHY DIDN'T YOU KILL ME
THAT NIGHT?
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN EASY ENOUGH,
GIVEN MY CONDITION.
>> I DON'T PLAY DIRTY.
THAT'S WHY.
>> [CHUCKLES]
I SEE.
>> WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
>> LET ME ASK YOU ONE MORE
THING: HALF-DEMON, WHAT NAME
DO YOU GO BY?
YOU MUST HAVE A NAME, EVEN
THOUGH YOU'RE JUST A HALF-DEMON.
>> HEY, LISTEN!
QUIT CALLING ME A HALF-DEMON,
WOULD YOU?
>> THEN TELL ME YOUR NAME,
AND I SHALL NEVER CALL YOU
HALF-DEMON AGAIN.
>> IT'S INUYASHA.
>> INUYASHA, YOU SAY.
I'LL REMEMBER THAT.
>> PREPARE TO DIE, KIKYO!
[GRUNTS]
HUH?
>> HMM.
>> WILL YOU STOP IT?
WHY DO YOU NEVER FINISH ME OFF?!
>> STOP COMING AFTER THE JEWEL.
I HAVE NO WISH TO WASTE
MORE ARROWS.
>> IT WAS A MYSTERY TO ME, TOO.
WHY DIDN'T SISTER KIKYO
FINISH INUYASHA OFF?
WHY DIDN'T SHE USE HER SACRED
ARROWS ON INUYASHA?
AROUND THAT TIME, KIKYO BEGAN
TO CLEANSE HERSELF EVERY DAY.
LOOKING BACK, I THINK IT BEGAN
FROM THE DAY SHE MET INUYASHA.
>> [SPEAKS JAPANESE]
KIKYO TOLD ME THIS HELPS
TO REDUCE SWELLING.
>> THE SACRED JEWEL!
>> AAH!
OHH!
HELP ME!
>> I SHALL TAKE YOU HOSTAGE
AND GET THE SACRED JEWEL
FROM THAT PRIESTESS KIKYO.
>> GET DOWN, KID.
YAAH!
HUH!
NO WAY WOULD I LET A WEAKLING
DEMON LIKE YOU STEAL THE SACRED
JEWEL FROM UNDER MY NOSE.
>> UM...
>> HMM?
>> THANK YOU FOR SAVING ME.
>> YOU GOT IT ALL WRONG.
I JUST DON'T WANT ANYBODY ELSE
TO HAVE THE SACRED JEWEL.
THAT'S ALL.
>> I WAS BAFFLED.
IF IT WAS THE JEWEL HE WAS
AFTER, THEN WHY DIDN'T INUYASHA
TAKE ME HOSTAGE LIKE MISTRESS
CENTIPEDE HAD INTENDED TO DO?
>> MY SISTER KIKYO HAD SENSED
THAT THE CORPSE OF MISTRESS
CENTIPEDE STILL CONTAINED
DEMONIC POWER.
>> THE POWER OF THE SACRED JEWEL
CANNOT POSSIBLY REACH HER
IN HERE.
INUYASHA, YOU'RE THERE,
AREN'T YOU?
WHY DON'T YOU COME DOWN?
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
WE'VE SPOKEN UP CLOSE.
>> SO, WHAT'S YOUR POINT?
>> I UNDERSTAND YOU SAVED
MY SISTER KAEDE.
>> HA!
OH, THAT.
>> I WANT TO THANK YOU, TOO.
>> TRUST ME, THE GRATITUDE THING
DOESN'T LOOK GOOD ON YOU.
>> INUYASHA, HOW DO I LOOK
TO YOU?
DO I SEEM HUMAN?
>> HUH?
NOW WHAT ARE YOU GOING ON
ABOUT?
>> I SHOW MY WEAKNESS TO NO ONE.
I MUST NEVER HAVE DOUBTS
OR DEMONS WOULD OVERCOME ME.
I AM HUMAN.
YET, I CANNOT BE HUMAN.
WE'RE QUITE ALIKE, YOU AND I.
YOU--A HALF-DEMON.
THAT'S WHY I COULD NOT KILL YOU.
>> HA!
IS THAT SUPPOSED TO BE
AN EXCUSE?
IT DOESN'T REALLY SEEM LIKE YOU.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
I SUPPOSE IT'S NOT LIKE ME.
INUYASHA.
>> HUH?
WHAT IS IT?
>> NEVER MIND.
I-IT'S NOTHING.
>> KIKYO.
KIKYO!
COME BACK HERE TOMORROW.
>> HUH?
>> HMM.
WHAT I MEAN IS, I WANT
TO GIVE YOU SOMETHING.
>> YOU WANT TO GIVE ME
SOMETHING?
THAT'S GOOD, BECAUSE I HAVE
SOMETHING I'VE BEEN THINKING
ABOUT GIVING YOU.
>> HUH? THE SACRED JEWEL?
>> NO SUCH THING.
>> HUH. SHOULDA KNOWN.
>> AREN'T THOSE BEADS USED
FOR SUBJUGATION?
ARE YOU GIVING THOSE
TO INUYASHA?
>> YES, I AM.
IT MAY BE A LITTLE UNDERHANDED
OF ME, BUT THESE WILL PREVENT
INUYASHA FROM DOING ANY MORE
WRONG.
NOW THEN, WHAT TRIGGER WORD
CAN I USE TO MAKE THE BEADS
TAKE EFFECT?
>> THAT NIGHT, IT SEEMED TO ME
THAT KIKYO APPEARED SOMEWHAT
HAPPY.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
I REMEMBER NOW.
THAT PRIESTESS TSUBAKI PUT
A CURSE ON ME.
UH, THE PATH I CHOOSE TO WALK
IS ONE OF CARNAGE.
SO WHY SHOULD I START FEARING
AN UNNATURAL DEATH?
>> SISTER KIKYO...
>> NOW, FOR THE BEADS.
"BELOVED."
THAT'S A GOOD TRIGGER WORD.
>> [BIRDS SINGING]
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> NO SENSE IN ME KEEPING IT.
SO I MIGHT AS WELL GIVE IT
TO YOU.
GO AHEAD.
TAKE IT.
THE ONLY THINGS MY MOTHER
LEFT ME WERE THAT AND THE ROBE
OF THE FIRE RAT.
>> YOUR MOTHER WAS HUMAN?
>> YEAH, WELL...
>> THIS MUST MEAN SO MUCH
TO YOU.
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
THE ROBE OF THE FIRE RAT
IS USEFUL ENOUGH.
IT'S ALL I NEED.
HUH?
>> I'M SO SORRY, INUYASHA.
I DIDN'T KNOW, AND I SHOT
SO MANY ARROWS AT IT.
>> HA!
AH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
OH, BY THE WAY, WHAT WAS IT
YOU SAID YOU WANTED TO GIVE ME?
>> UH, I'M SORRY.
I MUST HAVE FORGOTTEN IT.
>> COME ON!
I'VE BEEN WAITING
AND EVERYTHING.
>> ARE YOU SURE I CAN KEEP
THIS GIFT?
>> HMM!
SURE THING.
>> [CHUCKLING]
INUYASHA AND KIKYO.
>> [MOANS]
HUH?
THAT NIGHT, KIKYO COLORED
HER LIPS.
SHE LOOKED SO BEAUTIFUL.
BUT EVEN TO MY INNOCENT EYES,
THERE WAS A KIND OF SADNESS
ABOUT HER.
>> [CHILDREN LAUGHING]
>> SO, WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE
TO PLAY NEXT, CHILDREN?
>> LET'S SEE...
>> INUYASHA, WHY DON'T YOU
COME DOWN FROM THERE AND JOIN
US?
>> HA!
YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING.
>> LET'S PLAY BALL.
>> NO, PICK FLOWERS.
[LAUGHING]
[CHATTERING]
>> [GRUNTING]
IT'S NO USE.
I'LL NEVER BE AS GOOD
AS MY SISTER KIKYO.
HMM...
>> I'M IMPRESSED, KAEDE.
>> HUH?
KIKYO, IT'S YOU.
HMM?
UM, CAN I TELL YOU SOMETHING?
>> HMM. YES. WHAT IS IT?
>> MM. NOTHING. FORGET IT.
>> OH. ALL RIGHT.
>> I WANTED TO SEE KIKYO
LOOK BEAUTIFUL, AND I WANTED
TO DO WHAT I COULD TO HELP HER.
I THOUGHT I WAS THE ONLY ONE
IN THE WORLD WHO HAD SUCH
THOUGHTS ABOUT MY SISTER.
>> HMM.