- [LAUGHING]
COME TO ME!
- RUN FOR IT!
- AAH!
AAH! OH!
- OH! KAGOME!
- KAGOME!
- AHH...
- IT IS THIS WOMAN THAT
I HAVE BEEN MISSING.
[LAUGHING]
- [LAUGHING]
IT WAS YOU I DESIRED, WOMAN.
- NO!
- HANDS OFF!
UNH!
- AAH!
- GET OUT OF HERE, KAGOME.
- RIGHT.
- [BUZZING]
- THAT'S THE LAST TIME
YOU'LL INTERFERE.
- AAH!
- HOLD IT!
- WHAT DO YOU WANT WITH KAGOME?
- KAGOME?
YOU'RE MISTAKEN.
THAT WOMAN'S MINE.
- AAH!
UNH.
- [PANTING]
AAH!
- SHE BELONGS TO ME!
- [GRUNTING]
- DAMN YOU!
YOU'RE GOING DOWN!
WINDSCAR!
- WOMAN!
- HUH?
- YOU BELONG TO ME.
YOU'RE MINE!
- WHY DO YOU THINK HE
WANTED TO CAPTURE KAGOME?
- WELL, SHIPPO, THE ONLY
THING WE KNOW FOR SURE
IS THAT HE'S ONE OF
NARAKU'S INCARNATIONS.
THE SPIDER SCAR ON
HIS BACK PROVES THAT.
- UH, I DON'T THINK
THERE'S ANY WAY
HE COULD HAVE SURVIVED A DIRECT
BLOW FROM THE WINDSCAR.
STILL, I DON'T FEEL VERY SAFE.
- NO.
HE WENT DOWN TOO EASILY.
- INUYASHA!
- HMM?
- KAEDE! WHAT A RELIEF!
- WHAT WAS ALL THAT
COMMOTION ABOUT?
- YOU'RE TOO LATE
TO BE OF ANY HELP.
- HUH? WHAT HAPPENED?
- NOTHING.
JUST FORGET IT.
IT'S ALL OVER NOW.
AT LEAST, I THINK IT IS.
- [GROANING]
- DO YOU FEEL ANY BETTER YET?
- YES, THANKS TO YOUR CARE.
- I'LL CHANGE YOUR POULTICE
A LITTLE LATER ON.
- LADY KIKYO!
- HMM?
- [CRYING]
- YES? WHAT IS IT, MONK?
- THERE IS NO NEED TO
BE AFRAID ANY LONGER.
- MY MENTOR, MASTER MUSO,
WAS KILLED,
AND HIS FACE WAS STOLEN--
STOLEN!
- THAT'S TERRIBLE.
WHO DID IT?
- IT WAS A MAN WHO
HAD NO FACE AT ALL,
AND ON HIS BACK I SAW
THE MARK OF A SPIDER.
- A SPIDER?
- IT WAS HORRIBLE--
HORRIBLE!
- TAKE HIM INSIDE TO REST.
- OF COURSE.
- THE SPIDER PATTERN
ON HIS BACK?
IT MUST HAVE BEEN ONE
OF NARAKU'S INCARNATIONS.
THAT DEMON--
NOW WHAT IS HE UP TO?
- KIKYO.
- NARAKU, YOU HAVE GOOD REASON
TO BE CONCERNED ABOUT ME.
DO YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE INSIDE YOU, THE HEART
OF ONIGUMO BEATS STRONG.
[THUNDER]
- DAMN THAT NARAKU!
HOW LONG DOES HE INTEND TO KEEP
ME IMPRISONED LIKE THIS?
CURSE HIM!
- KAGURA.
- NARAKU!
- DO YOU WISH TO BE FREED?
- I PROMISE YOU, I WON'T
TRY TO RUN AWAY AGAIN.
- FOLLOW THE ONE WHO
CALLS HIMSELF MUSO.
- MUSO?
- YES.
HE IS YOUR YOUNGER BROTHER.
- UNH!
MUSO--ANOTHER OF
NARAKU'S INCARNATIONS.
- INFORM INUYASHA AND HIS
CLAN OF MUSO'S WHEREABOUTS.
- DO WHAT?
- [CHUCKLES]
THERE'S ONLY ONE POSSIBLE PLACE
THAT MUSO COULD BE HEADED FOR.
- DAMN.
HOW DARE HE DO THIS TO ME?
WHO IS THIS MAN...
INUYASHA?
INUYASHA!
I THINK I KNOW HIM...
FROM SOMEWHERE.
WHO AM I?
I WONDER.
- BYE, THEN.
- YOU SURE YOU WANT ME TO GO?
- YEAH.
YOU'D BETTER GO BACK
FOR THE TIME BEING.
- THAT'S NOT LIKE YOU AT ALL.
YOU'RE ALWAYS
GETTING INTO A SNIT
WHEN I HINT ABOUT
GOING HOME, INUYASHA.
- I DO NOT!
NOW, JUST GET GOING, WOULD YOU?
- WELL, IF YOU'RE SURE.
I KIND OF DID
WANT TO GO BACK
TO SEE HOW I MADE
OUT ON MY TEST.
- KAGOME, I THINK IT
WOULD BE WISE FOR YOU
TO LIE LOW FOR
A LITTLE WHILE...
AT LEAST UNTIL WE KNOW FOR SURE
WHAT NARAKU IS UP TO.
- HE'S RIGHT.
- YOU'RE SAFER
ON THE OTHER SIDE.
- YEAH, I GUESS.
[RUSTLING]
- GREETINGS.
- HEY, WHAT THE HELL
DO YOU WANT?
- HMM.
THAT'S SOME FINE
ARMOR YOU'RE SPORTING.
- HUH? WHAT?
- HMM.
[THUNDER]
WHAT IS IT ABOUT THIS PLACE?
IT LOOKS SO FAMILIAR.
- KAEDE, I WONDER IF
I REALLY SHOULD GO HOME.
- I DON'T KNOW JUST
WHO THIS MUSO IS,
BUT HE TRIED TO
CAPTURE YOU, CORRECT?
- YEAH.
BUT MUSO'S DEAD.
I MEAN, HE WAS DESTROYED
BY INUYASHA'S WINDSCAR.
- YES.
IT SEEMS INUYASHA'S
BEING EXTRA CAUTIOUS.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
HE'S FOUGHT SEVERAL OF
NARAKU'S INCARNATIONS,
BUT HE'S NEVER, EVER BEEN
THIS CAUTIOUS BEFORE.
- NARAKU'S DEVIOUS.
I HAVE AN UNEASY
FEELING ABOUT THIS.
I'D BETTER GO CHECK
ON SOMETHING.
- LIKE WHAT?
- YOU GO ON HOME NOW, KAGOME.
IN THE MEANTIME, I'M GOING
TO LOOK IN THE CAVE.
- WHAT CAVE?
YOU MEAN...
- HMM?
SOMETHING'S UP AHEAD.
[THUNDER]
A CAVERN.
I'VE BEEN HERE.
I'M CERTAIN.
- HEY, INUYASHA.
- YEAH?
- WHERE ARE WE GOING?
- NARAKU'S CASTLE.
- SO, YOU KNOW WHERE IT IS NOW?
- OF COURSE I DON'T, IDIOT.
- THEN WE'RE JUST WALKING
AROUND IN CIRCLES?
- STOP ASKING DUMB QUESTIONS!
WE ARE BACKTRACKING THE PATH
THAT MUSO TOOK HERE!
- SHOULD WE STOP IN AT ALL
THE VILLAGES HE RAIDED?
- YES, WE SHOULD,
AS WELL AS THE SITE
WHERE THE BANDITS
WERE ALL SLAUGHTERED.
- HUH?
KAGURA.
- YO.
- YOU WITCH!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- I HAVEN'T COME TO FIGHT.
I SIMPLY WANT TO TELL
YOU WHERE MUSO IS.
- WHERE MUSO IS?
- YOU MEAN, THAT DEMON
IS STILL ALIVE?
- YEAH, SOMETHING TOLD ME WE
WEREN'T THROUGH WITH HIM YET.
HOW COME YOU'RE SO HELPFUL
ALL OF A SUDDEN?
- YOU'RE FAMILIAR WITH THE CAVE
WHERE KIKYO AND ONIGUMO STAYED?
WELL, THAT'S WHERE
MUSO IS HEADED.
- WHAT?
- MUSO'S GONE TO ONIGUMO'S CAVE?
- I'VE TOLD YOU ALL.
FAREWELL.
- WAIT.
DID NARAKU SEND YOU
HERE TO TELL US?
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- DOES HE KNOW ABOUT
INUYASHA'S SECRET?
- SHUT UP, MIROKU!
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
- SECRET?
WHAT SECRET?
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT IT.
- AND THERE SHE GOES.
WHAT WAS THAT LITTLE
VISIT ALL ABOUT?
- LAST TIME WE SAW HER,
SHE WAS BETRAYING NARAKU
TO STEAL THE JEWEL SHARDS.
- IT DIDN'T SEEM LIKE
SHE WAS HELPING US
SO THAT SHE COULD
GET BACK AT NARAKU.
- I WONDER IF SHE
TOLD NARAKU ABOUT
WHAT SHE SAW THAT NIGHT--
HOW INUYASHA BECOMES MORTAL
DURING THE NEW MOON.
- EITHER WAY, SHE'S
STILL NOT OUR ALLY.
- WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO NOW?
- YOU MEAN, ABOUT MUSO?
MAYBE WE SHOULD TAKE KAGURA'S
WORD FOR IT AND BELIEVE HER.
- HUH?
- WELL, THAT'S A CHANGE.
MOST OF THE TIME,
YOU WOULD JUST JUMP
AT THE CHANCE
TO TAKE OFF AND FIGHT.
- SAVE IT, WOULD YOU?
- AAH!
I ONLY MEANT THAT, UH...
- INUYASHA, WHAT ARE
YOU SO ON EDGE ABOUT?
- I'M NOT UPSET, ALL RIGHT?
ARRGH!
THIS MUSO GUY IS REALLY
STARTING TO GET TO ME.
WHAT'S HIS DEAL, ANYWAY?
- HMM?
- I CAN'T UNDERSTAND NARAKU.
- GO TO INUYASHA AND TELL
HIM WHERE TO FIND MUSO,
THEN STAY NEAR
AND KEEP WATCH OVER HIM.
- IT'S LIKE HE'S CURIOUS
ABOUT MUSO'S ACTIONS.
[GASPS]
DOES THAT MEAN THAT, UNLIKE ME,
MUSO ISN'T UNDER
NARAKU'S CONTROL?
[THUNDER]
- WAIT, KAEDE!
- HUH?
YOU DIDN'T RETURN HOME, KAGOME?
- WELL, I THOUGHT
I'D BETTER TAKE A LOOK
INSIDE THAT CAVE, TOO.
- [SIGHS]
IT'S UP AHEAD.
- I REMEMBER.
SOMEONE WAS WITH ME...
RIGHT HERE.
THAT'S HER!
WHO IS SHE?
- THERE IT IS.
- SO THIS IS WHERE
ONIGUMO ONCE STAYED.
RIGHT HERE--
THIS IS WHERE IT ALL BEGAN.
- KAGOME?
- [GASPS]
HMM?
DON'T MIND ME.
- IT WAS THAT WOMAN I DESIRED.
THIS IS THE PLACE.
IT WAS HERE THAT I--
AAH.
HUH?
- WATCH YOUR STEP.
- I'M FINE.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME, KAEDE.
- AH!
IT'S HER AGAIN!
UHH!
IT'S THAT WOMAN--
THE ONE I DESIRED...
EVEN IF IT MEANT HAVING TO
SELL MY SOUL TO DEMONS.
[PANTING]
THAT WOMAN--
IT WAS HER I WANTED.
KIKYO!
- IT'S HIM!
- THAT MAN IS MORTAL?
- I FINALLY REMEMBERED
WHAT PAINED ME.
IT WAS KIKYO I LONGED FOR.
MMH!
- AAH!
- YOU AGAIN!
I KNOW YOU.
- KAEDE!
- I ONCE KNEW THIS DEMON,
BUT HIS NAME WASN'T MUSO.
WHY WOULD HE SHOW
HIMSELF AROUND HERE
AFTER ALL THESE
YEARS HAVE PASSED?
- STAY OUT OF MY WAY, OLD MAID.
I HAVE COME HERE
SEEKING THAT WOMAN--
THE WOMAN WHO IS
IDENTICAL TO KIKYO.
- I KNEW IT!
YOU ARE THE FUGITIVE ONIGUMO.
- ONIGUMO?!
- OUT OF MY WAY!
- LEAVE HER ALONE!
I'M THE ONE YOU WANT, RIGHT?
I AM NOT GOING TO GIVE
IN WITHOUT A FIGHT, PAL!
UNH.
KAEDE, RUN FOR IT!
- STOP!
- AAH!
- WHO ARE YOU, WOMAN?
WHO ARE YOU, AND WHY DO
YOU LOOK JUST LIKE KIKYO?
- KAGOME!
- [PANTING]
- IRON-REAPER SOUL-STEALER!
- INUYASHA!
- UNH.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHY DIDN'T YOU GO HOME?
- HA!
INUYASHA--ALWAYS INTERFERING.
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?!
- KAGOME!
- YOU WERE SUPPOSED
TO HAVE GONE HOME.
- SANGO, LOOK DOWN THERE.
IT'S MUSO.
- MY MEMORIES HAVE RETURNED.
I USED TO BE A BANDIT LONG AGO,
WHEN KIKYO AND I STAYED
HERE IN THIS VERY CAVE.
- KIKYO?!
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- INUYASHA, MUSO IS ONIGUMO.
- ONIGUMO?!
THE BASTARD WHO FED
HIS SOUL TO DEMONS
AND BECAME NARAKU'S VERY CORE?
- HMM.
YOU FLATTER ME, INUYASHA.
- I SEE.
ONIGUMO'S ENTIRE BODY
WAS BADLY BURNED.
EVEN HIS FACE WAS
SCORCHED OFF...
AND THAT IS WHY HE KEPT STEALING
THE FACES OF HIS VICTIMS.
- ONIGUMO'S HEART MUST
HAVE BURST OUT FROM NARAKU.
- I'VE REMEMBERED EVERYTHING,
INCLUDING HOW KIKYO
DIED BACK THEN.
ARRGH!
- DAMN IT!
YOU ARE THE ONE THAT
INJURED HER, YOU BASTARD!
- THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
WHY DO YOU THINK
I FED MY VERY SOUL
TO THE DEMONS THAT I SUMMONED?
I WANTED POSSESSION
OF THE SACRED JEWEL
AND A HEALTHY BODY SO
I COULD STEAL KIKYO AWAY
AND LEAVE THIS CAVE.
BUT WHEN I GOT MY NEW BODY,
NOTHING WENT AS I PLANNED.
THE FIRST THING I DID
WHEN I LEFT THE CAVE
WAS CUT DOWN THE VERY WOMAN
I HAD SOLD MY BODY AND SOUL FOR.
- UNH!
OHH.
HUH?
- WHEN NARAKU WAS BORN,
ONIGUMO'S CONSCIOUSNESS
STILL LIVED INSIDE HIM.
- BUT NARAKU WAS
CREATED FROM THE UNION
OF HUNDREDS OF DEMONS...
AND THOSE DEMONS
HAD ONE DESIRE--
THE DEATH OF MY SISTER,
THE PRIESTESS.
- KIKYO FOLLOWED HIM--
THAT HALF-DEMON INUYASHA--
STRAIGHT INTO HER VERY DEMISE.
KIKYO PERISHED,
AND THE SACRED JEWEL
WAS BURNED ALONG
WITH HER CORPSE.
AT THAT VERY SAME TIME--
- VANISH.
- SOMEONE PURGED ME
TO A DEEP, DARK PLACE.
- THAT MUST HAVE BEEN NARAKU.
- UH...UNH.
I DON'T KNOW EXACTLY HOW
MANY YEARS I LAY DORMANT FOR,
BUT WHEN I FINALLY AWOKE,
I HAD BEEN HURLED BACK INTO
THE OUTSIDE WORLD AGAIN.
- HE HAS FORGOTTEN EVERYTHING,
EVEN ABOUT NARAKU.
HAVE YOU NOT RECEIVED
ORDERS FROM NARAKU?
- HA!
I TAKE ORDERS FROM NO ONE.
I SLAUGHTER EVERYONE I HATE,
AND BURN THEM TO THE GROUND.
NOW, THEN, INUYASHA,
YOU'RE FIRST.
WHY ARE YOU STILL ALIVE, ANYWAY?
KIKYO'S DEAD.
- YOU'RE ONE TO TALK.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING COMING
BACK TO LIFE LIKE THIS?
- I'M GOING TO KILL YOU FIRST,
AND THEN I'LL DEAL
WITH THAT WOMAN.
- WHO, ME?
- YOU'RE NOT LAYING
A HAND ON KAGOME!
YOU GOT TO GET THROUGH ME FIRST!
- FINE.
THEN LET'S GET
ON WITH IT, SHALL WE?
- POISON INSECTS.
- KAEDE AND KAGOME,
GET BACK OUT OF DANGER.
- HMPH!
I DON'T KNOW WHY
NARAKU LET YOU OUT...
BUT YOU'LL GET EXACTLY THE SAME
TREATMENT I'D GIVE HIM.
AAH!
HERE'S PAYBACK FOR KIKYO!
- TRY IT!
- AAAH!
UNH!
- AAH!
- HIS SCAR CLOSED ON THE SWORD!
- I SEE.
IT ALL MAKES SENSE NOW.
MUSO HAS THE POWER
TO REGENERATE HIS BODY.
- YEAH? WHO CARES?
AAH!
UNH.
- IT SEEMS THAT YOUR STRANGE
SWORD IS USELESS AGAINST ME.
HOW VERY UNFORTUNATE.
- DAMN YOU!
- I KNEW THAT I SHOULD
HAVE SUCKED MUSO UP
WITH MY WIND TUNNEL
WHILE I HAD THE CHANCE.
- DOES THIS MEAN NARAKU
IS PROTECTING MUSO?
- IT'S LOOKING THAT WAY.
HE MUST HAVE SENT
THOSE POISON INSECTS HERE
TO PREVENT ME FROM
USING MY WIND TUNNEL.
- THEN WHY DOES
MUSO KEEP INSISTING
THAT HE TAKES
ORDERS FROM NO ONE?
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT HIS MOTIVATION IS.
- RARRGH!
- [BUZZING]
- HMM?
THE INSECTS AGAIN.
NARAKU!
- I CAME HERE TO
SEE YOU IN PERSON.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- I NEEDED TO TEST MY NEW POWER.
- I'VE TOLD YOU BEFORE,
A HALF-DEMON WHO HARBORS
ONIGUMO'S HEART
HAS ABSOLUTELY
NO POWER TO KILL ME.
- YOU SPEAK THE TRUTH, KIKYO.
INDEED, IF I STILL
HAD ONIGUMO'S HEART,
I WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO LAY
A HAND ON YOU NOW, WOULD I,
EVEN THOUGH YOUR BODY
IS MERE ARTIFICE.
- YOU WRETCH.
- I KNEW YOU WEREN'T REAL,
AND YET I WAS STILL UNABLE
TO REACH OUT AND STRIKE YOU.
- UNH!
- YOU...
A WOMAN MADE OF NOTHING
BUT CLAY AND BONES!
[LAUGHING]
- OH!
HUH?
- HUH?
HMM.
- WHAT'S WRONG, NARAKU?
WEREN'T YOU HERE TO KILL ME?
- DON'T SOUND SO SELF-ASSURED.
IT WAS NOT OUT OF FEAR
THAT I DECIDED TO SPARE YOU.
CONSIDER YOURSELF LUCKY.
I WILL NOT KILL YOU.
I WILL BREAK YOU.
ONIGUMO IS NOT YET
COMPLETELY SEVERED FROM ME.
- [LAUGHING]
- AAH!
YAAH!
AAH!
UNH!
- [LAUGHING]
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- DIE!
- [GASPS]
- WINDSCAR!
- UNH!
AAAH!
- IS HE DEAD?
- WE CAN'T BE CERTAIN--
NOT WITH HIS ABILITY
TO REGENERATE.
- AAH!
- [GRUNTING]
- UNH!
- YOUR EFFORTS ARE FUTILE.
- AAH! WINDSCAR!
- INUYASHA!
- THERE ARE ONLY SO MANY TIMES
HE CAN KEEP REGENERATING.
- HMM.
I HOPE YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
- MUSO SAID HE DOESN'T
TAKE ORDERS FROM NARAKU.
SO, HE'S NOT UNDER
NARAKU'S CONTROL?
HOW CAN HE BE PART OF NARAKU,
YET FREE FROM HIM?
- FOOL!
YOU STILL DON'T UNDERSTAND
THAT IT'S IMPOSSIBLE
TO DESTROY ME.
- MMH.
- HE'S REGENERATED AGAIN!
- DAMN IT ALL.
ISN'T THERE SOME WAY
I CAN DESTROY HIM?
- MRRM!
- HE'S TRANSFORMING
INTO SOMETHING ELSE!
- IMPOSSIBLE!
- IT APPEARS THAT
I'M GETTING ACCUSTOMED
TO THIS BODY OF MINE.
- UNH!
- INUYASHA, LOOK OUT!
- AAH!
AAH!
- INUYASHA!
- [GROANING]
- [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- ONIGUMO'S HEART WAS ALIVE
AND BEATING INSIDE NARAKU.
- NARAKU EXPELLED IT,
AND IT TURNED INTO MUSO.
- IT'S STRANGE, KAGOME.
NARAKU IS TRYING
TO PROTECT MUSO.
WHY GET RID OF HIM,
THEN TRY TO HELP HIM?
- NARAKU IS TRYING TO ABSORB
MUSO BACK INTO HIS BODY!
- HUH?
MUSO HAS HIS CLAWS IN NARAKU.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- ARE MUSO AND NARAKU ENEMIES?
NEXT TIME, "THREE-SIDED
BATTLE TO THE DEATH."
THE KEY TO IT ALL IS
THAT SPIDER ON THE BACK.