[BIRDS CHIRPING]
- DID YOU DRAW THESE, SHIPPO?
I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WERE SO CREATIVE.
[GIGGLES]
THE CAT'S ADORABLE.
- DOES SHE LOOK FAMILIAR?
SHE'S SUPPOSED TO BE YOU.
THIS ONE'S INUYASHA, AND THIS
ONE'S SUPPOSED TO BE KOGA.
IT'S A LOVE TRIANGLE BETWEEN
A TWO-LEGGED DOG, A WOLF-MAN,
AND A CAT
WHO HIGHTAILED IT HOME.
- SHIPPO, HOLD ON A MINUTE.
HAVE YOU SHOWN THIS
EMBARRASSINGLY FAMILIAR
PICTURE BOOK TO ANYBODY ELSE?
- I SHOWED IT TO KAEDE EARLIER,
AND SHE THOUGHT IT WAS
REALLY WELL-DONE.
- SO, BASICALLY,
KAEDE KNOWS EVERYTHING
ABOUT WHY INUYASHA AND I
ARE FIGHTING?
- YUP, BUT KAEDE ISN'T THE ONLY
ONE WHO'S SEEN MY DRAWINGS.
I WAS SO PROUD OF THEM, I ENDED
UP SHOWING THE WHOLE VILLAGE.
I GOT LOTS OF COMPLIMENTS.
[STRAINED LAUGH]
I WON'T BE SHOWING MY FACE
IN THE VILLAGE ANY TIME SOON.
I'LL DIE OF EMBARRASSMENT.
[SIGHS]
- IT'S NOT A FANTASY.
I'VE CLAIMED HER AS MINE.
I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU, KAGOME!
- KOGA IS THE YOUNG LEADER
OF THE DEMON WOLF TRIBE.
HE KIDNAPPED ME, HOPING I COULD
HELP HIM STEAL THE JEWEL SHARDS
AWAY FROM THE BIRDS OF PARADISE.
- DID SHE JUST HELP HIM?
- KAGOME?
- YEAH?
- YOU SOUND LIKE YOU'RE
IN LOVE WITH THIS NUT BAR!
- HUH? I DON'T LOVE INUYASHA.
THAT'S...IMPOSSIBLE.
- COME ON.
YOU MUST LOVE HIM, KAGOME.
IT'S WRITTEN ALL OVER YOUR FACE.
[GIGGLES]
- ALL RIGHT, MEN.
THIS SIDE'S ALL CLEAR.
HMM. LOOK AT HIM.
[SNORING]
- THE ENEMY!
- HUH? WHAT? WHERE?!
IS IT THE BIRDS OF PARADISE?
AAH!
[SPLASH]
[LAUGHING]
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT, HAKKAKU?
THE BIRDS OF PARADISE
ARE ALL DEAD,
BUT YOU LOOK FUNNY
FLYING OVER THAT CLIFF.
[LAUGHING]
- SHUT UP!
THAT WAS A DIRTY TRICK!
- THAT'S WHAT YOU GET
FOR SLACKING OFF
AND SLEEPING ON GUARD DUTY.
- DAMN IT. HEY, WHO ARE THEY?
- THEY'RE OUR BROTHERS
FROM THE NORTHERN CAVES.
- THERE'S SOMEONE WHO POSSESSES
A HUGE SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
- HE'S A LORD OF A CASTLE.
I KNOW IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE,
BUT WE'RE NOT
JOKING ABOUT THIS GUY.
- LET'S COMBINE FORCES
AND JOIN THE NORTHERN
AND EASTERN TRIBES TOGETHER.
THEN WE CAN STORM THE CASTLE.
WE'LL TAKE THE JEWEL SHARD
AND DIVVY IT UP EQUALLY.
- WELL, KOGA,
YOU WANT TO JOIN US?
- SORRY. NOT INTERESTED.
- WHAT?
- WHY THE HELL NOT?
- I HAVE SOMETHING
I HAVE TO TAKE CARE OF FIRST
BEFORE I DO ANYTHING ELSE.
- I SEE. WELL, NO SENSE
FORCING THE ISSUE.
- HE'S GOT AN INJURY.
DO YOU SEE THAT?
- YOU SURE YOU WANT
TO TURN THEM DOWN, KOGA?
- IF WE DON'T JOIN THEM,
THEN THE NORTHERN TRIBE WILL GET
ALL OF THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
- LET THEM GO.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
- WELL, IT MATTERS TO ME.
I'M GOING TO GO WITH THEM.
- ME, TOO!
- GO AHEAD. I COULD CARE LESS.
IF YOU WANT TO LEAVE,
I'M NOT GOING TO STOP YOU.
- WE'RE GOING TO GO JOIN
THE NORTHERN TRIBES!
- WHOEVER WANTS A PIECE
OF THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD,
YOU BETTER FOLLOW US!
- YEAH!
- DAMN.
[GROWLING]
[GRUNTING]
- CHEW ON THIS!
- 10 SECONDS,
AND NOW WE WILL TAKE OFF!
[GROANING]
DAMN IT!
I NEVER THOUGHT
THE BIRD OF PARADISE
WOULD BE ABLE TO STEAL
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD
OUT OF MY ARM.
BUT I'LL GET IT BACK.
JUST WAIT.
BUT FIRST, I HAVE TO
TAKE CARE OF THAT DOG.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE WAS ABLE
TO KILL THAT BIRD OF PARADISE
WITH ONE SWEEP OF HIS SWORD.
THE JERK.
I WON'T BE SATISFIED
UNTIL I WRING HIS STUPID NECK
WITH MY BARE HANDS.
UGH. THIS WOUND ISN'T HEALING
AS QUICKLY AS I HOPED IT WOULD.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
- I'M SURE IT'S THIS WAY.
I CAN SENSE THE JEWEL SHARDS.
- YOU SEE HOW HELPFUL KAGOME IS?
SHE'S THE ONLY ONE
WITH THAT ABILITY.
- THAT'S RIGHT, INUYASHA,
SO STOP FIGHTING WITH HER
AND JUST GET OVER IT, ALREADY.
- WE NEED YOUR ENERGY
DIRECTED TOWARDS SOMETHING
OTHER THAN ANIMOSITY.
- SO KNOCK IT OFF!
- HUH.
- WE'RE TRACKING A DEMON BEAR
THAT ATTACKED A VILLAGE?
- ACCORDING TO ONE
OF THE SURVIVORS, YES.
HE SAID IT STARTED OUT
AS JUST A MISCHIEVOUS CUB
RUINING THE FIELDS,
BUT THEN SUDDENLY IT GREW HUGE
AND ATTACKED THE VILLAGE.
INUYASHA, YOU SEEM DISPLEASED
ABOUT SOMETHING.
- HA! THAT'S THE UNDERSTATEMENT
OF THE YEAR.
YEAH, SURE, WE GOT TO SEEK OUT
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS
THAT KAGOME SENSES,
BUT WHY SHOULD I WASTE
MY TIME ON A BEAR HUNT
WHEN I COULD BE
HUNTING DOWN A WOLF?
- KOGA.
- WE ALREADY KNOW
THAT KOGA THE WOLF DEMON
HAS TWO SACRED JEWEL SHARDS
JAMMED IN HIS SKINNY
LITTLE HAIRY LEGS.
[SNIFFING]
I'D FEEL MORE LIKE FIGHTING
IF I SMELLED THE REEK
OF WOLF ON THIS MOUNTAIN,
NOT THE STENCH OF BEAR.
- SO, IN OTHER WORDS,
YOUR FIRST PRIORITY RIGHT NOW
IS BUTCHERING KOGA.
- HE'S HIS ARCH RIVAL IN LOVE.
[CLANG]
OOH! OOH!
UGH!
WHAT'D YOU DO THAT FOR?!
- HMM!
- SHIPPO, IF YOU BUG INUYASHA,
YOU'LL ONLY FEEL HIS FIST.
- HA HA HA.
- IS THAT THE BEAR?
- DON'T WORRY.
THEY'RE JUST ORDINARY THIEVES.
- WHO ARE YOU CALLING ORDINARY,
YOU ARROGANT BASTARD?
AND BY THE LOOKS OF YOU,
YOU AIN'T GOT NO MONEY,
SO WHY DON'T YOU JUST
LEAVE US THE WOMEN,
AND WE'LL CALL IT EVEN?
- DO YOU KNOW WHAT? I DON'T WANT
TO WASTE ANY MORE OF MY TIME,
SO IF YOU DON'T WANT
TO GET HURT, YOU BETTER LEAVE.
- UH.
- WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY TO US?
- KAGOME?
- HUH?
- I CAN FEEL THE JEWEL SHARD
COMING. GET BACK.
- I DON'T SEE ANYTHING
OUT THERE, DO YOU?
[CRASHING]
[GRUNTING]
[GROWLING]
[SCREAMING]
- THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD
IS IN HIS FOREHEAD!
- HUH. HE WOULD MAKE
ONE HELL OF A BEAR RUG.
HE MIGHT BE HUGE, BUT HE'S STILL
GOT THE BRAIN OF A BUSH PIG.
[GRUNTING]
[GROWLING]
- HUH?
NARAKU'S POISON INSECTS.
- INUYASHA, LOOK!
[GROWLING]
- THEY'RE TAKING OUT
THE JEWEL SHARD!
[GROWLING]
- IS IT A TRAP?
- PROBABLY.
- HUH. FINE WITH ME...
AND THIS TIME, NARAKU
WON'T MANAGE TO ESCAPE.
- WELL, DEAR, YOU'VE
DECIDED TO WATCH THIS
FROM A DISTANCE, HAVE YOU?
LET ME DO THE DIRTY WORK?
WELL, THAT MAKES THINGS
EASIER FOR ME IN THE LONG RUN.
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS
MAKE DEMONS EVEN
STRONGER, DON'T THEY?
WHAT AN UTTERLY ENTICING OPIATE.
YOU'RE PLANNING TO
LURE THEM HERE WITH THIS?
[SIZZLING]
BUT WHY? YOU CAN CONQUER THEM
WITHOUT ALL OF THIS.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU'RE
BEING EXTRA CAREFUL
OR IF YOU'RE BEING COWARDLY,
OR PERHAPS IT'S SIMPLY
YOUR INSATIABLE LOVE
FOR CLEVER ENTRAPMENTS.
WHICH IS IT, MY MASTER?
- HERE IT IS, BROTHERS,
THE CASTLE FULL
OF SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
WHEN THE CASTLE GUARDS APPEAR,
DON'T HESITATE. KILL THEM ALL!
[CHEERING]
- WHAT CASTLE GUARDS
IS HE TALKING ABOUT?
I DON'T SEE ANYONE.
- HMM?
SOMEONE'S THERE!
- LET'S GET 'EM!
[YELLING]
WHOA!
- IS THAT IT?
THEY'RE PATHETIC.
YOU'LL HAVE TO DO
BETTER THAN THAT.
BRING ME SOMEONE
WORTH MY EFFORT.
- AH!
[YAWNING]
HUH?
[SNORING]
- HEH HEH HEH.
[WHINING]
- SHH.
[GROWLING]
- HUH? I TOLD YOU TO BE QUIET.
EH! HUH?
AAH!
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH HIM?
- DIDN'T HE GO WITH
THE NORTHERN TRIBE?
- YEAH.
- WHAT'S WRONG? WHAT HAPPENED?
- I WAS ONLY ABLE TO GET ONE.
- YOU GOT A SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
- HURRY TO THE CASTLE, KOGA.
IF YOU DON'T, EVERYONE
WILL BE SLAUGHTERED.
- A JEWEL SHARD.
I'LL PUT IT TO GOOD USE.
[GRUNTING]
- COME INSIDE AND REST.
- YOU'RE AMAZING.
HOW DID YOU MAKE IT BACK
WITH ALL THOSE INJURIES?
[GRUNTING]
- AAH!
- HE'S DEAD!
[BUZZING]
[GRUNTING]
- WHAT'S ALL THIS?
- THEY'RE WOLVES.
- ARE THEY OF
THE DEMON WOLF TRIBE?
- WHAT WERE THEY DOING
IN THIS CASTLE?
BUT MORE IMPORTANTLY...
[GROANING]
- AAH! THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
THEY CAN'T STILL BE ALIVE!
- I DON'T SENSE
ANY LIFE IN THESE MEN.
THEIR SOULS HAVE LEFT THEM.
- THAT MEANS THEY'RE UNDEAD.
[GRUNTING]
[GROWLING]
- DO YOU SEE THAT?
EVEN IN YOU KNOCK THEM DOWN,
THEY REVIVE AGAIN RIGHT AWAY.
- HOW CAN THEY KEEP
COMING BACK TO LIFE
IF THEY WERE DEAD
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
- IF A MAN LOSES HIS HEAD,
I'LL PUT IT BACK ON.
IF HE'S CUT DOWN TO SIZE,
HE CAN STILL TAKE THEM OUT.
HE'S SIMPLY DANCING
MY UNDEAD DEATH SONG.
HMM. HE'S HERE ALREADY? TOO BAD.
[GRUNTING]
- WHAT?
UGH!
[GROANING]
- WHAT'S GOING ON AROUND HERE?
- WHAT'S MAKING THEM ALL
COLLAPSE LIKE THAT?
I DON'T GET IT.
[GASPING]
[THUNDER]
IT'S HIM.
INUYASHA!
- THAT'S KOGA FROM
THE DEMON WOLF TRIBE.
- KOGA?
- INUYASHA,
HOW DARE YOU DO THIS?
- BEFORE YOU
JUMP TO CONCLUSIONS,
YOUR PALS HERE WERE ALREADY DEAD
BY THE TIME I GOT TO THE CASTLE.
- SHUT UP! YOU CAN'T LIE TO ME.
YOU'RE COVERED HEAD TO FOOT
IN THEIR BLOOD!
- HUH? DAMN IT.
I'VE BEEN SET UP.
- KOGA, YOU'RE WRONG.
WE CAME HERE LOOKING
FOR A DEMON NAMED NARAKU,
AND WE FOUND THE WOLF TRIBE
SLAUGHTERED.
- KAGOME.
- BUT THEN THEY CAME TO LIFE
AND STARTED ATTACKING US,
BUT THEY WEREN'T REALLY ALIVE.
THEY WERE ZOMBIES.
- KAGOME, DON'T EVEN TRY
PROTECTING THAT CUR.
ALREADY DEAD WHEN YOU GOT HERE.
HOW STUPID DO YOU THINK I AM,
YOU BLOODTHIRSTY MUTT?
- OH, NO.
- IT LOOKS LIKE WE WERE SET UP.
THIS IS ONE OF NARAKU'S TRICKS.
IT WAS HIS POISON INSECTS THAT
LED US HERE IN THE FIRST PLACE.
THE DEMON WOLF TRIBES WERE
SOMEHOW ENTICED HERE, TOO,
AND THEN THEY WERE
QUICKLY SLAUGHTERED.
- KOGA CAME
TO RESCUE HIS COMRADES.
HE RUSHED OVER
AND ARRIVED JUST IN TIME
TO FIND INUYASHA
COVERED IN THEIR BLOOD.
- KOGA WON'T BE REASONED WITH.
THE SIGHT OF THE SLAUGHTER
HAS PUT HIM INTO
A FIXED RAGE OF VENGEANCE.
THEY'LL FIGHT TO THE DEATH.
- YOU'RE RIGHT. THE BLOOD HAS
GONE STRAIGHT TO KOGA'S HEAD,
AND I DON'T THINK
THERE'S ANYTHING
THAT WILL GET HIM TO BACK DOWN.
- I HAVE TO FIND
A WAY TO STOP THEM,
BUT...BUT HOW?
[GRUNTING]
- I HAVE TO FIND
A WAY TO STOP THEM,
BUT...BUT HOW?
[GRUNTING]
- HE'S GOTTEN STRONGER!
YOU GOT YOUR
STRENGTH BACK, KOGA?
I SEE YOU'VE MANAGED TO FIND
ANOTHER JEWEL SHARD
FOR YOUR ARM.
[GRUNTING]
YOU STOLE MY ORIGINAL JEWEL
SHARD THE LAST TIME WE MET,
BUT I WARN YOU,
THIS NEW ONE'S EVEN BETTER.
[PANTING]
- STRANGE LIGHT. IS THAT
THE GLOW FROM THE JEWEL SHARD?
- HUH?
- NO, IT'S DARKER,
AND THE ENERGY IS WARPED.
- THEN WHAT'S IT A FRAGMENT OF?
[GRUNTING]
- STOP IT, KOGA!
I WANT YOU TO LISTEN
TO ME, PLEASE!
THIS WHOLE THING'S A TRAP.
INUYASHA DIDN'T KILL
YOUR FRIENDS.
IT WAS SOMEBODY ELSE.
- SHUT UP! WORDS ARE CHEAP...
AND I BELIEVE WHAT I SEE
WITH MY OWN EYES.
- KOGA!
- FORGET ABOUT IT, KAGOME.
HE'S GOT A BLOCK OF WOOD
FOR A BRAIN,
SO HE CAN'T GRASP
ANYTHING TOO COMPLICATED.
THERE'S NO REASONING
WITH THE MORON.
ALL HE UNDERSTANDS IS
A FEW PUNCHES IN THE HEAD.
- THE DEMON WOLF TRIBES
LIVE IN PACKS,
AND THEY CHERISH THEIR
COMRADES LIKE FAMILY.
SEEING SO MANY OF HIS
BROTHERS DEAD ALL AT ONCE
WOULD MAKE HIM INSANE
WITH GRIEF.
- I THOUGHT HE MIGHT LISTEN TO
YOU, KAGOME, BUT I WAS WRONG.
HE'S TOO FAR GONE.
- YOU CAN'T BLAME INUYASHA
FOR FIGHTING BACK.
HE HAS TO DEFEND HIMSELF
AGAINST KOGA'S ATTACKS.
- NARAKU IS TRYING
TO MAKE ME FIGHT WITH KOGA.
HE'S PITTED US AGAINST
EACH OTHER WITH THIS SET-UP,
AND NOW HE'S SITTING BACK
WATCHING THE WHOLE SHOW
FROM SOME HIDEOUT CLOSE BY.
I CAN SMELL HIM
FROM INSIDE THE CASTLE.
- PAY ATTENTION
IF YOU WANT TO LIVE.
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
LOOKING AT, COWARD?!
- WHAT DO YOU THINK WE
SHOULD DO? SHOULD WE HELP?
- INUYASHA CAME HERE
LOOKING FOR NARAKU,
THE ONE WHO SET
THIS WHOLE STAGE.
- DO YOU THINK NARAKU'S
INSIDE THE CASTLE SOMEWHERE?
- CHARGING RIGHT
INTO THE ENEMY'S TRAP
IS GENERALLY
NOT A WISE STRATEGY.
- WE DON'T HAVE
MUCH OF A CHOICE.
HERE IT GOES!
[PANTING]
- WHO ARE YOU?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- YOU WANT A FORMAL
INTRODUCTION?
GOOD EVENING. MY NAME'S KAGURA.
YOU MUST BE SANGO,
AND YOU'RE MIROKU.
AM I RIGHT?
- YES, AND YOU ARE
ONE OF NARAKU'S MINIONS.
TELL US WHERE HE IS.
- HE'S NOT IN RIGHT NOW,
BUT HE LEFT YOU
A LITTLE SOMETHING
TO KEEP YOU ENTERTAINED.
NARAKU HOPES YOU WILL FIND
HIS LITTLE GIFT AMUSING.
- HUH?
- DEMON PUPPET!
- NOW, THEN,
IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I'M OFF TO SEE
THE OUTDOOR ENTERTAINMENT:
KOGA AND INUYASHA.
NEITHER OF THEM TAKE MY FANCY,
SO I DON'T CARE WHICH
OF THEM WINS THE DUEL.
[GASPING]
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- KOGA HAS BEEN TRICKED INTO
FIGHTING INUYASHA TO THE DEATH!
NARAKU'S GOAL IS TO GET A HOLD
OF THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS
IN KOGA'S LEGS,
BUT RATHER THAN TAKE HIM ON
HIMSELF AND GET HIS HANDS DIRTY,
HE'S PITTED KOGA
AGAINST INUYASHA,
HOPING THEY'LL FINISH
EACH OTHER OFF.
TETSUSAIGA GOT THROWN ASIDE?
IS INUYASHA'S ARM BROKEN?
HE'S WAY TOO PROUD TO LOSE OUT
TO THAT PRIMA DONNA
DEMON KAGURA.
NEXT ON "INUYASHA"...
SEE YOU SOON!