- OUR SWORN ENEMY, NARAKU,
BECOMES INCREASINGLY POWERFUL
AS HE TAKES POSSESSION
OF MORE AND MORE
SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
EACH AND EVERY TIME,
HE MANIPULATES
PEOPLE AND SITUATIONS
IN ORDER TO GAIN MORE POWER
WITHOUT GETTING HIMSELF
DIRECTLY INVOLVED.
WE HAVE TO FIND NARAKU
AND DESTROY HIM QUICKLY
TO UNDO THE CURSE HE PLACED
ON MIROKU'S HAND
AND TO HELP SANGO
RESCUE HER BROTHER KOHAKU.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
- [SNORING]
- [SNIFFING]
HMM?
UNH!
- MMM...HMM?
- [SNIFFING]
GRR!
- WHAT'S THE MATTER? INUYASHA?
- I SMELL TROUBLE COMING.
- [GASPS]
- NARAKU.
- OH!
[WIND BLOWING]
- HMM. THE SCENT OF THE WIND
HAS CHANGED.
- LORD SESSHOMARU!
[PANTING]
YOUNG RIN HAS BEEN ABDUCTED!
NARAKU'S INCARNATION, KAGURA,
APPEARED OUT OF NOWHERE
AND TOOK OFF WITH RIN!
- LET ME REASSURE YOU,
LORD SESSHOMARU.
[BUZZING]
- IF YOU HEED MY REQUEST,
I SHALL RETURN RIN
IN GOOD HEALTH.
- AH! IT'S NARAKU!
- WE MEET AGAIN.
SO, WHAT DO YOU HAVE
UP YOUR SLEEVE THIS TIME?
- NOTHING SPECIAL.
I SIMPLY WANT YOU
TO KILL INUYASHA.
- HUH. WHY ARE YOU
GOING TO ALL THIS TROUBLE
FOR SOMETHING SO TRIVIAL?
- AAH! WHAT IS THAT?!
A DEMON PUPPET?
- DOES NARAKU HONESTLY BELIEVE
THAT HE CAN THREATEN ME
INTO ACTION
BY ENDANGERING THE LIFE
OF A MERE MORTAL?
- WILL YOU TURN YOUR BACK
ON THE GIRL?
WILL YOU FORSAKE HER?
WAIT!!
LORD SESSHOMARU,
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
[BUZZING]
- WHERE ARE YOU HEADED, MY LORD?
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
- SO, SESSHOMARU, YOU'VE COME.
HMM.
- [PANTING]
UNH! UNH!
- ARE YOU SURE
IT'S NARAKU YOU SMELL?
- YEAH. I KNOW THAT STENCH!
LOOK OUT, NARAKU!
I'LL FIND YOU FOR SURE
THIS TIME!
AND I'LL KILL YOU!
- HE'S GONE OUT OF HIS WAY
TO HIDE HIMSELF ALL THIS TIME.
WHY WOULD HE SHOW UP NOW?
- YES, THAT BOTHERS ME, TOO.
- [GROANING]
OH, NOW I REMEMBER.
THAT KAGURA LADY TOOK ME AWAY.
- IT'S YOU AGAIN!
AAH! UNH!
- I WAS ABDUCTED.
WHERE AM I?
HUH?
WHO ARE YOU?
- NO, YOU CAN'T GO OUTSIDE!
- I HAVE TO GET BACK.
[GASPS]
- [ROARS]
- I TOLD YOU NOT TO GO OUTSIDE.
IF YOU DO,
THEY'LL TEAR YOU APART.
- WHO ARE YOU?
WERE YOU BROUGHT HERE
AGAINST YOUR WILL,
LIKE I WAS?
WE COULD RUN AWAY TOGETHER!
- MY JOB IS TO GUARD YOU.
- [SIGHS]
OH, I SEE.
- OH! YOU DIDN'T
TELL ME YOUR NAME.
YOU CAN CALL ME RIN,
IF YOU WANT.
HOW OLD ARE YOU?
AND HOW COME
YOU'RE A GUARD HERE?
DOES THAT MEAN YOU'RE A DEMON
LIKE THE OTHERS?
TELL ME,
WHAT DO YOU LIKE TO EAT?
DO YOU LIKE MELONS?
- YEAH, I GUESS.
YOU SURE TALK A LOT.
- HMM?
[SIGHS]
I KNOW, BUT I GET SCARED
WHEN I'M NOT TALKING.
I WONDER IF LORD SESSHOMARU
WILL COME TO RESCUE ME?
[WIND BLOWING]
- IF I MAY SO BOLD AS TO ASK,
HOW DO YOU PLAN
TO APPROACH THIS, MY LORD?
WHY DID YOU STOP?
IS SOMETHING THE MATTER?
- NARAKU'S CASTLE IS HERE.
- HUH?
UHH...
I DON'T SEE A CASTLE, MY LORD.
[JAKEN SCREAMS]
[JAKEN WHIMPERS]
THE BARRIER HAS OPENED UP.
MY LORD!
[JAKEN WHIMPERING]
WAIT!
- YOU PURPOSELY LEAVE YOUR SCENT
TO REVEAL YOUR CASTLE
SO THAT I WILL FOLLOW YOU HERE.
- WOULD YOU HAVE COME OTHERWISE?
- OH!
- I MUST INFORM YOU
THAT THE MORTAL GIRL YOU SEEK
IS NOT HERE IN MY CASTLE.
SHE WOULD NEVER
BE ABLE TO SURVIVE
THE AIRLESS ATMOSPHERE
OF THIS POISONOUS MIASMA.
THE GIRL IS UNDER MY PROTECTION
OUTSIDE THE CASTLE WALLS.
I ASSURE YOU SHE IS UNHARMED...
FOR NOW.
- NARAKU, DO ME THE HONOR
OF AT LEAST RECOGNIZING
THAT I AM NOT HERE
SIMPLY TO SAVE RIN.
- HUH?
- OF COURSE.
YOU OF ALL PEOPLE
SEEM TO DESPISE
TAKING ORDERS FROM OTHERS.
YOU WILL NOT KILL INUYASHA
WHEN TOLD TO DO SO.
NOR DID YOU COME
TO LOOK FOR THE GIRL.
I REALIZE THAT YOU
ARE HERE TO KILL ME.
- HMM.
YOU SOUND AS IF YOU BELIEVE
YOU'VE LED ME INTO YOUR TRAP.
PERHAPS LATER
I'LL HAVE YOU EXPLAIN YOURSELF.
IF YOU SHOULD SURVIVE THE NIGHT,
THAT IS.
- [CHUCKLES]
SESSHOMARU, YOU WILL ASSIST ME
WHETHER YOU LIKE IT OR NOT.
- [PANTING]
UNH!
- INUYASHA, WAIT FOR US!
- SLOW DOWN, WE'RE LOSING YOU!
- UNH!
WHAT'S THE HOLDUP?
- I CAN SENSE
A SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
- HUH?
- UH.
- HUH.
- IT'S COMING FROM OVER THERE.
- SO YOU THINK THE SHARD IS
IN THOSE MOUNTAINS OVER THERE?
- WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
- WE'LL GO AFTER
THE JEWEL SHARD.
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
INUYASHA, YOU GO AND TRY
AND FIND NARAKU'S CASTLE.
- RIGHT. MAKE SURE
YOU GET THE JEWEL.
- BE CAREFUL, INUYASHA.
UHH...OH.
[THUNDER]
- I WONDER WHAT'S GOING ON?
I'M STARTING TO LOSE
NARAKU'S SCENT.
UNH!
DOES IT MEAN THE BARRIER'S
BACK UP AROUND THE CASTLE?
I'VE GOT TO HURRY
BEFORE I LOSE HIM.
A BARRIER!
HUH! IT WON'T STOP ME!
WINDSCAR!
- AH!
- UNH!
- THE WINDSCAR DIDN'T WORK.
- HE WON'T GET AWAY THIS TIME.
UNH!
- [NARAKU CHUCKLES]
LORD SESSHOMARU,
I'M HONORED BY YOUR VISIT.
SO IN RETURN, I WILL
GLADLY ACCEPT YOUR CHALLENGE.
- AAH! WHAT'S HE BECOME?!
- HUH. A COLLECTION
OF REJECTED DEMONS.
THIS IS YOUR TRUE FORM, NARAKU?
- TRUE FORM? NO.
MY BODY IS FAR
FROM BEING COMPLETE.
- [JAKEN YELPS]
[WHIMPERING]
- HUH. YOU'LL DESTROY ME
FOR REFUSING TO DO AS YOU WISH?
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
HOW WOULD NARAKU BENEFIT
BY SESSHOMARU'S DEATH?
COULD THAT BE
WHAT NARAKU'S PLANNING?
- THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD
IS NEARBY.
- I DON'T LIKE THIS,
CONSIDERING WE'RE SO CLOSE
TO NARAKU'S CASTLE.
- YEAH, I AGREE.
I THINK THAT
THERE'S JUST ONE SHARD.
COME TO THINK OF IT,
SANGO'S BROTHER KOHAKU
HAD ONLY ONE SHARD IN HIM.
- HMM?
- IS IT KOHAKU?
- [CHEWING]
- THIS MELON IS REALLY SWEET.
- AHH. WOULD YOU LIKE
ANOTHER PIECE?
- YES. THANK YOU.
- HERE YOU ARE.
IF YOU LIKE IT THAT MUCH,
I CAN ALWAYS GO STEAL SOME MORE.
YOU DON'T
REMEMBER ANYTHING, KOHAKU?
- NO, I DON'T.
- NOT EVEN YOUR MOTHER
OR YOUR FATHER?
- I'VE FORGOTTEN.
- HUH.
I'VE NEVER HEARD OF A PERSON
FORGETTING EVERYTHING.
- IT'S NOT THAT.
IT'S JUST THAT...
I'M AFRAID I MIGHT REMEMBER
SOMETHING FRIGHTENING.
- I GUESS EVERYONE HAS
THINGS THAT THEY DON'T
WANT TO REMEMBER.
- HUH?
- I'M THE SAME.
MY PARENTS AND BROTHERS
WERE ATTACKED BY THIEVES.
THEY TRIED TO GET AWAY,
BUT THEY WERE KILLED.
I STILL HAVE NIGHTMARES
ABOUT THE NIGHT IT HAPPENED.
IT STILL SCARES ME.
AM I TALKING TOO MUCH?
YOU KNOW, PEOPLE ARE ALWAYS
TELLING ME TO BE QUIET.
- IT'S OK.
I DON'T MIND
IF YOU KEEP TALKING.
I DON'T GET TO TALK MUCH.
[BUZZING]
[ROARS]
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- KEEP QUIET.
- UH! IT'S HER AGAIN!
HER FACE IS
THE ONLY THING I REMEMBER.
I CAN'T GET HER OUT OF MY MIND.
[GROANS]
- UNH!
AH!
COME BACK HERE!
- I'D THINK TWICE
ABOUT FORCING THIS BOY
TO REMEMBER EVERYTHING.
HIS PAST REALLY
WOULD DESTROY HIM.
LET THE POOR LAD DIE IN BLISS,
FREE FROM ALL THOSE
TERRIBLE MEMORIES.
- KOHAKU, ARE YOU INSIDE?
KOHAKU.
- HMM.
- NARAKU, YOU'RE SUCH
A LOWLY DEMON.
YOU WILL NEVER HAVE THE POWER
OR RESOURCES TO HARM ME.
- HA HA HA!
- UH!
- HUH?
UNH!
- HUH. HOW LONG DO YOU INTEND
TO KEEP UP THIS LUDICROUS FARCE?
- [NARAKU CHUCKLES]
EVERY TIME YOU HACK AWAY
A PIECE OF ME,
YOU'RE SLOWLY COVERED
BY PIECES OF MY FLESH.
AND THEN...
- I KNEW IT!
NARAKU IS TRYING TO ABSORB
SESSHOMARU INTO HIS OWN BODY.
- HUH.
[PANTING]
HUH? WHAT'S GOING ON?
SESSHOMARU'S SCENT
COMES THIS FAR,
BUT THEN IT VANISHES.
- UH.
- WAIT! MAYBE THIS
IS NARAKU'S CASTLE!
UH! UH!
UNH!
THAT DEMONIC AURA
AND TOXIC GASES,
THIS HAS GOT TO BE
NARAKU'S BARRIER!
I'M SURE OF IT!
UNH!
AAH!
TETSUSAIGA!
THERE IT IS! NARAKU'S CASTLE!
- UH!
WHO'S THERE?
SOMEONE IS BREAKING
THROUGH MY BARRIER.
KAGURA, AFTER HIM.
- HUH? HMM.
- AN UNEXPECTED GUEST, NARAKU?
HOW VERY UNFORTUNATE FOR HIM.
I ASSURE YOU, HIS JOURNEY HERE
WILL HAVE BEEN IN VAIN.
BY THE TIME HE ARRIVES,
YOU'LL BE DEAD!
- [CHUCKLES]
JUST A LITTLE LONGER.
SOON YOU WILL BE
ABSORBED INTO MY BODY.
YOU WILL BE ONE WITH MY FLESH.
- UH! INUYASHA!
THE TETSUSAIGA'S BLADE IS RED.
- HMM? KAGURA.
- SO IT WAS YOU WHO BROKE
THROUGH THE BARRIER, INUYASHA.
- IN THE FLESH, KAGURA.
TAKE MY ADVICE: STAND BACK.
YOU'RE NO MATCH FOR ME
ANY LONGER.
BACK OFF AND LET ME PASS,
OR I'LL HAVE TO KILL YOU.
[BUZZING]
- THE SAIMYOUSHOU.
I CAN'T LET YOU PASS,
BECAUSE I'M UNDER WATCH MYSELF.
- HUH?
- I'D BETTER AT LEAST
PUT ON A SHOW OF FIGHTING HIM.
- HUH?
UNH!
HUH? WHAT'S GOING ON?
KAGURA'S WIND
HAS NO POWER AT ALL.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO FIGHT ME,
YOU BETTER GET SERIOUS!
- UNH!
- AAH!
YOU'LL HAVE TO DO
BETTER THAN THAT!
- THEY KNOW I'M NOT SERIOUS
ABOUT FIGHTING HIM.
I'LL HAVE TO TAKE THIS
UP A LEVEL.
[SNARLING]
- HMM.
PERFECT. THEY CAN
TAKE CARE OF HIM.
- HA! NO PROBLEM.
TRY THIS. WINDSCAR!
YOU'RE DEAD!
- [NARAKU LAUGHS]
- AH!
UNH!
- HMM?
PERHAPS I OVERESTIMATED
SESSHOMARU.
- OUT OF MY WAY!
WINDSCAR!
STEP ASIDE!
RRAAH!
- SESSHOMARU MAY BE DOOMED,
BUT WITH THAT SWORD,
INUYASHA COULD
PROBABLY DEFEAT NARAKU.
THEN I WOULD BE FREE.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- ♪ EVERY HEART ♪
♪ EVERY HEART ♪
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- I FAILED TO PREDICT
THAT INUYASHA WOULD COME HERE.
- I FOUND YOU, NARAKU.
AND THIS TIME, I'LL KILL YOU.
- FOOL. I'VE COMPLETELY ABSORBED
SESSHOMARU'S POWER INTO MY BODY.
YOU'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO DEFEAT ME NOW.
- SESSHOMARU?
- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT GOOD WILL COME OF IT,
BUT I'LL ABSORB YOU
INTO MY FLESH AS WELL.
- NEXT TIME,
"VANISHING POINT:
NARAKU DISAPPEARS."
- KOHAKU, KILL RIN.