>> EXCUSE ME, PASSING THROUGH.
[GROWLING]
>> AAH!
>> WHAT'S GOING ON IN HERE?
WHAT'S WRONG?!
HUH?
WHAT...WHAT HAPPENED?
>> I DON'T REALLY KNOW.
I WAS ONLY OUT OF THE ROOM FOR
A LITTLE BIT.
>> THIS IS TERRIBLE.
WHO ON EARTH COULD HAVE DONE
ALL THIS?
>> WELL, WE CAN'T JUST STAND
HERE!
WHAT ON EARTH ARE WE GOING
TO DO?!
>> WE CAN'T USE ANY OF THIS FOR
THE FESTIVAL NOW.
THERE WON'T BE ANY FOOD.
>> WE CAN'T GIVE UP YET.
>> HUH?
>> HOW COULD WE POSSIBLY PULL
IT OFF?
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT.
I HAVE AN IDEA THAT MIGHT WORK.
>> THAT'S ALL.
>> THAT'S 1,360 YEN, PLEASE.
[RUMBLING]
>> THERE'S 1,300...20...30...
>> WE DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME,
GIRLS, SO MOVE IT!
[GIRLS SHOUTING]
>> WHEW!
WE MADE IT, WITHOUT A SECOND
TO SPARE.
>> YEAH, WHATEVER.
BUT WHAT'S THIS STUFF SUPPOSED
TO BE, ANYWAY?
>> SALTY PICKLED POTATO CHIPS,
SWEET DUMPLINGS IN CORN SOUP,
PRE-COOKED SALISBURY STEAK WITH
YOGURT SAUCE, CHOCOLATE FONDUE
WITH PICKLED RADISHES, AND A
BUNCH OF OTHER STUFF.
>> KAGOME, YOU REALLY GET
COOKING WHEN YOU'RE UNDER
PRESSURE.
I HAD NO IDEA.
>> YEAH, WELL, LET'S JUST SAY
I'VE BEEN IN MY SHARE OF TIGHT
SPOTS.
>> SO, ARE ANY OF THESE THINGS
EDIBLE?
>> DUNNO.
>> YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME!
>> ON SECOND THOUGHT, IT'S
PROBABLY BETTER NOT TO
CHANCE IT.
>> YOU'RE NOT KIDDING.
>> AT LEAST THAT'S TAKEN
CARE OF.
WHO COULD HAVE DONE THAT TO THE
HOME EC ROOM, THOUGH?
[HISSING]
HMM...
>> HEY, KAGOME!
HELLO THERE!
WE'RE OVER HERE!
>> HI, YOU GUYS.
>> WHAT IS THAT THING?!
>> THAT'S A KUROTENMUDAKE!
IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
THAT WAS CLOSE.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?!
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE AT HOME!
>> WILL YOU SHUT YOUR TRAP?!
NEVER MIND WHY I'M HERE.
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?!
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
SERIOUSLY.
>> YOU KNOW.
YOU BROUGHT THOSE DRIED FOODS
BACK, DIDN'T YOU?
>> UH...
WHAT?!
ARE YOU TELLING ME IF YOU BOILED
THE DRIED FOOD, IT'LL TURN BACK
INTO DEMONS?!
>> YOU MEAN YOU BROUGHT THEM
BACK HERE WITHOUT KNOWING?
>> I WOULDN'T HAVE BROUGHT THEM
IF I KNEW, WOULD I?
>> GUESS THERE'S NO SENSE
WHINING ABOUT IT NOW.
SO HOW MANY DID YOU BRING?
>> LET'S SEE.
4, INCLUDING THE ONE JUST NOW.
>> 4?
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
NO WONDER THEY WERE GONE SO
QUICKLY.
>> SO I HAVE TO DEAL WITH DEMONS
AROUND HERE TOO, HUH?
WHAT A TOTAL PAIN.
>> DON'T YOU WORRY YOURSELF,
MY BOY.
I'LL DESTROY THE DEMON WITH A
HIGURASHI SHRINE SUTRA!
>> OH, NO, YOU DON'T, GRANDPA.
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS.
JUST LET US HANDLE IT, AND TRY
TO STAY OUT OF THE WAY.
>> WHAT ARE YOU SAYING, KAGOME?
YOU HAVE AN IMPORTANT
PRESENTATION, DON'T YOU?
>> SOUNDS SCARY, BUT I'LL HELP
YOU, KAGOME.
>> RIGHT!
THIS IS A ONCE-IN-A-LIFETIME
EVENT FOR YOU, KAGOME.
YOU LET US TAKE THINGS FROM
HERE.
>> LET'S DO IT!
>> YAY!
>> OW!
>> LISTEN UP, INUYASHA, AND
LISTEN UP GOOD.
YOU'VE GOT TO TAKE CARE OF THIS
BEFORE THINGS GET REALLY
COMPLICATED, YOU GOT IT?
>> YEAH.
SURE.
>> KAGOME!
>> AYUMI.
COVER THOSE THINGS UP!
WHY CAN'T YOU BE MORE CAREFUL?!
>> AAH!
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING, IDIOT?
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING OVER
THERE, SIS?
>> THEY CERTAINLY ARE LIVELY,
THOSE TWO.
>> WHAT WILL I DO?
HIS GAUDY OUTFIT IS BAD ENOUGH.
WITH HIS EARS STANDING UP LIKE
THAT, EVERYONE WILL FIGURE OUT
THERE'S SOMETHING UP WITH HIM.
[WHIMPERING]
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> ME?
NOTHING!
HA HA HA!
>> GEEZ.
HUH?
>> IT'S ALL OVER!
>> COME ON, LET'S GET GOING.
THE CHOIR PERFORMANCE IS
STARTING.
>> OH, YEAH, RIGHT.
>> WE'D BETTER MOVE IT!
>> HANG ON A SEC!
>> COME ON!
>> NO!
>> YOU CAN DO IT!
>> KAGOME!
[SHOUTING "HURRAY!"]
>> I WONDER WHY AYUMI HASN'T
SAID ANYTHING ABOUT INUYASHA.
HUH?
OH, YEAH, NOW IT ALL MAKES
PERFECT SENSE.
[SIGHS]
TALK ABOUT HAVING GOOD LUCK.
>> DON'T, KAGOME!
>> HUH?
>> DON'T GO AND JINX US.
SAVE THAT KIND OF TALK UNTIL
AFTER THE PERFORMANCE.
YOUR ALTO SOLO IS
SUPER-IMPORTANT!
REMEMBER!
>> OH, RIGHT.
CLUMSY ME.
OH, NO, I FORGOT ALL ABOUT IT.
>> KAGOME!
>> COMING!
>> HMM!
I CAN HANDLE THOSE WIMPY DRIED
DEMONS WITHOUT ANY HELP FROM
KAGOME.
4 MORE LEFT.
THEY'RE HIDING AROUND HERE
SOMEWHERE.
[SNIFFING]
GUESS I WON'T BE ABLE TO SNIFF
THEM OUT.
HUH?
I KNOW WHAT THAT IS!
THAT STUFF BURNS MY TONGUE!
[WHINING]
>> OHH...
THE DEMONS ARE SOMEWHERE AROUND
HERE.
I CAN'T SNEAK AWAY NOW, THOUGH,
OR I'LL LET EVERYONE DOWN AFTER
ALL THEIR HARD WORK.
>> HEY, MY MOM'S HERE!
SHE'S RIGHT IN THE BACK.
>> OH, WHAT SHOULD I DO?
>> GRR!
DAMN DEMONS!
WHERE DID THEY GO?
UNH!
>> CURSED DEMONS, WHERE ARE YOU?
SHOW YOURSELVES!
>> IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
>> NOW, NOW, SOTA, DON'T MAKE
A SCENE.
>> HERE'S YOUR DRINK, SIR.
I HOPE IT'S TO YOUR LIKING.
>> COME ON, OVER THIS WAY!
>> COMING.
LOOK, THERE'S KAGOME.
>> ♪ OVER YONDER SHINING BRIGHT
IS THE LIGHT OF THE SHIKON JEWEL
EVEN IN PEACE
IS THE JEWEL'S POWER
REMAINS EVER SO STRONG AND TRUE
ON BOTH HUMANS AND ON DEMONS
IT SLOWLY SHOWS ITS IMPACT
THROUGHOUT THE AGES
THE JEWEL'S POWER... ♪
>> OVER THERE!
IT'S GOT TO BE A DEMON!
I'VE GOT TO DO SOMETHING!
♪ ON BOTH HUMANS
AND ON DEMONS... ♪
DARN!
THIS IS NO TIME TO BE SINGING!
BUT I CAN'T PUT AYUMI AND
EVERYONE IN A BIND BY LEAVING
NOW!
IF I DO, THEY'LL NEVER LET ME
BORROW THEIR NOTES AGAIN!
THEN AGAIN, I CAN'T JUST IGNORE
THE DEMONS.
>> ♪ OVER YONDER
SHINING BRIGHT... ♪
>> NOTES OR DEMON?
[GRUNTING]
I DON'T NEED TO THINK ABOUT IT!
I KNOW WHAT'S MORE IMPORTANT!
>> ♪ ...FOUND AGAIN
SO THE FRAGMENTS... ♪
>> THERE'S ONE OF THE
TROUBLEMAKERS!
IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
>> ♪ AND NOW WE HOPE
THAT THE LAST SHARD
WILL BRIGHTLY SPARKLE OVER PEACE
BUT TO BECOME WHOLE AGAIN... ♪
>> INUYASHA.
THANK YOU.
>> ♪ AND NOW WE HOPE
THAT THE LAST SHARD
WILL BRIGHTLY SPARKLE
OVER PEACE ♪
>> TWO MORE TO GO.
WE'VE GOT TO HURRY AND FIND
THEM!
>> DAMN IT, IF THESE WEIRD
SMELLS DIDN'T INTERFERE, I'D
FIND THEM IN NO TIME.
>> KAGOME!
>> HUH?
THIS VOICE...
AAH!
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
IT'S ALMOST TIME FOR THE PLAY!
>> HUH?
UH...
>> THE ONLY WAY TO HANDLE THIS
IS TO END THE PLAY EARLY.
>> KAGOME.
>> HUH?
>> CHILL OUT, KAGOME.
YOU DON'T REALLY NEED TO BE
SO NERVOUS.
>> RIGHT.
I'M NOT ACTUALLY THAT NERVOUS.
>> HERE'S SOME ADVICE FOR YOU.
WHEN THE CURTAIN GOES UP, YOU
WON'T BE KAGOME ANYMORE.
IN THAT INSTANT, YOU'LL BECOME
ESCARGOT PUDDING!
>> RIGHT.
>> IF YOU BECOME ONE WITH THE
CHARACTER, YOUR LINES WILL COME
NATURALLY.
JUST BELIEVE IN YOURSELF.
>> YEAH, RIGHT.
THANKS, ERI.
>> OH, ONE MORE THING.
>> HMM?
>> IF YOU MESS UP, I'LL NEVER
LET YOU FORGET IT.
GOOD LUCK, AND I'LL SEE YOU
ON STAGE!
>> KAGOME.
>> HOJO?
>> HERE.
>> A PUMPKIN?
>> RUMOR HAS IT THAT EATING
PUMPKIN BEFORE PERFORMANCE WILL
KEEP AWAY THE STAGE JITTERS.
>> ISN'T IT SUPPOSED TO BE THAT
IMAGINING YOUR AUDIENCE IS
PUMPKINS GETS RID OF STAGE
FRIGHT?
>> SEE YA!
EAT UP THAT PUMPKIN, KAGOME.
>> WAIT!
HANG ON, HOJO!
HOJO, I CAN'T EAT THIS
THING RAW.
[PANTING]
>> COME ON OUT, DEMONS!
QUIT HIDING AND SHOW YOURSELVES!
[GROWLING]
>> THERE YOU ARE!
I'LL VANQUISH YOU WITH THIS
SACRED SUTRA!
>> IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
>> OH, SOTA, WHAT AM I GOING TO
DO WITH YOU?
HA HA HA!
[BIRDS SINGING]
[PEOPLE WHISPERING]
>> I CAN HARDLY WAIT.
>> ME EITHER.
[HORN]
[APPLAUSE]
>> JOSEPHINE!
WHERE ARE YOU, JOSEPHINE?
>> OH, HERE I AM,
LADY ESCARGOT PUDDING.
OH, WHAT'S KAGOME DOING?
SHE JUST SKIPPED 7 PAGES OF
DIALOGUE!
>> I KNOW THIS MAY SOUND
UNEXPECTED, BUT I WANT TO GET
MARRIED IMMEDIATELY.
YOU'LL FIND SOMEONE, WON'T YOU?
I'M SORRY, THIS IS THE ONLY
CHOICE I HAD.
>> OF COURSE, MISS.
BUT DON'T YOU THINK THAT COULD
WAIT UNTIL A LITTLE LATER?
>> I BEG YOUR PARDON, JOSEPHINE!
DO YOU REFUSE TO OBEY ME?
>> OH, NO, I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT
RIGHT AWAY!
AAH!
[LAUGHTER]
>> HEY, THIS DOESN'T SEEM RIGHT.
DIDN'T THEY SAY THIS WAS GOING
TO BE AN EPIC TRAGIC LOVE STORY?
>> YEAH, I GUESS.
BUT SO WHAT?
IT'S TOTALLY HILARIOUS!
>> IT WASN'T QUITE WHAT I WAS
EXPECTING.
>> KAGOME IS SHINING ON STAGE.
>> LADY ESCARGOT, TO ME YOU'RE
A MEUNIERE, AN OYSTER ON THE
HALF-SHELL!
>> YOU MAKE ME SO HAPPY,
PIERRE PANNACOTTA.
I THINK I'M DEEPLY, MADLY,
RAVENOUSLY--
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TO SAY IT.
COME, MY LADY.
LET ME FEEL YOUR EMBRACE!
>> PIERRE!
>> ESCARGOT!
>> HOLD IT RIGHT NOW!
>> UNH!
>> AAH!
>> NOW WHAT'S GOING ON
OUT THERE?
[GROWLING]
>> OH, NO, INUYASHA!
>> WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
YOU BETTER HAVE A GOOD EXPLANATION.
OK, WHO THE HELL DO YOU THINK
YOU ARE?
>> UM...UH...THE PRINCE?
>> OH, NO!
I'VE GOT TO DO SOMETHING!
PLEASE, STOP!
>> HUH?
>> YOU MUST NOT FIGHT OVER ME!
I BEG OF YOU, PLEASE, STOP THIS
VERY MINUTE!
>> WHAT'S THAT?
DID YOU GET HIT ON THE HEAD
OR...
>> NEVER MIND AND JUST FOLLOW
ALONG.
OK?
>> I'M WITH YOU, KAGOME.
>> MY DEAREST HANNABART PEKOPON,
THIS IS MY FAULT.
I IMPLORE YOU NOT TO BLAME
PIERRE!
>> HANNABART PEKOPON?
>> PIERRE, PLEASE LEAVE, I BEG
OF YOU!
I CANNOT INVOLVE YOU IN THIS
TANGLED WEB!
EXCELLENT!
NOW ALL I DO IS MAKE UP SOME
LINES AND WRAP THIS UP.
>> NO, I REFUSE TO LEAVE!
>> HUH?
>> STEP AWAY FROM LADY ESCARGOT!
>> AAH!
>> KEEP YOUR FILTHY HANDS OFF
HER, HANNABART!
WE WILL SEE WHICH OF US DESERVES
THE AFFECTION OF LADY ESCARGOT!
I CHALLENGE YOU TO A DUEL!
>> FINE WITH ME.
>> AH!
IT WAS GOING SO SMOOTHLY, TOO.
[RUMBLING]
>> WHAT THE--?
[ROARING]
>> A DEMON!
>> SO THIS IS WHERE YOU'VE BEEN
HIDING.
>> IT'S ALL OVER.
EVERYONE'S GOING TO FIND OUT.
AND AFTER I TRIED SO HARD TO
KEEP IT A SECRET.
>> WOW, THIS IS COOL!
>> HOW DID THEY DO THAT?
>> ALL RIGHT!
INUYASHA!
>> THIS IS GREAT!
SLAY THE DEMON!
>> HUH?
WAIT, THEY HAVEN'T FIGURED
IT OUT YET.
>> LOOKS LIKE OUR DUEL'S BEEN
POSTPONED.
>> LOOKS LIKE YOU GET
A REPRIEVE.
>> PREPARE TO DIE, DEMON!
>> OH!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, HOJO?
THAT'S A REAL DEMON!
INUYA--I MEAN, PEKOPON!
DO SOMETHING!
>> I'M ALREADY ON IT.
WINDSCAR!
>> AHH...
THAT'S A LITTLE OVERKILL, DON'T
YOU THINK?
[ROARING]
>> HAH!
HOW'S THAT?
>> LET'S GO, PEKOPON.
>> HUH?
>> PLEASE, TAKE ME AWAY NOW,
WHILE WE STILL HAVE THE CHANCE.
LEAD ME AWAY, BEYOND THE SKIES.
>> NO, SERIOUSLY, DO YOU HAVE
A HEAD INJURY?
>> JUST HURRY UP AND DO IT!
>> YEAH, YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
>> FAREWELL, EVERYONE.
AND REJOICE IN THE KNOWLEDGE
THAT I, ESCARGOT PUDDING, WILL
BE FREED FROM ALL MY WORLDLY
BURDENS, AND WILL LIVE HAPPILY
EVER AFTER!
FAREWELL!
>> BRAVO!
[WILD CHEERING]
>> AMAZING!
CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS WAS DONE BY
JUNIOR HIGH KIDS?
>> I CAN'T WAIT FOR NEXT YEAR'S
PRODUCTION.
>> YOU WERE GREAT, KAGOME.
THE PLAY WAS A HUGE SUCCESS.
>> I WAS REALLY WORRIED THERE.
BUT HOPEFULLY, IT TURNED OUT OK.
MORE OR LESS.
HUH?
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
IT FEELS LIKE AN EARTHQUAKE!
>> NOT A CHANCE.
I'M POSITIVE IT'S A DEMON.
>> A DEMON?
>> IT'S GOT TO BE POWERFUL IF IT
CAN RATTLE THE EARTH.
LOOKS LIKE THIS DEMON IS GOING
TO PUT UP EVEN MORE OF A FIGHT
THAN THE LAST ONES DID.
>> CAN YOU SENSE SOMETHING?
>> BETTER THAN THAT, I CAN
SEE IT.
LOOK UP THERE.
THAT'S OUR LAST DEMON!
[GROWLING]
>> IT'S UP ON THE ROOF?
>> LET'S GO, KAGOME!
>> COMING!
THIS THING IS SUPPOSED TO BE
A DEMON?
>> I GUESS SO.
I THINK IT'S CALLED
A YUMENAMAZU.
[GROWLING]
[GROWLING AND GULPING]
>> IS IT ALIVE?
>> AT LEAST WE HAVE OUR
MAIN DISH.
>> THIS WAS DEFINITELY A
FESTIVAL WE WON'T SOON FORGET.
>> KAGOME, YOU SURE WORKED HARD,
DEAR.
>> IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
>> THAT HAD TO BE ONE OF THE
LONGEST DAYS OF MY LIFE.
I'M EXHAUSTED.
>> YOU'RE KIDDING.
THOSE DEMONS WERE NOTHING
COMPARED TO FIGHTING NARAKU AND
THE BAND OF 7.
>> I WASN'T REFERRING TO
THE DEMONS.
>> ANYWAY, YOU'RE ALL DONE HERE
NOW, AREN'T YOU, KAGOME?
>> YEAH, I GUESS SO.
>> GOOD!
THEN IT'S TIME FOR US TO
HEAD BACK.
>> BACK?
TO WHERE?
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN, WHERE?
WE HAVE TO GO BACK AND FIND THE
SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
>> OH, RIGHT.
THE SHARDS.
>> WE'VE GOT TO HURRY AND FIND
A WAY TO STOP NARAKU.
>> UH-HUH!
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
[BUZZING]
>> WHAT TOOK YOU SO LONG?
>> I HEARD IT.
IT WAS VERY FAINT, BUT I'M
CERTAIN I HEARD IT.
STILL, IT WON'T BE EASY TO LAY
YOUR HANDS ON IT.
>> DON'T STALL, OR I'LL
KILL YOU.
TELL ME, WHERE CAN I FIND THE
LAST SHARD OF THE JEWEL?
>> THE LAST OF THE JEWEL SHARDS
IS AT THE BORDER OF THIS WORLD
AND THE NETHERWORLD.
>> AT THE BORDER OF THIS WORLD
>> THE SHRINE IS DESTROYED, AND
THE DEMON SEALED INSIDE IS
REAWAKENED.
>> WHENEVER THAT DEMON SEES A
BEAUTIFUL YOUNG GIRL, HE ASKS
HER TO BEAR HIS CHILD.
AND THEN HE ABDUCTS HER!
>> HORRIBLE!
NO, DESPICABLE!
>> MIROKU, YOU'RE ONE TO TALK.
>> FAIR LADIES, REST ASSURED,
YOU SHALL BE SAFE UNDER MY
PROTECTION.
>> NEXT TIME, "CHOKYUKAI AND
THE ABDUCTED BRIDE."
I LOVE PORK CUTLETS, BUT I
REFUSE TO BECOME A PIG DEMON'S
BRIDE!