[TELEPHONE RINGING]
- HIGURASHI RESIDENCE.
- HELLO, MR. HIGURASHI.
THIS IS YUKA.
- OH, SO GOOD OF YOU
TO CALL AT A TIME LIKE THIS.
- A TIME LIKE THIS?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- IT'S HER BACK.
SHE'S BEEN BEDRIDDEN
WITH PINWORMS FOR SO LONG,
HER BACK'S OUT.
- ARE THOSE CONTAGIOUS?
- UH...
- THANKS, GRAMPS.
YOU'RE A HUGE HELP.
GIVE ME THAT.
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
- HI, CAN I SPEAK
WITH KAGOME, PLEASE?
- NO.
SHE'S HAVING PROBLEMS
WITH HER DIABETES THIS WEEK.
- WHAT?
SHE'S NOT IN THE HOSPITAL
AGAIN, IS SHE?
- UH...
- HMM!
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
- BERIBERI, NEURALGIA,
AND RHEUMATISM?
- IT MUST BE SOMETHING SHE ATE.
UH...
- HEY, WOULD YOU GIVE IT
A REST, GRAMPS?
IF YOU DO HAVE TO MAKE
SOMETHING UP,
HOW ABOUT A YOUNG PERSON'S
DISEASE,
SOMETHING LIKE MONO
OR CHICKENPOX?
- MY ILLNESSES
ARE PERFECTLY VALID.
BESIDES, I'M DOING YOU A FAVOR,
ACTING AS YOUR
PERSONAL SECRETARY
EVERY TIME YOU CROSS OVER
TO THE FEUDAL ERA.
I THOUGHT I WAS BEING
VERY IMAGINATIVE.
- WHY DO YOU HAVE TO MAKE THINGS
UP WHEN I'M STANDING RIGHT HERE?
- HMM.
COME TO THINK OF IT,
WHY ARE YOU HERE?
YOU'RE USUALLY AWAY
ON THE WEEKENDS PLAYING
SUPERHERO IN THE FEUDAL ERA,
WHICH IS WHY I WAS
ANSWERING THE PHONE.
- I CAN STAY HERE ONCE
IN A WHILE WITHOUT HAVING
TO EXPLAIN MYSELF, CAN'T I?
THIS IS THE TIME PERIOD
I BELONG IN, AFTER ALL.
- WELL!
[GRUNTING]
- SOUTA, DON'T YOU HAVE
SOMETHING BETTER TO DO?
WHY DON'T YOU GO OUTSIDE AND
FIND A HUMAN TO INTERACT WITH?
- HEY, GREAT.
THEN HOW ABOUT SEEING A MOVIE
WITH ME THIS SATURDAY?
- THIS SATURDAY?
- YEAH. I'LL BRING
A THERAPEUTIC BACK PAD FOR YOU.
- YOU'VE GOT THE HOTS FOR SOME
OTHER GUY, DON'T YOU, KAGOME?
- UH...
[GRUNTING]
- BETTER LUCK NEXT TIME!
GAME OVER!
- HMM?
IT'S OUR TEMPLE.
I HAVE EVERY RIGHT TO BE HERE.
BESIDES, IT'S NOT LIKE
I'M WORRIED ABOUT
INUYASHA OR ANYTHING.
HMM!
I'VE GOT A DATE TODAY, SO DON'T
EXPECT ME TO WAIT AROUND!
YOU HEAR THAT?
OH...
- I HAVE HAD ENOUGH!
- LET'S GET AT IT!
[GROWLING]
[GRUNTING]
AAH!
[GROANS]
- INUYASHA'S BEEN
THROWN TO THE GROUND!
- HE MAY HAVE THE WILL TO FIGHT,
BUT HIS STRENGTH HASN'T
HAD TIME TO RECOVER YET.
- I'M NO MATCH FOR HIS MIGHT.
HUH?
- HE'LL TRY AND FIGHT ME
WITH THE SACRED JEWEL.
- I HAVE TO GET IT
BEFORE HE DOES.
- HANDS OFF, DEMON!
- SHIPPO!
- YOU WON'T ESCAPE.
[ROARING]
[SCREAMING]
- IT'S SHOW TIME.
MULTIPLY!
UNH!
OH! AH!
UH! AH! OH!
[GROWLING]
PERFECT.
HA HA HA!
HAPPY HUNTING.
OH!
OOH...
[GROANING]
- HMM?
OK. NOW WHAT?
I CAN BARELY SENSE IT,
BUT I'M ALMOST POSITIVE
THERE'S A SHIKON
JEWEL SHARD NEARBY.
PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER, GIRL.
THERE'S NOBODY DOWN THERE.
NOTE TO SELF,
IGNORE THOSE LITTLE VOICES.
HUH?
I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS.
I'M GONNA MISS MY DATE.
- IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
[ROARING]
- INUYASHA!
- HE'S STRUGGLING
MUCH MORE THAN USUAL.
- INUYASHA'S WOUNDS
HINDER HIM INDEED,
BUT THE TRUE PROBLEM
LIES WITH KAGOME.
WITHOUT HER, IT SEEMS THAT
INUYASHA IS UNABLE TO REALIZE
HIS FULL POWER
AND STAVE OFF A DEMON.
- THE DEMON DRAWS ON
THE POWER OF A JEWEL SHARD.
I CAN SENSE IT.
- WHAT?
- STRIKE THE JEWEL!
IT'S YOUR ONLY CHANCE!
- WE MUST HAVE KAGOME'S AID.
SHE COULD FIND WHERE
THE FRAGMENT IS HIDDEN.
- FORGET ABOUT HER.
WE'RE ON OUR OWN.
KAGOME'S GONE FOR GOOD.
THE TREE WILL ENSURE THAT
THE WELL THAT CONNECTED
OUR WORLDS REMAINS SEALED.
SHE'LL NEVER RETURN HERE.
I WON'T STAND FOR IT ANY LONGER.
KAGOME WILL NEVER SEE THESE
DANGEROUS BATTLES AGAIN!
IRON REAPER!
- GET LOST.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- HE MAKES ME SO MAD SOMETIMES,
GETTING IN THE WAY WHEN
I'M SUPPOSED TO BE CRAMMING,
MAKING ME LATE
WHEN I SHOULD BE TAKING TESTS.
- KAGOME, ARE YOU, UM,
MAD AT ME OR SOMETHING?
- UH, WHY WOULD I BE MAD?
GET OVER IT, GIRL.
YOU'RE ON A DATE WITH
THE HOTTEST GUY IN SCHOOL.
WHY BLOW IT THINKING ABOUT
A CREEP LIKE INUYASHA?
SO, UH, WHAT WERE YOU
SAYING JUST NOW?
- KAGOME.
IS THIS TOO HARD?
- TOO HARD?
IT HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH YOU...
AND EVERYTHING TO DO WITH
INUYASHA AND MY HURT PRIDE.
OH, DON'T BE SILLY.
I'M HAVING THE TIME OF MY LIFE.
- NO.
I THINK I KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE.
- HOJO, IT'S NOTHING LIKE THAT.
INUYASHA MEANS NOTHING TO ME.
- YOU FORCED YOURSELF
HERE FOR MY SAKE,
EVEN THOUGH
YOUR BACK'S IN AGONY.
- OH!
- A CONVENTIONAL ANSWER
WOULD HAVE SUFFICED
AND MIGHT HAVE BEEN
EASIER ON YOU.
- GRANDPA, YOU TOLD HOJO, TOO?
OPEN YOUR EYES, PEOPLE.
DO I LOOK SICK TO YOU?
INUYASHA!
I WONDER IF HIS WOUNDS
HAVE HEALED YET.
WHAT IF HE'S GOTTEN WORSE?
WHAT IF HE'S...
SORRY. GOTTA FLY.
- WAIT!
- I'LL MAKE IT UP TO YOU!
- COME BACK, KAGOME!
[PANTING]
- IT'S HERE.
I SENSE A SHIKON
JEWEL SHARD NEARBY.
I CAN'T SEE IT.
WHERE IS IT?
WHERE'S THE JEWEL SHARD?
[GROANING]
- AH! THE WOLVES HAVE FOUND ME!
- I NEED TO GET BACK TO YOU.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, INUYASHA?
OHH!
NOW WHAT'S GOING ON?
THE JEWEL.
[GROANING]
SHIPPO, IT'S YOU.
- AH!
KAGOME!
- OH, SHIPPO!
- I THOUGHT WE WOULD
NEVER MEET AGAIN!
- I DON'T KNOW HOW,
BUT I MADE IT BACK.
[GROWLING]
[GASP]
- HUH?
KAGOME'S SCENT!
- HMM?
- IT'S KAGOME!
I'D KNOW HER SCENT ANYWHERE!
- YOU WILL NOT ESCAPE!
- CARE TO WAGER ON THAT?!
TIME TO PUT AN END TO THIS.
UNH!
[SCREAMING]
- INUYASHA'S STRENGTH
HAS RETURNED.
HUH? COME BACK!
FINISH HIM OFF
BEFORE YOU GO TO HER!
HUH?
AH!
- MIND EXPLAINING
WHAT'S GOING ON UP THERE?
- INUYASHA'S INJURIES
HAVEN'T HAD TIME TO HEAL.
THE DEMON'S DETERMINED TO TAKE
ADVANTAGE OF HIS WEAKNESS.
- SO INUYASHA WAS IN TROUBLE.
- HERE THEY COME!
[GRUNTING]
- YOU COULD USE MORE FIBER!
[GROANING]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[GASP]
- INUYASHA.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I TOLD YOU TO STAY AWAY!
HUH?
- INUYASHA!
- UH...
- I WAS SURE YOU'D DIED
OF YOUR INJURIES,
BECAUSE YOU DIDN'T
COME BACK FOR ME THIS TIME.
- YOU SHOULD HAVE LISTENED.
I TOLD YOU NEVER TO RETURN.
- I KNOW,
BUT I HAD TO COME BACK.
I NEEDED TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
- SHE NEEDED TO SEE ME?
KAGOME...
- WHY ARE YOU LOOKING
AT ME LIKE THAT?
ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY YOU DIDN'T
FEEL THE SAME WAY ABOUT ME?
I SPENT ALL THAT TIME WORRIED
ABOUT YOU, AND FOR WHAT?
YOU DIDN'T EVEN CARE
THAT I WAS GONE!
YOU JUST DON'T GET IT, DO YOU?
[CRYING]
- COME ON, KAGOME.
STOP THE TEARS.
DON'T BE SAD OVER ME.
- WHO SAID ANYTHING
ABOUT BEING SAD?!
I'M CRYING OUT OF FRUSTRATION!
- 30 SECONDS,
AND THEY'RE ALREADY AT IT.
I SUPPOSE, THOUGH, I SHOULD
SIMPLY COUNT MY BLESSINGS
THAT THINGS HAVE
RETURNED TO NORMAL.
- KAGOME HAS RETURNED
FROM HER ERA.
LADY KAEDE, KAGOME IS BACK.
DID YOU HEAR ME?
- MIROKU, DO YE NOT
THINK IT PECULIAR?
- WHAT'S THAT?
- THE DROVES OF VENOMOUS INSECTS
VANISHED WITHOUT WARNING.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
- THAT YOUNG WOMAN.
SHE IS KIKYO.
NAY. KIKYO PERISHED
50 YEARS AGO.
- WHO'S THAT?
I'M SENSING SOMEONE.
SOMEONE'S NEAR, SOMEONE
WITH SHARDS OF THE JEWEL.
- HUH?
- A LOT OF THEM.
- I SENSED THAT
YOU WEREN'T FAR AWAY.
YOU'RE NARAKU, AREN'T YOU?
- HMM.
- AT LAST, I'VE FOUND YOU.
- NARAKU.
IT'S HIM.
- ANSWER ME ONE THING
BEFORE I AVENGE KIKYO'S DEATH.
NARAKU, WHY DO YOU BEAR
SUCH A GRUDGE AGAINST ME?
- GOOD QUESTION.
I SUPPOSE YOU WISH
AN ANSWER TO THAT QUESTION,
ELSE ETERNAL REST WILL
SURELY ELUDE YOU IN DEATH.
- IT IS HIM.
- HUH?
- KAEDE. HAH.
AGE HAS NOT BEEN KIND TO YOU.
- DO YE KNOW ME?
AYE.
ONIGUMO, IS THAT NOT YOUR NAME?
- ONIGUMO.
[CHUCKLES]
THAT NAME BRINGS ME
SUCH FOND MEMORIES.
NAY.
I AM NARAKU, NOT ONIGUMO,
YET IT CANNOT BE DENIED
THAT I WAS BORN OF
ONIGUMO 50 YEARS AGO.
ONIGUMO WAS SUCH
A FOOLISH MAN INDEED.
HE BEGAN TO FOSTER DESIRES
FOR THE KINDHEARTED YOUNG
PRIESTESS WHO NURSED HIM.
EVENTUALLY, HE SUCCUMBED
TO HIS WEAKNESS AND
CALLED FORTH THE DEMONS.
- MY SOUL IS WRENCHED
TO THE CORE, YET IT STILL
HOLDS VALUE.
FEAST ON MY FLESH.
I MUST POSSESS
MY FORMER MOBILITY.
THEN THE JEWEL WILL BE MINE,
NOT TO MENTION
THE LOVELY MAIDEN KIKYO.
FEAST ON ME, DEMONS.
DEVOUR ME!
AND IN EXCHANGE, BESTOW ME WITH
YOUR MOBILITY AND STRENGTH!
YES.
- AND THAT IS HOW THE MANY
DEMONS MERGED TO BECOME ONE,
A DEMON NAMED NARAKU--
MYSELF.
IT REQUIRED COUNTLESS
DEMONS TO CREATE MY BODY.
BECAUSE THE PRIESTESS KIKYO
WAS SO POWERLESS,
THE REGION TEEMED WITH DEMONS.
HER POWER HAD DIMINISHED
BECAUSE SHE HAD FALLEN IN LOVE
WITH A WORTHLESS HALF-DEMON.
- OH!
[SIGHS]
- SHE SUBMITTED
TO HER CHILDISH DESIRES
AND ATTEMPTED TO USE
THE SHIKON JEWEL
FOR HER OWN PURPOSES.
FOR THAT, SHE WAS PUNISHED,
AND, INUYASHA, YOU SUFFERED
THE PUNISHMENT, AS WELL.
- HUH?
UNH!
- DIE, INUYASHA.
- UNH!
[GROANING]
- FOOL!
I HAVE NO DESIRE
WHATSOEVER TO BECOME HUMAN.
BUT I SHALL TAKE
THE SHIKON JEWEL NONETHELESS.
THANKS.
- YOU BASTARD!
YOU ARE TO BLAME FOR
EVERYTHING THAT HAPPENED!
YOU DECEIVED KIKYO AND I.
YOU TRICKED US INTO TRYING
TO KILL ONE ANOTHER.
- THEN TELL ME, HOW IS IT
THAT THE TRUST YOU HELD
IN EACH OTHER WAS
SO EASILY DESTROYED?
- WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
- IT WAS ANGER,
A BITTER ANGER,
THAT SET YOU
AGAINST ONE ANOTHER.
THAT, INUYASHA, IS
THE TRUE LEGACY OF THE TRUST
YOU SUPPOSEDLY HELD
FOR ONE ANOTHER.
EVEN KIKYO COULD NOT
COMPREHEND IT.
SHE SHOULD HAVE CHOSEN TO LIVE
AND USE THE POWER OF
THE SACRED JEWEL TO SAVE HER.
INSTEAD, SHE CHOSE DEATH.
HAD SHE PLEADED FOR HER LIFE,
HER PATHETIC, WRETCHED WISH
WOULD HAVE BEEN EASILY GRANTED.
THEN SHE WOULD HAVE UNDERSTOOD
THE ULTIMATE TRUTH OF DARKNESS.
FOOLISH WOMAN.
IT IS CLAIMED THAT
THE SACRED SHIKON JEWEL
GROWS MORE BEAUTIFUL
WHEN IT IS TAINTED WITH MALICE.
- KAGOME, LOOK INSIDE HIM!
HOW MANY FRAGMENTS ARE THERE?
- I KNOW THERE ARE LOTS.
10--NO, 20!
WAIT, THERE'S EVEN MORE
THAN I CAN COUNT!
- HEY, NARAKU, WANT TO SEE
SOMETHING REALLY SCARY?
I'LL SLIT YOU FROM HEAD TO TOE
TO SHOW YOU WHAT MALICE MEANS.
[GRUNTING]
IRON REAPER!
HUH?
[CHUCKLES]
- A CLOUD OF DESTRUCTION!
RUN!
- INUYASHA!
[WIND WHISTLING]
- FAREWELL, INUYASHA.
IT SEEMS YOU HAVE SUCCUMBED
TO MY CLOUD OF DESTRUCTION.
[GRUNTING]
- THINK AGAIN.
[GASP]
- IMPOSSIBLE.
HOW COULD HE HAVE
BROKEN THROUGH?
[GRUNTING]
- HE GOT AWAY.
THAT WICKED DEMON
MANAGED TO ESCAPE ME.
NO!
COME BACK AND FIGHT ME!
- A SPIDER ON HIS BACK?
- YES.
INUYASHA SAID THAT HE SAW
A SPIDER-SHAPED BURN MARK
IN THE MIDDLE OF NARAKU'S BACK.
- THE THIEF ONIGUMO SUFFERED
FROM TERRIBLE BURNS.
PERHAPS THAT PROVES
THAT NARAKU IS ONIGUMO.
- A SPIDER ON HIS BACK.
THAT SHALL SERVE
AS NARAKU'S OWN SIGN.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- A FAMILY CALLS ON US
TO AID THE SOUL OF A WOMAN
WHO HAS PASSED AWAY BY
PROTECTING IT FROM EVIL DEMONS.
THE DEMONS STEAL HER SPIRIT
AND THOSE OF NUMEROUS OTHERS
AND MAKE AWAY WITH THEM.
IT TURNS OUT THAT
THE SPIRIT-THIEVING DEMONS
ARE BEING CONTROLLED
BY A FEARSOME PRIESTESS.
PRIESTESS?
WAIT.
THAT COULD BE KIKYO.
IF IT IS HER, WHAT DO WE DO?
NEXT TIME, "A WICKED SMILE:
KIKYO'S WANDERING SOUL."
SEE YOU SOON!