>> 50 YEARS EARLIER, INUYASHA
AND KIKYO HAD FALLEN INTO
NARAKU'S TRAP, AND THEIR LOVE
FOR EACH OTHER HAD TURNED TO
DEADLY HATRED.
I BROKE THE SPELL ON INUYASHA,
AND KIKYO WAS LATER RESURRECTED
THROUGH URASUE'S BLACK MAGIC.
I DO BELIEVE THAT A MORTAL CAN
UNDERSTAND A DEMON'S FEELINGS.
THE FRIENDSHIP I SHARE WITH
INUYASHA, SHIPPO, AND EVEN
KIRARA IS VERY REAL.
STILL, I CAN'T EVEN BEGIN TO
COMPREHEND THE PAIN OF SOMEONE
LIKE KIKYO, WHO DIED AND THEN
WAS BROUGHT BACK TO LIFE.
KIKYO, SOMEDAY, THE PAIN IN YOUR
HEART WILL SUBSIDE.
>> HMM.
THAT GIRL.
[MOANING]
>> A SOUL COLLECTOR.
WHAT IS IT DOING HERE?
DON'T INTERFERE.
GO AWAY!
LEAVE ME ALONE!
HUH?
>> SO YOU WANTED TO DIE, OR
RATHER, YOU WANTED TO REMAIN
DEAD?
>> I KNOW YOU.
YOU'RE KIKYO, AREN'T YOU?
>> HOW IS IT THAT YOU KNOW MY
NAME?
>> I KNEW IT WAS YOU.
>> URASUE MUST HAVE BROUGHT HER
BACK TO LIFE.
I HAD NO IDEA THAT OTHERS SHARED
MY SUFFERING.
[MEN YELLING]
[SCREAMING]
>> DESTROY THEM, MY LIFELESS
CLAY WARRIORS!
STAIN THE EARTH WITH THE
ENEMIES' BLOOD!
>> AAH!
>> HA HA HA!
HA HA HA!
TAKE A GOOD LOOK AT ME, MOTHER.
I SHALL FILL THIS WORLD WITH THE
WALKING DEAD.
[WOLF HOWLING]
[SNIFFING]
>> SO WHAT'S THE MATTER?
SMELL SOMETHING?
>> NOW I KNOW WHAT IT IS, THE
SMELL OF MEDICINAL HERBS.
>> HERBS?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> IT'S THE EXACT SAME SMELL AS
THE HERBS USED BY THE SORCERESS
URASUE WHEN SHE RESURRECTED
KIKYO.
>> DID SOMEONE SAY URASUE?
>> I HOPE I'M WRONG ABOUT THIS.
WAIT HERE.
I'LL CHECK IT OUT.
>> UNH!
INUYASHA!
UNH!
>> HOW CAN HE EXPECT US TO JUST
SIT AROUND AND WAIT?
>> YEAH.
WE'RE AS WORRIED AS HE IS.
>> I DON'T GET IT.
WHEN KIKYO WAS RESURRECTED, I'M
SURE SHE KILLED URASUE.
[GROANING]
HOW COULD URASUE BE BACK?
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
[THUD]
>> HUH?
OHH!
CLAY WARRIORS?
STOP!
WHAT DO YOU WANT WITH ME?
AAH!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I COMMAND YOU TO LEAVE ME ALONE!
OBEY ME!
AAH!
NO!
I REFUSE TO GO BACK!
RELEASE ME!
>> LET HER GO!
>> OHH!
>> IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
>> SO I WAS RIGHT--THE CLAY
WARRIORS URASUE CREATED.
>> INUYASHA!
>> HUH?
>> INUYASHA.
>> ARE YOU OK?
>> YEAH.
>> THOSE FIGURES AGAIN.
LOOK AT THEM MIROKU.
>> HUH.
THOSE ARE THE CLAY
WARRIORS BAKED FROM HUMAN BONES
AND GRAVEYARD SOIL.
>> WHAT ARE THEY DOING HERE,
THOUGH?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON,
BUT IT SEEMS LIKE THEY WERE
AFTER THAT GIRL.
[GASPS]
>> IS SHE ALIVE?
>> FUNERAL INCENSE.
[GASPS]
>> YEAH.
IT'S THE SMELL OF MEDICINAL
HERBS USED BY URASUE.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
>> THIS GIRL IS DEAD JUST LIKE
KIKYO.
SHE WAS REVIVED BY URASUE'S
BLACK MAGIC.
>> THE WALKING DEAD LIKE KIKYO.
[GRUNTS]
>> IT HAPPENED A LONG TIME AGO,
SOON AFTER I BEGAN TRAVELING
WITH INUYASHA.
I WAS CAPTURED BY URASUE, WHO
HAD STOLEN KIKYO'S ASHES.
>> I NEED YOU IN ORDER TO
COMPLETELY RESURRECT KIKYO.
>> I WAS PUT INTO A TUB FILLED
WITH WATER THAT REEKED OF
MEDICINAL HERBS.
IT WAS A HORRIBLE, FRIGHTENING
EXPERIENCE.
URASUE WAS A SORCERESS WHO USED
BONES AND SOIL FROM THE
GRAVESITE TO REVIVE THE DEAD.
SHE HAD TRIED TO DRAW OUT
KIKYO'S SOUL, WHICH HAD
TRANSMIGRATED INTO ME.
ULTIMATELY, URASUE RESURRECTED
KIKYO, BUT IN THE END, URASUE
WAS DESTROYED BY THE VERY WOMAN
SHE HAD BROUGHT BACK FROM THE
GRAVE.
>> THE SCENT OF THE HERBS HAS
LED US THIS FAR, BUT WE'VE FOUND
NOTHING.
>> NO. I WOULDN'T SAY NOTHING.
IT'S FAINT, BUT KIKYO'S SCENT IS
STILL HERE.
>> KIKYO'S SCENT?
>> I'M FAIRLY SURE SHE'S NOT
HERE ANYMORE THOUGH.
UNH!
>> I'VE HEARD THAT A STRANGE
ARMY OF SOLDIERS HAS RECENTLY
DESTROYED A NUMBER OF CASTLES IN
THIS AREA.
>> HUH. I'VE GOT BETTER THINGS
TO DO THAN GET INVOLVED IN
STUPID HUMAN WARS.
>> THERE ARE RUMORS THAT IT'S A
DEMON THAT'S BEHIND THE ATTACKS.
THESE SOLDIERS CANNOT BE SLAIN
WITH SWORDS, AND EVEN SPEARS
WILL NOT PIERCE THEIR ARMOR.
>> AND YOU THINK THEY'RE
URASUE'S WARRIORS?
>> ONE THING IS FOR CERTAIN, AND
THAT IS THAT SOMEONE IS BRINGING
THE CLAY WARRIORS TO LIFE.
>> COULD KIKYO BE DOING IT?
YOU THINK SHE'S CONTROLLING
URASUE'S SOLDIERS?
>> WHO'S TO SAY REALLY?
HOWEVER, THE FACT IS UNDENIABLE
THAT WHEN WE CAME UPON THE
RESURRECTED GIRL WE ALL
DEFINITELY SENSED KIKYO'S
PRESENCE.
>> DAMN IT!
WHAT'S GOING ON ANYWAY?
>> HEY, INUYASHA.
WHERE ARE YOU HEADED NOW?
>> WHERE ELSE?
I'M GONNA SLAY WHOEVER'S
CONTROLLING THOSE CLAY WARRIORS.
>> OHH.
WHENEVER KIKYO'S INVOLVED,
INUYASHA PLUNGES IN WITHOUT
ANOTHER THOUGHT.
>> HEY.
YOU FINALLY WOKE UP.
ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE FEELING OK?
[GRUNTING]
DON'T OVERDO IT.
JUST GO ON AND REST.
>> SO MANY PEOPLE INTERFERING
LIKE THOSE SOUL COLLECTORS LAST
NIGHT.
[GASPS]
>> SOUL COLLECTORS?
>> SHE SHOULD HAVE JUST LEFT ME
FOR DEAD WHERE SHE FOUND ME?
>> DID YOU SEE KIKYO?
YOU MEAN HER SOUL COLLECTORS?
>> HMM.
SO THAT WAS KIKYO.
I WONDERED WHERE SHE HAD
DISAPPEARED TO AFTER SHE KILLED
MY MOTHER.
>> YOUR MOTHER?
WHO WOULD THAT BE?
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> WHOEVER'S CONTROLLING THESE
SOULLESS WARRIORS IS AROUND HERE
SOMEWHERE.
>> NEXT, WE'LL ATTACK THIS
CASTLE, EVEN THOUGH IT'S HEAVILY
GUARDED.
>> NO ONE CAN HOPE TO OVERCOME
THE POWER OF OUR ARMY.
>> OUR DREAM OF REIGNING THROUGH
THE LAND WILL SOON COME TRUE.
>> IT'S ALL BECAUSE OF YOU,
MILORD.
>> AND THE CLAY WARRIORS CREATED
BY ENJU AND ME.
HA HA HA!
HMM?
[THUNDER]
>> UNH!
WHERE IS KIKYO?
UNH!
I DON'T SENSE HER PRESENCE
ANYWHERE.
HUH?
>> WHAT BUSINESS DO YOU HAVE IN
THIS CASTLE?
>> SO IT WASN'T KIKYO!
YOU'RE THE ONE!
YOU'RE CONTROLLING URASUE'S CLAY
WARRIORS AND WAGING WAR ON THIS
REGION!
THIS PLACE REEKS OF DEAD MEN.
>> MY NAME IS KAWARAMARU.
I AM URASUE'S SON.
>> HUH?
URASUE'S SON?
>> YOU WERE A TRAVELING
COMPANION OF THE PRIESTESS WHO
KILLED MY MOTHER.
PREFECT TIMING.
I BUILT AN ARMY OF SOLDIERS IN
ORDER TO CONQUER THE NEIGHBORING
LANDS, BUT FIRST, I SHALL DEAL
WITH YOU.
TURN HIM TO FLESH AND BONE!
>> NOT HAPPENING!
YOU'RE DEAD!
IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
A MIASMA HAS BEEN PLACED IN THE
CHEST OF THOSE CLAY WARRIORS.
>> YOUR SKIN AND FLESH WILL
MELT.
I'LL USE YOUR BONES TO MAKE YOU
MY SLAVE!
[GRUNTING]
[COUGHING]
>> MY VISION'S GETTING BLURRY.
MOVE!
UNH!
WIND SCAR!
>> HMM. HE ESCAPED.
>> FRAGMENTS OF CLAY WARRIORS
FROM MY KILN.
KAWARAMARU FORCED ME TO MAKE
THEM.
>> KAWARAMARU?
>> MY NAME IS ENJU.
URASUE BROUGHT THE ONE KNOWN AS
KAWARAMARU AND ME BACK FROM THE
DEAD TO SERVE HER.
SHE EVEN CALLED US HER CHILDREN.
IT SEEMS SO VERY LONG AGO.
>> SHE USED HER BLACK MAGIC?
>> KAWARAMARU WAS ONCE A
WARRIOR, WHO WAS BETRAYED BY A
VASSAL.
HE EXCELS IN COMMANDING
SOLDIERS, AND AFTER HE WAS
REBORN, URASUE GAVE HIM THE
POWER TO CONTROL CLAY WARRIORS.
BEFORE MY DEATH, I USED TO BE A
POTTER BY TRADE.
>> YES, I THINK I UNDERSTAND.
KAEDE USED TO BELIEVE THAT
URASUE BROUGHT THE DEAD BACK TO
LIFE IN ORDER TO TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF THE POWERS THEY HAD WHILE
ALIVE.
>> URASUE MADE ME HELP HER
CREATE CLAY WARRIORS.
AND SHE INTENDED TO MAKE THAT
PRIESTESS HELP SEARCH FOR SHARDS
OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AAH!
>> AND THEN URASUE WAS KILLED.
THEN KAWARAMARU BEGAN TO ORDER
ME TO MAKE THE CLAY WARRIORS.
I DIDN'T WANT TO.
I DIDN'T WANT ANY PART OF
CREATING CLAY WARRIORS WHO
KILLED PEOPLE, BUT WHEN I BECAME
FRAIL FROM A WEAKENED SPIRIT,
KAWARAMARU BROUGHT BACK MORE
SOULS OF THE DEAD TO ANIMATE
THIS BODY.
I DIDN'T WANT ANY.
I JUST WANTED TO REST IN PEACE.
>> AND SO YOU RAN AWAY?
>> HUH?
>> YOU ARE BEAUTIFUL, EVEN
THOUGH YOU WERE ONCE DEAD.
>> MIROKU, COME ON.
>> YOU SAY YOU WANT TO REST IN
PEACE, YET YOU HAD A SECOND
CHANCE AT LIFE.
WHY DIDN'T YOU CHERISH SUCH A
GOLDEN OPPORTUNITY?
TURN AROUND.
LOOK AT THE BUDDHA'S SMILE.
HE SMILES BECAUSE HE LOVES ALL
FORMS OF LIFE, EVERY LIVING
BEING.
>> OH, MIROKU.
>> INCREDIBLE, MIROKU.
WHAT A GREAT THING TO SAY.
>> HE MIGHT BE ABLE TO DECEIVE
YOU TWO, BUT HE'S NOT FOOLING
ME.
>> AND SO IT SEEMS KAWARAMARU
DOES NOT INTEND TO LET YOU GO.
>> UNH!
>> THEY FOLLOWED HER!
>> SHIPPO, KIRARA, LISTEN!
STAY HERE AND PROTECT ENJU.
>> COUNT ON IT!
THEY WON'T GET NEAR HER.
>> STOP RIGHT THERE, OR I'LL
SHOOT.
>> IT'S USELESS TO TALK TO THEM.
LIFELESS CLAY WARRIORS WOULD
NEVER UNDERSTAND.
HYAH!
>> HE CRUSHED THE CLAY WARRIORS
I MADE.
>> NOBODY WILL DENY THAT MIROKU
ISN'T A LECHEROUS MONK, BUT HE
HAS INCREDIBLE SPIRITUAL POWERS.
>> ENJU, WE'RE GONNA BREAK UP
EVERY ONE OF THESE CLAY
WARRIORS.
>> NOBODY COULD POSSIBLY WANT TO
BE A SOLDIER AFTER DEATH!
>> AAH!
RETURN TO THE SOIL AND FIND
ETERNAL PEACE.
>> IT'S USELESS.
A HANDFUL OF SOLDIERS WON'T STOP
HIM.
KAWARAMARU CONTROLS THOUSANDS
MORE.
BESIDES--HMM?
OHH!
>> HUH?
[GRUNTING]
>> OVER THERE!
>> KAWARAMARU'S ARMY IS OFF TO
CONQUER ANOTHER CASTLE
SOMEWHERE.
>> THERE MUST BE THOUSANDS OF
THEM.
>> WE CAN STILL DEFEAT THEM.
SO PROMISE ME THIS--IF WE WIN
THIS BATTLE, PROMISE YOU'LL TRY
LIVING.
WHY?
WHY ARE YOU DOING ALL THIS FOR
ME?
>> HOLD IT RIGHT THERE!
>> HUH?
>> HYAAAH!
>> IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
>> INUYASHA.
>> HUH?
>> LOOK AT THAT WARRIOR, THE ONE
IN THE BLUE ARMOR.
IS HE THE GENERAL?
>> YEAH.
SO WE JUST HAVE TO STOP HIM!
>> UNH!
THERE ARE TOO MANY OF THEM.
I'LL USE MY WIND TUNNEL.
>> STOP, MIROKU.
THE CLAY WARRIORS HAVE MIASMA IN
THEIR CHESTS.
IF YOU'RE NOT CAREFUL, THE
TOXINS WILL POISON YOU.
>> THEN I'LL HAVE TO USE SACRED
SUTRAS!
>> OUT OF THE WAY!
MOVE IT!
BLADES OF BLOOD!
>> YOUR EFFORTS ARE IN VAIN.
>> INUYASHA!
>> HUH?
>> MIROKU!
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE
DOING?
GET OUT OF HERE!
RUN FOR IT, KAGOME!
>> YOU, TOO, SANGO.
MOVE IT!
YOUR PROTECTIVE MASK WON'T GUARD
AGAINST THIS POISON.
>> KIRARA, TAKE KAGOME.
>> I'VE GOT HER!
TRANSFORM!
>> I'M TRYING TO PROTECT YOU
HERE.
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING, JUMPING
INTO THE MIDDLE OF THIS?
>> SORRY.
>> SO DID SANGO BRING THE DEAD
GIRL THAT URASUE RESURRECTED?
>> YES. SHE WAS THE ONE WHO
CREATED THE CLAY WARRIORS.
UNTIL SHE RAN AWAY, THAT IS.
>> HMM.
>> SHE DIDN'T WANT TO HAVE TO
MAKE ANY MORE OF THOSE CLAY
KILLERS.
>> SHE DIDN'T HAVE PROBLEMS
MAKING THE FIRST COUPLE
THOUSAND, AND ONLY NOW SHE'S
SICK OF IT?
SOUNDS A LITTLE TOO CONVENIENT.
>> INUYASHA!
>> KILL ME.
THAT'S WHAT I'VE WANTED ALL
ALONG.
>> HMM.
HUH?
>> THAT'S WHY I RAN AWAY FROM
YOU.
>> ENJU.
>> WE ARE THE WALKING DEAD.
WE HAVE NO RIGHT TO BE IN THIS
WORLD.
>> HA!
DON'T MAKE ME LAUGH.
IF THAT'S THE CASE, THEN WHY
WERE WE ALL RESURRECTED?
WAS IT JUST MOTHER'S WHIM?
WHY WON'T YOU COME JOIN ME?
ENJU, IF WE SLAY EVERY LIVING
PERSON, YOU CAN FINALLY FIND
PEACE AS ONE OF THE WALKING
DEAD.
>> GRR!
UNH!
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND WHY ENJU
WANTED TO DIE SO BADLY?
SHE WANTED TO DIE BECAUSE SHE
DOESN'T WANT YOU TO KILL
ANYMORE.
>> A LIVING MORTAL COULD NEVER
UNDERSTAND WHAT WE FEEL!
>> DAMN!
FOOLS LIKE YOU ARE BETTER OFF
DEAD!
>> HA HA!
YOU'RE WRONG.
WE HAVE BEEN REBORN.
WE'LL DO AS WE PLEASE.
[HORSE NEIGHS]
ARISE FROM THE EARTH!
I SUMMON YOU, DEMON OF HELL!
[GRUNTING]
[GROWLING]
HA HA HA!
DEMON OF HELL, BY MY MOTHER'S
SORCERY, AWAKEN!
ATTACK.
DESTROY THEM!
>> JUST TRY IT!
[GROWLS]
AAH!
[DEMON GROANING]
>> INUYASHA!
>> HA HA!
HE'LL SQUEEZE THE VERY LIFE OUT
OF YOU.
>> I'LL USE MY WIND TUNNEL.
GET AWAY FROM THERE.
>> STAY OUT OF IT, MIROKU.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF HIM!
GET BACK!
>> KAGOME.
>> COMING.
>> ENJU.
>> HA HA HA!
>> YOU'RE DISGUSTING.
YOU CAN'T USE HUMAN SOULS FOR
YOUR OWN LITTLE GAMES!
NOW DIE!
[DEMON GROWLING]
>> AAH!
>> THE POWER OF THE WIND SCAR
BLASTED THE DEMON AKURA
AND KAWARAMARU INTO ASHES.
>> KAWARAMARU.
>> YOU SURE THIS IS OK?
>> DEFINITELY.
MY MOTHER USED TO TELL ME, WE
REALLY DON'T KNOW WHAT OUR
PURPOSE IS HERE ON EARTH, BUT WE
KEEP ON GOING.
>> THAT'S WHAT MAKES THINGS
INTERESTING.
I SUPPOSE THERE'S NO TELLING
WHAT TOMORROW WILL BRING.
>> HEY. I WONDER WHAT ENJU'S
UP TO.
>> HMM?
SHE'S PROBABLY JUST FEEDING A
FIRE.
>> HUH?
WAS IT KIKYO THAT BID YOU TO
COME?
I AM GIVING LIFE A CHANCE NOW
JUST AS I PROMISED.
>> GIVING LIFE A CHANCE.
>> [WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> WHY ARE THE VILLAGERS AFTER
MIROKU?
>> KNOWING HIM, HE PROBABLY GOT
HIMSELF INTO TROUBLE A LONG TIME
AGO.
>> STILL, THEY WERE AWFULLY
ANGRY.
>> I CAN'T IMAGINE WHAT ALL THIS
IS ABOUT.
OH, NEVER MIND.
NO SENSE BROODING OVER IT.
>> YOU'VE GOTTEN YOURSELF INTO
SO MANY TIGHT SPOTS, YOU CAN'T
GET YOUR STORIES STRAIGHT.
>> PLEASE.
THIS IS ALL JUST A BIG
MISUNDERSTANDING.
>> NEXT TIME, "THE MYSTERIOUS,
LECHEROUS MONK."
>> COME ON.
LET'S GET THIS MATTER CLEARED
UP.