>> HERE WE COME.
IT'S THE START OF "INUYASHA."
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL THE
SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY HIROKU
WITH MY TETSUSAIGA.
>> KOGA AND SESSHOMARU.
THEY SEEM TO BE TOTAL OPPOSITES,
BUT THEY HAVE ONE THING IN
COMMON: NEITHER OF THEM CAN
STAND INUYASHA.
>> IT'S UP TO ALL OF US.
>> TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FEUDAL FAIRY TALE.
>> "INUYASHA."
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> UHH!
>> [GASPING]
>> ALMOST HAD HIM.
>> SURE ISN'T EASY FINDING FOOD
IN UNFAMILIAR TERRITORY.
>> I KNOW, AND I'M DYING
OF HUNGER.
[WOLVES WHINING]
>> OUR BAD LUCK'S GOT TO CHANGE.
>> WE WOULD'VE BEEN BETTER OFF
ATTACKING THAT HUMAN VILLAGE
A WHILE BACK.
>> NAH, KOGA ORDERED US NOT TO
BOTHER HUMANS ANYMORE.
>> AND IF WE WENT AFTER PEOPLE
AGAIN, KAGOME WOULD BE REAL MAD.
>> WE SURE HAVE TRAVELED
A LONG WAY.
>> YEAH.
>> [INDISTINCT VOICE
IN DISTANCE]
>> HUH?
>> [SECOND INDISTINCT VOICE
IN DISTANCE]
>> HUH?
>> WHO WAS THAT?
[RUSTLING]
>> [GRUNTING] HUH?
>> WHAT?
IT'S A HUMAN GIRL.
[GROWLING]
HEY, HEY!
CALM DOWN,, YOU MUTTS.
>> WE CAN'T EAT HUMANS.
[WHINING]
>> [WHIMPERING]
>> ALL RIGHT, OUR WORK
HERE'S DONE.
I'M GOING ON AHEAD.
YOU CAN EAT WHATEVER YOU LIKE
IN THIS VILLAGE.
[GROWLING]
>> UHH, UHH, UHH--UHH!
>> [WHIMPERING] AAH!
>> [WHIMPERING]
>> [INDISTINCT] HUH?
>> MASTER JAKEN!
>> HMM?
>> [THINKING] NO SURPRISE
THAT SHE'S AFRAID.
RIN WAS ONCE ATTACKED BY WOLVES.
YOU THERE!
WOLVES!
LEAVE THIS AREA IMMEDIATELY!
>> WHY SHOULD WE?
BESIDES, WHO DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE TALKING TO?
>> WE'RE THE RIGHT- AND
LEFT-HAND MEN OF KOGA, THE YOUNG
LEADER OF THE WOLF DEMON TRIBE!
I'M HAKKAKU, THE SHREWD ONE.
>> I'M GINTA.
I'VE GOT DIMPLES.
>> HA HA HA HA!
YOU MUST HAVE HEARD OF US.
>> NOPE, NEVER HEARD OF YOU.
>> WHOA?
>> WHAT?
>> COWER IN FEAR, MANGY WOLVES!
IT HAS BEEN CENTURIES SINCE
I BEGAN SERVING LORD SESSHOMARU.
CROSSED THROUGH 3,000 WORLDS
HAVE I.
HIS MOST LOYAL FOLLOWER.
I ANSWER TO THE NAME JAKEN!
>> OH, BOY.
WHAT A BRAGGART.
>> WE'VE NEVER HEARD OF YOU
OR THIS SESSHOMARU.
>> HOW DARE YOU INSULT MY LORD!
YAAA!
>> WE'LL TAKE YOU ON IF IT'S A
FIGHT YOU'RE LOOKING FOR!
>> [GROWLING]
>> JAKEN, WHAT'S ALL THIS
COMMOTION?
>> LORD SESSHOMARU.
[GROWLING]
WHO ARE YOU AND WHAT DO
YOU WANT?
>> YOU LOOKING FOR A FIGHT?
>> WE CAN LEAVE, BUT IT AIN'T
OUT OF FEAR.
>> YEAH, YOU DON'T SCARE US,
MISTER.
AAH!
>> UH, RIN.
>> YES?
>> WEREN'T YOU GOING TO CATCH
YOURSELF SOME FISH?
>> [GASPING] YES!
>> [BREATHING HEAVILY]
>> I GOTTA SAY, HE WAS KIND OF
SCARY, DON'T YOU THINK?
>> I AGREE, BUT AIN'T WE
SEEN HIM BEFORE?
>> THE GUY SAID HIS NAME WAS
SESSHOMARU.
I'M SURE I'VE HEARD OF HIM
SOMEWHERE BEFORE.
WONDER WHO THE BIG MOUTH IS.
[GROWLING]
>> ANYWAY, WE'D BETTER GET
BACK TO KOGA.
>> YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
LET'S GO, WOLVES.
>> [BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GROWLING SOFTLY, PANTING]
>> HMPH.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
AROUND HERE, MUTTFACE?
>> JUST WHAT I WAS GONNA
ASK YOU.
>> [SCOFFS]
WELL, YOU SEE, I WOULD BE
LOOKING FOR NARAKU, EXCEPT THAT
I KEEP RUNNING INTO YOU.
>> SHUT UP, YOU MANGY WOLF.
YOU DON'T NEED TO
BUTT INTO THIS.
I'M THE ONE WHO'S
GONNA GET NARAKU.
>> UHH!
>> HEY!
>> SO SORRY, KAGOME.
I STILL HAVEN'T LOCATED NARAKU
FOR YOU.
NEXT TIME, I'LL BRING HIS HEAD.
>> [GIGGLING]
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT, REALLY.
>> HEY, KOGA!
>> AWW.
FOUND ANYTHING TO EAT?
>> NO, NOT EXACTLY.
>> YOU CAME BACK EMPTY-HANDED?
>> LISTEN UP, YOU SKINNY WOLVES.
YOU BETTER NOT BE THINKING ABOUT
ATTACKING ANY HUMANS.
>> WHAT'S IT TO YOU?
>> WHAT DID YOU SAY?
>> AS IF WE'D ATTACK HUMANS.
I'LL CATCH A BOAR OR TWO
IN NO TIME.
>> THEN HOW COME HE TRIED
TO EAT ME BEFORE?
>> HE'S JUST PUTTING ON AN ACT
BECAUSE HE DOESN'T WANT KAGOME
TO HATE HIM.
>> LIKE INUYASHA, KOGA SAYS WHAT
HE THINKS KAGOME WANTS TO HEAR.
>> AH!
OOH, THAT REMINDS ME.
HERE, WHY DON'T YOU EAT
SOME OF THESE?
>> HEY, KAGOME'S GIVING AWAY THE
LAST OF HER NINJA SNACKS!
>> KAGOME, I KNOW HOW MUCH YOU
WORRY ABOUT ME.
>> NOT REALLY.
>> UHH!
YOU DON'T NEED TO GIVE
OUR FOOD TO HIM.
>> SHE CAN DO WHAT SHE WANTS!
>> UHH!
IF THAT'S THE WAY YOU WANT ME!
>> [GRUNTING]
>> GIVE IT BACK!
>> [BOTH TALKING AT ONCE]
>> HEY, COME ON!
CUT IT OUT, YOU TWO!
>> KAGOME, EVER HEARD OF A GUY
CALLED SESSHOMARU?
>> A FAIR-SKINNED DOG DEMON
WHO WEARS A FUR OVER HIS KIMONO.
>> YEAH, I KNOW HIM.
HE'S INUYASHA'S OLDER BROTHER.
>> HUH?
>> INUYASHA'S BROTHER?
>> YOU MUTT!
UHH!
I CAN'T TAKE YOUR STENCH
ANOTHER MINUTE!
>> YOU'RE ONE TO TALK,
YOU PUNY WOLF!
>> WHAT KIND OF GUY IS THIS
SESSHOMARU?
>> WHERE TO START?
WELL, HE DOESN'T GET ALONG WITH
INUYASHA VERY WELL AT ALL,
AND HE HAS A POWERFUL EVIL SWORD
NAMED TOKIJIN.
HE'S EXTREMELY STRONG AND A BIT
ON THE CRUEL SIDE.
>> CRUEL?
>> [BOTH GRUNTING]
>> INUYASHA AND KOGA CAN SCRAP
LIKE THAT FOREVER, BUT I FEEL
PRETTY CERTAIN THAT THEY'D
NEVER KILL EACH OTHER.
I DON'T THINK SESSHOMARU WOULD
HESITATE TO KILL HIS OPPONENT,
THOUGH.
>> HEAR THAT?
>> WHO KNOWS, THOUGH?
HE COULD'VE CHANGED
FOR THE BETTER.
HE DOESN'T SEEM AS COLD-HEARTED
AS BEFORE.
[CRASHING]
>> [INUYASHA AND KOGA
TALKING AT ONCE]
>> WOULD YOU TWO KNOCK THAT OFF?
>> SOUNDS LIKE ONE DANGEROUS
OPPONENT.
>> GOOD THING WE DIDN'T
ENGAGE HIM IN A FIGHT.
>> HMM?
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER?
[BARKING, GROWLING]
>> [IMITATING WOLF]
>> ANYONE WANT TO EXPLAIN
WHAT THEY'RE DOING?
>> YOU HEAR THAT?
THEY ATTACKED THAT GIRL
THAT WE SAW EARLIER.
>> THE LITTLE KID WHO WAS
TRAVELING WITH SESSHOMARU.
>> I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU,
BUT I'M GETTING TIRED OF THIS.
>> IT CAN'T GO ON FOR
TOO MUCH LONGER.
>> INUYASHA, STET.
>> [GRUNTING] UHH.
THANKS A LOT, TRAITOR.
>> I'LL ACCEPT THIS FOOD WITH
GRATITUDE AND THINK OF IT AS A
TOKEN OF YOUR DEEP LOVE FOR ME.
>> DON'T GIVE IT TOO MUCH
THOUGHT, HEH.
>> SEE YA.
STOP!
WAIT UP, KOGA!
>> SEE YA LATER, KAGOME.
>> WELL, AT LEAST THE
FIGHT IS OVER.
>> NOW I GUESS WE CAN PICK UP
WHERE WE LEFT OFF AND GO ON TO
THE NEXT VILLAGE.
>> [GRUNTING]
YOU'RE NOT JUST GONNA
LEAVE ME HERE!
>> OH, THESE DON'T SMELL AT ALL
LIKE MEAT, BUT THEY'RE GOOD.
>> HEY, IF WE KEEP GOING THIS
DIRECTION...
>> WE'LL HIT THAT SAME RIVER.
>> SHOULD BE A RIVER UP A WAYS.
WE'LL TAKE A RAFT WHEN WE
GET THERE.
>> NO, NO.
I THINK WE SHOULD ACTUALLY
GO ON AHEAD.
>> HE'S RIGHT.
FORGET THE RIVER!
>> NAH, THESE THINGS ARE
MAKING ME THIRSTY.
>> OK, THEN, LET'S GO
UP THE RIVER A WAYS!
>> OR EVEN DOWN THE RIVER
A WAYS.
>> WHY SHOULD WE DO THAT
WHEN THERE'S GOOD, CLEAN WATER
RIGHT UP AHEAD?
>> GOOD POINT.
>> I GUESS.
[THINKING] I CAN'T TELL HIM.
I KNOW EXACTLY WHAT'D HAPPEN
IF WE TOLD KOGA
ABOUT SESSHOMARU.
>> YOU MORONS!
WHY SHOULD I HAVE TO GO OUT OF
MY WAY TO AVOID INUYASHA'S
OLDER BROTHER?
HE'S JUST ANOTHER MANGY MUTT.
BRING HIM ON!
SHOW ME WHERE HE IS!
>> [THINKING] HE'LL GO OUT OF
HIS WAY TO START A FIGHT!
>> KOGA, L-LET'S GO THAT WAY.
IT'S WAY BETTER.
>> UHH!
>> HOW COME YOU TWO ARE SUDDENLY
BENT ON ORDERING ME AROUND?
>> WE'RE NOT ORDERING
YOU AROUND.
MORE LIKE SUGGESTING.
>> WE DON'T ASK MUCH.
JUST THIS ONCE.
>> OK?
>> HANDS OFF ME!
I'M THE LEADER HERE.
I GIVE THE DIRECTIONS AND
YOUR JOB IS TO FOLLOW.
>> WE DON'T WANNA FOLLOW.
THAT'S WHY WE'RE STOPPING YOU!
>> WE DON'T WANT TO GO THERE!
>> YOU DON'T WANT TO FOLLOW ME?
THEN GO ON HOME
TO THE MOUNTAINS.
>> HOW CAN YOU SAY SUCH A THING
TO US?
>> YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW WE FEEL.
>> SINCE WHEN DO I CARE
HOW YOU FEEL?
>> [WHIMPERING]
>> HUH?
>> HOW COULD YOU?
>> [SOBBING]
>> WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO
THOSE TWO IDIOTS?
[BIRD CAWING]
>> YOU POSSESS IT.
I KNOW YOU POSSESS IT.
>> WHAT WAS THAT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> YOU HAVE A SHARD OF THE
SACRED JEWEL.
>> A DEMON.
>> GIVE IT TO ME.
GIVE ME THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD!
>> AAH!
>> UHH!
>> [ROARING]
>> NEMU.
>> WHAT STRENGTH!
>> HMM?
>> OUR VILLAGE HAS LONG BEEN
TORMENTED BY THAT DEMON,
BUT NO MORE, THANKS TO YOUR
KIND ASSISTANCE.
>> LATELY, IT SEEMS THERE'S BEEN
AN INCREASE IN DEMON ATTACKS
ALL OVER.
>> YOU MUST SPEND THE NIGHT
WITH US.
>> HOW VERY KIND.
WE'LL ACCEPT YOUR GENEROSITY.
>> FOR ONCE, WE CAN ACCEPT THEIR
HOSPITALITY WITHOUT GUILT!
>> ESPECIALLY SINCE THERE'S
NO REASON FOR MIROKU
TO DO AN UNNECESSARY EXORCISM.
>> PLEASE, PLEASE.
>> WE'RE NOT GOING TO FIND
NARAKU IN A VILLAGE LIKE THIS,
NOT WHILE IT'S UNDER ATTACK
BY THEIR DEMONS.
>> DON'T BE A PARTY POOPER.
LET'S JUST ACCEPT THEIR OFFER.
>> STUPID KOGA.
I DON'T BELIEVE HIM.
>> HOW COULD HE BE SO CRUEL
WHEN WE WERE JUST
LOOKING OUT FOR HIM?
[GASPING]
[GROANING]
>> HE'S WAY TOO RASH.
THAT'S HIS PROBLEM.
OOH!
[GRUNTING]
[MUNCHING]
[WHIMPERING]
AAH!
[COUGHING]
>> HE'S ARROGANT CAUSE HE'S THE
LEADER OF THE TRIBE.
>> MAYBE WE SHOULD JOIN
KAGOME AND HER FRIENDS
AND SERVE UNDER HER.
>> MMF.
GREAT PLAN.
KAGOME WOULD NEVER TREAT US
LIKE THIS.
>> HMM.
OH, YEAH, I FORGOT ABOUT
INUYASHA.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
AND HE'S JUST AS ROUGH AS KOGA.
[CRASH]
>> [ROARING]
WHO ARE YOU?
YOU'RE NOT FROM AROUND HERE.
ARE YOU?
>> AAH!
>> [ROARING]
>> [SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
WAIT FOR ME!
>> EVERY MAN FOR HIMSELF!
>> [SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
>> YOU'RE DESPICABLE, GINTA.
KOGA WOULD NEVER TURN HIS BACK
ON A COMRADE, LET ALONE
ABANDON HIM!
>> WELL, I AIN'T KOGA.
>> YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT, AND IF HE
HADN'T INSISTED ON COMING
THIS FAR, WE WOULDN'T BE
IN THIS MESS.
>> YOU SAID IT.
ALL HE THINKS ABOUT IS GOING
AFTER NARAKU AND NOTHING ELSE.
>> I KNOW HE WANTS TO GET
REVENGE, BUT STILL.
>> IT DIDN'T SEEM LIKE IT'D
BE THAT DIFFICULT UNTIL
NARAKU DISAPPEARED.
>> [BREATHING HEAVILY]
WHY DON'T WE GIVE UP ON
FINDING NARAKU'S CASTLE?
>> WHAT DID YOU SAY?
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN?
NARAKU SLAUGHTERED ALL OUR
FRIENDS AND FAMILY.
>> HOW COULD WE EVER FORGET?
>> IT'S JUST THAT THERE'S
NO WAY TO FIND HIM.
>> I'LL NEVER GIVE UP.
I'LL BEAT NARAKU TO DEATH!
I HAVE TO, OR ELSE OUR FALLEN
COMRADES WILL NEVER FORGIVE ME.
>> [BREATHING HEAVILY]
>> THAT'S WHAT THIS JOURNEY IS
ABOUT, A VENDETTA FOR OUR
LOST COMRADES.
>> KOGA IS THE LEADER
OF THE TRIBE.
HE FEELS RESPONSIBLE
FOR THEIR DEATHS.
>> HE'S ROUGH AND HE'S RUTHLESS,
BUT HE CHERISHES
ALL HIS COMRADES.
>> HE SAVED OUR BUTTS MORE THAN
A COUPLE TIMES, TOO.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> HUH?
I KNOW THAT SCENT.
IT'S SESSHOMARU.
>> AND HE'S COMING THIS WAY.
>> OH, NO, KOGA'S UP AHEAD,
REMEMBER?
>> THEY'LL RUN INTO EACH OTHER!
>> AND IF THEY RUN INTO EACH
OTHER, [GASPING] LOOK OUT.
[GASPING]
>> YOU DISGUSTING MUTT!
STOP GIVING ME THAT SMUG LOOK.
>> LORD SESSHOMARU.
HE'S THE ONE.
>> [ROARING]
>> AAH!
>> WE HAVE TO DO SOMETHING!
>> YEAH, WE GOTTA DO SOMETHING
TO KEEP THEM APART.
>> WHAT'LL WE DO, THOUGH?
>> YOU TELL ME.
[GROWLING]
>> HMM.
THEM AGAIN.
>> THIS ROAD IS CLOSED!
YOU CANNOT PASS!
>> TURN AROUND AND TAKE
ANOTHER ROUTE.
>> WHAT DO WE DO NOW IF WE CAN'T
TAKE THIS ROUTE?
>> LORD SESSHOMARU?
>> WE'RE THE PERSONAL ASSISTANTS
OF KOGA, THE GREAT YOUNG LEADER
OF THE WOLF DEMON TRIBE.
I'M GINTA FROM THE
FIRES OF HELL.
>> AND I'M SLAYER HAKKAKU!
>> THAT WASN'T WHAT THEY SAID
EARLIER ON.
>> THIS ROAD IS CLOSED!
TURN AROUND!
>> [GRUNTING]
YOU GOT THAT?
[WHIMPERING]
[GRUNTING]
HOW WAS THAT?
>> THROWING STARS ATTACK!
>> LIGHTNING BOLT ATTACK!
UHH!
>> [GRUNTING]
WELL?
>> MAKE WAY.
>> [WHIMPERING]
>> YOU GO ELSEWHERE.
THIS PATH IS CLOSED!
>> NOTHING TO SEE HERE.
MOVE ALONG.
>> ARE THEY TRYING TO GET
THEMSELVES KILLED?
>> I TOLD YOU TO MAKE WAY.
>> [SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
>> I DON'T THINK SESSHOMARU
WOULD HESITATE TO KILL
HIS OPPONENT.
>> [WHIMPERING]
>> IT'S ALL OVER, GINTA!
>> HAKKAKU, WE HAVE A CHANCE OF
MAKING IT OUT OF HERE ALIVE
IF WE DRIVE KOGA AWAY.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> YOU'RE RIGHT!
LET'S GET KOGA OUT OF HERE!
>> SOMEBODY LOOKING FOR ME?
>> HUH?
AAH!
KOGA!
>> WHO ARE YOU?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
HE REEKS LIKE THAT FILTHY MUTT
INUYASHA.
>> [GASPING]
LORD SESSHOMARU?
>> THAT'S HIM.
INUYASHA'S OLDER BROTHER.
>> DON'T GO PICKING A FIGHT
WITH HIM.
>> SO YOU'RE INUYASHA'S BROTHER.
HMPH.
EXCEPT THAT YOU'RE NOT
A HALF-DEMON.
>> WHAT'S THIS?
LOOKS LIKE I STRUCK A NERVE.
>> KOGA, NO!
>> STAND BACK, RIN.
>> LORD SESSHOMARU!
>> [THINKING] FOOLS.
THEY JUST SIGNED THEIR OWN
DEATH WARRANTS!
>> [GRUNTING]
>> IT'S ALL OVER!
UHH!
>> HMM?
>> GIVE IT TO ME.
HAND OVER THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARD.
>> NO.
>> [INDISTINCT]
[ROARING]
>> HEY, LOOK OUT, MY LORD!
>> [ROARING]
>> UHH.
THANKS, BUT I COULD'VE
HANDLED HIM MYSELF.
>> HELP ME, MASTER JAKEN!
>> HMM?
>> [INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
>> [GROWLING]
>> AAH!
>> MASTER JAKEN!
AAH!
>> [GROWLING]
>> NO VILLAGE FOR YOU, WORM!
>> [GRUNTING]
>> [WHIMPERING]
>> UNNECESSARY INTERFERENCE.
>> FEELING'S MUTUAL.
>> OK.
>> OK?
>> COME ON, FELLAS.
WE HAVE A LONG WAY TO GO.
>> A-ARE YOU CONTENT WITH
LETTING THEM GO, MY LORD?
THOSE WOLVES OF KOGA'S ARE THE
VERY ONES THAT ATTACKED
YOUNG RIN!
>> IF HE TRIED THE SAME THING
TODAY, I WOULD'VE KILLED HIM.
>> HMM?
>> NARAKU IS THE ONLY ONE
I'M CONCERNED ABOUT NOW.
UNNECESSARY CONFLICTS
DON'T INTEREST ME.
>> UH--HUH?
>> HURRY, MASTER JAKEN,
OR YOU'LL BE LEFT BEHIND.
>> HUH?
AAH!
HEY, WAIT FOR ME!
>> EAT UP.
I SAVED THESE FOR YOU.
>> HMM?
>> I'M SURE KAGOME WOULD'VE
WANTED ME TO SHARE THESE
WITH YOU.
>> I WON'T ARGUE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> SO, HOW ABOUT EXPLAINING
WHAT YOU WERE UP TO EARLIER?
>> WE KNEW SESSHOMARU WAS IN THE
AREA, AND WE THOUGHT YOU'D START
FIGHTING WITH HIM IF YOU MET UP.
>> HOW COME?
>> OH...
>> I'LL LET YOU TAKE A SHOT
AT THAT ONE.
>> ONE DAY I'LL DEFEAT THAT
INUYASHA, BUT AS OF YET, I HAVE
NO GRIPE WITH HIS OLDER BROTHER.
>> OH, I SEE.
>> YOU WERE ACTUALLY WORRIED
OVER A STUPID THING LIKE THAT?
>> YEAH, BUT WHO'S TO SAY THAT
SESSHOMARU WOULDN'T HAVE STARTED
A FIGHT WITH YOU?
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
>> WHY WOULD HE?
>> WELL, YOU KNOW.
THAT HUMAN GIRL WITH HIM.
>> OH, THAT KID.
RIGHT.
I WONDER WHY HE'D LET A LITTLE
KID TAG ALONG WITH HIM
LIKE THAT.
>> OH, WELL, UH, UH,
I DON'T KNOW.
>> NOW, IF IT WAS A PRETTY GIRL
LIKE KAGOME, I'D UNDERSTAND
BRINGING HER ALONG,
BUT A YOUNG KID LIKE THAT?
>> [GASPING]
[WHIMPERING]
>> CUT IT OUT!
YOU GUYS DON'T THINK I'M
STRONG ENOUGH TO DEFEAT
SESSHOMARU?
FINE.
THEN I'LL GO PROVE YOU WRONG.
RIGHT NOW.
>> [WHIMPERING]
>> NO!
PLEASE!
DON'T GO!
STAY HERE!
[GRUNTING]
>> [GRUNTING]
ALL RIGHT.
[GRUMBLING]
[ROOSTER CROWING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
>> SURE IS A NICE MORNING.
>> HUH?
I DON'T LIKE THIS SMELL.
>> HEY.
>> HEH.
MORNING, KOGA.
>> HEY, YOURSELF.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
DIDN'T WE JUST GET RID OF YOU?
>> I WANTED TO THANK YOU
FOR THE FOOD YESTERDAY.
>> WOW, THEY'RE BEAUTIFUL!
>> I FIGURED SINCE GIRLS SEEM TO
LIKE STUFF LIKE THIS.
>> OH, YEAH, THAT'S BELIEVABLE.
EAT A HUMAN ONE DAY, GIVE ONE
PRESENTS THE NEXT.
>> BE SEEING YA.
>> I'M TALKING HERE!
>> KOGA SURE HAS CHANGED
SINCE WE FIRST MET HIM.
>> YOU'RE A GOOD INFLUENCE
ON HIM, KAGOME.
>> YOU THINK SO?
>> HMPH.
>> INUYASHA STILL HAS A LOT OF
CHANGING AND GROWING UP
TO DO, THOUGH.
>> [GROWLING]
>> AAH!
>> REALLY?
NOW WHO'S GOT A LOT OF GROWING
UP TO DO?
HUH?
WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME THAT?
>> [INDISTINCT] WITH KIKYO!
>> HUH?
>> KOGA!
HEY, UP HERE!
>> [GRUNTING, BREATHING HEAVILY]
QUIT SITTING AROUND DAWDLING!
TODAY'S THE DAY WE'RE GONNA
FIND NARAKU!
>> HMM.
YOU HEARD HIM.
LET'S GET GOING.
>> WE'LL FOLLOW KOGA
WHEREVER HE LEADS US.
>> HEY!
>> WAIT UP, WOULD YOU, KOGA?
JUST LIKE THE GOOD OLD
DAYS, HUH?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> KAGOME AND THE OTHERS ARE
TRAPPED IN THE COCOON OF THE
POISON MOTH DEMON, KURAMARU.
>> AN EVIL NIGHTMARE HAS CREATED
A REALM OF FEAR
AND INTENSE DESPAIR.
SORRY, INUYASHA.
I CAN'T FIGHT ANYMORE.
>> ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
IS YOUR POWER SO WEAK
IT CAN BE OVERPOWERED
BY A DREAM?
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
THE COCOON WON'T DISAPPEAR!
>> HOW COULD I SAVE THEM?