>> HERE WE COME.
IT'S THE START OF "INUYASHA."
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL THE
SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY NARAKU WITH
MY TETSUSAIGA.
>> MOUNT HAKUREI BEGINS TO
DISINTEGRATE, AND INUYASHA GOES
OFF TO SAVE KOGA.
DURING THAT SHORT TIME, THE
NEWLY REBORN NARAKU CONFRONTS
KIKYO.
WHAT IS HIS TRUE OBJECTIVE?
>> IT'S UP TO ALL OF US.
>> TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FEUDAL FAIRY TALE, "INUYASHA."
>> ALL RIGHT, HIT 'EM.
>> OH, LOOK, IT'S KOGA.
>> IF YOUR COMRADES ARE SO
PRECIOUS TO YOU...
>> WHAT NOW?
>> IT'S BREAKING UP.
>> HA HA HA...
KIKYO, I SHOULD BE SEEING YOU
SOON.
>> AH.
KOGA.
>> DAMN IT.
>> INUYASHA.
KAGOME.
>> WE HAVE TO GET OUT OF HERE
QUICKLY OR NARAKU WILL KILL US.
>> KAGOME, I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL.
BUT THERE'S NOTHING MORE WE CAN
DO FOR KOGA.
WE HAVE TO GIVE UP ON SAVING
HIM.
>> AHHH.
>> I'D NEVER PUT YOU IN DANGER.
>> KOGA.
KOGA.
OH, KOGA.
>> HEY, SHIPPOU.
>> YES, WHAT?
>> TAKE KAGOME, AND GET OUT OF
HERE FAST.
CAN YOU MANAGE THAT?
>> UH-HUH.
INUYASHA, AREN'T YOU COMING?
>> TAKE GOOD CARE OF KAGOME,
GREAT DEMON SHIPPOU.
>> INUYASHA...
>> WE CAN'T LEAVE YOU.
>> YOU WANT TO SAVE THAT SCRAWNY
WOLF, DON'T YOU?
YOU'LL ONLY BE IN MY WAY IF
YOU'RE WITH ME.
NOW GO.
>> TRANSFORM!
KAGOME, CLIMB ON BOARD.
>> QUICKLY, KAGOME.
>> THERE'S NO TIME TO LOSE.
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
I PROMISE TO BRING THAT SCRAWNY
WOLF BACK FOR YOU.
>> HMM.
>> COME ON.
BE CAREFUL, INUYASHA, YOU COME
BACK TO US.
YOU PROMISED, REMEMBER.
>> I WILL.
>> OH.
>> IS THIS EVIL PRESENCE NARAKU?
STILL, I SENSE SOMETHING
DIFFERENT IN IT.
>> MOUNT HAKUREI IS
DISINTEGRATING.
>> NARAKU.
>> AH, KIKYO, WE MEET AGAIN.
>> AHH.
MIASMA IS HORRIBLE.
IF HE FELL INTO THAT POOL,
THERE'S NO WAY TO SAVE HIM.
WHAT THE HELL ARE THOSE THINGS?
>> THERE HE IS.
ARE YOU READY FOR SOME
LASER?
AHH.
HE'S STARTING TO DISSOLVE.
DAMN NARAKU, HE WAS GOING TO
DEVOUR KOGA ALONG WITH THE
SACRED SHARDS IN HIS LEGS.
AH.
YOU'RE ALIVE, ARE YOU,
YOU SCRAWNY WOLF?
>> YEAH, MANGY MUTT.
NARAKU? WHAT HAPPENED TO NARAKU?
>> WE'LL TALK ABOUT IT LATER.
FIRST WE GET OUT OF HERE.
>> IT'S NO USE, ALL THE OPENINGS
ARE ALREADY SEALED.
ISN'T THERE ANY WAY OUT?
>> IT'S FAR TOO EARLY TO GIVE
UP.
IF THERE'S NO EXIT, WE'LL HAVE
TO MAKE ONE.
[GRUNTING]
>> WAY TO GO, MIROKU.
>> COME ON.
>> THE MOUNTAIN'S CRUMBLING.
>> WHERE'S INUYASHA?
ANYBODY SEEN HIM YET?
>> MAYBE HE DIDN'T MAKE IT OUT
IN TIME.
>> NO, I'M POSITIVE, HE'LL GET
OUT ALIVE.
IT'D TAKE A LOT MORE THAN THIS
TO KILL INUYASHA.
YOU BETTER BE OK, INUYASHA.
YOU PROMISED ME YOU'D COME
BACK.
>> THE EXIT, WHERE'S THE EXIT?
>> YOU IDIOT.
DON'T YOU EVEN KNOW THE WAY OUT?
>> I USED TO, BUT ALL THE
EXITS HAVE BEEN SEALED.
>> YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
I AIN'T GONNA DIE IN THIS PLACE
WITH YOU.
>> WE AGREE FOR ONCE.
JUST WHAT I WAS THINKING.
I'M NOT DYING HERE.
>> HUH?
>> THERE IT IS, OUR WAY OUT.
HUH?
KIKYO.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHY SHOULD I HAVE A VISION OF
KIKYO AT A TIME LIKE THIS?
>> NARAKU, WHAT IS THE MEANING
OF YOUR APPEARANCE?
>> ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
THIS IS MY NEW, REJUVENATED
BODY.
>> DON'T MAKE ME LAUGH.
DO YOU THINK MY EYES CAN'T SEE
THE TRUTH?
YOU MAY LOOK FORMIDABLE
BUT SUCH FINERY IS NOTHING BUT A
FAADE.
YOU ESCAPED MOUNT HAKUREI AND
WENT SO FAR AS TO PUT UP A
SACRED BARRIER.
WHAT WERE YOU AFTER?
>> SO YOU NOTICED, DID YOU?
HOW VERY ASTUTE.
>> JUST BEFORE THE MOUNTAIN
COLLAPSED, YOUR INCARNATION,
KAGURA, LEFT MOUNT HAKUREI WITH
SOMETHING IN HER POSSESSION.
TELL ME, WHAT'S YOUR PURPOSE?
>> INUYASHA.
HUH?
I SENSE THEM.
I SENSE THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
>> IS IT KOGA?
>> THEY'RE COMING THIS WAY.
INUYASHA!
>> HE MADE IT OUT ALIVE.
>> LOOK, THEY'RE BOTH SAFE.
>> NOT AGAIN.
KAGOME!
>> WHAT ABOUT KAGOME?
>> WATCH OUT.
>> AHHH.
>> INUYASHA.
KOGA.
>> STUPID ME, WHAT WAS I
THINKING PUTTING HIM IN CHARGE?
I'M SORRY, KAGOME, YOU MUST HAVE
BEEN SCARED WITHOUT ME THERE.
>> YOU INGRATE, DON'T ACT LIKE
YOU GOT OUT ALIVE ALL BY
YOURSELF.
>> SHUT YOUR MOUTH, MUTT.
>> HE'S RIGHT, KOGA.
YOU SHOULD AT LEAST SAY THANKS
OR SOMETHING.
>> HUH?
>> INUYASHA WENT TO SAVE YOU
LONG BEFORE I EVEN ASKED HIM TO.
>> HMM...
>> HUH, DON'T GET ME WRONG.
I JUST DIDN'T WANT NARAKU TO GET
YOUR SCARED JEWEL SHARDS.
THAT'S THE ONLY REASON I WENT
AFTER YOU.
>> OH, YEAH?
THEN I DON'T NEED TO THANK YOU.
>> THAT'S THE LEAST YOU COULD
DO.
>> YOU WANT MY THANKS OR NOT?
>> ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
HE WANTS YOU TO THANK HIM.
>> HMM.
I'LL ASK YOU JUST ONE MORE TIME.
NARAKU, TELL ME WHAT YOUR TRUE
PURPOSE HERE IS.
>> I'M SURPRISED.
DID YOU COME ALL THIS WAY AND GO
TO ALL THIS TROUBLE TO ASK ME
SUCH A SIMPLE MATTER?
>> I'M THE ONE WHO'S ASKING THE
QUESTIONS.
>> ROUND AND ROUND GOES THE
SPINNING WHEEL.
SPINNING AND WEAVING A RED
THREAD OF FATE.
MEETING RASETSU, OR SHOULD I
SAY, KANSUKE, WAS NO
COINCIDENCE.
IT WAS ALL ACCORDING TO MY PLAN.
>> YOU MEAN...
>> I MERELY TOOK ADVANTAGE OF
HIS DESIRE TO FIND A PLACE TO
DIE.
IT WAS ALL SO SIMPLE.
I PUT RUMORS INTO THAT DYING
MAN'S HEAD ABOUT THE SACRED
GROUNDS OF MOUNT HAKUREI.
AND THUS SET HIM ON YOUR PATH.
NOW DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
HA HA HA.
YOU DID NOT COME HERE OF YOUR
OWN ACCORD.
I LURED YOU HERE.
>> HMM.
>> I HAVE OFTEN HEARD YOU HUMANS
REFER TO THIS AS FATE OR
DESTINY.
>> ONCE THE THREADS OF DESTINY
BECOME TANGLED, THEY CANNOT BE
UNDONE.
TO WALK DOWN THIS PATH ONCE
MORE ONLY CONFIRMS MY CURSED
DESTINY.
>> ONLY THE WEAK UTTER SUCH
NONSENSE.
IT IS DIFFERENT FOR THE TRULY
POWERFUL.
THEY CREATE THIS SO-CALLED FATE
OR DESTINY WITH THEIR OWN HANDS.
>> YOU'RE THE ONE SPEAKING
NONSENSE, NARAKU.
>> OH, YES, YOU WERE INTERESTED
IN FINDING OUT ABOUT MY TRUE
AIM.
>> HMM.
>> YOU WISH TO KNOW?
THEN I SHALL TELL YOU.
YOU SHALL LEARN MY PURPOSE.
WHAT IT IS I NEED TO ACCOMPLISH
AT MOUNT HAKUREI.
HERE IS YOUR ANSWER.
>> AH.
AHH...
>> YOUR IMITATION BODY IS FORMED
OF BONES AND GRAVEYARD SOIL.
YOU DON'T EVEN BLEED.
>> AHH...
I CURSE YOU, NARAKU.
>> YOU UNDERESTIMATED ME, KIKYO.
YOU CAME HERE FEELING SELF-
ASSURED, SO CERTAIN THAT I WOULD
NOT BE ABLE TO KILL YOU.
YOU BELIEVED THAT AS LONG AS I
HAVE THE HEART OF THAT WORTHLESS
HUMAN, THAT PATHETIC BANDIT,
ONIGUMO, WHO LOVED YOU WITH ALL
HIS BEING...
YOU BELIEVED I WOULDN'T
HARM YOU.
I FEEL NOTHING, EVEN AFTER
WOUNDING YOU SO.
NO REMORSE, NO SADNESS.
>> DOES THAT MEAN HIS HEART NO
LONGER BEATS INSIDE YOU?
I SEE.
THAT'S WHAT KAGURA HAD IN HER
POSSESSION, HIS HUMAN HEART.
UH...
>> THE BOTTOM OF THIS CREVICE IS
FILLED WITH MY MIASMA.
AN IMITATION BODY LIKE YOURS
WILL DISSOLVE EASILY IN A MATTER
OF SECONDS.
>> MMM.
>> KIKYO, THIS WILL BE YOUR
BURIAL GROUND.
>> NO, WHY ARE THESE MEMORIES
COMING BACK TO ME NOW?
>> AHH.
>> AH.
AHH...
INUYASHA.
>> HUH?
>> INUYASHA?
>> I DON'T LIKE THIS.
I'VE GOT A BAD FEELING ABOUT
SOMETHING.
>> INUYASHA?
>> NOW, DO YOU UNDERSTAND,
KIKYO?
AT LAST THE NEW BODY I HAVE
DESIRED FOR SO LONG IS MINE.
>> I MUST SAY, YOU TOOK
EXTRAORDINARY STEPS TO KILL A
MERE WOMAN, NARAKU.
>> SESSHOUMARU.
>> HE SHOWS LORD SESSHOUMARU
SUCH A LACK OF RESPECT.
HE'S GROWN TOO FULL OF HIMSELF.
>> JAKEN, LISTEN TO ME.
STAY WELL BACK.
>> HUH?
>> I NEVER EXPECTED YOU TO BE
FOLLOWING ME AS WELL,
SESSHOUMARU.
SO YOU FIND ME THAT INTERESTING,
DO YOU?
>> SILENCE.
YOU ARE THE ONE WHO KEEPS
MEDDLING IN OUR AFFAIRS.
SO WE MERELY ...
>> I SAID BACK AWAY, JAKEN.
>> HUH?
>> SINCE YOU'VE EMERGED FROM
YOUR BARRIER, I ASSUME YOU'RE
CAPABLE OF PRODUCING A
SIGNIFICANT AMOUNT OF POWER.
>> WHY DON'T YOU SEE FOR
YOURSELF?
>> HMM.
>> GOT HIM!
>> HA HA HA!
>> HE'S LAUGHING?
>> SESSHOUMARU, I SHALL NOW
REVERSE THE POWER OF YOUR SWORD
AND FIRE IT BACK AT YOU.
>> AAH!
LORD SESSHOUMARU IS BEING PUSHED
BACK.
>> HUH.
IT'S USELESS.
I WILL NEVER DIE.
HA HA HA HA...
>> SUCH IMPUDENCE.
YOU MERELY WISH TO TEST THE
POWER OF YOUR NEW BODY AGAINST
ME.
>> SESSHOUMARU.
>> INUYASHA, STILL ALIVE, ARE
YOU?
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> IT SEEMS THAT NARAKU'S MAIN
INTEREST WAS NOT YOU.
BUT RATHER HIS REAL OBJECTIVE
WAS TO KILL THAT WOMAN.
>> HUH?
KIKYO'S BOW.
NO, KIKYO.
WHAT HAPPENED?
DID NARAKU KILL KIKYO?
NO, IT CAN'T BE!
>> NARAKU CANNOT KILL ME.
NOT AS LONG AS HE HAS ONIGUMO'S
HEART, A HEART WHICH CARES FOR
ME.
>> SOUL COLLECTORS.
I FAILED YOU AGAIN, KIKYO.
I LET YOU DIE.
I WASN'T THERE FOR YOU WHEN YOU
DIED ALONE.
>> THIS MIASMA IS TERRIBLE.
THERE'S NO WAY SHE COULD SURVIVE
IT.
UGH!
HUH!
LORD SESSHOUMARU.
>> HOLD ON, SESSHOUMARU.
>> DID YOU JUST WATCH HER GET
KILLED?
DIDN'T YOU DO ANYTHING TO HELP?
I TOLD YOU TO STOP.
>> I DON'T CARE TO KNOW WHAT
YOUR CONNECTION TO THAT WOMAN
WAS.
THE PERSON RESPONSIBLE FOR
KILLING KIKYO WAS NARAKU...
AND YOU.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO
DIDN'T SAVE HER.
INUYASHA, BLAME YOURSELF.
RATHER THAN TAKE YOUR ANGER OUT
ON ME, I SUGGEST YOU GO AFTER
NARAKU.
>> EXACTLY.
>> KIKYO, FORGIVE ME.
>> INUYASHA.
AH!
THAT'S--WHERE'S KIKYO?
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN TO HER?
>> YEAH.
NARAKU WASN'T AFTER ME.
HE WANTED KIKYO.
HE WANTED TO TAKE HER LIFE.
>> IT CAN'T BE.
KIKYO IS GONE?
>> DAMN THAT NARAKU.
MAKING ME TAKE CARE OF THIS
THING.
>> KIKYO IS DEAD.
>> HUH, WHAT DID YOU SAY?
>> KIKYO IS DEAD
AND NARAKU KILLED HER.
>> DAMN, I'M SICK OF THIS.
WHY SHOULD I HAVE TO BABY-SIT
THIS KID?
>> KAGURA, IS KIKYO STILL ALIVE
OR IS THAT A LIE?
>> INUYASHA WON'T COME.
HE'S BUSY LOOKING FOR KIKYO.
>> IS THAT BABY AN INCARNATION
OF NARAKU?
WHAT DOES HE WANT WITH ME?
>> YOU ARE THE ONLY ONE WHO CAN
SEE THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
KAGOME, I WANT YOUR EYES.
>> NEXT TIME, THE DARKNESS IN
KAGOME'S HEART.
>> INUYASHA WILL NOT COME TO
SAVE YOU.