>> OUR ARCHENEMY NARAKU HAD
SOMEHOW COMPLETELY CONCEALED
HIMSELF FROM US.
50 YEARS EARLIER, THE BANDIT
ONIGUMO TRANSFORMED HIMSELF
INTO NARAKU.
MAD KILLER RESATSU, WHO HARBORED
A DEEP GRUDGE AGAINST ONIGUMO,
MET KIKYO SHORTLY BEFORE
HIS DEATH.
LITTLE DID WE KNOW,
AS WE JOURNEYED IN OUR SEARCH
FOR NARAKU, A CHANCE MEETING
AWAITED US.
IT SEEMS LIKE
SUCH A PEACEFUL VILLAGE.
>> THERE'S NO SIGN
THAT NARAKU'S BEEN HERE.
>> SOMETHING'S ODD HERE, THOUGH.
>> WHAT IS IT?
I DON'T SEE ANYTHING.
>> ALL THE FIELDS ARE IN RUINS.
>> SHE'S RIGHT.
WHAT COULD HAVE HAPPENED?
>> A WILD BOAR, PERHAPS?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S A LOT OF DAMAGE.
>> THAT'S HIM!
>> HUH?
>> HMM?
>> STOP! DON'T GO!
>> VILLAGERS?
>> YOU WITH THE FAIR HAIR!
>> LOOK AT THOSE EARS!
HE'S NOT HUMAN!
>> [GROANS]
>> WHAT DO THEY WANT WITH YOU?
>> YOU GOT BUSINESS WITH ME?
>> [TOGETHER] SAVE US, DOG GOD,
WE BEG YOU.
>> HUH?
>> WHAT DOG GOD?
>> HONORABLE DOG GOD.
>> DOG GOD.
>> [TOGETHER] DOG GOD.
>> THESE PEOPLE THINK
I'M A DOG GOD?
HMM?
WHAT IS THIS?
PICKLED VEGETABLES?
>> WE REALIZE THAT FOR
SOMEONE OF YOUR STATURE,
PICKLED VEGETABLES ARE BUT
A MEAGER OFFERING.
>> BUT THIS IS ALL THE FOOD
WE HAVE TO OFFER, YOUR EMINENCE.
>> WE HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO APPEAL TO YOU,
HONORABLE DOG GOD.
>> QUICKLY, LADIES.
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
FAN HIM.
>> THEY MUST BE VERY DESPERATE
TO BE APPEALING TO INUYASHA
FOR HIS HELP.
>> WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
>> ALL THE FIELDS IN OUR VILLAGE
HAVE BEEN RAVAGED BY A BAND
OF MONKEYS.
>> MONKEYS?
>> WE HAVE LONG HEARD THAT
MONKEYS HOLD A DEEP FEAR
OF DOGS.
>> PLEASE, DOG GOD,
LEND US YOUR ASSISTANCE.
>> [TOGETHER] DRIVE OUT THE
MONKEYS AND SAVE OUR VILLAGE!
>> OF COURSE WE'LL HELP YOU.
WE'LL DRIVE OUT THE MONKEYS.
>> OHH!
>> HEY, I MAY BE GOOD,
BUT I'M HARDLY A GOD.
>> SO, WHAT'S A LITTLE
MONKEY BUSINESS ON THE SIDE?
>> WE DON'T HAVE TIME
TO BE MONKEYING AROUND.
>> REST ASSURED SANGO AND I WILL
CARRY ON AND KEEP LOOKING FOR
NARAKU WHILE YOU TAKE CARE OF
THE TROUBLEMAKERS.
>> MIROKU'S RIGHT.
>> INUYASHA, THESE POOR PEOPLE
ARE IN TROUBLE.
WE CAN'T JUST WALK AWAY
FROM THEM.
>> [SIGH]
THIS IS A JOKE.
WHY DO I HAVE TO HANDLE THE
MONKEYS FOR THESE VILLAGERS?
>> IT JUST GOES WITH
THE TERRITORY--YOU KNOW,
BEING A DOG GOD.
>> AN HONORABLE DOG GOD.
>> YOU THERE!
>> HUH?
>> [ROARING]
>> AAH!
>> IT'S A MONKEY DEMON!
>> HUH.
>> PATHETIC DOG DEMON,
THE VILLAGERS MUST HAVE SENT YOU
TO COME AFTER ME, KNOWING
HOW MUCH I DESPISE MUTTS.
YOU'LL BE DOG MEAT!
>> YOU'RE MAKING ME GLAD
I WAS FORCED TO VOLUNTEER.
UHH!
I'LL TAKE ON A DEMON LIKE YOU
ANY DAY.
HUH?
>> [SCREAMING]
>> OOF!
>> OW!
>> OH.
>> LITTLE MONKEYS!
>> THEY'RE ADORABLE!
>> [ALL GROANING]
HUH?
OH!
>> HEY, ARE YOU THE MONKEYS
THAT HAVE BEEN PLUNDERING
THE FARMERS' FIELDS?
>> [WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY]
>> I GUESS YOU GOT US.
SORRY. SO SORRY. SO SORRY.
AND TO PROVE THAT WE'LL NEVER DO
ANYTHING NAUGHTY AGAIN,
WE'LL GIVE YOU OUR SPECIAL
SPIRITUAL STONE.
>> HA HA!
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO DO THAT,
BUT I WOULDN'T TURN DOWN A GIFT.
>> INUYASHA...
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT, SHIPPO?
>> IT'S A STANDARD TRICK
IN THE MINI-DEMON WORLD TO CATCH
YOUR ENEMY OFF GUARD BY GIVING
HIM A GIFT, SO I'D THINK TWICE
ABOUT ACCEPTING THAT
IF I WERE YOU.
GUESS IT'S TOO LATE NOW.
>> AAH!
>> UHH!
>> HA HA HA HA!
>> OH!
>> YOU COULD HAVE
TOLD ME SOONER.
>> HA HA HA HA!
SERVES YOU RIGHT.
>> RIGHTLY SERVED.
THE DOG DEMON'S STUCK.
>> [TOGETHER] MOONED YA!
MONKEY BUMS ARE BRIGHT AND RED.
MORE BRAINS HERE
THAN ARE IN YOUR HEAD.
>> SAYS YOU!
WATCH WHERE YOU'RE POINTING
THOSE THINGS, OR I'LL REALLY
HAVE TO BRAIN YOU.
>> STICKS ALONE
MAY BREAK OUR BONES...
>> BUT NAMES WILL NEVER HURT US.
TILL OUR SPELL IS BROKEN, YOU'LL
STAY HERE STUCK TO THIS STONE.
>> SO THAT'S WHAT YOU THINK,
IS IT?
[GRUNTING]
>> [ALL WHIMPERING]
>> YOU FORGET I STILL HAVE
ONE FREE HAND LEFT TO CLOBBER
YOU MONKEYS.
>> [WAILING]
>> UHH!
>> HMM?
UHH!
>> INUYASHA!
>> [TOGETHER] HA HA HA HA!
>> SQUASHED LIKE A BUG, HE IS.
>> LET'S FOLLOW THEM, KAGOME!
>> RIGHT!
>> KAGOME!
>> UH, DON'T MOVE AN INCH.
WE'LL BE BACK FOR YOU.
>> SURE. OW.
>> THEY CAN'T GET AWAY!
INUYASHA'S GONNA BE STUCK TO THE
STONE UNTIL THE SPELL'S BROKEN,
AND THEY'RE THE ONLY ONES
WHO CAN BREAK IT!
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
WAIT, SHIPPO!
>> WAIT A MINUTE, MIROKU.
WEREN'T WE SUPPOSED TO LOOK FOR
SIGNS OF NARAKU?
>> WE DON'T HAVE INUYASHA
TO SNIFF HIM OUT, AND WE DON'T
HAVE KAGOME, WHO CAN SENSE
THE SACRED JEWEL.
WHAT GOOD IS SEARCHING
ON OUR OWN?
>> HUH?
>> I HAD TO SAY WE'D KEEP
SEARCHING, OR INUYASHA WOULDN'T
HAVE LIFTED A FINGER TO HELP
THOSE VILLAGERS.
>> HA HA HA HA!
>> [PANTING]
I MUST TAKE CONTROL.
>> [CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
>> GO!
>> OH, YEAH?
[SCREAMING]
>> [INDISTINCT]
>> [SCREAMING]
FISH!
>> 3 MONKEYS...
>> ARE BETTER THAN ONE!
[SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
>> AAH!
TOP THIS!
>> AND NUT!
>> YOU'RE PRETTY GOOD.
>> YEAH, YOU TOO.
>> OK, LISTEN UP.
TIME FOR A SNACK.
SO, HOW COME YOU'VE BEEN
WRECKING ALL THE FARMERS'
FIELDS?
>> WE HAVEN'T BEEN WRECKING THEM
ON PURPOSE.
WE'RE LOOKING FOR THE MONKEY GOD
THAT'S BEEN KIDNAPPED.
>> WHAT MONKEY GOD IS THAT?
>> THE DEITY WHO WAS ENSHRINED
IN THIS VILLAGE.
>> WE'RE THE 3 MONKEY SPRITES
WHO SERVE UNDER THE MONKEY GOD.
>> PART OF OUR TRAINING WAS
TO MAKE SURE WE PROTECTED
THE SHRINE.
>> BUT THE SHRINE WAS BURNED
DOWN, WITH THE WARS AND ALL.
>> AND THE SACRED OBJECT
CONTAINING THE SPIRIT OF
THE MONKEY GOD WAS STOLEN
FROM INSIDE THE SHRINE.
>> SO YOU THINK THAT
THE SACRED OBJECT IS SOMEWHERE
IN THE VILLAGE?
>> YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
WE BELIEVE THAT THE SACRED
OBJECT IS BURIED IN A FIELD
SOMEWHERE NEARBY.
I HAD A PREMONITION IN MY DREAM,
SO I'M SURE IT'S TRUE.
>> I HAD THE SAME DREAM.
>> DON'T FORGET ABOUT ME.
>> IN MY DREAM, OUR GOD WAS
IN A PLACE THAT WAS VERY DARK
AND DAMP.
>> IN MINE, HE WAS IN A PLACE
THAT WAS SMALL AND SUFFOCATING.
>> AND IN MY DREAM, HE WAS
COMPLAINING THAT THE PLACE
STUNK OF VEGETABLES.
[CRASH]
>> [TOGETHER] HUH?
>> SOMETHING'S COMING THIS WAY.
>> [SIGH]
LISTEN, I'M NOT GOING TO
CRITICIZE OR LECTURE YOU,
BUT YOU REALLY SHOULD BREAK
THE SPELL YOU PUT ON INUYASHA.
>> NO WAY.
>> WHY?
>> BECAUSE.
WE'VE FORGOTTEN HOW TO UNDO
THE SPELL.
>> UHH!
YOU MONKEYS!
[GROWLING]
>> IF I WERE YOU GUYS, I'D END
THE JOKE RIGHT HERE AND NOW.
TAKE IT FROM ME,
INUYASHA WON'T GO EASY ON YOU
JUST 'CAUSE YOU'RE LITTLE GUYS.
>> BUT WE'RE NOT JOKING.
WE REALLY HAVE FORGOTTEN
HOW TO UNDO THE SPELL.
[3 PUNCHES]
>> [GROANING]
>> [GROWLING]
>> THIS ISN'T GOOD.
>> [GRUNTING]
YOU'RE DEAD.
>> NO, WAIT!
ONCE WE FIND THE MONKEY GOD,
THEN WE CAN BREAK YOUR SPELL,
OK?
>> YEAH. RIGHT. THE MONKEY GOD.
HE'S THE ONE WHO TAUGHT US
THE TRICK IN THE FIRST PLACE.
>> THEN LET'S HURRY BACK
TO THE VILLAGE AND FIND
THAT SACRED OBJECT.
>> HMM?
>> TAKE YOUR TIME CATCHING UP.
>> YOU SHOULD HAVE WAITED
BACK THERE IN THE FIRST PLACE.
>> NO! WAIT!
>> AREN'T YOU GETTING TIRED?
>> DUH.
NO WAY AM I GONNA KEEP HANGING
ON TO THIS STUPID BOULDER
FOREVER.
[GRUNTING]
>> HOW CLUMSY OF YOU, INUYASHA.
>> NICE ROCK YOU GOT THERE,
MUTT.
>> GRRRR! WHY, YOU...
HUH?
>> SUCH A SHAME YOU CAN'T USE
THE TETSUSAIGA.
PITIFUL.
>> NO. DON'T. GIVE IT BACK!
GIVE ME BACK MY SWORD!
>> I'LL TAKE GOOD CARE
OF KAGOME.
>> NO! WAIT!
HUH?
>> I SHALL GLADLY USE
THE TETSUSAIGA IN YOUR PLACE,
LITTLE BROTHER.
>> [WHIMPERS]
>> LET'S BE ON OUR WAY, KAGOME.
>> NO! COME BACK!
GET BACK HERE!
I CAN'T AFFORD TO WAIT AROUND.
>> THE SECRET ABODE
OF THE MONKEY GOD?
>> YES.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE
IN THIS VILLAGE.
>> YOU HAVE IT.
>> GIVE IT BACK!
>> I KNOW OF NO SUCH THING,
HONESTLY.
>> [TOGETHER] HUH?
>> HE'S HERE ALREADY!
>> HURRY UP AND TELL US
WHERE YOU'VE HIDDEN HIM.
>> OUR LIVES ARE AT STAKE.
YOU GOT TO HELP US!
[CRASH]
>> OH, LOOK. IT'S THE DOG GOD!
>> [GRUNTING]
WHERE IS THE MONKEY GOD?
YOU BETTER GET THIS BOULDER
OFF ME, OR YOU'RE ALL DEAD.
>> HOW'D YOU GET HERE SO FAST?
>> DON'T GET TOO CLOSE.
THAT GUY'S DANGEROUS.
>> ARE YOU POSITIVE YOU CAN'T
REMEMBER HOW TO TAKE THIS SPELL
OFF ME?
>> [TOGETHER] NOT AT ALL.
[3 PUNCHES]
>> DO YOU MEAN THAT YOUR HAND
GOT STUCK TO THE BOULDER
BECAUSE OF THE MONKEY SPELL?
ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE A REAL
DOG GOD?
>> OF COURSE NOT!
THAT'S WHAT I'VE BEEN TRYING
TO TELL YOU!
>> ACTUALLY, HE'S ABOUT
THE FURTHEST THING FROM A GOD.
>> ACCORDING TO THESE MONKEY
SPRITES, ONLY THE MONKEY GOD
CAN UNDO THE SPELL.
>> AND YOU GOT TO FIND HIM!
IF YOU PEOPLE ARE HIDING
ANYTHING FROM ME, I SWEAR I'LL
DESTROY YOUR WHOLE VILLAGE!
>> INUYASHA, SIT, BOY.
>> UHH!
KAGOME, HOW COULD YOU?
>> STAY THERE. KEEP QUIET.
>> SHALL WE SPLIT UP AND SEARCH?
>> I SUPPOSE, IF IT WOULD STOP
THE PLUNDERING.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I APPRECIATE YOUR HELP.
>> WHAT'S IT LOOK LIKE?
>> WELL, IT'S A ROCK, AND IT'S
ABOUT THIS BIG, I THINK.
>> IT'S ENGRAVED WITH THE SYMBOL
OF THE MONKEY GOD.
>> AND IT'S ROUND AS A MONKEY'S
HEAD.
>> HANG ON, NOW.
THERE WAS A ROCK LIKE THAT
UP IN THE MOUNTAIN AT THE BACK.
>> TO THE MOUNTAIN!
>> THE MOUNTAIN!
>> ALL RIGHT!
I CAN HANDLE ONE MORE MOUNTAIN.
THAT IT?
>> [TOGETHER] NUH-UH.
>> THAT'S NOT THE ONE?
THAT'S GREAT.
HUH?
AAH!
>> INUYASHA!
>> I RECALL SEEING A STONE
LIKE THAT IN THIS RIVER.
>> TO THE RIVER!
>> THE RIVER!
>> IS THIS THE ONE?
>> NUH-UH.
AND IT DOESN'T LOOK GODLY
AT ALL.
>> THIS ISN'T THE ROCK, EITHER.
AAH!
>> INUYASHA!
>> [GURGLING]
>> I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE IT'S THAT ROCK
IN THE FOREST.
>> WASN'T IT NEXT TO THE JIZO
SHRINE OVER IN THE EAST?
>> I KNOW.
IT'S OVER IN THE SOUTH VALLEY.
>> THERE WAS A ROCK
UNDER THE HOUSE.
>> UHHHH!
>> HELLO! WE'RE BACK!
HUH?
>> INUYASHA?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> DON'T JUST STAND THERE.
START LOOKING FOR THE SACRED
MONKEY STONE.
OW.
>> I SEE.
SO ALL THIS HAPPENED
WHILE SANGO AND I WERE AWAY?
>> IT'S QUITE THE PROBLEM.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THEN I'LL USE MY POWERS
TO SOMEHOW REMEDY THE SITUATION.
>> [TOGETHER] HUH?
>> DO YOU MEAN YOU'LL BE THE ONE
TO FIND THE MONKEY GOD?
>> OF COURSE I WILL.
HOWEVER, MY SPIRITUAL POWERS ARE
ONLY EFFECTIVE IN THE MORNING.
>> [TOGETHER] THAT'S OK!
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> WE MIGHT AS WELL
FIND OURSELVES A PLACE
TO STAY FOR THE NIGHT.
>> THE MONK IS GONNA SAVE US!
>> TRICK IS MORE LIKE IT.
>> ARE YOU CERTAIN
YOU WANT TO TELL SUCH A LIE?
>> IT'LL WORK OUT SOMEHOW.
>> THERE'S SOMETHING FISHY
ABOUT THIS.
>> YES.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU FELL FOR
SUCH AN OBVIOUS TRICK.
>> HEY, SPARE ME THE LECTURES
AND GET THIS THING OFF ME,
OR YOU'LL REGRET IT.
>> AND HOW'S THAT?
>> WITH MY HAND STUCK LIKE THIS,
I CAN'T EXACTLY USE
THE TETSUSAIGA.
>> AAH!
>> INUYASHA'S STUCK.
>> IF WE DON'T DO SOMETHING...
>> [SCREECHING]
>> [SHOUTS IN JAPANESE]
>> WIND TUNNEL!
>> GET BACK, MIROKU!
>> WHAT?
>> [GRUNTING]
STONE WIELDER BOULDER DREAMER!
>> [SHRIEKING]
>> WHAT ARE YOU TWO LAUGHING AT?
>> THIS BOULDER COULD BE
A GOOD THING, INUYASHA.
>> HE'S RIGHT.
YOU COULD USE IT
LIKE ANOTHER WEAPON.
>> WHAT ARE YOU FOOLS IMAGINING,
ANYWAY?
>> IF INUYASHA STAYS STUCK TO
THE BOULDER...
SEE YOU LATER, GUYS.
I'M GOING BACK HOME NOW.
>> HEY, WAIT, KAGOME!
>> NO CAN DO.
>> DON'T JUST LEAVE ON ME!
[GRUNTING]
DAMN.
>> I LIKE IT.
>> OH, GREAT. NOT YOU, TOO.
WHAT ARE YOU PICTURING?
>> I KNOW, INUYASHA.
WHY DON'T I TRY SUCKING UP THE
BOULDER THROUGH MY WIND TUNNEL?
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
>> CAN YOU SUCK UP THE BOULDER
AND NOT ME?
>> IF I STOP IN THE NICK
OF TIME, IT JUST MIGHT WORK.
HERE'S THE PLAN.
I'LL OPEN MY WIND TUNNEL
LIKE THIS, SUCK UP THE ROCK,
AND JUST AS YOU GET NEAR IT,
I'LL CLOSE MY--UGH.
>> [TOGETHER] HUH?
>> WHAT NOW?
WHAT DID YOU STOP TALKING FOR?
>> WELL, IT'S JUST IF YOU'RE
HALF SUCKED IN...
WELL, NO, NOTHING. NEVER MIND.
>> NOW WHAT ARE YOU IMAGINING?
>> NOTHING. JUST FORGET IT.
LET'S GIVE IT A TRY.
DON'T WORRY.
I PROBABLY WON'T SUCK YOU IN.
>> UH-UH! STOP!
>> AHCHOO!
AH.
>> WHY DON'T YOU GO ON INSIDE
WITH THE OTHERS?
YOU DON'T HAVE TO STAY OUT HERE
IN THE COLD WITH ME.
>> WOULDN'T YOU BE LONELY
SITTING OUT HERE
ALL BY YOURSELF?
>> HUH! NOT HARDLY, STUPID.
>> I'LL GO, THEN, IF YOU WANT.
>> I NEVER SAID I WANTED YOU TO.
>> YOU SURE?
>> MM-HMM.
>> [THINKING] HOW ARE WE GONNA
GET THAT THING OFF HIM?
THERE MUST BE ANOTHER WAY.
EXCUSE ME.
>> HMM?
>> CAN I SEE THAT?
>> MM-HMM.
>> THIS IS ABOUT ALL THAT
WE CAN OFFER, I'M AFRAID.
SO IS THERE A PROBLEM?
>> THIS IS QUITE AMAZING.
>> [TOGETHER] WHAT?
>> LOOK AT THIS STUFF, GUYS.
WASN'T THIS CABBAGE GROWN
IN THE FIELDS HERE?
>> AND IT HAS THE GLOW
FROM OUR MONKEY GOD.
>> IT'S DARK AND DAMP, JUST AS
IT APPEARED IN MY DREAMS.
>> SMALL AND SUFFOCATING.
>> AND IT STUNK OF VEGETABLES!
>> AHA!
THE MONKEY GOD HAS TO BE
IN THE FIELDS.
>> HE MUST BE BURIED SOMEWHERE
DEEP UNDERGROUND.
>> WE'LL TURN THE VILLAGE
UPSIDE DOWN IF WE HAVE TO.
>> [TOGETHER] YEAH!
>> HA HA!
>> PLEASE, NOT OUR FIELDS AGAIN.
>> SIT, BOY.
>> [TOGETHER] AAH!
>> I WAS WONDERING IF YOU
COULD SHOW ME SOMETHING,
IF YOU DON'T MIND.
I KNEW IT.
THE PICKLING STONE
IS GLOWING, TOO.
>> THIS IS THE SACRED OBJECT.
>> [TOGETHER] HONORABLE
MONKEY GOD!
>> GLOW?
I DON'T SEE ANYTHING AT ALL.
>> WHAT A TERRIBLE THING TO DO
TO THE SACRED OBJECT!
>> SEE?
YOU DID STEAL IT,
JUST LIKE WE SAID!
>> NOT AT ALL.
I FOUND IT ON THE OUTSKIRTS
OF THE VILLAGE.
I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE
A PERFECT WEIGHT FOR PICKLING.
>> THEN YOU FOUND IT
OUTSIDE OF THE FOREST?
>> LIAR!
THE SACRED OBJECT WAS KEPT IN
THE SHRINE, DEEP IN THE FOREST.
>> WE SPRITES GUARDED IT CLOSELY
ALL NIGHT AND ALL DAY.
>> YEAH, EVEN ON THE DAY
OF THE FIRE.
WE GAVE EVERYTHING WE HAD
TO TAKE THE SACRED OBJECT
OUT OF THE BURNING SHRINE.
WE'VE BROUGHT IT FAR ENOUGH.
IT SHOULD BE SAFE HERE.
>> LOOK! ACORNS!
>> LOTS AND LOTS OF 'EM!
>> [ALL LAUGHING]
>> HEY, GUYS, LOOK!
OVER HERE, TOO!
HA HA HA HA!
>> AHA.
>> [TOGETHER] AHA.
>> HUH?
>> SO, IN OTHER WORDS,
YOU GUYS FORGOT ALL ABOUT IT.
>> NOW, THEN,
THE PURIFICATION WATER.
>> AT LONG LAST, I AM FREE.
>> [TOGETHER] AH, MONKEY GOD!
[LAUGHING]
>> WE'VE LONGED TO SEE YOU!
>> IT REEKED OF VEGETABLES!
>> MONKEY GOD!
>> SO, TELL ME, SPRITES,
HAS ANYTHING NOTEWORTHY HAPPENED
IN MY ABSENCE?
>> [TOGETHER] NOPE, NOT A THING.
>> HEY!
[WHIMPERING]
>> THEY FORGOT ABOUT YOU.
>> THE MONKEY GOD HAS GIVEN
HIS PROMISE TO PROTECT YOU.
IN RETURN, YOU MUST BUILD
A NEW SHRINE AND MAKE
REGULAR OFFERINGS.
>> [TOGETHER] THANK YOU.
>> [GRUNTS]
>> MUST FEEL GOOD,
FINALLY GETTING THAT WEIGHT
OFF YOUR HAND.
>> WHAT A WASTE OF TIME.
I KNEW WE SHOULDN'T HAVE
STOPPED HERE.
>> YOU ARE A VERY SHREWD
YOUNG GIRL.
I COMMEND YOUR POWERS
OF DEDUCTION.
YOU DID WELL TO FIND ME.
>> YOUR DREAM MESSAGES MADE IT
FAIRLY OBVIOUS WHERE YOU WERE.
>> HUMPH!
YOU 3 WERE JUST TOO STUPID
TO FIGURE IT OUT.
>> HEY, NOW, WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT DID YOU SAY TO US?
>> [SHOUTING AT ONCE]
>> I WANTED TO GET OUT OF THERE
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
I WAS CONCERNED ABOUT
THE STRANGE OCCURRENCE OUTSIDE.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> SHORTLY AFTER I WAS PLACED
IN THE PICKLING TUB, I FELT
AN AWFUL DEMONIC AURA PASS OVER
THE SKIES ABOVE THE VILLAGE.
IT WAS AN ENORMOUS AND SINISTER
PRESENCE--THE LIKES OF WHICH
I HAD NEVER FELT BEFORE.
>> [GASP]
>> A DEMONIC AURA?
>> SO WHAT WAS IT, MONKEY GOD?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT WAS OR
WHERE IT CAME FROM, BUT I FELT
ITS PRESENCE WHILE I WAS
IN THE PICKLING TUB.
>> THEN WHAT?
>> IN WHICH DIRECTION DID IT GO?
>> IT DISAPPEARED.
>> DISAPPEARED?
>> IT DIDN'T JUST PASS OVER
COMPLETELY.
IT SUDDENLY VANISHED
INTO THIN AIR.
>> INUYASHA...
>> IT COULDN'T HAVE BEEN ANYONE
BUT NARAKU.
>> THE DEMONIC AURA HEADED
IN THE DIRECTION OF THE OX
AND TIGER.
>> OX AND TIGER?
OH, THAT'S NORTHEAST.
>> I'M SORRY I CAN'T PINPOINT
EXACTLY WHERE IT DISAPPEARED.
>> SO, SHALL WE GO?
>> YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, WE'VE GOT
THE DIRECTION, SO LET'S MOVE.
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> [GRUNTING]
>> [MEOW]
>> LOOK! THEY'RE ACORNS!
>> [TOGETHER] HA HA HA HA!
>> YOU LITTLE MONKEYS!
>> HA! SCARED YA!
MOONED YA, SHIPPO!
>> MOONED YA, INUYASHA!
>> [TOGETHER] AND DON'T GET INTO
ANY PICKLES!
[LAUGHING]
>> GRRRR! WHAT'S WITH THEM?
>> THOSE GUYS WERE SOME TOUGH
RIVALS, WEREN'T THEY?
>> HA! JUST PESKY MONKEYS.
HEY, SHIPPO!
>> HUH?
UH, HEY, WAIT UP, INUYASHA!
>> QUIT DAWDLING.
WE'RE HEADING NORTHEAST.
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
KAGOME IS SICK?
SHE MUST'VE BECOME
EXHAUSTED WITH ALL THIS
SEARCHING FOR NARAKU.
HER COLD GOT WORSE,
AND SHE'S RUNNING A FEVER.
I HAD HER RETURN HOME
TO HER OWN ERA.
>> THEY'VE GOT MEDICINE
AND DOCTORS THERE.
I HOPE SHE RECOVERS QUICKLY.
>> INUYASHA WENT BACK
TO SEE HER.
>> TO WISH HER WELL?
>> LIKE HE'S THE KIND OF GUY
TO DO THAT.
>> NEXT TIME, "NURSING BATTLE
OF THE RIVAL LOVERS."
>> RIVALS?
WHO ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?