>> LORD SESSHOMARU.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
[BIRD CAWS]
>> SO YOU WERE THE ONE BEHIND
ALL THIS, SESSHOMARU!
IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
UNH!
>> LORD SESSHOMARU!
MAKE SURE HE DOESN'T GET AWAY
ON ME!
LORD SESSHOMARU!
>> WHY, YOU--
>> STOP YOUR BARKING, INUYASHA.
>> WHAT?!
>> THIS WOMAN HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH YOU.
>> WAIT A MINUTE, ISN'T THAT
LADY ONE OF SESSHOMARU'S
COHORTS?
>> HUH?
I GUESS NOT.
>> PLEASE ACCEPT THIS.
USE THIS SWORD TO PUT AN END TO
INUYASHA'S LIFE.
>> YOU'RE UNDER THE WRONG
IMPRESSION.
DID YOU TRULY BELIEVE THAT THIS
IS WHAT I DESIRED?
FOR YOU TO STEAL HIS SWORD
FOR ME?
>> AND YOU DO NOT?
>> I WILL NOT ACCEPT HELP
DEFEATING INUYASHA, ESPECIALLY
NOT FROM SOMEONE LIKE YOU.
>> PLEASE, DON'T GO!
LORD SESSHOMARU!
LORD SESSHOMARU...
>> YOU WENCH!
GIVE ME BACK MY TETSUSAIGA!
>> HMM.
>> UNH!
>> INUYASHA!
>> HE'S GOING TO TURN INTO
A STATUE, TOO!
>> UNH!
DAMN YOU!
IRON REAVER--UNH!
>> INUYASHA!
INUYASHA!
>> ARE YOU OK?
SAY SOMETHING!
>> SHE WON'T GET AWAY, DAMN IT.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO FOLLOW?
>> OH, YEAH.
YOU TWO GO BACK AND CHECK UP ON
MIROKU AND SANGO WHILE I'M GONE.
>> OH, RIGHT.
YOU'RE BACK TO NORMAL, SO WITH
ANY LUCK, THE SPELL ON MIROKU
AND SANGO SHOULD BE BROKEN, AND
THEY'LL BE BACK TO NORMAL, TOO.
>> ARE YOU SURE YOU'LL BE ALL
RIGHT ON YOUR OWN, THOUGH?
>> DAMN RIGHT I WILL!
I AM GOING TO GET BACK
MY TETSUSAIGA!
>> THIS TREE.
OF COURSE.
I REMEMBER NOW.
I SHALL SEE FOR MYSELF WHETHER A
HALF-DEMON LIKE YOU COULD TRULY
WIELD THE TETSUSAIGA.
[ROARS]
>> WHAT IS THAT?
>> A DEMON?
>> YOU'RE AN EYESORE.
GET OUT OF MY WAY.
>> WHAT DID YOU SAY?
>> WAIT!
LOOK AT HIM!
I THINK HE'S INJURED.
>> IT MAKES NO DIFFERENCE.
BEFORE WE TAKE ASANO CASTLE,
LET'S TEAR THIS WRETCH TO
SHREDS.
[SHOUTING]
[SCREAMING]
>> HAH!
PATHETIC HUMANS.
>> WHAT MANNER OF BEAST ARE YOU?
>> MOVE.
>> NOT ON YOUR LIFE!
[BIRDS SINGING]
DAMN YOU, HALF-BREED INUYASHA.
>> [GASPS]
>> I WANT THE TETSUSAIGA.
GIVE IT TO ME.
>> LORD SESSHOMARU!
OH, HOW I'VE SEARCHED FOR YOU,
LORD SESSHOMARU.
>> IT'S YOU, JAKEN.
>> YES.
OH, THAT DESPICABLE INUYASHA.
HE NOT ONLY TOOK THE TETSUSAIGA,
HE TOOK YOUR LEFT ARM, TOO.
>> LORD SESSHOMARU, IF THAT IS
HIS NAME.
>> CURSE THAT INUYASHA!
[FOOTSTEPS]
>> DO YOU REMEMBER NOW?
ON THAT DAY SO VERY LONG AGO,
YOU WERE LEANING AGAINST A TREE
AND RESTING FROM YOUR INJURIES.
IT'S STILL SO VIVID.
I WILL NEVER FORGET THE SIGHT OF
YOU THAT DAY.
I HAD NEVER SEEN ANYONE AS
HANDSOME AS YOU.
AND I GAZED FOR A LONG, LONG
TIME.
LATER THAT DAY, I WENT TO A
NEARBY PASTURE TO PICK FLOWERS
FOR YOU.
AND I WAS FILLED WITH SO MUCH
HAPPINESS.
[FLUTE MUSIC]
>> IS THAT DEMON STILL THERE?
>> YES, MY LORD.
HE IS STILL THERE.
>> WHAT IS SARA DOING?
>> IT SEEMS THAT THE PRINCESS
GOES THERE EVERY DAY TO CHECK
ON HIM.
>> ALL RIGHT!
SUMMON THE TROOPS!
WE GO TO SLAY THE DEMON!
>> BUT WHY, MY LORD?
>> I WILL NOT HAVE MY DEAR
DAUGHTER STOLEN BY A DEMON!
BEFORE WE SHAME THE ASANU CLAN
FOR ALL ETERNITY, WE MUST TAKE
IMMEDIATE ACTION!
[HORSES GALLOPING]
>> PLEASE WAIT, FATHER!
LORD SESSHOMARU PROTECTED OUR
CASTLE!
HE IS OUR SAVIOR!
>> OUT OF THE WAY, SARA!
>> AAH!
MY FATHER'S ACTIONS WERE
UNFORGIVABLE.
THERE'S NO POSSIBLE WAY I CAN
EVER MAKE AMENDS.
>> THE SOUND OF A FLUTE.
>> HUH?
>> I THOUGHT I HEARD A FLUTE
THAT DAY.
>> YES.
IT WAS THIS SAME FLUTE.
[PEOPLE TALKING]
>> HUH?
>> SANGO!
MIROKU!
>> HUH?
>> KAGOME, SHIPPO, WHAT ON EARTH
HAPPENED?
>> WEREN'T WE OUT BY THE SEA
JUST NOW?
>> I'LL EXPLAIN IT ALL LATER.
BUT BEFORE THAT, WE HAVE TO GO
AFTER INUYASHA.
[FLUTE PLAYING]
[HORSES GALLOPING]
>> HUH?
[WHINNIES]
WHO ARE YOU MEN?
>> WRETCHED DEMON, PREPARE
TO DIE!
>> HOW DARE YOU THREATEN
MY LORD!
>> JAKEN.
>> YES?
>> GET OUT OF THE WAY.
>> WELL, OF COURSE, BUT I--
>> RIFLE SQUADS, STEP TO THE
FOREFRONT!
[FLUTE PLAYING]
SARA'S PLAYING.
NEVER MIND.
RIFLE SQUAD, TAKE AIM AND FIRE!
>> LORD SESSHOMARU!
>> OH!
LORD SESSHOMARU.
[MEN SCREAMING]
>> SIR, THE RIFLE SQUAD!
>> CURSE HIM FOR ALL ETERNITY,
THAT BLASTED DEMON!
>> YOU FOOLISH MORTALS!
YOU WON'T GET AWAY WITH DEFYING
LORD SESSHOMARU!
>> RETREAT!
RETREAT!
[MEN YELLING]
>> LORD SESSHOMARU, ALLOW ME TO
TAKE CARE OF THESE PESKY FOOLS
FOR YOU.
>> LET THEM GO.
>> HUH?
>> THE FLUTE?
>> UHH.
>> THE FLUTE HAS STOPPED.
>> IT WAS SHORTLY AFTER THAT,
THE ASANO CASTLE BURNED TO THE
GROUND.
IT WAS MY FATHER, SOJU ASANO,
WHO HAD SET THE CASTLE ON FIRE.
[CRAZY LAUGHTER]
HE WAS SO FRIGHTENED BY YOU,
LORD SESSHOMARU, THAT HE MUST
HAVE GONE MAD.
HE CHOSE DEATH, AND HE WENT DOWN
WITH HIS CASTLE.
I HARBOR NO ILL WILL TOWARDS YOU
FOR WHAT HAPPENED.
MY DERANGED FATHER WAS TO BLAME.
AFTER HIS DEATH, I ENTERED A
NUNNERY TO PRAY FOR THE REPOSE
OF MY FATHER AND HIS VASSALS.
BUT CALL IT PUNISHMENT OR CRUEL
TWIST OF FATE, I BECAME GRAVELY
ILL WITH A WASTING SICKNESS.
IT QUICKLY TOOK HOLD OF MY BODY,
AND I LEARNED THAT I HAD ONLY
A VERY FEW DAYS LEFT TO LIVE.
I WOULD HAVE ENDED MY LIFE
WITHOUT EVER REVEALING MY
FEELINGS FOR YOU.
BUT THEN INUYASHA APPEARED.
WHEN I SAW INUYASHA, I HAD
SECOND THOUGHTS ABOUT MY
RESOLVE.
IF I COULD JUST LIVE A LITTLE
LONGER, I COULD SOMEHOW ATTACK
HIM.
EVEN IF IT MEANT DYING IN THE
PROCESS, I WOULD STEAL THE
TETSUSAIGA AWAY FROM HIM.
I FELT IT WAS THE LEAST I COULD
DO, TO ATONE FOR WHAT MY FATHER
HAD DONE.
[WOMEN SOBBING]
THAT'S WHEN SOMETHING STRANGE
HAPPENED.
I WAS SUDDENLY SURROUNDED BY
APPARITIONS.
[DEMONS GROWLING]
CAN NO ONE ELSE SEE THIS?
[EVIL LAUGHTER]
>> SARA, WE CAN MAKE YOUR WISH
COME TRUE.
YOUR SPIRITUAL ENERGY WILL
BECOME OUR STRENGTH.
IF YOU GIVE US YOUR PHYSICAL
BODY, WE'LL BE ABLE TO KILL
INUYASHA AND TAKE POSSESSION OF
THE TETSUSAIGA.
WELL, SARA?
DON'T YOU WANT TO TELL
SESSHOMARU HOW YOU FEEL?
>> LORD SESSHOMARU...
MY BEAUTIFUL LORD SESSHOMARU.
I HAD NO DOUBTS ABOUT ACCEPTING
THEIR PROPOSAL.
WITHOUT RESERVATION, RATHER
HAPPILY IN FACT, I GAVE MY BODY
AND SOUL TO THOSE DEMONS.
[WOMEN EXCLAIMING]
[DEMONS GROWLING]
SUCH AN ENORMOUS SPIRITUAL
ENERGY.
MY SOUL AND BODY HAD BEEN
RELEASED.
I WAS REBORN.
LORD SESSHOMARU, PLEASE, AT
LEAST ACKNOWLEDGE ALL I HAVE
DONE FOR YOU UNTIL THIS DAY.
>> SO THAT IS YOUR TRUE FORM,
IS IT?
>> TRUE FORM?
WHAT CAN YOU POSSIBLY MEAN BY
THAT, LORD SESSHOMARU?
>> THERE YOU ARE, WENCH!
>> IT'S INUYASHA.
>> IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
HUH?
IT FIGURES!
SO YOU'RE GOING TO GET IN THE
WAY, ARE YOU, SESSHOMARU?
>> DON'T LAY A FINGER ON HER.
SHE IS NONE OF YOUR CONCERN,
INUYASHA.
>> OH, YEAH?
THAT'S WHAT YOU THINK!
I'M GOING TO GET MY TETSUSAIGA
BACK!
BLAZE OF BLOOD!
>> UNH!
CURSE YOU, INUYASHA.
I WILL SEND YOU TO YOUR DEATH.
WHAT?
>> I'VE SEEN MORE THAN ENOUGH OF
YOUR DISGUSTINGLY WRETCHED FORM,
WOMAN.
>> LORD SESSHOMARU...
>> LOOK, THERE, IT'S INUYASHA!
>> TAKE US DOWN, KIRARA.
>> HEY, LOOK WHO'S FIGHTING
DOWN THERE.
>> IT'S SESSHOMARU AND THAT
WOMAN.
>> WHY ARE THEY FIGHTING?
[SCREAMING
>> DAMN YOU, SESSHOMARU.
YOU'VE EXPOSED US!
>> YOUR DISGUISE DIDN'T FOOL ME.
>> HA HA HA.
GOOD FOR YOU, SESSHOMARU.
YOU FOUND US OUT.
IT'S AS YOU THOUGHT: SARA WAS
SIMPLY A MEDIUM.
IT WAS NEVER INUYASHA WE WERE
AFTER--IT WAS YOU!
WE USED INUYASHA.
WE KNEW IF WE STOLE HIS SWORD,
YOU WOULD COME WITHOUT FAIL.
IT SEEMS OUR PLAN WAS RIGHT
ON TARGET.
>> OH, LOOK AT ALL THOSE DEMONS!
>> INUYASHA!
>> HIRAIKOTSU!
>> INUYASHA, GET OUT OF THE WAY!
WIND TUNNEL!
>> HEY, MIROKU, DON'T GO SUCKING
UP MY TETSUSAIGA, TOO!
>> I DON'T PLAN ON IT.
>> DAMN IT.
>> HUH?
WAIT, INUYASHA.
LOOK AT THAT FLUTE.
>> WHAT NOW?!
>> THE NUN HAD THAT SAME FLUTE
WITH HER WHEN THE CONVENT
EXPLODED.
>> YEAH, AND YOUR POINT
WOULD BE?
>> THE DEMON COULD BE THAT NUN
WHO DIED IN THE EXPLOSION.
>> YOU MEAN THAT SWARM OF
DEMONS?
>> SO YOU THINK THOSE DEMONS
POSSESSED THE NUN WHOSE BODY
VANISHED?
>> THAT MUST BE IT.
>> HUH!
THEN THE BEST THING WE CAN DO
FOR HER IS DESTROY HER!
>> THIS WOMAN'S SPIRITUAL ENERGY
HAS BECOME OUR POWER.
AND ONCE WE ABSORB YOUR DEMONIC
POWERS, WE WILL BECOME THE MOST
POWERFUL DEMON OF ALL!
>> HUH.
NOTHING BUT TRASH.
>> LORD SESSHOMARU.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME, I BEG YOU.
>> SO SHE HASN'T BEEN
COMPLETELY TAKEN OVER.
>> SILENCE, WOMAN.
YOU ARE NOW A PART OF US.
SOON YOU WILL LOSE ALL VOLITION,
AND YOU WILL NOT BE ABLE TO
MOVE OR EVEN PASS ON TO THE
NETHERWORLD!
>> IT'S MY FAULT.
MY FOOLISHNESS IS TO BLAME.
FORGIVE ME, FOR BEING A BURDEN.
>> I SAID, KEEP QUIET!
>> LORD SESSHOMARU, IF YOU ARE
ABLE...
IF YOU ARE ABLE TO, PLEASE
DESTROY ME AND THESE TERRIBLE
DEMONS WHO POSSESS ME!
>> IT'S USELESS.
THAT SWORD IS CONSUMED BY SHEER
ANGER AND HATRED.
TO THOSE OF US WHO THIRST FOR
BLOOD, THAT SWORDS REVITALIZES
US!
YOU CANNOT DESTROY US!
THAT SWORD ONLY GIVES US POWER!
AAH!
[DEMON ROARS]
>> KAGOME!
>> I'M GOING TO TRY.
I WANT TO SAVE HER.
I DON'T KNOW, BUT MAYBE I CAN
PURIFY HER BODY OF THOSE DEMONS.
HIT THE MARK!
>> DAMN YOU, MEDDLING GIRL!
>> KAGOME, THE DEMONS HAVE
MULTIPLIED!
>> CRAP!
>> I'M SORRY!
BUT IF WE DON'T DO ANYTHING,
THAT WOMAN'S DOOMED.
>> IF I CANNOT USE MY TOUKIJIN,
THERE IS ONLY THIS.
>> THE TETSUSAIGA!
>> SESSHOMARU IS WIELDING THE
TETSUSAIGA!
>> TETSUSAIGA, YOU CAN DESTROY
100 DEMONS IN A SINGLE STROKE.
LEND ME YOUR POWER.
[SCREAMING]
>> IMPOSSIBLE!
AAH!
>> THE TETSUSAIGA!
I'VE GOT YOU BACK AT LAST,
TETSUSAIGA.
NOW I'LL SHOW YOU.
THIS IS MY TETSUSAIGA!
HUH?
KAGOME!
>> GO!
HURRY, INUYASHA, YOUR WINDSCAR.
>> YEAH, SURE.
WINDSCAR!
[BIRDS SINGING]
>> AT LAST I'VE BEEN SET FREE
AGAIN.
LORD SESSHOMARU, THANK YOU
FOR HELPING ME.
I HAVE NO REGRETS, BECAUSE IN
THE END, I WAS ABLE TO EXPRESS
MY TRUE FEELINGS TO YOU.
MY LOVE FOR YOU.
>> GO AND PLAY YOUR FLUTE IN
THE NETHERWORLD.
>> OH, WHAT A SHAME.
I CAN'T HELP BUT FEEL SORRY FOR
THE WOMAN.
>> HMM.
>> NO, I BELIEVE THAT EVERYTHING
TURNED OUT FOR THE BEST.
>> WAS THE LADY'S SOUL SAVED
IN THE END?
>> I BELIEVE SO, JUDGING FROM
THE PEACEFUL EXPRESSION I SAW
ON HER FACE.
>> I SUPPOSE, IN THE END,
SESSHOMARU SAVED LADY SARA.
>> HAH!
AS IF SESSHOMARU WOULD EVER DO
SOMETHING LIKE THAT!
HE JUST HAPPENED TO BE PASSING
THROUGH, LIKE THE WIND.
COME ON!
>> WHERE COULD HE HAVE GONE?
OH, I DON'T LIKE THIS ONE BIT!
>> HMM?
OH, LORD SESSHOMARU!
>> OH, THANK GOODNESS!
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN,
LORD SESSHOMARU?
>> NOWHERE.
>> WELL, YOU MUST HAVE BEEN
SOMEWHERE.
DON'T BE SO VAGUE.
>> LET'S GO.
>> OK!
>> FORGIVE ME, MY LORD.
LORD SESSHOMARU!
[THUD]
OW!
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> WHAT DID YOU SAY, HACHI?
MASTER MUSHIN IS GOING TO DIE?
>> I'M SURE OF IT.
I SAW SOMETHING I WISH I HADN'T.
>> MUSHIN?
YOU MEAN THE MONK WHO RAISED
MIROKU?
>> EVERYONE DIES EVENTUALLY.
NO SENSE GETTING SENTIMENTAL.
>> INUYASHA!
>> NO, INUYASHA IS RIGHT.
ALL THAT LIVES MUST SOMEDAY DIE.
>> MIROKU, ISN'T THERE ANYTHING
WE CAN DO?
>> NEXT TIME, "THE LAST BANQUET
OF MIROKU'S MASTER."
>> LET US AT LEAST GIVE HIM A
FINE SENDOFF TO THE NETHERWORLD.