>> OUR JOURNEY CONTINUES
TO DEFEAT OUR ARCH ENEMY NARAKU.
AND FIND THE FEW REMAINING
SACRED JEWEL SHARDS BEFORE
HE DOES.
THERE IS ONE OTHER WHO PURSUES
NARAKU--SESSHOMARU,
INUYASHA'S OLDER BROTHER.
SESSHOMARU IS A FULL-BLOODED
DEMON, AND CANNOT STAND THE
SIGHT OF HIS HALF DEMON BROTHER,
WHOM HE CONSIDERS A DISGRACE
TO THE FAMILY.
INUYASHA AND SESSHOMARU'S FATHER
WAS A GREAT DOG DEMON,
WHO RULED OVER THE LANDS
OF THE WEST.
THE DEMON SWORD TETSUSAIGA WAS
BURIED IN THEIR FATHER'S GRAVE.
AND THAT IS THE VERY SOURCE
OF THE TWO BROTHER'S HOSTILITY
TOWARD EACH OTHER.
>> THERE'S A BARRIER AROUND
THE SWORD.
>> HUH?
UH?
OH, NO!
INUYASHA IS IMMUNE TO THE SPELL
THAT THWARTED LORD SESSHOMARU.
>> NO, YOU SHOULD SHUT UP
AND LET ME PROTECT YOU, OK?
>> HMM?
THE TETSUSAIGA IS PULSING.
>> REACTING TO INUYASHA'S
DECLARATION THAT HE WOULD
PROTECT ME,
TETSUSAIGA TRANSFORMED INTO
THE SWORD OF THE FANG.
SESSHOMARU LOST HIS LEFT ARM.
HE'S TRIED TO TAKE TETSUSAIGA
FROM INUYASHA A NUMBER OF TIMES,
BUT INUYASHA HAS NEVER LOST IT
TO HIM.
THEY'RE BLOOD BROTHERS.
IS SESSHOMARU SO COLD-HEARTED
BECAUSE HE'S A DEMON?
STILL, THERE'S A WOMAN WHO LOVES
EVEN HIM.
>> AHH.
MM, THE OCEAN AIR FEELS SO GOOD.
>> HUH.
PERSONALLY, I CAN'T STAND
THIS SALTY SMELL.
>> NO?
WELL I LIKE IT.
>> ME, TOO.
I SHOULD'VE BROUGHT
MY BATHING SUIT.
>> KAGOME, WE DIDN'T COME HERE
TO FROLIC IN THE SURF.
>> YEAH, BUT THERE'S NOTHING
WRONG WITH RELAXING
ONCE IN A WHILE.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
ONCE IN A WHILE?
IF YOU ASK ME, ALL YOU EVER DO
IS RELAX.
>> HMM.
HEY, WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT
EXACTLY?
>> HEH HEH, THAT REMINDS ME,
KAGOME, DO YOU SENSE ANY
SACRED JEWEL SHARDS?
>> UHH.
NOPE.
>> AND I'M NOT SENSING
A DEMONICAL AURA EITHER.
IT SEEMS THAT THIS AREA HAS BEEN
BLESSED WITH PEACE.
>> THAT'S WHY WE'VE GOT TO ENJOY
OUR LITTLE VACATION.
INUYASHA!
FETCH, BOY!
>> HUH?
AH, KAGOME!
STOP TREATING ME LIKE A DOG.
>> [SOBBING]
>> HOW VERY SAD, DEAR PRINCESS.
>> PLEASE, I AM NO LONGER
A PRINCESS, REMEMBER?
I AM SIMPLY SARA, CALL ME SARA.
>> WHAT A TERRIBLE SHAME,
IF ONLY ASANO CASTLE
HADN'T BURNED DOWN.
>> I WISH YOU HADN'T FALLEN ILL,
AND IN THIS IMPOVERISHED PLACE,
NO LESS.
>> IT'S SO HORRIBLY SAD.
>> SAD, PERHAPS,
BUT THIS IS MY FATE.
I'M AFRAID I'VE BEEN SUCH
A BURDEN TO YOU ALL.
>> OH, NO, NOT IN THE LEAST,
MY LADY.
>> WE'VE BEEN TRULY BLESSED
HAVING BEEN ABLE TO SERVE YOU
FOR A TIME.
WE ALL FEEL THE SAME WAY.
>> AND I HAVE BEEN BLESSED
AS WELL.
HAVING BEEN SURROUNDED BY PEOPLE
LIKE YOU AND THE VILLAGERS.
MY FLUTE.
I'LL PLAY.
ONE LAST TIME.
ONE FINAL SONG.
[FLUTE PLAYS]
>> HUH?
>> HMM.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
>> WAIT!
HANG ON A MINUTE, INUYASHA.
>> AHH.
>> LADY SARA!
LADY SARA!
>> THERE'S ONE REGRET,
ONE BIT OF UNFINISHED BUSINESS.
AAH, AH...
>> HUH?
WHAT'S THE MATTER, MIROKU?
>> HMM?
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> DO YOU SENSE IT, TOO,
THEN, KAGOME?
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TWO
TALKING ABOUT?
>> A HUGE DEMONIC AURA
IS FORMING DOWN THERE.
>> REALLY?
[GROWLING]
>> AN EVIL THAT BIG COULD ONLY
MEAN...
>> YOU THINK IT'S NARAKU?
>> YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT THE
DEMONIC AURA GROWING DOWN THERE,
BUT IT ISN'T NARAKU.
>> I'M NOT SENSING ANY
JEWEL SHARDS, EITHER.
STILL...
>> IT'S GOT NOTHING TO DO
WITH US, LET'S GET GOING.
>> OHH!
>> WAIT A MINUTE,
THAT'S THE CONVENT.
>> SOMETHING MUST HAVE HAPPENED.
COME ON!
>> HUH.
WHAT A PAIN IN THE NECK.
YOU MIND TELLING US WHAT
HAPPENED HERE?
>> THE MOMENT LADY SARA
PASSED ON INSIDE,
THERE WAS A BLINDING LIGHT.
>> LADY SARA?
>> ONE OF THE NUNS WHO LIVED
IN THE CONVENT HERE.
>> SHE WAS A KIND AND GENEROUS
WOMAN WHO GAVE US VILLAGERS
MEDICINE.
>> HEAR THAT, MIROKU?
THE PART ABOUT THE BLINDING
LIGHT?
>> YES.
SOMETHING TELLS ME THE FLASH
THEY SPEAK OF HAS SOMETHING
TO DO WITH THE DEMONIC AURA
WE FELT EARLIER.
>> SPEAKING OF WHICH, THE AURA
SEEMS TO HAVE DISAPPEARED.
>> YEAH, I DON'T SENSE IT NOW.
>> LADY SARA, LADY SARA.
>> HER BODY, HOW HORRIBLE.
>> OVER THERE, KAGOME!
THE BEDDING HAS A CLEAR OUTLINE
OF A HUMAN BODY.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT, AND IT'S NOT
CHARRED AT ALL.
>> THAT WAS WHERE LADY SARA'S
BODY LAY.
THEN SUDDENLY, IT VANISHED
WITH THE LIGHT.
>> VANISHED?
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
>> SAY, MASTER JAKEN, LET'S PLAY
A GAME OF TONGUE TWISTERS.
>> TONGUE TWISTERS?
>> ME FIRST--RED JAKEN,
BLUE JAKEN, GOLD JAKEN.
>> RED JAKEN, BLUE JAKEN,
GOLD JAKEN.
>> HEY, YOU'RE PRETTY GOOD.
>> OF COURSE.
>> ONE MORE TIME.
RED JAKEN, BLUE JAKEN,
GOLD JAKEN.
>> FORGET IT.
>> WHY NOT?
SAY IT!
>> OHH.
LORD SESSHOMARU STILL SEARCHES
FOR NARAKU,
BUT WE HAVE YET TO FIND HIM.
OH, HOW LONG MUST WE CONTINUE
THIS FUTILE JOURNEY?
OOH, OH!
HUH?
>> IS SOMETHING THE MATTER,
LORD SESSHOMARU?
>> AAH!
[FLUTE PLAYS]
OHH.
>> IT'S BEEN QUITE SOME TIME,
LORD SESSHOMARU.
>> HUH!
WHO ARE YOU?
AN ACQUAINTANCE OF MY MASTER?
>> FORGIVE ME.
I AM SARA.
>> HUH?
WHO?
>> I AM FROM ASANO CASTLE.
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN IT?
>> ASANO CASTLE?
>> HUH?
>> THE FIRST TIME I SAW YOU,
LORD SESSHOMARU,
WAS AT ASANO CASTLE DURING
A MORE TURBULENT TIME.
>> MY LORD, IT SEEMS THE ENEMY
IS PLANNING TO END THE BATTLE
TONIGHT.
>> HMM.
IT'S BEEN A MONTH SINCE
THE SIEGE BEGAN.
PROVISIONS HAVE RUN OUT,
AND MORALE IS LOW.
THERE IS NO CHOICE BUT TO ACCEPT
DEATH AND MAKE THIS OUR
FINAL RESTING PLACE.
EVERYONE, LISTEN WELL.
WE WILL SET FIRE TO THE CASTLE,
AND OPEN THE MAIN GATES.
>> IS THERE NO OTHER CHOICE?
>> CAN WE NOT PRESERVE OUR
DIGNITY AT LEAST?
>> NO.
DO NOT ATTEMPT TO FIGHT
THE ENEMY, DO WHAT YOU MUST
TO SURVIVE.
>> UHH!
AAH!
>> MY LORD, MY LORD!
>> WHAT IS IT?
TELL ME WHAT'S HAPPENING.
>> SOMETHING SEEMS TO BE
ATTACKING THE ENEMY CAMP.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> WHAT MANNER OF BEAST ARE YOU?
AAH...
>> MOVE.
>> NOT ON YOUR LIFE!
>> A MERE RACCOON, OR MAYBE HELP
FROM HEAVEN.
>> FATHER?
>> HUH?
OH, SARA.
LOOK AT THAT FELLOW DOWN BELOW.
HE SINGLE-HANDEDLY BROKE THROUGH
THE ENEMY LINES,
AND IS SLAUGHTERING THEM ALL.
>> AAH!
>> LORD SESSHOMARU.
>> I DON'T KNOW YOU.
>> PLEASE, DON'T GO.
I WANT TO DO WHAT I CAN TO MAKE
YOUR WISH COME TRUE.
>> HELP ME?
YOU?
>> YES, AND WHEN I'VE HELPED YOU
REALIZE YOUR DESIRE,
I ONLY ASK THAT YOU ACKNOWLEDGE
MY FEELINGS FOR YOU.
>> HEY, HEY, HEY.
WILL YOU STOP THIS NONSENSE?
THERE'S NO WAY SOMEONE LIKE YOU
CAN FULFILL LORD SESSHOMARU'S
WISHES.
>> JAKEN!
LEAVE HER.
>> AAH!
YES, ME LORD.
>> I WILL FULFILL YOUR WISH
NO MATTER WHAT IT TAKES.
>> HMM.
AS YOU PLEASE.
>> GOOD.
>> HUH?
WHAT?
SUCH A STRANGE MORTAL.
LORD SESSHOMARU, WHO WAS THAT
ODD WOMAN ANYWAY?
>> SHE SURE WAS PRETTY.
>> WELL, FACE POWDER DOES
MIRACLES.
HONESTLY, AS IF A MERE HUMAN
CAN HELP OUR LORD.
>> ARE YOU BLIND, JAKEN?
>> HUH?
>> THAT WAS NO HUMAN.
IT WASN'T?
>> IT WAS A DEMON.
NOW, PERHAPS SHE WAS ORIGINALLY
HUMAN, BUT NEVER QUITE BECAME
A FULL DEMON.
>> WHAT?
>> I WONDER WHAT CAUSED
THAT EXPLOSION AT THE CONVENT.
>> WHO KNOWS.
>> I'VE HEARD THAT WHEN
A DEMONIC AURA ACCUMULATES AS
RAPIDLY AS THE ONE WE WITNESSED,
IT CAN ACTUALLY CAUSE
EXPLOSIONS.
BUT WHAT PUZZLES ME EVEN MORE
THAN THE EXPLOSIONS IS WHY
THE BODY OF LADY SARA VANISHED.
ARE THE TWO RELATED?
>> YOU KNOW, I HAVE
A BAD FEELING ABOUT THIS.
>> I'M NOT SURPRISED,
BUT YOU GOT TO ADMIT IT'S GOT
NOTHING TO DO WITH US.
BETTER NOT GO STICKING OUR NOSES
INTO IT.
[GROWLS]
WHAT THE--
>> WHAT IS THAT?
>> A WHALE?
>> NO, IT'S--A DEMON.
[HISSES]
>> LOOK, INUYASHA, OVER THERE!
>> HUH?
>> WHAT'S THAT WOMAN DOING
UP ON THE CLIFF?
>> WHO KNOWS, BUT MY GUESS
IS SHE'S PROBABLY WHAT THAT
SEA DEMON IS AFTER.
>> DON'T WORRY, I'LL SAVE YOU,
YOUNG LADY!
>> WAIT, MIROKU!
UHH.
I SHOULD'VE FIGURED AS MUCH.
HE'S SO PREDICTABLE.
>> AWW, MAN.
I COULD SAVE A THOUSAND LIVES
AND IT WOULDN'T BE ENOUGH
AROUND YOU GUYS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOIN' ON MY BACK?
>> NEVER MIND, JUST GET GOING!
>> GIDDY UP!
>> UHH, ALL RIGHT ALREADY.
>> QUICK, MIROKU, GET ON!
>> UH!
>> UHH, HIRAIKOTSU!
>> YEAH!
WELL DONE, SANGO.
SANGO, LISTEN.
YOU TAKE CARE OF THE GIRL.
I'LL VANQUISH THIS CREATURE
WITH MY WIND TUNNEL.
>> RIGHT, GOT IT.
>> HMM.
>> OHH!
>> SANGO?
OH!
>> MIROKU!
SANGO!
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO THEM?
THEY'RE FROZEN SOLID!
>> WHAT THE HECK IS GOING ON
HERE?
>> IT IS THE WRATH
OF THE SEA GOD.
>> SEA GOD?
>> WHAT, YOU MEAN THAT DEMON?
>> THEIR HEARTS ARE STILL
BEATING.
THAT MEANS THEY'RE ALIVE.
>> THAT'S A GOOD START,
BUT HOW CAN WE SAVE THEM?
>> HOW ELSE?
WE GOTTA FIND THAT SEA DEMON
AND DESTROY IT.
>> YOU CAN'T DESTROY A GOD.
>> WHO CARES IF IT'S A GOD,
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
>> IT'S COMING.
[ROARS]
>> HUH.
SOME SEA GOD.
WIND SCAR!
[HOWLS]
HMM?
HEY, WHAT'S THAT?
SEAWEED?
>> INUYASHA!
IT DIDN'T WORK,
THEY DIDN'T CHANGE BACK.
>> OH, NO, YOU'RE KIDDING.
>> WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WHY DIDN'T THEY CHANGE BACK
TO NORMAL?
>> HMM.
>> THEY LOOK LIKE GLASS.
>> EVEN THEIR CLOTHES AND
SANGO'S WEAPON HAVE HARDENED.
>> I DON'T GET IT.
HOW COME THEY DIDN'T TURN BACK
TO NORMAL?
>> I THINK IT'S POSSIBLE
THE CURSE OF THE SEA GOD
HASN'T BEEN BROKEN.
I KNOW I SHOULD BE GRATEFUL
THAT YOU SAVED ME, BUT THAT'S
WHERE THE PROBLEM LIES.
>> HUH?
>> THE REASON THE CURSE COULDN'T
BE BROKEN IS BECAUSE YOU SAVED
ME FROM THE GOD.
>> HUH?
>> SO, WHY ARE YOU HERE, ANYWAY?
>> I CAN EXPLAIN IT IN DETAIL
LATER.
BUT FIRST WE SHOULD HURRY
AND GET YOUR FRIENDS TO SAFETY
BEFORE THE TIDE COMES IN
AND THE WAVES CARRY THEM BOTH
FAR OUT TO SEA.
>> HMM.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> DO YOU THINK YOU CAN BRING
THEM TO MY VILLAGE?
>> YEAH, SURE.
LEAVE THEM TO ME.
>> MY NAME IS UMINEKO.
>> WHY WERE YOU TIED UP
LIKE THAT?
>> I WAS AN OFFERING
TO THE SEA GOD.
>> OFFERING?
>> CORRECT.
EVERY 4 YEARS THE SEA IN
THIS AREA BECOMES VERY ROUGH,
SO IN MY VILLAGE IT IS A
TRADITION TO OFFER A SACRIFICE
TO THE SEA GOD.
>> OH, NO!
IT IS JUST AS I FEARED.
>> DID THIS HAPPEN TO EVERYONE
BECAUSE WE DEFEATED THE SEA GOD?
>> WE DIDN'T DO IT.
I'M THE ONE TO BLAME.
IF HE HAD TO CURSE SOMEONE,
IT SHOULD'VE BEEN ME.
>> ISN'T THERE ANY WAY TO TURN
THEM BACK TO NORMAL?
>> PERHAPS.
>> UH?
>> THERE IS A CHANCE THAT THE
SEA GOD'S SHRINE IS DESTROYED.
>> WHAT?
THE SEA GOD'S SHRINE?
>> CORRECT.
>> ALL RIGHT, SHOW US WHERE
THIS SHRINE OF YOURS IS.
>> OF COURSE.
>> HUH?
>> LONG AGO, THE ASANO CLAN
RESIDED UP HERE.
THERE USED TO BE A FINE CASTLE
ON THE TOP OF THE CLIFF.
THERE'S THE SHRINE.
>> HMM.
>> LEGEND HAS IT THAT TURNING
THE VERTICAL OPENING IN
THE ROCK SIDEWAYS WOULD MAKE
THE SHRINE COLLAPSE.
AND THEN THE ENTIRE CLIFF WOULD
SINK INTO THE SEA.
>> HUH.
THEN YOU SHOULD'VE JUST
DESTROYED THE SHRINE IN THE
FIRST PLACE.
>> THAT IS A GOOD POINT,
AND THE VILLAGERS ATTEMPTED
IT ONCE.
BUT NOT EVEN 5 OF THE
STRONGEST MEN WERE ABLE
TO BUDGE THE HEAVY STONE.
>> HUH, THEN I'LL GIVE IT
A SHOT.
UHH!
>> COME ON, INUYASHA,
YOU CAN DO IT!
>> IT'S NOT EVEN MOVING.
>> DAMN IT ALL.
>> INSTEAD OF USING YOUR
BARE HANDS, WHY DON'T YOU TRY
USING A TOOL?
>> HUH?
WHAT KIND OF TOOL?
>> WELL, LIKE THAT SWORD
OF YOURS, FOR INSTANCE.
>> HMM?
OH, I GET YOU.
HMM.
HERE GOES.
UHH!
>> IT'S OPENING!
>> UHH...
UH.
>> YES, IT'S MOVING.
>> YOU CAN DO IT, INUYASHA.
>> HEY, KAGOME, SOMETHING ABOUT
THAT WOMAN IS GIVING ME
THE CREEPS.
>> WHAT?
>> REMEMBER WHEN MIROKU AND
SANGO WERE TURNED INTO STATUES?
THE WOMAN WAS TIED TO THE POST,
AND THEY WERE BOTH LOOKING
STRAIGHT AT HER.
>> YEAH, SO WHAT ABOUT IT?
>> IF THE SEA GOD HAD DONE THAT
TO THEM, WOULDN'T THEY BE
LOOKING OUT TOWARD THE SEA?
>> GOOD POINT.
>> ALSO, I SAW HER SMILE WHEN
INUYASHA STARTED MOVING
THE STONE WITH HIS SWORD.
I'M STARTING TO THINK THIS MIGHT
BE A TRAP.
>> ME, TOO.
>> IT WASN'T THE SEA GOD
WHO DID THAT TO MIROKU
AND SANGO, IT WAS THAT WOMAN.
>> YEAH, BUT THEN, WHY?
>> UHH...
>> HMM.
>> [GASPS]
HANG ON, DON'T DO IT!
>> AAH!
I DID IT.
HUH?
AAH!
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
DAMN.
>> AAH!
UMINEKO, WATCH OUT!
LOOK, SEAWEED!
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> JUST LIKE THE SEA GOD.
>> THAT'S IT, THE SEA GOD
AND UMINEKO MUST HAVE BEEN
DEMON PUPPETS.
>> HUH?
DAMN.
WHAT IS HAPPENING INSIDE THERE?
>> INUYASHA, WHERE'S YOUR
TETSUSAIGA?
>> STILL INSIDE THE SHRINE.
>> OHH!
[SCREECHES]
DAMN, NOW WHAT?
>> [LAUGHS]
>> CURSE YOU, INUYASHA.
TETSUSAIGA...
GIVE ME THE TETSUSAIGA.
>> INUYASHA, UNFORTUNATELY FOR
YOU I AM TAKING YOUR TETSUSAIGA.
>> SHE'S GOT YOUR SWORD,
SHE STOLE IT!
>> THAT'S WHAT SHE WAS AFTER
ALL ALONG.
>> [GROWLS]
>> OH, NO, WHAT IS IT THIS TIME?
>> LORD SESSHOMARU,
WHY ARE YOU HERE?