[BELLS CHIMING]
- [SHOUTING]
- YOU'VE BROUGHT THE GIRL.
- [GROANING]
- NO, KAGOME!
CAREFUL!
- I DID IT!
I WON!
WHOO!
- HMM. WRONG ONE.
- YOU'RE GOOD, KAGOME.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU, MIROKU.
- THESE WESTERN KARUTA CARDS
ARE FASCINATING.
- LIKE I SAID, THEY'RE
NOT KARUTA CARDS.
THEY'RE PLAYING CARDS.
- PLAYING CARDS?
- YEAH.
IT'S JUST A GAME.
- YOU MIND KEEPING IT DOWN?
- HMM?
- CAN'T YOU PLAY
A LITTLE MORE QUIETLY?
- OH, QUIT YOUR WHINING
AND JOIN US.
- NOT ON YOUR LIFE.
- WHAT'S HE SO ANGRY ABOUT?
- HE'S IN A BAD MOOD.
- SITTING THERE AND FEELING
SORRY FOR YOURSELF
WON'T MAKE TETSUSAIGA
ANY STRONGER.
- BUTT OUT!
YOU'RE WRONG AGAIN!
- THE PROBLEM IS
NARAKU'S BARRIER.
- UNTIL HE'S ABLE
TO BREAK THROUGH IT,
HE CAN'T EVEN GET NEAR NARAKU.
- WIND SCAR!
[GRUNTING]
- THE WIND SCAR DIDN'T WORK!
- I'LL SAY IT AGAIN.
I ONLY CONTINUE
TO GROW IN POWER.
- YES, THIS IS DEFINITELY
A PROBLEM.
- YOU PEOPLE DON'T
NEED TO WORRY.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
- OH, YEAH?
HOW ARE YOU GONNA DO THAT?
- HAVE YOU COME UP
WITH SOME NEW IDEAS?
- HMM...
- I KNEW IT.
HE'S ALL TALK.
- I SHOULDN'T HAVE
GOT MY HOPES UP.
- KNOCK IT OFF, WOULD YOU?!
- I'LL TAKE CARE OF
THIS PROBLEM FOR YOU.
- HUH?
- MASTER...INUYASHA...
- MYOGA, IT'S YOU AGAIN.
- I KNOW HOW TO HANDLE
NARAKU'S BARRIER.
- WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT IT?
- FIRST LET ME TELL YOU HOW MUCH
TROUBLE IT WAS FINDING YOU.
- SPIT IT OUT!
TELL ME, AND YOU CAN
SUCK AS MUCH OF KAGOME'S
BLOOD AS YOU WANT.
- I'M NOT A BLOOD BANK,
YOU KNOW!
- LOOK, THIS IS NO TIME FOR
TELLING JOKES, I'M AFRAID.
YOU MUST GO IMMEDIATELY TO
THE CAVE OF THE DEMON BATS.
- CAVE OF THE DEMON BATS?
- THE CAVE OF
THE DEMON BAT TRIBE
IS LOCATED NEAR A VILLAGE
ON THE WESTERN SHORE.
THE CAVE IS PROTECTED BY
AN IMPENETRABLE BARRIER,
AND NO ONE IS ABLE
TO DESTROY THEM.
THE GUARDING OF THE BARRIER
HAS BEEN PASSED DOWN
FROM GENERATION TO GENERATION.
THE CURRENT GUARDIAN DEMON
MUST BE SLAIN.
IN OTHER WORDS,
YOU MUST KILL THE DEMON GUARDIAN
WHO HAS THE POWER
TO RETAIN THIS BARRIER
AND LET TETSUSAIGA
SUCK ITS BLOOD.
- BY KILLING SUCH
A STRONG OPPONENT,
THE SWORD WILL ABSORB
THE DEMON BATS' POWER.
- AND THAT WOULD MAKE
THE SWORD MUCH STRONGER.
- YES, EXACTLY.
NOW THEN, KAGOME,
ABOUT OUR LITTLE DEAL.
[GRUNTS]
- ALL RIGHT!
WHAT ARE WE WAITING FOR?
TIME TO GO DEMON HUNTING.
I'M IN, IF THAT'S ALL IT TAKES
TO MAKE MY SWORD STRONGER.
I'LL KILL A THOUSAND
OF THEM IF I HAVE TO.
- YOU WENCH!
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN
YOU WOULD LIE TO US!
- [GROANING]
- YOU PROMISED US OUR VILLAGE
WOULDN'T BE ATTACKED
IF YOU GAVE THEM YOUR DAUGHTER.
WELL?
- MORE VILLAGERS
HAVE BEEN KILLED!
YOU PROMISED IT WOULD HAPPEN!
- WHY DO THEY KEEP ATTACKING?
- SHE'S PROBABLY IN LEAGUE
WITH THOSE DEMON BATS HERSELF.
- SHE DESERVES NO MERCY FROM US.
ATTACK HER!
- [SHOUTING]
- HUH?
WHAT? WHO ARE YOU?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I HEARD YOU MENTION
THE DEMON BATS.
TELL ME WHERE I CAN FIND
THEIR CAVE, OLD MAN.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- HOW DARE YOU ATTACK
A DEFENSELESS WOMAN?
- HOW THE HELL WOULD WE KNOW
WHERE THE DEMON BAT CAVE IS?
- WHY DON'T YOU ASK
THAT LYING WENCH?
THE TRAITOR DARES TO
CALL HERSELF HUMAN,
BUT SHE BEDDED WITH
ONE OF THE BAT DEMONS
AND BORE HIM A CHILD.
- HUH?
- THE CHILD OF A DEMON?
- WHY DO YOU WANT
TO KNOW THE LOCATION
OF THE BAT DEMON CAVE?
- WHY ELSE?
I'M GONNA DESTROY THEM.
- WHAT?
- INUYASHA, HOLD ON A MINUTE.
THE VILLAGERS SAID YOU GAVE
YOUR CHILD TO THE DEMON BATS.
EXACTLY WHAT DID
THEY MEAN BY THAT?
- FOR GENERATIONS,
THIS REGION HAS BEEN A HOME
AND HUNTING GROUND TO
THE DEMON BAT TRIBE.
THEY'RE TERRIFYING,
PREYING ON BOTH
HUMANS AND ANIMALS
AND FEEDING ON THEIR BLOOD.
BUT TSUKUYOMARU WAS
NOT LIKE THE OTHERS.
MY DAUGHTER'S FATHER WAS
DIFFERENT FROM THE OTHER DEMONS.
HE DID NOT KILL HUMANS,
AND AFTER SHIORI WAS BORN,
THE OTHER BATS STOPPED
ATTACKING OUR VILLAGE.
I ASSUMED HE CONVINCED
THEM TO DO SO.
FINALLY, OUR VILLAGE
WAS AT PEACE.
- WAS AT PEACE?
- SHIORI'S FATHER PASSED AWAY,
AND THEN THERE WAS
NO ONE TO STOP THEM.
- THE DEMON BATS!
- AAH!
- [SHOUTING]
- SOON AFTER,
SHIORI'S GRANDFATHER,
TAIGOKUMARU, CAME TO SEE ME.
HE PROMISED TO LEAVE
OUR VILLAGE ALONE
IF I GAVE HIM MY DAUGHTER.
YOU SEE, HE AND SHIORI'S FATHER
WERE GUARDIANS OF THE BARRIER,
A DUTY PASSED DOWN
THROUGH GENERATIONS.
AS TSUKUYOMARU'S DAUGHTER,
SHIORI HAD INHERITED
HIS GUARDIAN POWERS.
- HUH?
- BUT WHY DID IT HAVE TO
BE YOUR DAUGHTER SHIORI?
IF HER GRANDFATHER HAD
THE GUARDIAN POWER ALREADY,
THEN HOW COME--
- THEIR POWER TO CREATE
THE BARRIER WANES WITH AGE,
AND ONCE THE GUARDIAN
PASSES ON HIS DUTY,
HE LOSES THE POWER.
- IN OTHER WORDS,
YOU'RE SAYING YOUR DAUGHTER
IS THE ONLY ONE LEFT
WHO HAS THE POWER TO
PROTECT THE BARRIER.
- EWW!
LOOK AT THE DEMON GIRL!
HA HA HA!
- SHE'S A HALF-DEMON!
- UNH!
- [LAUGHTER]
- [CRYING]
I'M HOME, MOMMY.
- WELCOME HOME, DEAR.
SHIORI, HOW DID YOU GET ALL
THOSE CUTS ON YOUR FACE?
- IT'S NOTHING.
I JUST FELL ON THE BEACH.
- [CRYING]
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
I TOLD YOU, I JUST FELL,
THAT'S ALL.
- SHIORI, I'M SO SORRY.
- [CRYING]
- I AGONIZED OVER WHAT TO DO,
BUT IN THE END, I GAVE
MY GIRL TO TAIGOKUMARU.
- [SHOUTING]
- HAVE YOU BROUGHT THE GIRL?
- AS PROMISED, I BROUGHT SHIORI.
IN RETURN, NEVER ATTACK
OUR VILLAGE AGAIN.
- I GIVE YOU MY PROMISE.
- YOU MUST GO WITH HIM, SHIORI.
- MOMMY, I'VE CHANGED MY MIND.
I'M AFRAID OF HIM.
- YOU MUST GO WITH HIM.
- YES, FOR THE VILLAGE.
- MOMMY!
- PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
YOU'LL BE HAPPIER WITH THEM.
- PARDON MY ASKING, BUT SHE
IS A HALF-DEMON, RIGHT?
- HOW CAN A HALF-DEMON CHILD
HAVE SUCH POWERS?
- I SEE YOU, TOO,
ARE A HALF-DEMON.
YOU SHOULD KNOW
BETTER THAN ANYONE
THAT HALF-DEMONS ARE
ACCEPTED BY NEITHER
THEIR DEMON NOR THEIR
HUMAN BRETHREN.
- MM-HMM.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THIS,
MASTER INUYASHA?
- HMPH. DON'T KNOW.
- SHIORI HAD AMPLE POWER
TO FULFILL HER DUTIES.
THAT'S WHY...
I THOUGHT IT WOULD
BE FOR THE BEST
FOR HER TO BE WITH THEM,
ESPECIALLY IF IT WOULD
SAVE OUR VILLAGE.
BUT THE DEMON BATS
DIDN'T KEEP THEIR WORD.
- HMPH.
TAKE ME THERE.
I WANT YOU TO TAKE ME THERE,
TO THE OLD MAN,
OLD WHAT'S-HIS-NAME, ALL RIGHT?
- WE'LL GO WITH YOU.
- NO. I CAN HANDLE THIS ALONE.
- BUT...
- I'M THE ONLY ONE WHO
NEEDS TO SEE THEM.
[PANTING]
- [LAUGHING]
[SNARLING]
- AAH!
AAH!
[SCREAMING]
- [GROWLING]
- TELL ME, WHAT'S ON
YOUR MIND, MASTER?
- JUST THINKING OF OLD TIMES.
HMM?
MYOGA, WHO SAID YOU
COULD COME WITH ME?!
- WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
IT'S NOT LIKE I'M IN THE WAY.
- GO BACK, MYOGA.
I TOLD EVERYONE I
WAS GOING ON MY OWN.
- DON'T BE SO HARSH.
- IT'S THIS WAY.
- HMM?
- LET'S KEEP GOING, MASTER.
COME ON.
- HMM.
IT'S YOUR LIFE.
- [GASP]
- EAT.
I CAN'T HAVE YOU
DYING OF STARVATION.
[CHUCKLES]
- IT'S THAT CAVE THERE,
WHERE IT'S GLOWING.
- HUH?
MOMMY!
- SHIORI.
- HEY, MYOGA,
ARE YOU SURE THIS IS GONNA MAKE
MY SWORD BECOME STRONGER?
- YES, BUT UNFORTUNATELY,
FIRST YOU MUST SLAY THE GIRL.
- HUH?
- SHIORI!
SHIORI!
- OH, MOMMY!
- HUH?
HUH?
- [GASP]
- I WAS WONDERING WHAT ALL
THE RUCKUS WAS ABOUT.
IT SEEMS WE HAVE VISITORS.
- IS THAT HIM?
- YES, THAT'S HIM.
HOW DARE YOU DECEIVE ME?!
- I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- YOU PROMISED YOU'D
LEAVE THE VILLAGE ALONE
IF I GAVE YOU MY DAUGHTER,
BUT YOU DIDN'T!
- INDEED.
DON'T TELL ME THAT YOU
HONESTLY BELIEVED THAT.
AS IF I WOULD KEEP A PROMISE...
TO A HUMAN.
- THEN RETURN MY DAUGHTER TO ME!
- MOMMY!
- I WILL NOT!
SHIORI WILL GUARD THE BARRIER
FOR THE REMAINDER OF HER LIFE.
SHE INHERITED THE DUTY
FROM HER FATHER,
AND SHE IS DOING A FINE JOB.
INDEED, IT IS HARD TO BELIEVE
THAT SHE HAS A HUMAN
FOR A MOTHER.
- [GROWLING]
- CALM DOWN.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO TAKE
YOUR DAUGHTER BY FORCE.
- YOU ACTUALLY THINK
YOU CAN WIN?
- THAT COCKY OLD BAT IS
STANDING IN FRONT OF SHIORI.
IF I ATTACK NOW...
I CAN SLAY HIM WITHOUT
HURTING SHIORI.
HYAH!
WIND SCAR!
HMM.
HUH?
HE REPELLED MY WIND SCAR!
- EI! THE RUMORS WERE RIGHT.
THE BARRIER OF THE DEMON BAT
IS VIRTUALLY IMPENETRABLE.
- WHO ARE YOU,
AND WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- IT DOESN'T MATTER WHO I AM!
JUST GIVE THE GIRL BACK!
- I SEE.
THE HUMANS MUST HAVE SENT YOU.
THEN YOU MUST PERISH!
- [GROANING]
- [CHUCKLES]
NEXT TIME, I WON'T MISS.
- DAMN YOU!
- [GROANING]
- STOP!
- HUH?
- PLEASE DON'T DO THIS,
GRANDFATHER.
DON'T HURT MY MOMMY, PLEASE!
I PROMISE TO GUARD THE BARRIER,
SO PLEASE...
JUST DON'T HURT MY MOMMY!
[CRYING]
- DID YOU HEAR THAT?
THIS YOUNG CHILD HAS FAR MORE
SENSE THAN EITHER OF YOU.
- SAVE IT FOR SOMEONE WHO CARES.
- LET ME ASK YOU THIS:
DO YOU THINK SHIORI WILL BE
HAPPY BACK IN THE HUMAN VILLAGE?
I DON'T.
THE VILLAGERS OSTRACIZED HER
BECAUSE SHE WAS HALF-DEMON.
THEY DIDN'T HESITATE
FOR A SECOND
TO SACRIFICE HER LIFE
FOR THEIR OWN.
HOW CAN I GIVE MY
PRECIOUS GRANDDAUGHTER
BACK TO SUCH SELFISH HUMANS?
- IT DIDN'T WORK?
- I SHOULD GIVE UP.
- ARE YOU SURE?
- TAIGOKUMARU SPOKE
THE TRUTH ABOUT SHIORI.
THE VILLAGERS DIDN'T
ACCEPT EITHER OF US.
MAYBE SHE'S BETTER OFF THERE.
- HMPH! YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
- HMM?
- DEMONS NEVER
ACCEPT HALF-DEMONS,
EVEN IF THEY'RE
RELATED BY BLOOD.
- I'M A FULL-BLOODED DEMON,
AND I HAVEN'T EVER
HAD ANY PROBLEMS
ACCEPTING YOU, INUYASHA.
- THAT GOES FOR ME, TOO.
THAT'S ONLY BECAUSE
I PROTECT YOU BOTH.
- ANYWAY, OUR HANDS ARE TIED
IF YOU'RE UNABLE TO
BREAK THROUGH THE BARRIER.
- AND THAT'S PRECISELY
THE REASON WE CAME HERE, RIGHT?
- EVEN I KNOW THAT MUCH.
- KILL A HALF-DEMON WHO
GENERATES A STRONG BARRIER
AND LET TETSUSAIGA
SUCK ITS BLOOD?
THEN THE SWORD WILL
GROW IN POWER
AND BE ABLE TO BREAK
THROUGH NARAKU'S BARRIER.
THERE'S NO WAY INUYASHA WOULD
KILL ANOTHER HALF-DEMON, THOUGH.
SHE'S JUST A LITTLE GIRL.
- MOMMY, I MISS YOU.
[CRYING]
IF ONLY FATHER WERE STILL ALIVE.
WHY DID HE HAVE TO DIE?
[SOBBING]
- I SUPPOSE SHE DOES
MISS HER MOTHER.
UNLESS SOMETHING'S DONE,
THERE'S NO TELLING WHEN SHE'LL
ASK TO RETURN TO THE VILLAGE.
THEN I MUST DESTROY THEM ALL--
THE ENTIRE VILLAGE
AND YOUR MOTHER, AS WELL!
- [SOBBING]
[RUFFLING]
HUH?
- [SHRIEKING]
- HALF-BREED?
MOTHER...
WHAT'S A HALF-BREED?
- INUYASHA?
- HUH?
IT'S YOU.
- I GUESS YOU'RE PROBABLY
THINKING ABOUT SHIORI.
- NOT JUST HER.
- YOU'VE GOT A BIG HEART,
YOU KNOW.
- COME ON, KAGOME.
DON'T BE STUPID.
- IT MUST HAVE BEEN REALLY HARD.
CAN'T IMAGINE WHAT IT
MUST HAVE BEEN LIKE.
BUT YOU KNOW SOMETHING?
I THINK...
NO, WAIT A MINUTE.
I MEAN, MIROKU AND SANGO,
SHIPPO,
AND EVEN MYOGA--
YOU KNOW WHAT WE ALL THINK?
- YEAH, I KNOW.
- WHAT A GOOD BOY.
- STOP TREATING ME LIKE A DOG!
HUH?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- [SHRIEKING]
- [GASP]
WHAT IS THAT?!
THE BAT DEMONS ARE COMING!
- [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- I'LL DO MY BEST AS
GUARDIAN OF THE BARRIER,
SO PLEASE SPARE MY MOMMY
AND THE VILLAGERS.
- LITTLE SHIORI--
SO YOUNG AND SINCERE.
UNLESS INUYASHA KILLS
THIS INNOCENT CHILD,
THE TETSUSAIGA CAN'T
INCREASE ITS POWER.
THERE'S NO WAY INUYASHA COULD
DO SUCH A HORRIBLE THING.
- WAIT.
THERE IS ANOTHER WAY.
- NEXT TIME, "THE RED TETSUSAIGA
BREAKS THE BARRIER."
INUYASHA'S CONCERN TRANSFORMS
THE TETSUSAIGA.