[FOOTSTEPS]
- [GASPS]
THE MOON IS ABOUT TO DISAPPEAR.
[GASPS]
A SHOOTING STAR!
I WISH I COULD STAY WITH LORD
SESSHOMARU FOREVER AND EVER.
- RIN.
- HUH?
- DON'T FALL BEHIND.
- OH. YES, MY LORD.
- HMM.
SOMETHING FEELS STRANGE.
AURA, WHY ARE YOU SO RESTLESS?
- TOMORROW IS A NEW MOON.
EVEN THE MOON HAS TIMES WHEN
IT CAN HIDE IN DARKNESS.
WITH NARAKU HOLDING
ONTO MY HEART,
THERE'S NOWHERE FOR ME TO RUN.
- [DISTANT ROARING]
- WHAT?
THE DEMON SPIRITS
THAT NARAKU KEPT AROUND HIM.
[GASPS]
THEY'VE GONE THROUGH
THE BARRIER.
- "NARAKU'S BARRIER,
KAGURA'S DECISION."
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
- WAIT, KOGA!
KOGA!
[PANTING]
LET'S REST A BIT.
I JUST CAN'T KEEP UP
WITH THIS PACE.
- EVEN THE WOLVES
ARE OUT OF BREATH.
GIVE US A REST, WOULD YOU, KOGA?
- DAMN YOU PATHETIC WEAKLINGS.
IF I HAD TO WAIT
FOR BOTH OF YOU,
WE WOULDN'T REACH NARAKU'S
CASTLE IN 100 YEARS.
- IS THAT WHERE WE'RE GOING?
YOU MEAN TO TELL US THAT WE
JUST HAVEN'T BEEN RUNNING
AROUND IN CIRCLES?
- NO CHANCE.
I CAN SMELL HIS FOUL ODOR.
NARAKU IS NEARBY.
I'M SURE OF IT.
THIS TIME, I WILL ATTACK
HIS CASTLE AND KILL HIM.
- [MEN SHOUTING]
- UNH!
- [MEN SCREAMING]
- I'LL AVENGE MY COMRADES
WHO WERE DECEIVED
AND SLAUGHTERED...
WITHOUT FAIL.
- MMM.
[SNIFFING]
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, INUYASHA?
ISN'T THIS THE RIGHT DIRECTION?
- SHUT UP!
STOP YAKKING AND LET ME
CONCENTRATE.
- SNIFFING AROUND ON ALL FOURS
WON'T GET US ANY CLOSER TO
NARAKU'S CASTLE, WILL IT?
- [SNIFFING]
AW, DAMN IT ALL.
- INUYASHA, MAYBE YOUR NOSE
ISN'T WORKING RIGHT NOW.
TONIGHT IS THE FIRST NIGHT,
REMEMBER?
- RIGHT.
TONIGHT'S THE NIGHT
OF THE NEW MOON.
- NIGHT OF THE NEW MOON?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
THE NIGHT OF THE NEW MOON
IS WHEN INUYASHA
LOSES HIS POWERS
AND BECOMES A MERE MORTAL.
- INUYASHA, LET'S NOT DO
ANYTHING RASH TONIGHT.
EVEN IF WE DO FIND
NARAKU'S CASTLE,
YOU CAN'T FIGHT
WITHOUT YOUR POWERS.
- WE'VE MADE IT THIS FAR.
I AIN'T HOLDING BACK NOW.
- LET'S GET REAL.
WE CAN'T DO ANYTHING HASTY.
- HUH?
- LOOK!
A CYCLONE!
- AND IT'S COMING THIS WAY.
AAH!
- OH!
- YO, KAGOME.
IT'S GREAT TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
- KOGA! IT'S YOU AGAIN!
- WELL, THAT'S WHAT YOU GET
FOR SNIFFING AROUND
ON THE GROUND.
- HEY, MUTT,
YOU FOLLOWED THE SCENT
AROUND HERE, TOO, DID YOU?
- YOU MANGY WOLF.
ARRGH!
UNH!
I'LL KILL YOU!
- SIT, BOY.
- KOGA, DID YOU COME TO FIND
NARAKU'S CASTLE, AS WELL?
- YEAH.
I DON'T KNOW WHY,
BUT I'M PICKING UP STRONG WHIFFS
OF NARAKU'S FOUL STENCH.
THAT NEVER HAPPENED BEFORE.
- THAT MUST MEAN...
- THE BARRIER AROUND NARAKU'S
CASTLE HAS WEAKENED.
- IN ANY CASE,
IF I FOLLOW THIS SCENT,
I'LL FIND HIS CASTLE.
DON'T WORRY, KAGOME.
I PROMISE I'LL KILL
NARAKU THIS TIME.
HUH?
- I DON'T THINK I'M YOUR TYPE.
- NO, INUYASHA!
- HMM?
- DON'T TRY AND STOP ME.
I'M GOING TO SETTLE THIS TODAY,
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
- NOT IF I CAN HELP IT.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
SOMETHING'S DIFFERENT ABOUT YOU.
[SNIFFING]
YOU DON'T SMELL LIKE A MUTT.
DID YOU TAKE A SOAK
IN THE RIVER OR WHAT?
- HUH?
- HEY!
DON'T GET SO CLOSE TO MY KAGOME!
LET HER GO!
- TAKE IT ELSEWHERE, GUYS.
- YOU CREEP!
AAH!
- HEY, KOGA, WAIT UP!
- WE'VE FINALLY
CAUGHT UP WITH HIM.
- HUH?
OH, RIGHT.
I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS.
LATER, KAGOME.
UNH!
- ARE YOU RUNNING AWAY AGAIN?
- NARAKU'S HEAD IS MINE!
- PLEASE!
COME ON, KOGA, SLOW DOWN!
WAIT FOR US!
- OH, HELLO, KAGOME.
- OH. HI, BOYS.
- CAN'T STAY AND CHAT.
- [WOLVES PANTING]
- DAMN THAT FLEABAG KOGA.
- DO YOU THINK WE
SHOULD GO AFTER HIM?
- NO, I THINK IT'S BETTER
NOT TO DO ANYTHING TONIGHT.
- WHAT, ARE YOU CRAZY?
HE'S GOING TO SHOW US UP!
- CALM YOURSELF DOWN, INUYASHA,
OR WOULD YOU RATHER
HAVE NARAKU SEE YOU
IN YOUR HUMAN FORM, AS WELL?
IF HE LEARNS THAT YOU LOSE
YOUR POWERS SOME NIGHTS,
YOUR LIFE WILL BE IN DANGER.
YOU HAVE TO BE EXTRA
CAREFUL AROUND NARAKU.
- HMM.
DAMN.
WHAT LOUSY TIMING,
ESPECIALLY WHEN NARAKU'S
SCENT IS ALL OVER THE PLACE.
[THUNDER]
- UGH.
THE AIR IN THIS CASTLE
IS SO STIFLING.
ALL THE VASSALS WHO
WERE AT THIS CASTLE
WERE EXPOSED TO NARAKU'S
TOXIC MIASMA AND DIED.
[GASPS]
WHY ARE YOU SNEAKING UP FROM
BEHIND LIKE THAT, KANA?
[GASPS]
AND AGAIN, KOGA--
THE LEADER OF
THE WOLF DEMON TRIBE.
IS HE NEAR THIS CASTLE?
IS IT A COINCIDENCE?
OR PERHAPS...
KANA, TELL ME, DOES
NARAKU KNOW ABOUT THIS?
- HE DOESN'T.
HE'S GONE.
- HMM.
THAT'S RIGHT.
NARAKU DISAPPEARS
ONCE IN A WHILE.
- KAGURA?
- I'LL GO AND KILL HIM.
THERE'S NO NEED TO WAIT
FOR NARAKU'S ORDERS.
- YOU'D BETTER NOT, KAGURA.
- HMM.
I DESPISE NARAKU'S METHOD
OF STOOPING TO TRICKERY.
I'LL KILL FOR JEWEL SHARDS.
I NEED NO SCHEMES.
- IT'S IN NARAKU'S HANDS--
BOTH LIFE AND DEATH.
- HMM?
- WE ARE ALL MERELY
NARAKU'S TOOLS.
- I COULD CARE LESS.
HE'S NOT HERE NOW.
- [GROWLING]
- THIS IS A STRANGE FOG.
- I CAN'T SEE A THING.
- DAMN!
- THE SMELL IS STRONGEST
RIGHT HERE.
THE CASTLE HAS TO BE CLOSE BY.
- HUH!
KOGA, UP THERE!
- HMM?
SKELETONS WITH SWORDS?
AAH!
- UNH!
- HMM?
- HELLO.
IT'S BEEN TOO LONG, KOGA.
- NOT YOU AGAIN.
- WHAT'S WITH THOSE SKELETONS?
- THEY ARE THE GUARDS
OF THE CASTLE.
THEY'RE COUNTLESS IN NUMBERS.
- WIND SORCERESS KAGURA.
I HAVEN'T FORGOTTEN
YOUR DESPICABLE FACE--
NOT FOR ONE MINUTE.
HOW COULD I?
YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO KILLED MY COMRADES.
PREPARE TO DIE!
IT'S PAYBACK TIME
FOR ALL YOU DID!
- I MISSED YOU, TOO.
I WAS SO CLOSE TO GETTING YOUR
SACRED JEWEL SHARDS BEFORE.
I'LL GET THEM
THIS TIME FOR SURE!
HMM.
IT WILL BE EASY
TO SLOW HIM DOWN.
I'LL MAKE HIM DANCE FOR ME.
DANCE OF THE DEAD!
- [SNARLING]
- AAH!
TRICKS!
YAAH!
UNH!
- DANCE OF BLADES!
- NOT THIS TIME.
[GRUNTING]
SURPRISE!
- HMM.
- GOT HER.
HUH?
- FOOL!
I'LL CRIPPLE YOU!
DANCE OF THE DRAGON!
- NOW WHAT?
- A WHIRLWIND OF BONES,
THAT'S WHAT!
- HRRM!
HRRM!
- MMH.
[CHUCKLES]
- [GRUNTING]
- YOU CAN CHOOSE
YOUR OWN FATE, KOGA.
YOU CAN LET THE SKELETONS
IN THE WHIRLWIND
SLICE YOU TO PIECES,
OR YOU CAN LEAP OUT
AND BE SLAIN BY ME.
EITHER WAY, SUITS ME FINE.
- KOGA'S STRONG,
BUT HE DOESN'T STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST THAT THING.
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO NOW?
- WELL, IT'S NOT LIKE WE'RE
STRONG ENOUGH TO HELP.
- [GRUNTING]
- [LAUGHS]
- LOOK AT THAT WENCH.
I THINK SHE'S COMPLETELY
ENJOYING THIS.
- IF WE COULD GET THAT
POWERFUL FAN OF HERS,
MAYBE WE'D HAVE A CHANCE
OF RESCUING KOGA.
- YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT!
GET UP CLOSE AND SNATCH
IT FROM HER.
- WHO?
- YOU, OF COURSE.
- ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
SHE'LL NOTICE ME
BEFORE I GET CLOSE,
AND I'LL BE HACKED TO BITS.
- THEN HOW ARE WE GOING TO
FIGHT KAGURA AND THAT WIND?
HMM?
WAIT A MINUTE.
YES, THE WIND!
THERE IS A WAY!
- ITA, STOP ACTING FOOLISH!
- KOGA'S ACTIONS ARE PROOF
THAT NARAKU'S BARRIER
HAS BECOME WEAKER.
- I THINK THAT WE
SHOULD AT LEAST VERIFY
THE EXACT LOCATION
OF THE CASTLE.
- WE CAN'T TAKE INUYASHA
IN THE STATE HE'S IN.
- WE WON'T, BECAUSE MIROKU
AND I CAN GO ALONE.
- AND IF INUYASHA OBJECTS
TO US LEAVING HIM BEHIND,
WE'LL HAVE KAGOME MAKE HIM SIT.
THEN WE CAN SIMPLY
KNOCK HIM OUT.
- OH, NOT THAT METHOD AGAIN.
- I KEEP TELLING YOU...
KOGA LIKES TO BE COMPLIMENTED,
SO I JUST THOUGHT
IF I FLATTERED HIM,
I COULD DISTRACT HIM
FROM BECOMING CURIOUS
ABOUT HOW YOU SMELLED.
- STILL, YOUR EYES WERE
ALL SPARKLY AND STUFF.
YOU KNOW, YOU GET TOO FRIENDLY
WITH THAT WILD ANIMAL, KAGOME.
- I DON'T DO THAT.
- YEAH, YOU DO.
- DON'T YOU START!
- I'M NOT STARTING ANYTHING!
- INUYASHA!
- HUH?
I KNOW THAT VOICE.
- KAGOME!
- OH, NO.
THEY'RE KOGA'S FRIENDS!
INUYASHA, HIDE.
- HUH?
- HMM?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- UNH!
- THE WOLF DEMON TRIBE
HAS COME BACK AGAIN.
- HUH?
WE CAN'T LET THEM SEE HIM.
- KAGOME!
KAGOME!
QUICKLY! WE NEED YOUR HELP!
- WHAT?
KOGA AND KAGURA ARE
FIGHTING EACH OTHER?
- YES, AND THINGS DON'T LOOK
TOO GOOD FOR KOGA RIGHT NOW.
- INUYASHA, YOU MUSTN'T
SHOW YOURSELF.
- HUH.
YOU DON'T NEED
TO WORRY ABOUT THAT.
THERE'S NO WAY THAT
I'M GOING TO HELP KOGA.
IF KAGURA'S SHOWN UP,
THAT MEANS NARAKU'S
CASTLE IS NEARBY.
STILL, NARAKU HAD
PUT UP A BARRIER
TO STOP US FROM GETTING CLOSE.
I DON'T LIKE THE LOOKS OF THIS.
- I GUESS WE HAVE TO
GO CHECK THIS OUT.
- SANGO?
- INUYASHA, YOU'RE GOING
TO STAY HERE WITH KAGOME, OK?
YOU WANT TO KEEP YOUR MORTAL
STATE A SECRET, DON'T YOU?
- HUH.
YOU GOT TO BE KIDDING.
- HUH?
AAH!
[GRUNTING]
- OH, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- WHAT AN IDIOT.
- LISTEN UP, YOU TWO.
IF YOU TELL A SOUL ABOUT THIS,
I'LL KILL YOU BOTH.
- UHH...
- GOT IT.
WE WON'T.
- INUYASHA...
- WELL, HE SHUT THEM
UP REAL GOOD.
SO, SHALL WE GO?
- MMM.
I CAN SMELL BLOOD IN THE AIR.
GO!
TWIST AND TURN HARDER.
WHAT'S THE MATTER, KOGA?
TOO SCARED TO COME OUT, ARE YOU?
OR...ARE YOU ALREADY DEAD?
- DAMN THAT WITCH!
[GRUNTING]
IT'S USELESS.
NO MATTER HOW MANY
BONES I DESTROY,
THERE'S COUNTLESS MORE.
MY STRENGTH WON'T
HOLD UP FOREVER.
WHAT WILL I DO?
HUH?
- HA.
MAYBE I'LL LET HIM OUT.
IF HE'S SLASHED IN
TOO MANY PIECES,
I'LL HAVE A HARD TIME
FINDING THE JEWEL SHARDS.
- NO NEED TO WORRY ABOUT THAT!
- HUH? HE'S UP THERE!
- YOU WENCH!
- WELL, YOU'RE PRETTY
PERSISTENT, AREN'T YOU?
BUT NOT FOR MUCH LONGER.
- YOU'RE DEAD, KAGURA!
- UNH!
- [ROARING]
- [SCREAMING]
I CAN'T MOVE!
- YOU FOOL!
YOU CAN RUN AND JUMP,
BUT YOU CAN NEVER
ESCAPE MY WIND.
DANCE OF BLADES!
- OOH!
MY SACRED JEWEL SHARDS!
- UNH!
UNH!
- NOW, THEN...
I HAVE THE TWO SHARDS
FROM YOUR LEGS.
YOU'RE JUST AN ORDINARY
DEMON NOW.
IT'S TIME TO FINISH YOU OFF.
- DAMN YOU.
- [CHUCKLES]
- KAGURA!
- [GASPS]
UNH!
- [MOANING]
YOUR LIFE HAS BEEN SPARED, KOGA.
- HRRM.
- SHE GOT AWAY.
- MIROKU, LOOK AT KOGA.
- HMM?
- KOGA!
HUH?
- LOOK!
YOUR LEGS!
- SHE TOOK THE SACRED JEWEL
SHARDS FROM BOTH YOUR LEGS.
- KOGA!
YOU'RE BADLY WOUNDED.
LET ME SEE WHAT I CAN DO.
- LEAVE HIM ALONE, KAGOME.
HE'S GOING TO DIE ANYWAY.
- YOU MUTT.
HUH?
INUYASHA?
- HUH.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE
PATHETIC, KOGA--
GETTING ALL CUT UP LIKE
THAT BY KAGURA.
- LOOK WHO'S TALKING.
YOU'RE NOTHING BUT
A WEAK MORTAL.
- HMM.
- YOU SEE?
I TOLD YOU HE WAS JUST
A HALF-DEMON, HAKAKU.
- AND YOU WERE RIGHT.
- I HEARD THAT...
[GROANS]
THAT HALF-DEMONS FEAR
FOR THEIR LIVES.
I ALSO HEARD WHEN THEY'RE
IN THE MORTAL STATE,
THEY NEVER APPEAR
BEFORE AN ENEMY.
YOU'RE PRETTY GUTSY, YOU KNOW,
DARING TO COME AROUND ME
WHEN YOU LOOK LIKE
THAT, INUYASHA.
- HMM.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
SO NOW THAT YOU KNOW
MY SECRET, KOGA...
- YOU WANT TO FIGHT?
- I'M GOING TO HAVE TO FINISH
YOU OFF RIGHT HERE AND NOW.
- [GROANING]
- KOGA!
THIS IS AN OINTMENT THAT I
BROUGHT BACK FROM MY COUNTRY.
IT WORKS REALLY WELL ON CUTS.
- THANKS VERY MUCH, KAGOME.
- HUH.
I TOLD HER TO STAY
AWAY FROM HIM.
[THUNDER]
- HMM.
SERVES HIM RIGHT.
STILL...
HOW IS IT THAT BOTH
KOGA AND INUYASHA
GOT SO CLOSE TO THE CASTLE?
IT MUST MEAN THAT NARAKU'S
BARRIER HAS WEAKENED.
THAT'S RIGHT.
NARAKU ISN'T HERE.
HE'S GONE.
[SIGHS]
WHAT A RELIEF.
INDEED...
WHY SHOULD I HAND THEM
OVER TO NARAKU?
NOW IS THE TIME TO ESCAPE--
WHEN NARAKU'S BARRIER IS WEAK.
BUT NARAKU...
THAT'S...
[GASPS]
AAH!
- DO NOT FORGET, KAGURA,
I HOLD YOUR HEART RIGHT HERE
IN MY VERY HANDS.
- HUH?
NARAKU, DAMN YOU!
- IT WOULD BE SIMPLE TO TURN YOU
BACK INTO YOUR ORIGINAL FORM.
NEVER FORGET THIS, KAGURA:
YOU WERE CREATED
FROM A PART OF ME.
YOU ARE NOTHING MORE
THAN MY ESSENCE.
- IT'S NO USE.
[SIGHS]
I CAN'T ESCAPE FROM HIS GRASP.
HMM?
A SHOOTING STAR!
THERE IS SOMEONE WHO CAN HELP.
YES!
HE CAN HELP ME.
HE HAS THE POWER TO SEVER
THE BOND BETWEEN NARAKU AND I.
[THUNDER]
- KAGURA, YOU HAVE ESCAPED.
- IT SPARKLED!
HEE HEE!
A STAR JUST SPARKLED!
DID YOU SEE, LORD SESSHOMARU?
UH, HELLO?
OHH.
LATELY, LORD SESSHOMARU
DOES THINGS
THAT EVEN I, HIS VASSAL,
CAN'T FATHOM.
I'M SO LONELY.
THAT FOOLISH CHILD IS
IGNORANT OF MY WOES,
AND DOES NOTHING BUT
SLEEP THE DAYS AWAY.
AAH!
AH, OH!
LORD SESSHOMARU!
- HIS SCENT IS IN THE AIR.
- OH?
[SNIFFING]
YOU'RE RIGHT!
IT'S THE SCENT OF
THAT NARAKU FELLOW
WHO WAS SO RUDE TO YOU,
LORD SESSHOMARU.
IS HE NEARBY?
AAH!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHOA!
- UNH...
- [WHIMPERING]
HUH?
- YO.
- YO, YOURSELF.
- SESSHOMARU,
I ASSUME YOU CAME HERE
FOLLOWING NARAKU'S
SCENT, AS WELL.
- LORD SESSHOMARU,
THIS WENCH IS
NARAKU'S INCARNATION!
- WIND SORCERESS KAGURA,
I RECALL.
- SO...YOU REMEMBER ME.
I AM VERY FLATTERED.
TAKE YOUR HAND FROM YOUR SWORD.
I DIDN'T COME TO FIGHT,
SESSHOMARU.
I HAVE A PROPOSITION YOU
MIGHT BE INTERESTED IN.
- PROPOSITION?
- YOU KNOW WHAT THESE ARE,
SESSHOMARU.
I'LL GIVE YOU THESE
SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
IN RETURN, I WANT YOU
TO KILL NARAKU.
- WHAT?!
- FREE ME.
RELEASE ME FROM HIS GRASP.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- MY NAME IS KAGURA.
I AM THE WIND.
I LIVE FREELY.
- YOU'LL BETRAY ME, KAGURA?
- SILENCE, NARAKU!
SO YOU'RE ALSO A HALF-DEMON
WHO SOMETIMES LOSES HIS POWERS.
- FOOLISH WOMAN.
DID YOU THINK YOU COULD
ESCAPE MY CLUTCHES?
- I AM KAGURA,
AND I'M AS FREE AS THE WIND.
- NEXT TIME, "THE HOWLING
WIND OF BETRAYAL."
- I SAW YOU, INUYASHA,
AS A MORTAL.