AAH!
UGH!
UNH...
- STAY IN THERE
AND DON'T DO ANYTHING FOOLISH.
- UGH...LET ME OUT!
THEY SAID THEY WERE
FROM THE PANTHER DEMON TRIBE.
- IT'S NOT YOU THAT WE'RE AFTER.
WE WANT THE PRIESTESS
WITH THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS!
- WELL, YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO GET THROUGH ME FIRST,
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT!
- HUH?
OH...
- AAH!
- HA HA HA!
- I KNOW INUYASHA WILL COME
FOR ME.
I JUST HAVE TO BE PATIENT.
[WIND BLOWING]
OH!
AAH!
WHO IS IN HERE?
- WIND SCAR!
UNH!
HEH HEH.
I KNEW IT!
IT WAS JUST A BARRIER!
[RUMBLING]
HUH?
- THAT WASN'T BAD
FOR A MUTT LIKE YOU!
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- KOGA, WAIT!
- SLOW DOWN, BOSS!
- HEY!
- WE'RE HERE, INUYASHA!
- HMM?
IT TOOK YOU LONG ENOUGH!
- WHAT IS THAT?
- THE CASTLE ENTRANCE.
THE CATS MUST BE HIDING
SOMEWHERE INSIDE IT.
-IF THEY'RE AROUND,
KAGOME MUST BE THERE, TOO.
- YEAH, LET'S GO.
UNH!
[OWL HOOTING]
WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
- IT SEEMS
LIKE A REGULAR VILLAGE.
- YOU KNOW,
IT'S A PRETTY GOOD SIZED TOWN
BUILT AROUND THE CASTLE.
- WHY HERE OF ALL PLACES?
WHAT'S A VILLAGE DOING HERE?
UGH.
MMM.
- NO ONE SEEMS TO BE HERE.
- NO ONE'S AROUND, BUT IT LOOKS
LIKE PEOPLE LIVE HERE.
THERE'S NO SIGN OF KOGA
AND HIS MEN, EITHER.
- YEAH.
- HUH?
- GRR.
- OH!
- [GROWLING]
- HUNH!
THAT'S WHERE YOU WERE HIDING!
AAH!
[GRUNTING]
- [GRUNTING]
- KAGOME, WHERE ARE YOU?
UNH!
OH!
UGH!
UNH!
[WHINING]
- SHIPPO!
WIND SCAR!
UNH!
UGH...OH!
- WATCH WHERE YOU'RE POINTING
THAT THING!
THEY COULD BE HIDING KAGOME
IN ANY ONE OF THESE HOUSES!
- HUH?
- [GROWLING]
- STOP!
UNH!
- YOU WON'T GET AWAY!
YAH!
UNH!
- YOU CERTAINLY ARE IMPATIENT!
- HUH?
- HOW RUDE!
BREAKING OUR BARRIER
AND BUSTING IN LIKE YOU DID!
- STOP YAKKING
AND TELL ME WHERE KAGOME IS!
- DON'T WORRY,
SHE'S SAFE.
- COME ON! ANSWER ME!
- WHEN THE MOON IS
DIRECTLY OVERHEAD,
THAT'S WHEN WE PLAN
TO SACRIFICE HER TO OUR MASTER.
- SACRIFICE?
GRR!
- NATURALLY,
YOU'LL BE JOINING HER.
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- WHERE'S THIS SMOKE
COMING FROM?
- DON'T WORRY;
I THINK IT'S JUST A SMOKESCREEN.
- OOH, WHAT A STINK!
HUH?
- [GROANING]
- HOLD ON, INUYASHA!
- MY POWER...
- HA HA HA!
HOW'S THAT FOR POTENT?
CONSIDERING HOW KEEN
OUR SENSE OF SMELL IS,
IT MUST BE EVEN WORSE
FOR YOU DOGS!
- IS THIS A TRAP
TO STOP INUYASHA?
- YES, BUT IT'S NOT GOING
EXACTLY ACCORDING TO PLAN.
- [GRUNTING]
- CAPTURE THEM
BEFORE THEY ESCAPE!
OH!
- AAH!
- [GRUNTING]
- HUH?
SESSHOMARU!
- WHAT IS THE MEANING OF THIS,
KARON?
IS IT ME THAT YOU HAVE
BUSINESS WITH,
OR WITH THESE PEOPLE?
- THE ELDER BROTHER HAS ARRIVED.
YOUR TIMING COULDN'T
HAVE BEEN BETTER.
SONS OF THE DOG LEADER
WILL BE WAITING AT THE CASTLE.
RAH!
- UGH, WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
DOING HERE, SESSHOMARU?
- JUST WHAT I WAS THINKING.
LEAVE WHILE YOU CAN.
- HMM, WHAT DID
YOU SAY?
- THIS IS MY WAR.
I WON'T LET YOU
GET INVOLVED.
- HA! I DON'T NEED TO HAVE
YOUR PERMISSION!
KAGOME'S BEEN CAPTURED
BY THOSE DEMON CATS!
- YOU ARE SUCH A FOOL!
- UNH! AAH!
- UGH!
UNH, HEY!
WHAT ARE YOU COMING
AFTER ME FOR?
- SILENCE, INUYASHA!
- HUH?
WHAT THE HELL?
- REMEMBER YOUR PAST,
INUYASHA.
YOU LOST YOUR HEART TO A MORTAL
AND ENDED UP UNDER A SPELL
FOR YEARS.
CONSEQUENTLY, YOU HAVE NO RIGHT
TO BE PART OF THIS BATTLE.
- LORD, SESSHOMARU!
WE NEED ALL THE ALLIES
WE CAN GET!
WE MUSTN'T BE TOO CHOOSY
AT A TIME LIKE THIS!
DUH...AAH!
- THAT GUY'S SCARY!
OOH!
- I'VE NEVER SEEN HIM LOOK
SO UPSET.
- WAS IT SOMETHING YOU SAID,
INUYASHA?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- MASTER!
- HUH?
- HACHI, IT'S YOU!
- OOH--AAH!
HA!
- I THOUGHT YOU'D RUN OFF ON US,
HACHI.
- NO, I DID, AT LEAST,
I WAS TRYING TO.
- UNH! MASTER INUYASHA!
- MMM.
UNH!
- OOH!
I'VE COME TO LEND
MY ASSISTANCE.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING
AROUND HERE,
OLD MAN?
- SOMETHING TELLS ME THAT THIS
HAS TO DO WITH THE GREAT WAR
THAT YOUR FATHER RAGED
MANY EONS AGO.
- EONS AGO?
- HEY! I THOUGHT HACHI SAID
IT HAPPENED 50 YEARS AGO?
- NO, NO, NO!
IT WAS LONG BEFORE THAT!
IT WAS WHEN YOUR FATHER WAS
STILL IN THE WESTERN PROVINCE.
- THAT'S ALL NEWS TO ME.
THE PANTHER TRIBE OF CAT DEMONS
ATTACKED THE WEST
AND TRIED TO CONQUER
ALL OTHER DEMONS.
BUT YOUR FATHER STEPPED IN
IN ORDER TO STOP THEM.
THE PANTHER TRIBE LEADER WAS
AN ENORMOUS CAT DEMON.
YOUR FATHER PROTECTED HIS MEN
AND BATTLED THE DEMONS.
- [GROWLING]
- ROWR!
- RAH!
[SCREAMING]
- NATURALLY, IT WAS YOUR FATHER
WHO EMERGED VICTORIOUS.
THE OTHER DEMONS WHO ESCAPED
DOMINATION BY THE PANTHER TRIBE
WERE EXTREMELY GRATEFUL.
HOWEVER, A CAT'S ANGER
RUNS DEEP,
AND THEY CURSED YOUR FATHER
AND HIS FAMILY FOR ALL ETERNITY
AND SWORE THAT THEY WOULD
ONE DAY GET THEIR REVENGE.
- SO, IT'S TRUE THAT A CAT'S
WRATH LASTS 7 GENERATIONS?
- LIKE YOU, LORD SESSHOMARU
DID NOT PARTICIPATE
IN THE GREAT WAR,
EITHER.
BUT I'M CERTAIN THE CATS ARE
COMING AFTER HIM
TO GET THEIR REVENGE.
- WHAT WERE YOU DOING
WHEN ALL OF THIS WAS GOING ON?
- NATURALLY, I WAS WATCHING
OVER HIS HOME WHILE HE WAS AWAY!
- THAT'S TYPICAL.
- YOU KNOW, IT'S STRANGE
THAT HE WAS SO ADAMANT
ABOUT WANTING INUYASHA
TO LEAVE.
WASN'T IT?
- HUH!
HE JUST DOESN'T WANT TO ADMIT
TO HIMSELF
THAT A HALF-DEMON CAN SHARE
HIS BLOODLINE.
- STILL, I THINK IT WOULD
BE NOBLE FOR THE TWO OF YOU
TO JOIN FORCES
AND FIGHT YOUR FATHER'S ENEMY
TOGETHER.
- I'M NOT GONNA HAVE ANYTHING
TO DO WITH EITHER SESSHOMARU
OR MY FATHER!
I CAME TO TAKE BACK THE JEWEL
SHARDS AND KAGOME.
THAT'S IT.
- OH.
WELL, GOTTA RUN!
- HUH?
- FAREWELL!
- OH!
MYOGA'S GETTING AWAY!
- WELL, THAT MEANS TROUBLE.
- AAH! AAH!
AAH!
HOT HOT HOT!
HOT!
YAH!
- [SCREAMING]
- UNH!
- ARE YOU GOING TO ASK
YOUR BROTHER FOR HELP?
HA HA HA!
- NOT LIKELY.
- DAMN! NO TRACE
OF KAGOME ANYWHERE.
WHERE COULD THOSE ROTTEN CATS
HAVE TAKEN HER, ANYWAY?
- SAY, KOGA?
- HUH?
WHAT IS IT?
- ISN'T THIS PLACE
THE CAT DEMONS' HIDEOUT?
DO YOU REALLY THINK
THAT WE SHOULD TACKLE THEM
ON OUR OWN?
- JUST WHAT ARE YOU SUGGESTING?
- WELL, WE COULD JOIN INUYASHA
AND THE OTHERS.
- NOT ON YOUR LIFE!
YOU DON'T ACTUALLY EXPECT ME
TO ASK THAT MUTT FOR HELP?
- NO, NO, OF COURSE NOT!
WHAT I ACTUALLY MEANT WAS
WE COULD OFFER TO HELP HIM!
- HA! I'M NOT AS HELPLESS
AS YOU TWO SEEM TO THINK I AM.
- WE JUST THINK
IT WOULD BE THE EASIEST WAY
TO HELP RESCUE KAGOME.
- YEAH, YEAH, WE WERE JUST
THINKING OF HER, THAT'S ALL.
- UGH.
- YOU MUST BE KOGA
OF THE DEMON WOLF TRIBE!
- AAH!
- WHOEVER IT IS DOESN'T SMELL
OF CATS.
WHO'S THAT?
- AAH!
- YOU'RE ROYOKAN!
- HUH!
- YOU MEAN, THE DEMON WHO'S
THE KEEPER OF THE FOREST?
- THE DEMON FROM HELL
WHO GOBBLES UP ANYONE
WHO HAPPENS TO GET LOST?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING
AROUND HERE?
AND WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- THAT'S WHAT I'D LIKE
TO ASK YOU.
YOU'RE NOT ACCOMPANYING
LORD SESSHOMARU, ARE YOU?
- SESSHOMARU?
WHO THE HELL'S THAT?
- YOU DON'T KNOW?
- NO.
- YOU SUMMONED ME TO COME.
NOW LET ME SEE
YOUR SO-CALLED MASTER.
- ALL IN GOOD TIME,
ONCE THE PREPARATIONS
ARE COMPLETE.
IN THE MEANTIME,
WON'T YOU STAY HERE WITH ME?
- LET ME TAKE CARE OF THE WENCH,
LORD SESSHOMARU!
FEEL THE POWER OF THE STAFF
OF TWO HEADS!
BE STRONG, STAFF!
MMM...AAH!
OOH--OOF!
UGH...AAH!
- I AM INDEED IMPRESSED.
YOUR WEAPON IS FORMIDABLE!
AAH!
- [GRUNTING]
- HUH? AAH!
- DAMN YOU!
- INUYASHA!
- WHERE ARE YOU?
- HE'S DOWN THERE!
- KILALA!
- GRR!
MMM!
- UNH!
[SCREAMING]
- AHH, THE MEMORIES.
IT'S EXACTLY LIKE THE LAST TIME
WE FOUGHT.
BACK THEN IT WAS A DRAW,
THIS TIME,
YOU WON'T BE SO LUCKY!
- I WOULD HARDLY CALL
THAT A DRAW.
YOU SIMPLY RETREATED
IN DEFEAT.
- NOW, NOW, YOU'RE ONE TO TALK
WITH ALL THE MEN YOU LOST.
I WASN'T NEARLY AS DETERMINED
BACK THEN AS I AM RIGHT NOW.
BECAUSE NOW
WE HAVE OUR MASTER.
- [GROWLING]
- NOW, THINGS ARE
COMPLETELY DIFFERENT.
- 50 YEARS AGO,
THE PANTHER DEMON TRIBE,
WHO FATHER FOUGHT,
CAME BACK.
HMM?
LORD SESSHOMARU!
MY MEN AND I HAVE COME TO LEND
OUR ASSISTANCE!
- LET'S GET THEM!
- WE'LL TEACH THOSE
CATS A LESSON!
- WHY DO YOU WISH
TO ASSIST ME?
- WE ARE INDEBTED TO YOUR FATHER
FROM THE LAST WAR.
SO, THIS TIME, WE WOULD LIKE
TO ASSIST YOU, MY LORD.
- WHAT ARE WE WAITING FOR?
IT'S BEEN SO LONG
SINCE WE FOUGHT THOSE CATS!
- LORD SESSHOMARU!
[PANTING]
I BRING TERRIBLE NEWS!
- JAKEN?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
"SEALED HIM DOWN?"
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY "ROAD?"
- IN THE END, MY MEN AND I
FAILED LORD SESSHOMARU.
WE SAID WE'D DEFEND
THE FRONTLINES,
AND HE WAS BATTLING
IN FINE FORM AT THE TIME.
- AAH!
- AAH! SESSHOMARU!
- MOVE BACK!
RETREAT!
JOIN UP WITH LORD SESSHOMARU!
- I GUESS THEY LOST.
- YEAH, THEY RAN AWAY.
- AAH, I FOUGHT AS HARD
AS I COULD!
THOSE CATS WERE NOTHING
BUT COWARDS!
- THAT'S ENOUGH.
WHO CARES ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED
IN THE PAST?
JUST HOW DEEP IS THIS FOREST,
ANYWAY?
- I'LL SAY.
- IF I DIDN'T KNOW
ANY DIFFERENT,
I'D SAY THAT WE'VE BEEN GOING
IN CIRCLES.
- ALL RIGHT!
AAH!
THEY'LL SNIFF OUT THE AREA.
[BARKING AND HOWLING]
- WHAT THE--?
- I'LL TAKE OVER NOW!
HYAH!
[GRUNTING]
HUH?
IT'S HER!
UNH!
SHE'S PUT UP THE DEMONIC AURA!
HMM!
HA...GAH!
- I SEE YOU HAVE A COUPLE
OF JEWEL SHARDS!
- [GRUNTING]
- DON'T BREATHE IN THIS SCENT!
- HEE HEE HEE!
- GRR...UNH!
- AAH!
- SHE'S A SORCERESS!
- IT LOOKS LIKE THEY TRAPPED US
INSIDE THE FOREST!
- UNH!
HUH?
THE ONLY THING I CAN SMELL NOW
IS FLOWERS!
- UNH!
- MIROKU!
SANGO!
- YOU AND YOUR FRIENDS
WILL BE SACRIFICED
AND OFFERED TO OUR MASTER.
- AAH!
- YOU WILL GIVE US YOUR JEWEL
SHARDS AND YOUR LIVES!
AND OUR MASTER
WILL BE RESURRECTED!
HA!
- OH...
- OH, WHERE COULD HE
HAVE GOTTEN TO?
LORD SESSHOMARU?
WHERE ARE YOU?
I CAN'T FIND YOU!
OH! HUH?
AAH!
- [GROWLING]
- STAY AWAY!
OOH! OOH! OOH!
NOT CATS AGAIN!
OOH, AAH!
YAH!
NO!
OOH...NO!
- [INDISTINCT]
- OH!
- UNH!
GRR!
- MY CHANCE TO GET AWAY!
AAH! OOH!
- UNH!
UNH...WHOA!
HEY.
- [WHINING]
- HAVE YOU SEEN MY FRIENDS
AROUND HERE?
- NO, BUT DO YOU KNOW WHERE
LORD SESSHOMARU MIGHT HAPPEN
TO BE?
- HOW WOULD I KNOW?
BESIDES, WHAT THE HECK IS
HE DOING HERE?
THIS ISN'T ANY OF HIS BUSINESS.
- HOW DARE YOU SAY THAT
AND DEFILE YOUR FATHER'S MEMORY?
- NOW YOU'VE TOTALLY LOST ME.
- YOUR FATHER WAGED WAR AGAINST
THE PANTHER TRIBE
A LONG TIME AGO.
- OH, THAT!
MYOGA TOLD ME!
BUT I THOUGHT SESSHOMARU DIDN'T
EVEN FIGHT IN THAT BATTLE.
- THE PANTHER TRIBE SHOWED UP
AGAIN 50 YEARS AGO
BENT ON REVENGE!
YOUR FATHER
HAD PASSED ON,
BUT THEY CAME TO RAVAGE
THE COUNTRYSIDE
AND KILL
HIS PEOPLE!
BUT AT THAT TIME,
YOU WEREN'T MUCH HELP!
- HMM?
- [PANTING]
LORD SESSHOMARU!
UGH! I BRING TERRIBLE NEWS!
- WHAT IS IT?
- FORGIVE ME,
BUT I ACTED ON MY OWN
AND WENT TO FETCH INUYASHA!
HE MAY BE A HALF-DEMON,
BUT HE'S
STILL YOUR FATHER'S SON!
- I SEE.
WHERE IS HE?
WHAT, IS HE TOO COWARDLY
TO SHOW HIMSELF?
OR DID HE SIMPLY REFUSE TO COME
TO HIS BROTHER'S AID?
- NEITHER, I'M AFRAID THAT
HE'S BEEN PLACED UNDER A SPELL!
- A SPELL?
- INDEED.
HE LOST HIS HEART
TO A MORTAL PRIESTESS
AND FELL PREY
TO HER SACRED POWERS.
- HOW FOOLISH OF HIM.
- YES. WHO ARE THOSE DEMONS?
- MY FATHER SAVED THEM
IN THE GREAT WAR.
- WE HAVE ALLIES!
HOW WONDERFUL!
I WAS CONCERNED,
I ADMIT,
BUT NOW THAT YOUR FATHER'S
ALLIES HAVE COME TO OUR AID,
WE CAN GO INTO BATTLE
WITH CONFIDENCE.
UGH!
OF COURSE, LORD SESSHOMARU
HAD NEVER EXPECTED YOU
TO COME TO HIS ASSISTANCE.
BUT VICTORY WOULD HAVE BEEN
SO EASY IF WE HAD THE
TETSUSAIGA,
THE SWORD THAT WAS FORGED
BY YOUR FATHER.
- HA! SESSHOMARU CAN'T WIELD
MY SWORD!
- THAT'S NOT THE POINT,
YOU UNGRATEFUL SON!
- WOULD YOU STOP HARPING ON ME
ABOUT THE PAST?
- HUH?
NO, WAIT!
PLEASE DON'T LEAVE ME!
- NOW I GET IT.
ALL OF THAT STUFF HAPPENED WHILE
I WAS STILL UNDER THE SPELL.
- UNH...
OH...
HUH?
- HUH?
OH...
UGH, WHERE ARE WE?
- YEAH?
- THANK GOODNESS
YOU'RE BOTH FINALLY AWAKE!
- KAGOME!
I'M GLAD YOU'RE ALL RIGHT!
- SO, IS THIS
SOME KIND OF PRISON CELL
THEY'VE PUT US IN?
- YES, AND WE'RE NOT
THE ONLY PEOPLE IN HERE,
EITHER.
- WHO ELSE IS IN HERE?
- LOOK.
- WHO ARE THEY?
DO YOU THINK THEY'RE
THE VILLAGERS?
- NO WONDER THERE WAS NO SIGN
OF LIFE IN THE TOWN.
- YEAH, I THINK IT WAS
LIKE A SECRET VILLAGE.
I GATHER THAT THESE ARE
THE PEOPLE WHO ESCAPED THE WARS.
- I SEE. IT'S A PERFECT PLACE
TO HIDE AND LIVE IN PEACE.
- AT LEAST IT WAS UNTIL
THE PANTHER TRIBE DISCOVERED IT
AND MADE IT THEIR HOME BASE.
- YOU'VE GOT TO HELP US
OR ELSE WE'RE ALL GOING TO BE
KILLED BY THOSE CATS.
- I'M AFRAID.
WHY DID THOSE DEMONS
HAVE TO COME?
- DON'T WORRY, EVERYONE!
YOU CAN CHEER UP BECAUSE HELP IS
DEFINITELY ON THE WAY!
- THE DEMONS WILL GET WIND OF IT
FOR CERTAIN!
- I CAN ASSURE YOU
THAT THE PERSON COMING
TO SAVE US
IS MUCH STRONGER
THAN THOSE CATS ARE.
- I'M TERRIFIED!
- OH!
- O LORD, PLEASE HELP
ALL OF US.
- WHO'S STRONGER THAN THE CATS?
INUYASHA AND KOGA!
THEY'RE BOTH STRONG,
AND THEY'RE DEFINITELY
COMING FOR US!
- I WOULDN'T BE SO SURE
ABOUT SESSHOMARU, THOUGH.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- HE'S HERE BATTLING
THE PANTHER DEMON TRIBE.
- WHY IS HE DOING THAT?
- THE TIME HAS ALMOST COME.
SOON, YOU WILL BE RESURRECTED,
MASTER.
- HA! IT'S THE OLDER BROTHER
AGAIN.
- GO HOME, WOLF!
YOU'RE NOT WANTED HERE!
- [GRUNTING]
- GET OUT OF MY WAY!
- JAKEN TO THE RESCUE!
- THEY'RE HERE!
HA HA HA!
- YAH!
WHERE HAVE YOU GOT KAGOME?
- [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- I DON'T CARE WHO THIS MASTER
OF YOURS IS!
YOU'RE NOT SACRIFICING ANYONE
TO BRING HIM BACK!
- OUT OF MY WAY, INUYASHA.
I'LL BE THE ONE WHO BRINGS THEM
DOWN.
- NOT HAPPENING.
I'M GONNA HACK THEM TO PIECES
WITH MY TETSUSAIGA!
- IF ONLY I HAD THE TETSUSAIGA
50 YEARS AGO...
- SESSHOMARU, I HEARD ABOUT
THE BATTLE WHEN I WAS UNDER
THAT SPELL.
WHAT EXACTLY HAPPENED?
NEXT TIME, "THE PANTHER TRIBE
AND THE TWO SWORDS OF THE FANG."
- FATHER, WHY DID YOU LEAVE ME
TENSEIGA?