- HUH?
- [SHRIEKING]
- THE BAT DEMONS ARE COMING.
- THOSE ARE THE DEMON BATS.
- [SHRIEKING]
- THEY'RE HEADING
TOWARD THE VILLAGE.
- AAH!
- WHAT ARE YOU PEOPLE
GAWKING AT?
LET'S GET GOING!
- HMM. RIGHT.
- HA HA HA HA!
- [SCREAMING]
- THE VILLAGE!
- THEY DON'T DESERVE
YOUR SYMPATHY,
NOT AFTER THEY TREATED YOU
AND YOUR MOTHER SO POORLY.
DON'T WORRY.
JUST PROTECT
THE BARRIER WITH ME,
AND I WILL SPARE
YOUR MOTHER'S LIFE.
- HUH?
- DO AS I SAY.
ANNIHILATE THE VILLAGE!
- HOLD IT RIGHT THERE!
- HUH?
- [INDISTINCT]
UHH!
OLD MAN, YOU WON'T
GET AWAY WITH THIS.
- [GRUNTS]
YOU'RE BECOMING
QUITE THE NUISANCE.
- INUYASHA!
- GIVE THOSE DEMONS
WHAT FOR! YAY!
- NICE MOVES, MIROKU.
NICE!
- AAH!
- INUYASHA!
- TOOK YOU LONG ENOUGH.
WHAT WAS THE HOLDUP, ANYWAY?
HOW MANY OF THESE THINGS
ARE THERE, DO YOU THINK?
- MORE THAN
WE COULD EVER COUNT.
- LET ME TAKE
A SHOT AT THEM.
- [KIRARA SNARLING]
- [INDISTINCT] UHH!
- THE BARRIER!
- YEAH. IT DEFLECTED
SANGO'S [INDISTINCT].
- [GRUNTS]
- HA HA HA HA!
- IT'S NOT LOOKING GOOD.
AND WITH SHIORI AROUND,
I CAN'T EVEN USE MY WIND TUNNEL
ON THEM, EITHER.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
CAN'T YOU MAKE A MOVE?
HA HA HA HA!
- DAMN IT ALL.
THERE'S GOT TO BE SOME WAY
THAT WE CAN GET SHIORI
OUT OF THE OLD DEMON'S GRIP.
- PLEASE THINK OF SOMETHING!
- HUH?
- ALL OUR LIVES DEPEND ON YOU.
- THE BAT DEMONS WILL SLAY
ALL OF US.
- IT'S THE VILLAGERS.
- HUH. YOU DON'T NEED
TO ASK ME FOR FAVORS.
I WAS GONNA
FINISH HIM OFF ANYWAY.
BUT FIRST I'VE GOT TO GET SHIORI
AWAY FROM HIM.
- YOU CAN'T.
THAT'S INSANE!
- AND BESIDES, THE GIRL
IS ON THE DEMON'S SIDE.
- HMM. YOU WANT ME
TO KILL HER, TOO, THEN?
- WELL,
THERE'S NOT MUCH CHOICE.
- AFTER ALL, SHE IS
THE CHILD OF A DEMON.
- HOW CRUEL.
SHIORI'S MOTHER SACRIFICED HER
FOR ALL THESE VILLAGERS HERE
IN ORDER TO SAVE THEM
FROM THE DEMON BATS.
- TALK ABOUT BEING SELFISH!
- HEY, MIROKU,
I DON'T THINK THERE'S ANYONE
INUYASHA DESPISES MORE THAN
PEOPLE LIKE THIS.
- YES, SEEING AS
HE'S BEEN TREATED BADLY
BY PEOPLE JUST LIKE THEM.
- DID YOU HEAR THAT, SHIORI?
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
- [SIGHS]
- YOU HEARD WHAT
THESE PEOPLE SAID ABOUT YOU.
GOING BACK TO THE VILLAGE
MIGHT NOT BE A GOOD IDEA.
DO YOU STILL
WANT TO GO BACK?
- THAT'S THE MAN
WHO WAS WITH MOMMY TODAY.
- IF YOU DECIDE
YOU WANT TO GO BACK HOME,
THEN I'LL HELP YOU GET THERE.
- YOU'LL HELP HER?
HA HA HA HA!
YOU FOOL, DON'T TELL ME
YOU THINK YOU CAN DEFEAT ME--
TAIGOKUMARU.
- [GROWLS]
RUN!
- HA HA HA HA!
I SEE YOU'RE ALSO
A HALF DEMON.
THAT UNDENIABLE STENCH
IS OVERWHELMING.
- OH, REALLY?
ARE YOU GOING SOMEWHERE
WITH THIS?
- YOU'RE RECALLING
YOUR OWN SITUATION.
THAT'S WHY YOU FEEL
SUCH GREAT SYMPATHY FOR SHIORI.
- SHE'S GOT
NOTHING TO DO WITH IT.
I JUST CAN'T STAND ROTTEN
OLD BATS LIKE YOU, IS ALL.
- HE'S A HALF DEMON?
THEN HE'S JUST LIKE ME.
- HMM.
SHIORI, MAKE UP YOUR MIND.
DO YOU WANT TO GO BACK
TO THE VILLAGE OR NOT?
- I DO.
I WANT TO BE WITH MOMMY,
BUT I CAN'T.
HMM?
- [PANTING]
OH!
- MOMMY?
- SHIORI.
- [GASP] MOMMY!
- IF YOU DON'T STAY AND PROTECT
THE BARRIER WITH ME,
YOUR MOTHER WILL DIE.
YOU UNDERSTAND THAT,
DON'T YOU?
- HMM?
WHAT DO I DO?
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I SHOULD DO.
- HOW DARE YOU CONFUSE
THE GIRL?
- SHIORI,
LOOK AFTER YOURSELF!
- CURSE YOU!
- YAH!
[SCREAMING]
- THE BARRIER'S EVEN STRONGER
THAN I THOUGHT.
- HA HA HA HA!
FINE WORK, MY GIRL.
YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- HMM.
IF I COULD GET EVEN PART
OF TAIGOKUMARU'S BODY
OUTSIDE THE BARRIER,
I'D AT LEAST STAND A CHANCE.
DOESN'T THE GIRL
HAVE THE POWER TO ADJUST
THE SIZE OF THE BARRIER?
HUH?
LOOK OUT!
EVERYONE OUT OF THE WAY!
- [SCREAMING]
- [PANTING AND GROANING]
- THE VILLAGE IS GONE.
- PLEASE HELP US.
- HA HA HA HA!
I HAVE NO USE
FOR THIS VILLAGE.
DESTROY EVERY ONE OF THEM.
- TAIGOKUMARU!
- [BAT DEMONS SNARLING]
- I BEG YOU TO STOP.
- IT'S HER MOTHER.
- THIS VILLAGE
WAS SAFE FROM YOUR ATTACKS
WHILE YOUR SON TSUKYUMARU
WAS ALIVE.
THAT WAS BECAUSE
HE PROTECTED US.
YOUR SON WANTED SHIORI
AND I TO LIVE HAPPILY.
HE PREVENTED ANY ATTACKS
ON THE VILLAGE.
- [WHIMPERS]
- PLEASE, I BEG YOU TO HONOR
YOUR SON'S WISHES.
- YOU WANT ME TO HONOR
HIS WISHES?
HA HA HA HA!
HOW LUDICROUS.
TSUKYUMARU WAS INDEED MY SON,
BUT HE WAS A FOOL,
AND FALLING IN LOVE
WITH A MORTAL
ONLY HASTENED HIS DEMISE.
- HUH? WHAT DO
YOU MEAN BY THAT?
- JUST AS YOU STATED,
HE SAID HE WOULD PROTECT
THIS VILLAGE.
HE SAID THAT UNLESS
WE ABIDED BY HIS WISHES,
HE WOULD ABANDON HIS DUTY
AS GUARDIAN OF THE BARRIER
AND WOULD LEAVE THE TRIBE.
EVEN HIS HEART
HAD BEEN STOLEN BY THE MORTAL.
AND THAT'S WHY...
- WHY WHAT?
- [GROWLS]
- THAT'S WHY WHAT?
DON'T TELL ME YOU...
YOU DIDN'T KILL
YOUR OWN FLESH AND BLOOD?!
- HA HA HA HA!
I DID.
I TOOK GREAT PLEASURE
IN HASTENING HIS TRIP
TO THE NETHER WORLD.
- [GASPS]
- AND I HAD SHIORI,
SO THE BOY WAS OF NO USE TO ME.
- [MOANING]
-GOTCHA. CAN YOU HEAR ME?
- TAIGOKUMARU,
YOU DON'T DESERVE TO LIVE!
HUH. I CAN FIX THAT FOR YOU.
- HA HA HA HA!
TRY IF YOU DARE.
AS YOU CAN SEE,
SHIORI CAN'T ADJUST
THE SIZE OF THE BARRIER.
WHEN YOU SLAY ME,
YOU WILL ALSO TAKE
THE GIRL'S LIFE.
- [GROWLS]
DAMN YOU!
- DO YOU REALLY THINK
YOU CAN DO IT, INUYASHA?
- IS THERE SOME WAY
HE CAN GET THE OLD MAN
WITHOUT HURTING SHIORI?
SHE CAN'T CONTROL THE BARRIER.
EVEN IF INUYASHA
DOES BREAK THROUGH IT SOMEHOW,
HE'LL ACCIDENTALLY KILL HER
IN THE PROCESS.
- HA HA HA HA!
WHAT'S THE MATTER, FOOL?
ARE YOU GOING TO
KILL ME OR NOT?
- OH, SHUT UP, YOU OLD BAT.
I'M TIRED OF PLAYING GAMES.
- NO!
YOU MEAN UP TILL NOW,
YOU'VE GONE EASY ON ME?
IN THAT CASE, I DARE YOU
TO USE YOUR FULL POWER!
- GLADLY. BACKLASH WAVE!
UHH!
THERE'S A HOLE IN THE BARRIER
FROM THE OLD BAT'S ATTACK.
MY BACKLASH WAVE SHOULD GO
THROUGH IT AND REACH THE BAT.
- THE DEMONIC AURA
FROM HIS SWORD
IS TWISTING THROUGH MY OWN
AND HEADING
STRAIGHT TOWARD ME!
- GO THROUGH THAT HOLE
AND BLAST HIS HEAD OFF!
- [GASPING]
- THE BARRIER'S BENDING!
- DID IT WORK?
- [GASP] IT WENT
BACK TO NORMAL!
- AND TAIGOKUMARU
DIDN'T GET HURT!
- GRR! I WAS A SECOND
TOO LATE.
- HA HA HA HA!
FINE WORK, MY SWEET GIRL.
KEEP IT UP.
- GET OUT.
- HUH?
- I WILL AVENGE
MY FATHER'S DEATH.
- [SCREAMING]
HOW DARE YOU?
AND YOU A MERE HALF DEMON!
I NEVER EXPECTED
SHE POSSESSED SUCH GREAT POWER.
EVEN I WAS UNABLE TO CONTROL
THE BARRIER AS SHE DOES.
- SHE'S FALLING!
- SHIORI!
SHIORI!
- YAAH!
EVEN THOUGH MY GRANDDAUGHTER IS
A MERE HALF DEMON,
I WOULD NEVER ALLOW THE HUMANS
TO HAVE HER!
- GET OUT OF THE WAY!
- HA HA HA HA!
- MOMMY, NO!
- TIME TO SAY
YOUR PRAYERS, OLD BAT!
- NOT AGAIN!
[SCREAMING]
- GOT HIM!
- WITH THE BACKLASH WAVE!
- [INUYASHA PANTING]
- IT'S OVER.
- YES.
- OVER HERE, PEOPLE!
THERE.
- UHH!
- SHIORI!
- MOMMY!
[CRYING]
- SHIORI, I'M SO SORRY.
THAT MUST HAVE BEEN
SO TERRIBLE FOR YOU.
- I MISSED YOU.
- MM-HMM.
- WELL, GUYS,
WE'VE DONE ALL WE CAN HERE.
LET'S GET GOING.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
- MYOGA, WHAT ARE
YOU STILL DOING HERE?
- HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN OUR REASON
FOR COMING HERE?
YOU NEED TO SLAY THE DEMON
WHO PROTECTED THE BARRIER
AND ALLOW TETSUSAIGA
TO SUCK ITS BLOOD!
SO MAKE UP YOUR MIND.
DO YOU WANT TO MAKE
THE SWORD STRONGER
OR DON'T YOU?!
- [GASP]
YOU CAME HERE
TO KILL MY GIRL?
- YEAH, AT FIRST.
OH, DON'T WORRY.
I MAY BE A HALF DEMON,
BUT I'M NOT EVIL ENOUGH
TO KILL A LITTLE GIRL.
- ESPECIALLY WHEN SHE'S
SO SWEET AND INNOCENT.
- AND A HALF DEMON LIKE HIM.
- I'LL JUST HAVE TO FIND
SOMEONE ELSE
WHO CAN PUT UP
AN EVEN STRONGER BARRIER
AND KILL HIM INSTEAD.
- YOU'VE CHANGED,
MASTER INUYASHA.
YOU WEREN'T
LIKE THIS BEFORE.
- WHAT'S THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
- UH, I--WELL, UH...
- HE MEANS
THAT YOU'VE GROWN UP.
- HMM.
- WELL, WE BETTER BE
HEADING OFF NOW.
- FAREWELL.
- WAIT!
- HUH?
- SHIORI?
- HMM?
- TAKE THIS.
- HUH?
- HMM?
- YOU WANT ME
TO BREAK THE ORB?
- MM-HMM.
SMASH IT TO PIECES.
THIS BLOOD CROW CRYSTAL
IS A PRECIOUS HEIRLOOM
PASSED DOWN TO EACH GUARDIAN
OF THE DEMON BAT BARRIER.
THIS IS WHAT GIVES US
THE ABILITY TO PUT UP
A POWERFUL BARRIER,
AND IT STORES ALL THE POWER OF
EACH GENERATION OF GUARDIANS,
LIKE MY GRANDFATHER'S
AND MY FATHER'S.
SO IF YOU BREAK THE CRYSTAL,
I THINK YOU'LL BE ABLE TO
STRENGTHEN YOUR SWORD.
THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT,
ISN'T IT?
- WE COULDN'T HAVE ASKED
FOR ANYTHING BETTER.
SMASH THE THING,
MASTER INUYASHA!
- YEAH. GOOD IDEA.
THE SOONER WE GET RID OF
THAT EVIL THING, THE BETTER.
- [GASP]
- HUH?
- IT'S RELEASING
A DEMONIC AURA!
- LET GO OF IT!
AAH!
HUH?
- MOMMY, YOUR HANDS!
- [GASP]
- HUH?
- THE CRYSTAL
PUT UP A BARRIER.
- I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN
IT WOULDN'T BE SO EASY TO BREAK.
HUH.
THIS IS GETTING AMUSING.
BUT NOT FOR ME!
UHH!
- [GASPING]
- AAH!
- YOU OK?
- YEAH, SURE.
- I WOULD NEVER LET YOU GO
THAT EASILY, SHIORI.
- THAT'S GRANDFATHER'S VOICE.
- SIMPLY BREAKING
THE CRYSTAL
COULD NOT SEVER YOUR BOND
WITH THE DEMON BAT TRIBE,
EVEN THOUGH YOUR MOTHER
IS MORTAL.
- TAIGOKUMARU.
- GRANDFATHER!
- I'LL KILL YOU THIS TIME!
- OH, REALLY?
UHH!
- INUYASHA!
- SHIORI, JOIN ME
AND ALL THE OTHERS IN HELL.
WHAT!
AAH!
- AAH!
- IT'S BROKEN!
- [SCREAMING]
- HMM?
- [GASP]
- SHIORI.
- HMM.
- CURSE YOU. AAH!
- THE BAT'S POWER
IS GETTING WEAKER.
NOW'S MY CHANCE!
- [SCREAMING]
- LET THE LITTLE GIRL
GO FREE! AAH!
- [SCREAMING]
- [GASPING]
- UHH!
- WHOA!
THE CRYSTAL BROKE!
- THIS TIME,
IT'S REALLY OVER.
HUH?
MY SWORD!
WHOA. THE BLADE
IS TURNING RED!
- LOOK. THE TETSUSAIGA HAS
ABSORBED THE CRYSTAL'S POWER.
- MAKING INUYASHA'S SWORD
A GREAT DEAL STRONGER.
- SHIORI?
- THANKS FOR HELPING.
- HUH. I'M THE ONE WHO
SHOULD BE THANKING YOU
FOR SAVING ME.
YOU WEAKENED
THE OLD BAT'S POWER.
- UH-UH. I WASN'T THE ONE
WHO DID THAT.
SOMEONE PUT HIS ARMS
AROUND US--
AROUND ME AND MOMMY.
HE WANTED TO PROTECT US.
- THAT WAS TSUKYUMARU.
THAT WAS YOUR FATHER,
SHIORI.
- HMM.
- I'M SURE YOUR FATHER
WOULD HAVE WANTED YOU
TO LIVE IN FREEDOM, TOO,
SHIORI.
- UH...
- UH-UH.
- HMM.
HA HA!
COME ON, LET'S GO.
- I'M STARVING.
- ME, TOO.
- WHAT ARE WE WAITING FOR?
- GOOD-BYE!
- INUYASHA WANTED
TO HELP THE GIRL.
I'M PRETTY SURE HE FORGOT
ALL ABOUT MAKING HIS SWORD
STRONGER,
AND THAT EXPLAINS WHY THE SPIRIT
OF SHIORI'S FATHER
HELPED HIM DEFEAT THE DEMON.
- I WONDER WHAT INUYASHA'S
THINKING ABOUT.
- INDEED.
HE IS AWFULLY PENSIVE
FOR SOMEONE
WHO DOESN'T SPEND
SO MUCH TIME THINKING.
- GRR! YOU WERE SAYING?
- SUCH A SHAME.
- HMM?
- I FEAR THEIR PROBLEMS
AREN'T OVER--
SHIORI AND HER MOTHER,
I MEAN.
- HA!
OH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT
THOSE TWO.
A GOOD HALF DEMON
CAN'T GO AROUND
AFRAID OF
EVERY LITTLE HARDSHIP.
HMM?
- YES, INDEED,
AND HERE WE HAVE
A FINE EXAMPLE
OF HOW A GOOD HALF DEMON
SHOULD BEHAVE.
- LET'S HOPE SHIORI
DOESN'T BECOME AS WARPED.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?!
- THAT'S MORE LIKE
THE REAL INUYASHA.
- [GROWLING]
WHAT ARE YOU JABBERING ABOUT?
- IT'S STRANGE
SEEING YOU LOST IN THOUGHT.
GROWLING SUITS YOU
A LOT BETTER THAN THINKING.
- HE'S RIGHT.
YOU SHOULDN'T DO THINGS YOU
DON'T HAVE SO MUCH PRACTICE IN.
- SHUT UP, MYOGA.
I'LL KILL YOU BOTH!
- WE WERE WORRIED ABOUT YOU,
THAT'S ALL.
- WHAT HE SAID. WHAT HE SAID!
- STOP MAKING FUN OF ME!
- HEY, DON'T BLAME ME
IF YOU FALL OFF.
- INUYASHA DIDN'T SAY A WORD
WHEN HE LEFT SHIORI.
NOT EVEN A "DO YOUR BEST"
OR "GOOD LUCK,"
EVEN THOUGH THERE WERE A LOT
OF THINGS HE COULD HAVE SAID.
INUYASHA CHOSE SILENCE
TO ENCOURAGE HER,
BUT I'M SURE
SHE GOT HIS MEANING.
- [BOTH GRUNTING]
- HUH?
HEY, WHAT'S
THE MATTER, KAGOME?
- GOOD BOY!
- GRR! WOULD YOU STOP
TREATING ME LIKE A DOG?
- GOOD BOY!
- YOU'RE STARTING TO
GET ON MY NERVES, SHIPPO.
- THAT'S ENOUGH.
- HE STARTED IT.
- AW, COME ON, MIROKU.
BE A GOOD SPORT!
- I KNEW I SHOULDN'T HAVE
COME ALONG WITH YOU.
- [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
♪ EVERY HEART ♪
- WE MEET UP WITH THE 4 SIBLINGS
OF THE PANTHER DEMON TRIBE.
- THEY'RE AFTER TWO THINGS:
SACRED JEWEL SHARDS
AND MASTER INUYASHA'S HEAD.
- HUH! I COULD CARE LESS
ABOUT THEM.
- IT ALL STARTED 50 YEARS AGO,
WHEN SESSHOMARU MEDDLED IN
THE GREAT WAR.
- ISN'T THAT AROUND THE TIME
INUYASHA WAS SEALED TO THE TREE?
NEXT TIME, "THE PLOT
OF THE PANTHER DEVAS."
- FINE. I'LL TAKE THEM ALL ON!