- I HAVE ERECTED A BARRIER.
THOSE SERVANTS OF YOURS
MAY NOT ENTER.
WITHOUT YOUR SOULS OF THE DEAD,
YOU REMAIN HELPLESS.
KIKYO, WHAT CAN YOU
BE THINKING?
THERE AT THE MOUNTAIN,
WHERE THE MAGIC WAS BROKEN,
WERE THE DEMONS
WHO WERE TO CREATE MY BODY.
INUYASHA STUMBLED
ONTO THE SCENE,
LURED BY THE MIASMA,
AND BEGAN TO DO BATTLE
WITH THE ONE WHO WOULD WIN.
THEN YOU APPEARED.
[ROARING]
YOUR ARROWS HAVE
THE POWER TO BREAK
WHICHEVER SPELL YOU CHOOSE.
AND YET, IF YOU WANTED TO
PREVENT THAT UNHOLY FUSION,
YOU OUGHT TO HAVE AIMED
STRAIGHT FOR THE DEMON.
THE DEMON WOULD DISINTEGRATE
AND THE SPELL BE EASILY BROKEN.
BUT BEFORE THE ONE
BECAME COMPLETE,
WERE YOU TRYING TO SEE
WHAT LAY BEYOND?
- AND THERE YE WERE.
YOUR DISGUISE IS
FINE...ONIGUMO.
- HUH. ONIGUMO.
NOW THAT BRINGS ME BACK.
50 YEARS AGO, YOU SAVED ME,
TOOK PITY ON ME,
AND SHELTERED THAT
FUGITIVE IN A CAVE.
ONIGUMO OFFERED HIS BODY
TO THE DEMONS,
WHO LATCHED ONTO HIS EVIL SOUL.
AND THUS WAS BORN NARAKU.
- THAT'S--
- YES, INDEED.
THE VERY THING YOU GAVE YOUR
LIFE TO ERASE FROM THIS WORLD.
A SHARD OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
- THEY SAY IT WAS
YOUR DESIRE TO POSSESS IT
THAT BROUGHT YOU TO KILL ME.
- DISCUSSING IT WITH ONE
WHO IS NO MORE
THAN A COLLECTION OF
DEAD SOULS IS UNSEEMLY,
BUT THE SEARCH FOR THE REMAINING
FRAGMENTS FRUSTRATES ME.
THAT GIRL WHO WAS SO LIKE
AND YET UNLIKE YOU--
A BATTLE BETWEEN THOSE
WHO CAN PURIFY EVIL.
IF YOU YEARN FOR THIS WORLD,
I BID YOU...GO AFTER HER.
[BIRD CHIRPING]
- WELL? WOULDN'T YOU SAY THOSE
TWO HAVE BEEN ACTING STRANGE?
- YEP.
- I...
INUYASHA?
HELLO!
- WHAT?
- INUYASHA, LET'S GO.
WE HAVE TO SAVE KIKYO.
IT'S STILL EARLY.
THEY CAN'T HAVE GONE FAR.
- I'LL SAVE HER ON MY OWN.
- STOP BEING SUCH
A STUBBORN FOOL.
- UGH!
- YOU FORGOT WHO IT WAS
THAT KIDNAPPED KIKYO.
I WANT MY OWN REVENGE.
I WOULDN'T EVEN HAVE
THIS HOLE IN MY RIGHT HAND
IF IT WEREN'T FOR NARAKU.
- HE'S AN ENEMY
TO ALL OF US, REMEMBER?
- WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
YOU'RE SO SPECIAL?
- LOOK, WE ALL KNOW WHAT
HAPPENED BETWEEN YOU AND KIKYO.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO SNEAK AROUND
TRYING TO FIX EVERYTHING
BEHIND OUR BACKS.
- I DON'T SNEAK AROUND, OK?
I'VE NEVER SNUCK IN MY LIFE!
- INUYASHA! OVER THERE!
- HUH?
- IT'S KIKYO'S SOUL GATHERERS.
- THEN SHE'S EVEN CLOSER
THAN WE THOUGHT.
- YOU COMING?
- MM-HMM.
- NOT THAT I'M COMPLAINING
OR ANYTHING, KAGOME,
BUT WHY AREN'T YOU
WITH INUYASHA?
- I, UM...UH...
- BECAUSE RIGHT NOW,
HE ONLY CARES FOR KIKYO,
THAT'S WHY.
BESIDES, WHY
HANG OFF HIM ANYWAY?
HE'S NOT EVEN MY BOYFRIEND.
[GASPS]
OH, NO!
I THINK I'M BLUSHING!
[GASPING]
I AM! I AM BLUSHING!
- WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH KAGOME?
- DON'T ASK ME.
- KIKYO DIED
BECAUSE OF HIM.
I WILL NOT LET NARAKU HAVE HER!
- LOOK! MORE GATHERERS!
[BUZZING]
UH-OH.
BUT THAT'S--
LOOK OUT! IT'S A TRAP!
- BE CAREFUL!
- WHAT IS THAT UP THERE?
I CAN'T--
HUH?
WHERE AM I?
- THAT'S HIM!
THE ONE WHO ATTACKED US!
- INUYASHA! IT'S INUYASHA!
- THIS PLACE--
I DON'T KNOW WHERE I--
[GASPS]
IT CAN'T BE!
THE SHIKON JEWEL!
- INUYASHA!
- HUH?
AAH!
K-KIKYO.
OF COURSE!
IT'S 50 YEARS AGO.
THE DAY KIKYO KILLED ME.
AND THIS IS THE VILLAGE
WHERE I ATTACKED
SO THAT I COULD STEAL
THE SACRED JEWEL.
KIKYO, WAIT!
IT WAS ALL JUST A TRAP!
KIKYO, DON'T DO IT!
KIKYO, NO!
IS THIS HELL?
IS IT A DREAM?
HOW DID I GET HERE?
- INUYASHA
AND THE OTHERS, GONE.
HMM. AND THE WIND--
IT'S STARTING TO PICK UP.
- IT'S SO CLOSE.
TOO CLOSE.
AAH!
IT'S PULLING ME IN!
- LOOK, KIRARA.
SEE?
THERE'S NOBODY BEHIND US.
HUH? WHAT'S WRONG?
WHY ARE YOU--AAH!
HUH?
WHERE'D KIRARA GO?
WHAT? KAGOME!
SANGO! WAIT UP!
THEY ALL LEFT THEIR CLOTHES.
WHERE'D EVERYBODY GO?
IF HERE'S WHERE
THEIR CLOTHES ARE,
WHERE'D THE REST OF THEM GO?
INUYASHA! MIROKU!
OW! KAGOME! SANGO!
[PANTING]
- HUH?
HUH?
[WHIMPERS]
AAH!
KOHAKU?
- THE EVIL SPELL
OF ILLUSORY DEATH.
THE SOUL IS SUCH
A FRAGILE THING.
SADNESS, FEAR, CONFUSION.
IF EVEN SLIGHTEST DOUBT EXISTS
AND IS TOUCHED BY
THE CREEPERS OF THIS WORLD,
THAT SOUL WILL BE
CONSUMED WITH DARK.
- WHERE CAN EVERYONE
HAVE GONE OFF TO?
AAH!
EW! WHAT'S THAT?
AAH! AAH!
- PERHAPS BECAUSE OF
THE JEWEL SHARDS,
THAT GIRL ALONE
IS UNAFFECTED.
ONLY SHE SHALL MAKE IT HERE.
THE STAGE HAS BEEN
SET FOR YOU.
- AREN'T YOU THE CLEVER ONE.
- SO SHE'S DESTROYED
THE GOLLUM.
HOW DARE SHE DEFY ME.
- KIKYO.
KIKYO! YOU'RE OK!
KIKYO!
WE'VE BEEN...SO WORRIED
ABOUT YOU.
[MOANS]
AAH!
[SCREAMS]
[WHIMPERS]
KIKYO.
- NARAKU FINDS HIMSELF
FRIGHTENED OF YOU.
HE TRIES TO CONTROL ME
WITH THE SACRED JEWEL,
HOPING THAT I MIGHT BE
TURNED AGAINST YOU.
- WILL SHE SAVE ME?
[WHIMPERS]
- THE JEWEL SHARD
IN YOUR CHEST!
- SURELY THE PRIESTESS
WHO ONCE STOOD GUARD
OVER THE SACRED JEWEL OF 4 SOULS
HAS NOT FALLEN SO LOW AS TO BE
CONTROLLED BY A MERE SHARD.
- OH!
[WINCES AND GROANS]
- KIKYO!
[WINCES]
- SHE CAME TO ME IN
HER PAIN, ALL ALONE.
KIKYO, YOU'LL NEVER
BE ALONE AGAIN.
I SWEAR IT.
I WILL ALWAYS PROTECT YOU.
HUH?
BUT I DON'T--
YOU MEAN THERE'S SOMEONE
ELSE I SHOULD PROTECT?
WHO, THOUGH?
WHO'S THIS OTHER PERSON
I'M SUPPOSED TO--
KAGOME.
OF COURSE!
HOW THE HECK COULD I HAVE--
WHERE'S KAGOME?
TELL ME!
- INUYASHA!
IS SHE MORE IMPORTANT
TO YOU THAN I AM?
- IT'S ALL BEEN
AN ILLUSION, HASN'T IT?
- AAH!
- MIROKU!
[WHIMPERING]
AHH!
HEY, ARE YOU OK?
- MY--MY--
THE WIND TUNNEL--I--
- HE'S SCARED.
REALLY SCARED.
- WAKE UP! SNAP OUT OF IT!
- IT WAS SWALLOWING UP
MY ENTIRE BODY.
- IT'S THAT TREE,
THOSE ROOTS.
- QUICK! YOU GOT TO
FIND SANGO AND SHIPPO.
BET YOU ANYTHING
THEY'RE UNDER THE SAME
SPELL THAT GOT YOU AND ME.
I GOT TO GO FIND KAGOME.
KAGOME! WHERE ARE YOU?
KAGOME!
- INUYASHA.
- KAGOME!
THOSE ROOTS CAUSED
SOME KIND OF AN ILLUSION.
SEEMS LIKE YOU GOT AWAY
FROM IT OK, THOUGH.
- UH...UH...
UH...
- HUH?
[GASPS]
HUH?
KIKYO!
THOSE ARE KAGOME'S
JEWEL SHARDS!
KAGOME.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
YOU DIDN'T!
DON'T TELL ME IT WAS YOU!
- WHAT'S WRONG, INUYASHA?
TELL ME--
WHY IS IT I FEEL
THAT YOU'RE UNHAPPY
TO KNOW I'M WELL?
- ANSWER ME!
JUST WHAT DID YOU DO TO HER?
- I TRIED TO KILL HER.
WHAT IS IT THAT YOU PLAN
TO DO ABOUT IT?
WILL YOU KILL ME?
[GROWLING]
TELL ME--WHEN NARAKU
HAD YOU UNDER HIS SPELL,
WHAT WAS IT THAT
YOU THOUGHT ABOUT?
[SIGHS]
- I...I SWEAR I'LL
ALWAYS PROTECT YOU.
[SNICKERS]
[LAUGHS]
- NOW, COULD YOU HAVE SAID THAT
IF YOU WERE GOING TO KILL ME?
EMBRACING DEATH TOGETHER--
NOW THAT'S A DAY I'LL WAIT FOR.
- KAGOME, TELL ME
WHAT SHE DID TO YOU.
- SHE TOOK THE SACRED
JEWEL BACK FROM ME.
I'M SORRY.
- THAT'S NOT WHAT I'M ASKING!
DID KIKYO REALLY TRY TO--
- THEN DON'T ASK ME!
[GASPS]
- KAGOME.
I CAN'T DO IT.
I FEEL LIKE
I'M TELLING ON HER.
- SO, UH...ARE YOU TWO
FINISHED TALKING?
- [VOICE-OVER]
TO KIKYO, MY LIFE...
IT HAS NO MEANING.
- THOSE ROOTS CAUSED
SOME KIND OF AN ILLUSION.
SEEMS LIKE YOU GOT AWAY
FROM IT OK, THOUGH.
- UH...UH...
- [VOICE-OVER]
THE ILLUSORY DEATH.
OUR PAIN AND CONFUSION
PUT US ALL TO THE TEST.
MINE, TOO.
IT GAVE ME A SMALL LOOK
INTO MY OWN HEART.
INTO A PLACE WHERE...
INUYASHA AND KIKYO WERE...
IN LOVE WITH EACH OTHER.
[WIND HOWLING]
- YOU'RE CARELESS, NARAKU.
- SO, KIKYO?
- ONCE YOUR LITTLE POPPET
IS BROKEN, YOU SEE NOTHING.
REMEMBER THAT.
YOUR PETTY FEATS OF MINOR
SORCERY CAN NOT AFFECT ME.
AS FOR THE BARRIER
AROUND THE CASTLE,
THE ONE YOU ERECTED
TO KEEP OUT INUYASHA,
THAT WAS EASY ENOUGH
FOR ME TO BREAK.
YOU WANTED IT, DIDN'T YOU?
I LEAVE IT TO YOU
TO STAND GUARD OVER.
AFTER ALL, WHO NEEDS
ITS POWER MORE THAN YOU?
AND YOU DO NEED IT, DON'T YOU?
DEMON NARAKU?
OR IS IT...
HALF-DEMON NARAKU?
- A MERE HALF-DEMON,
I, NARAKU?
- TRUE, YOU DISGUISED
YOURSELF WELL,
BUT YOU'RE STILL
THAT FUGITIVE HUMAN,
AND THE BLOOD OF WHO YOU
ONCE WERE CAN NEVER BE ERASED.
YOU SEEK THE SACRED JEWEL
TO BECOME A FULL-FLEDGED
DEMON, DO YOU NOT?
- IF SO, WHY GIVE ME THE SHARDS?
AM I NOT THE ONE YOU SEEK TO
AVENGE YOUR DEATH 50 YEARS AGO?
- HA HA! IT WAS ONLY
MY BODY THAT DIED.
I MAY HAVE LEFT IT
BEHIND THAT DAY,
BUT WITH THIS NEW ONE,
I'M EVEN STRONGER.
I DON'T ASK THAT
YOU UNDERSTAND.
I'M RETURNING TO THE TEMPLE.
I WILL NEITHER RUN NOR HIDE.
SEND A MESSENGER
IF YOU NEED ME.
- IT'S APPEARED AGAIN.
NO MATTER HOW OFTEN
I CHANGE FLESH,
THE BURN SCARS OF THE FUGITIVE
ONIGUMO WILL NOT LEAVE MY BACK.
- GO, NARAKU.
GATHER THE SHARDS OF THE JEWEL,
AND ONCE YOU'VE FOUND THEM ALL,
THEN I WILL SEND YOU TO HELL.
I'M FREE TO HATE.
MY SOUL IS SO MUCH FREER NOW
THAN IT WAS THEN.
FREE TO HATE...
FREE TO LOVE.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- [VOICE-OVER]
OH, GREAT!
MY SACRED JEWEL'S BEEN STOLEN.
NOW I CAN'T GO BACK HOME.
LEND ME YOURS,
MIROKU, PLEASE?
I NEED TO GO BACK HOME
FOR MY TEST TOMORROW.
WHAT?
OH, SANGO, YOU WILL?
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
UH, MYOGA?
WHO'S THAT?
THE MAN WHO MADE TETSUSAIGA?
NEXT TIME,
"TETSUSAIGA AND TENSEIGA."
SEE YOU SOON!