- I DON'T BELIEVE THIS!
HOW CAN THEY NOT KNOW
WHAT A BATH IS?
[SHIVERS]
OH! COLD!
- COME, CHILD.
YOU'LL GET SICK
IF YOU DON'T GET OUT.
- I CAN'T!
I'M COVERED
WITH BLOOD AND DIRT!
AND I FEEL LIKE MY HAIR
HASN'T BEEN WASHED IN A WEEK!
[TAKES A DEEP BREATH]
[SIGHS]
THE JEWEL OF 4 SOULS.
REMEMBER ME?
I'M KAGOME HIGURASHI.
I THOUGHT I WAS A NORMAL GIRL,
AT LEAST TILL I FELL IN THE WELL
AND CAME OUT IN FEUDAL JAPAN.
- ONCE AGAIN I LIVE.
ALREADY MY STRENGTH RETURNS.
AGAIN MY FLESH IS RESTORED.
YOU HAVE THE JEWEL,
DON'T YOU?
GIVE IT TO ME!
- WHAT--WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
LET GO!
EVERYONE WANTS THE JEWEL
THAT WAS SOMEHOW IN MY BODY.
IT'S LIKE THEY CAN'T
HELP THEMSELVES.
[SCREECHING]
IT BELONGED TO SOMEONE
NAMED KIKYO,
BUT HOW'D IT PASS
FROM HER TO ME?
NOW I'M SUPPOSED TO WORK WITH
SOME HALF-DEMON CALLED INUYASHA
TO COLLECT THE PIECES,
WHICH, OF COURSE,
HE WANTS FOR HIMSELF.
[SHATTERING]
I CALL IT A DREAM,
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
THIS IS TOO WEIRD
TO BE A DREAM!
- WHAT DID YOU DO TO IT?
- STOP BARKING, INUYASHA.
- LEAVE IT TO HER
TO WIND UP BREAKING IT!
- TECHNICALLY, IT WASN'T
KAGOME WHO BROKE IT
BUT THE CROW'S FOOT
SHE ATTACHED TO HER ARROW
THAT ACTUALLY CAUSED IT.
AS HE SAW, THE JEWEL
HAS NOW BEEN SCATTERED
INTO MANY DIFFERENT PIECES.
100...1,000--WHO KNOWS?
YET HOWEVER MANY
SHARDS THERE MAY BE,
ALL IT WILL TAKE IS
ONE IN THE WRONG HANDS
TO BRING DISASTER.
I'M SO SORRY.
I HAD NO IDEA.
IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
- KAGOME, INUYASHA,
ONLY BY WORKING TOGETHER
WILL THE TWO OF YE BE ABLE TO
RECOVER THE SHARDS OF THE JEWEL.
- HUH?
- HMM!
YOU WON'T CATCH ME
COMPLAINING.
I'M ONE OF THE WRONG HANDS
YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT.
- OH, AYE,
THAT I KNOW TOO WELL.
- BUT...I WANT
TO GO BACK HOME!
HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO DO THAT ANYWAY?
INUYASHA HELP?
HA!
[SIGHS]
HMM?
- AAH!
- HMM?
- SIT, BOY!
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
- THEE ALL RIGHT, INUYASHA?
- OH, MAN.
I FORGOT ABOUT THIS
STUPID NECKLACE OF YOURS.
- IT SERVES YOU RIGHT FOR SPYING
ON ME, YOU PEEPING TOM!
[MOANS]
- HA! SHOWS WHAT YOU KNOW.
THE REASON I REALLY
CAME WAS TO--
- YE REALLY CAME TO STEAL
THIS SHARD, CORRECT?
- THINK YOU'RE PRETTY SMART,
YOU OLD HAG.
- I SEE. YE THINK
TO DO IT ALONE, DO YE?
YE FORGET ONLY YON GIRL
CAN FIND THOSE SHARDS,
WHILE ONLY YE, INUYASHA,
HAVE STRENGTH ENOUGH
TO TAKE THEM BACK ONCE FOUND.
- IN CASE YOU HAVEN'T NOTICED,
I'M STILL HERE, AIN'T I?
I CAN PUT UP WITH
ANYTHING FOR THE JEWEL.
- YOU REALLY DO HATE ME,
DON'T YOU?
- HUH?
KIKYO.
[GROWLS]
- AND WHAT AILS YE NOW,
INUYASHA?
- MMM! OH, MY! OH, ME!
50 YEARS LATER, AND THE SACRED
JEWEL FINALLY RESURFACES!
I'D ALMOST GIVEN UP HOPE.
[GIGGLES]
[LAUGHS]
- LADY KAEDE?
- HMM?
- IT'S MY DAUGHTER.
- I SEE.
LET'S HEAD BACK.
I'LL BE CHECKING ON
YE TWO LATER.
TRY NOT TO FIGHT.
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
- HEY.
- NOW WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- GET UNDRESSED.
[CRASH]
OW!
THAT HURT!
WHY DID YOU--
- YOU'RE SUCH A PIG!
- I DIDN'T SAY,
"GET NAKED," STUPID!
I JUST CAN'T STAND
SEEING YOU IN THOSE CLOTHES!
- WHY?
BECAUSE I LOOK LIKE KIKYO?
[GRUNTS]
- THAT'S GOT NOTHING
TO DO WITH IT, OK?
- OH, PLEASE! MY LITTLE
BROTHER IS MORE MATURE.
LOOK, I DON'T WANT
TO DO THIS EITHER, OK?
BUT WE GOT TO WORK TOGETHER.
- I AIN'T GOT TO DO NOTHING.
IT'S YOU WHO NEEDS ME.
- OH, I GET IT.
SO YOU DON'T CARE
IF I JUST GO BACK HOME.
- HEY, WHERE YOU GOING?
- WHAT DO YOU CARE?
I'M GOING HOME.
GOOD-BYE, INUYASHA.
- YOU CAN'T JUST LEAVE!
YOU--
- MY NAME ISN'T "YOU."
IT'S KAGOME.
- WAIT, STUPID!
- IT'S NOT STUPID EITHER.
- WILL YOU JUST WAIT
AND HEAR ME OUT?
- WHY? SO YOU CAN
TRY AND STOP ME?
- NO. SO YOU CAN GIVE ME
YOUR JEWEL SHARD.
- OH, THIS?
SIT, BOY!
[GRUNTS]
- WHY, YOU!
- IT'S KAGOME.
WHY, THAT STUPID,
IGNORANT, LITTLE...
HE NEVER ONCE USED MY NAME.
NOT ONCE!
- THIS WAY, LADY KAEDE.
- HER LAPSED WITHOUT
WARNING, DID SHE?
- AYE...THOUGH SHE SEEMED
JUST FINE THIS MORNING.
- WELL...
HMM?
NO! STAY BACK.
- WHAT?
[GASPS]
LOOK! SHE MOVED!
- IT LOOKS LIKE HAIR.
[RATTLING]
OH!
- THAT'S WHERE I CAME OUT.
IT SHOULD TAKE ME BACK, RIGHT?
[GASPS]
BONES.
- WE CALL IT
THE BONE EATER'S WELL.
IT'S A RESTING PLACE
FOR THE BODIES OF MONSTERS,
THOUGH THE FLESH OF THOSE BODIES
DISAPPEARS QUICKLY ENOUGH.
- AND THOSE MUST BE THE BONES
OF MISTRESS CENTIPEDE.
- NO WAY.
I CAN'T GO IN THERE NOW.
WHAT THEN?
HMM?
[SCREECHING]
HUH?
[WHIMPERS]
AAH!
[GASPS]
THAT LOOKS LIKE...HAIR!
- OH, MY! OH, ME!
YOU CAN SEE IT THEN.
NY NET OF HAIRS, I MEAN.
PITY...BECAUSE
SEEING'S NOT ENOUGH.
- WHO ARE YOU?
[SNICKERS]
- I'M GOING HOME!
- HUH!
- GOOD-BYE, INUYASHA.
- LET HER GO.
BETTER OFF WITHOUT HER.
[GRUNTS]
HUH?
WELL, I GUESS I SHOULDN'T
ASK WHAT YOU'RE UP TO.
HA! ALL RIGHT!
NOW THIS IS WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT!
- HOW DO YOU DO?
I'M YURA OF THE HAIR,
THOUGH YOU NEEDN'T
BOTHER TO REMEMBER...
BECAUSE YOU'LL BE DEAD SOON!
[GASPS]
- OH! OOH!
- I'LL BE HAVING THE JEWEL,
IF YOU DON'T MIND.
[GASPS]
- OH!
YOU NAUGHTY, NAUGHTY GIRL.
YOU'VE SHATTERED THE JEWEL!
WHERE'S THE REST?
OR I SHALL BE CROSS.
- YOU GIVE THAT BACK!
- ANSWER THE QUESTION.
WHERE IS THE REST OF IT?
- I'M...I'M NOT REALLY SURE.
- OH...
IN THAT CASE--
[GRUNTS]
I MAY AS WELL
FINISH YOU RIGHT NOW!
[GASPS]
- OH...
IN THAT CASE--
[GRUNTS]
I MAY AS WELL
FINISH YOU RIGHT NOW!
[GASPS]
[GRUNTING]
- AAH! AAH!
- NO FAIR ESCAPING!
THAT'S STRANGE.
COME TO THINK OF IT,
SO WAS THAT GIRL.
- HUH.
I KNEW SOMETHING WAS STRANGE.
I RECOGNIZE THESE GIRLS
FROM THE VILLAGE.
LOOK! IS SOMEONE GOING
TO TELL ME WHAT'S GOING ON,
OR DO YOU WANT ANOTHER FIGHT?
BECAUSE THAT'S FINE IF YOU DO.
JUST DON'T EXPECT
I'LL GO EASY ON YOU.
- INUYASHA, WAIT!
- HUH?
[GRUNTING]
- DO NOT HURT THEM.
'TIS NOT THEIR DOING.
- OLD KAEDE.
[GRUNTS]
WHAT HAPPENED?
YOU LOOK AWFUL!
- MUST YE ALWAYS TREAT
AN OLD WOMAN THUS?
- ABOUT THE GIRLS--
IT'S THEM OR US,
AND I CHOOSE US!
- WELL, SOMEONE ELSE
IS CONTROLLING THEM.
[GASPS]
WHERE'S KAGOME?
TELL ME YE KNOW
WHERE SHE IS!
- ALL I KNOW IS THAT
SHE SAID SHE WAS GOING HOME.
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL ANYWAY?
I CAN HANDLE THIS WITHOUT HER.
- YEA, NAY!
YE MUST NOT HURT THEM,
INUYASHA.
- YOUR HEART BLEEDS IN MORE
WAYS THAN ONE, OLD WOMAN,
BUT IF YOU'RE PLANNING
ON SEEING TOMORROW,
WE GOT TO DO SOMETHING.
[GRUNTING]
- CONTROL THE STRINGS,
AND YE CONTROL THE PUPPETS.
IF NOT--
- I DON'T SEE YOU
HELPING NONE, OLD WOMAN!
- THE HAIR, INUYASHA!
FIND YE THE HAIR,
AND MEHAP WILL WAKE!
- HAIR?
I DON'T SEE ANY HAIR!
- OH, ME! OH, MY!
I'LL DEFINITELY BE WANTING
THIS ONE FOR MY COLLECTION.
[SHOUTS]
- HUH? HUH?
- A TRAP!
INUYASHA, FLEE THE HAIR!
[GRUNTING]
[CHUCKLING]
[GRUNTS]
- WHOEVER'S DOING THIS
AIN'T TOO SMART,
BECAUSE EVEN ALL TANGLED UP,
I DON'T NEED TO SEE TO DRAG OUT
WHOEVER'S ON THE OTHER END.
- OH...SO SORRY.
[GROANS]
PERHAPS IT'S TIME
TO TIE THINGS UP.
[GRUNTING]
- AAH!
[MOANING]
- INUYASHA!
- AAH!
[GRUNTING]
AAH!
- HUH?
THE HAIR IS SLACK.
THE CUT WAS NOT CLEAN.
[PANTING]
- OH, MAN!
I THOUGHT I WAS A GONER!
- AND SO WOULD YE HAVE BEEN
WERE YE NORMAL, INUYASHA.
HUH?
- HUH?
- MEN FROM THE VILLAGE.
- KNOW SOMETHING?
I'M GETTING REAL SICK OF THIS.
- INUYASHA...SAVE YOURSELF.
FORGET THIS OLD WOMAN.
- AW, SPARE ME
THE NOBLE ACT, WILL YOU?
HEY, ARE YOU OK?
[GRUNTING]
- AAH!
- GEESH! THANKS A LOT.
- OH!
OH, WHAT PRETTY SILVER HAIR.
- AAH!
- HANG ON TIGHT, YOU HEAR?
- BEWARE, INUYASHA,
LEST YOU TOUCH.
THE HAIR WILL--
AAH!
- HEY, DID YOU SAY
SOMETHING, OLD WOMAN?
- NOT AT ALL.
- HE'S STUBBORN,
BUT HE'S ALSO FUN,
AND I POSITIVELY MUST HAVE
THIS PRETTY SILVER HAIR OF HIS.
- DID I HEAR YOU SAY
YOU COULD SEE THE HAIR?
- MM-HMM.
- CAN YOU TELL ME WHERE
IT'S BEING PULLED FROM?
- DON'T BE ABSURD.
WITH ME IN THIS CONDITION AND...
ASSUMING I DID KNOW FROM WHENCE
THE STRANDS OF HAIR CAME,
YOU MUST FIND KAGOME.
- YOU MEAN
SHE CAN SEE IT, TOO?
- AYE, AND TO DEFEAT THIS FOE,
YOU'LL BE NEEDING THAT POWER.
WITHOUT IT, YE HAVE NO HOPE.
NONE.
[GRUNTING]
[SIGHS]
[MOANS]
AHH...OH.
WHERE AM I?
[GASPS]
I'M IN THE WELL...
WHICH IS WHERE I FELL
WHEN THAT WOMAN PUSHED ME BACK.
- BUT WE'VE ALREADY BEEN
IN HERE A DOZEN TIMES.
[GASPS]
- BUT, LOOK, GRANDPA,
I KEEP TELLING YOU,
THIS IS WHERE SHE FELL.
- BUT ARE YOU SURE
YOU WEREN'T DREAMING?
- BUT I WASN'T!
- UH, GRANDPA!
SOTA!
AHH.
I'VE COME HOME...
BACK TO MY OWN TIME.
- YOU WERE MISSING
FOR 3 FULL DAYS.
THE LEAST YOU COULD
HAVE DONE WAS CALLED.
- AND WHY ARE YOU WEARING
THOSE WEIRD OLD CLOTHES?
- IT'S NOT A DREAM.
I'M REALLY BACK.
I'VE COME HOME.
[WHIMPERS]
[SOBS]
GRANDPA! I WAS SO SCARED!
- KAGOME, WHAT ON EARTH?
[SOBBING]
[INUYASHA GRUNTING]
- THERE.
THAT OUGHT TO BE ENOUGH.
WELL, ALL THINGS
CONSIDERED, OLD WOMAN,
IT'S THE LEAST
I CAN DO FOR YOU.
- WHY...I'M RESTING,
NOT DEAD.
- THEN THINK OF IT
AS A HIDING PLACE.
I'LL EVEN COME BACK
AND DIG YOU UP, IF I REMEMBER.
- DO YE PROMISE?
YE WON'T FORGET
WHERE YE LEFT ME?
[SIGHS]
DO NOT FORGET, INUYASHA.
- OK. I HEARD YOU.
GEES!
- CURSE THAT STUPID WOMAN,
TAKING OFF ON ME
RIGHT WHEN I NEED HER!
- OH, I MUST BE IN HEAVEN.
AHH!
[CHUCKLING]
- LITTLE GIRL, COME OUT,
COME OUT, WHEREVER YOU ARE.
- AHH! SHAMPOO!
IT'S A GOOD THING.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- INUYASHA CAN'T SEE THE HAIR
THAT YURA CONTROLS,
SO HOW CAN HE BEAT
AN ENEMY WHO'S PRACTICALLY
TOYING WITH HIM?
IN ORDER TO HELP KAEDE IN TIME,
WE HAVE TO DEFEAT YURA FAST,
BUT HOW?
NO MATTER WHAT INUYASHA DOES,
HE CAN'T SEEM TO HURT HER.
YURA MUST HAVE
A WEAKNESS SOMEWHERE.
NEXT TIME ON "INUYASHA..."
SEE YOU SOON.