>> I'M KAGOME HIGURASHI,
AND I WAS BORN INTO AN OLD
AND RESPECTED FAMILY OF
SHRINEKEEPERS.
I'M A NINTH-GRADE STUDENT
IN MIDDLE SCHOOL, LEADING
A PRETTY NORMAL LIFE.
OR SO IT WAS UNTIL MY 15th
BIRTHDAY, WHEN I WAS DRAGGED
INTO THE FEUDAL ERA BY A DEMON
THAT POPPED OUT OF
THE SHRINE WELL.
THAT'S HOW I MET THE YOUNG
HALF-DEMON INUYASHA.
HE AND PRACTICALLY EVERY OTHER
DEMON IS AFTER THE SACRED JEWEL
OF FOUR SOULS--A TREASURE THAT
INCREASES A DEMON'S POWER.
I'VE BEEN GOING BACK AND FORTH
BETWEEN MY WORLD AND THE FEUDAL
ERA, WHERE I TRY TO HELP
INUYASHA AND OTHER FRIENDS
FIND SHARDS OF THE SHATTERED
JEWEL.
ONE GREEDY DEMON--NARAKU--
IS TRYING TO GET THE SACRED
JEWEL FOR HIMSELF.
SCHEMING TO ABSORB THE DEMON
POWERS OF INUYASHA'S BROTHER
SESSHOMARU, NARAKU LURES HIM
TO HIS CASTLE.
AND JUST AS NARAKU IS
ABOUT TO COMPLETELY CONSUME
SESSHOMARU'S BODY, INUYASHA
BREAKS THROUGH HIS BARRIER
AND RUSHES INTO THE CASTLE.
>> YOU'RE DEAD!
WIND SCAR!
>> HE'S BROKEN THROUGH
MY BARRIER.
>> DIE!
>> HUH?
>> INUYASHA IS ABOUT TO FINISH
NARAKU OFF FOR GOOD,
BUT IT ISN'T MEANT TO BE.
>> YOU FOOL!
DON'T THINK THAT YOU CAN EVER
ESCAPE MY GRASP.
>> NARAKU HAD USED SANGO'S
YOUNGER BROTHER KOHAKU
AS A DIVERSION TO MAKE
HIS OWN ESCAPE.
THEN HE SIMPLY VANISHED
BEFORE OUR EYES.
>> DAMN THAT NARAKU.
THE CASTLE LOOKS ABANDONED,
SO HE PROBABLY WON'T BE
COMING BACK.
>> I'M AFRAID YOU'RE RIGHT.
AFTER YOU BROKE THROUGH
HIS DEMONIC BARRIER,
NARAKU HAD TO MOVE ON
OR ELSE RISK BEING ATTACKED.
>> [GROWLING]
>> HMM.
>> MAN.
NARAKU IS PROBABLY VULNERABLE
ENOUGH RIGHT NOW FOR ME
TO KILL HIM, TOO.
I WAS SO CLOSE.
DAMMIT!
>> [THINKING] I WONDER IF COMING
HOME WAS THE RIGHT THING TO DO.
I FEEL BAD ABOUT LEAVING
INUYASHA AND THE OTHERS.
HERE I AM, PERFECTLY SAFE,
JUST PASSING THE TIME STUDYING
WHILE THEY COULD BE
IN REAL DANGER.
I HOPE THEY'RE ALL OK.
>> THIS PROBLEM WILL BE
ON THE TEST IN TWO DAYS,
SO MEMORIZE IT NOW
WHILE YOU HAVE THE CHANCE.
>> UH, WHAT TEST?
>> [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
>> I CAN'T SIT AROUND
WORRYING ABOUT OTHER PEOPLE.
I'VE ONLY GOT TWO DAYS
TO CATCH UP.
AND IF I DON'T CRAM NOW,
I'LL END UP FLUNKING.
>> YOU WANT TO WALK HOME
WITH US?
>> SURE. YOU BET.
SO YOU SEE THE BIND I'M IN.
DO ME A FAVOR,
AND LEND ME YOUR NOTES.
>> IT'S NOT THAT SIMPLE.
>> WE HAVE TO STUDY FOR
THE TEST, TOO, YOU KNOW.
>> OH, COME ON, YOU GUYS.
I JUST WANT TO BORROW THEM
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
I'LL GIVE THEM RIGHT BACK
TO YOU.
>> I KNOW HOW HARD IT MUST BE
WITH ALL THE SCHOOL YOU MISS
'CAUSE YOU'RE SICK ALL THE TIME.
>> I KNEW YOU'D UNDERSTAND.
SO HELP ME OUT AND LET ME
MAKE A SUPER-FAST COPY
OF YOUR NOTES, OK?
>> ALL RIGHT.
I GUESS THAT'S WHAT
FRIENDS ARE FOR.
>> SO YOU WILL?
>> JUST MAKE IT QUICK.
>> OH! YOU'RE THE BEST!
>> BUT IN EXCHANGE...
>> HUH? WHAT? OH.
>> [TOGETHER] THANKS, KAGOME.
>> AW.
>> MMM.
>> [SIGH]
>> UH, KAGOME?
>> HUH?
>> THERE YOU GO, THINKING AGAIN.
>> ABOUT WHAT?
>> COME ON. YOU CAN'T FOOL US.
YOUR JEALOUS BOYFRIEND;
THE ONE WITH THE ATTITUDE.
>> OH, THAT GUY.
I WASN'T THINKING ABOUT HIM.
>> JUST FESS UP FOR ONCE.
>> SO, HOW'S IT GOING?
>> UH, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU WANT ME TO SAY.
>> THERE MUST BE SOMETHING NEW.
>> WELL, I MET HIS OLDER BROTHER
THE OTHER DAY.
>> OH, SO HE HAS A BROTHER?
>> SO, IS HE A PUNK AS WELL?
>> I BET HIS BROTHER'S
JUST AS STRONG.
>> OH, YEAH,
HE'S STRONG, ALL RIGHT--
MAYBE EVEN THE STRONGER
OF THE TWO.
YOU GET THE TWO OF THEM IN THE
SAME ROOM, AND LET ME TELL YOU,
THE FUR STARTS FLYING.
>> [THINKING] KAGOME'S BOYFRIEND
IS DEFINITELY DANGEROUS.
A GOOD FRIEND WOULD STEP IN
AND SAY SOMETHING TO HER,
WOULDN'T SHE?
>> [THINKING] HER FUTURE'S
ON A COLLISION COURSE WITH DOOM.
>> [THINKING] LOVE CAN CONQUER
ALL, KAGOME.
ALL YOU NEED IS TO KEEP
BELIEVING.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER?
>> [TOGETHER] NOTHING.
>> WHAT DO YOU SAY?
CAN I COPY YOUR NOTES NOW?
>> [TOGETHER] HUH?!
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> THE COLLEGES ARE IN EXAMS.
>> LOOKS LIKE YOUR IDEA
WASN'T SO ORIGINAL.
>> WHAT'LL WE DO--STAND IN LINE?
>> IT'S OK.
WE CAN MAKE COPIES
SOMEWHERE ELSE.
NO PROBLEMO.
BROKEN?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, CLOSED?
NO WAY!
AAH!
THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING TO ME!
>> SEE YOU LATER, KAGOME.
>> WE'D BETTER GET GOING.
GOT TO STUDY.
>> HOPE IT ALL WORKS OUT
FOR YOU.
>> WAIT! DON'T GO!
THEY LEFT.
YOU TRAITORS!
>> UHH!
[GROWLING]
>> HUH?
>> WHAT'S TAKING KAGOME SO LONG
TO GET BACK?
I THOUGHT SHE SAID
SHE WOULDN'T BE LONG THIS TIME.
>> WELL, SHE SAID SHE'D BE
AT LEAST 2 OR 3 DAYS.
>> PATIENCE IS A VIRTUE,
INUYASHA.
>> WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
YOU SHOULD BE AS WORRIED
AS I AM.
>> IT'S NOT AS THOUGH WE ONLY
STARTED HUNTING DOWN NARAKU
A COUPLE DAYS AGO.
BESIDES, INUYASHA, YOU COULD USE
A LITTLE REST, ESPECIALLY AFTER
THAT LAST BATTLE.
>> HUH!
WHAT ARE YOU GOING ON ABOUT,
SANGO?
I'M NOT LIKE YOU WEAKLING
HUMANS.
A LITTLE BATTLE HERE AND THERE
DOESN'T MAKE ME TIRED.
>> THAT'S JUST IT.
WE CAN'T KEEP UP WITH YOUR
ENERGY, AND YOU SHOULDN'T
EXPECT US TO.
>> SO YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO'S TIRED, NOT ME.
>> I UNDERSTAND.
NARAKU'S DEMONIC AURA REMAINS
HIDDEN AND AS ELUSIVE AS BEFORE.
[THINKING] I'VE HAD MY SOUL
COLLECTORS LOOK FOR THE MIASMA,
BUT THERE'S NOT EVEN A HINT
OF A BARRIER.
HOW HAS HE HIDDEN
SUCH A STRONG MIASMA?
>> DAMN.
>> GET THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD
FROM KOHAKU'S CORPSE.
>> [THINKING] I USED TO THINK
THIS KID WAS JUST A MINDLESS
PUPPET, YET HE REFUSED TO KILL
THE ABDUCTED GIRL.
NOR DID HE ALLOW HIMSELF
TO BE KILLED BY SESSHOMARU.
KOHAKU, LET ME ADVISE YOU THAT
IF YOU CONTINUE TO DEFY NARAKU,
YOU WON'T LIVE FOR MUCH LONGER.
[THINKING] NOT THAT I'M ONE
TO TALK.
>> [THINKING] NARAKU
DISAPPEARED, AND HE'S TAKEN
KOHAKU WITH HIM.
KOHAKU.
WHERE ARE YOU, MY BROTHER?
>> [MEOW]
>> HUH?
>> SANGO?
>> MIROKU.
>> SO, MIROKU'S GONE
TO WOO SANGO, THEN, HAS HE?
>> THAT HAS TO BE IT.
ACCORDING TO KAGOME,
THAT'S WHAT SANGO'S BEEN
SECRETLY WAITING FOR--
WHATEVER THAT MEANS.
>> KIRARA, CAN I SIT HERE?
I PRESUME YOU MUST BE VERY
WORRIED ABOUT YOUR BROTHER.
>> YES, I AM.
>> [MEOW]
>> IT'S EASIER SAID THAN DONE,
BUT DON'T WORRY YOURSELF
TOO MUCH.
>> HUH?
>> I UNDERSTAND WHAT YOU'RE
GOING THROUGH.
>> HMM.
>> YOU'D PROBABLY RATHER BE
ALONE, I SUPPOSE.
>> HUH?
YOU MEAN...IS THAT ALL?
>> IT'S JUST...I'VE COME TO KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE LIKE.
I THOUGHT AFTER GIVING ME
THE ENCOURAGEMENT, YOU WOULD TRY
SOMETHING LECHEROUS.
>> HMM.
SANGO, LISTEN.
YOU SHOULD HAVE TOLD ME SOONER
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANTED.
AAAAAHHH!
>> OH, MY.
>> OOH!
NICE CONTACT ON THAT ONE.
>> [THINKING] EVERYONE IS CRAZY
AROUND HERE!
>> I GUESS THERE'S NO OTHER WAY
BUT TO STUDY.
HUH?
AAH!
I DON'T UNDERSTAND A THING!
[THINKING] THERE'S ONLY
ONE THING TO DO.
HI. IS THIS SESKO?
YEAH. IT'S KAGOME HERE.
[THINKING] ASK SOMEONE ELSE.
OK, THANKS.
ALL RIGHT. BYE.
[HUMMING]
HUH?
YOU KNOW, I CAN'T REMEMBER WHY
I CALLED HER IN THE FIRST PLACE.
>> SIS, WHAT ABOUT
YOUR TEXTBOOK?
>> [THINKING] I HARDLY
ACCOMPLISHED A THING LAST NIGHT.
>> SIS, HEY.
HEY, WAIT UP!
>> DON'T TALK TO ME,
OR I'LL FORGET EVERYTHING
I MEMORIZED THIS MORNING.
TODAY'S MY LAST CHANCE
TO GET BACK ON TRACK!
>> SURPRISE! INUYASHA'S HERE.
>> YO.
>> AAH!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> YOU'RE LATE,
SO I CAME TO GET YOU.
ISN'T IT KIND OF OBVIOUS?
COME ON. LET'S GET GOING.
>> ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR MIND?
I'VE GOT AN IMPORTANT TEST
TOMORROW!
>> WHAT ARE YOU SO MAD ABOUT?
>> BYE! SEE YOU LATER!
>> LISTEN, DO NOT GO OUTSIDE,
WHATEVER YOU DO.
STAY PUT IN THE HOUSE
AND WAIT FOR ME.
UNDERSTAND?
>> HUMPH! ALL RIGHT. WHATEVER.
>> I'LL BE BACK AROUND
SUPPERTIME, SO SEE YOU THEN.
>> RIGHT.
>> HMM. WHERE'S KAGOME?
>> SHE LEFT ALREADY.
>> OH, DEAR.
I SPENT ALL MORNING MAKING THE
LUNCHES, AND SHE FORGOT HERS.
>> HUH? THAT'S A LUNCH?
>> WOULD YOU BE KIND ENOUGH
TO TAKE IT TO HER FOR ME?
>> HMM?
>> HERE.
>> [TALKING AT ONCE]
>> [SNIFFING]
[THINKING] HA HA HA!
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS FOLLOW
KAGOME'S SCENT, AND I'LL
CATCH UP TO HER RIGHT AWAY.
>> STOP! THIEF!
SOMEONE CATCH HIM!
>> HUH?
>> HOLD IT!
WHOA! UHH!
>> OUT OF MY WAY,
OR YOU'RE GONNA GET HURT!
>> [SCREAMING]
>> HUH?
YOU WANT TO DIE,
YOU LITTLE PUNK?
>> [GROWLING]
>> OOH! UHH!
[GROANING]
>> KAGOME'S WORLD IS A LOT
MORE DANGEROUS THAN I FIGURED
IT WOULD BE.
>> [GROANING]
[SIRENS]
>> NOW WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
>> [CRYING]
AAH!
>> HUH?
[PEOPLE SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
>> [TOGETHER] HUH?
>> HAH!
>> [GASP]
OH!
>> DON'T JUST STAND THERE.
COME ON!
HAH!
UH!
>> [GASP]
>> HUH?
>> OH.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER?
FUZZY EARS!
>> KNOCK IT OFF. STOP TOUCHING!
[GROWLS]
SEE YA.
>> HA HA HA!
DOGGIE MAN,
THANK YOU FOR SAVING ME!
>> MAN, THIS PLACE IS
ONE DISASTER AFTER ANOTHER.
HUMPH.
>> [SIGH]
HMM.
AAH!
UH...
>> SOMETHING THE MATTER, KAGOME?
>> UH, NOPE. DON'T MIND ME.
HEH HEH HEH.
[THINKING] I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
WHAT'S INUYASHA DOING HERE?
>> HMM?
>> UH...
AHEM.
>> HMM?
>> [GASP]
SIT!
>> AAH!
>> AH.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
HUH?
>> SIT, YOU SAY?
WELL, THEN, KAGOME,
WHY DON'T YOU STAND FOR US?
[LAUGHTER]
>> [THINKING] WHY DOES SHE
DO THIS TO ME?
>> WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
DIDN'T I MAKE IT CLEAR
THAT YOU WERE TO STAY HOME?
>> QUIT NAGGING.
IT WASN'T MY IDEA.
YOUR MOTHER ASKED ME TO COME.
>> MY MOM DID?
>> [GRUNTING]
YOU FORGOT THIS.
>> OH. THIS IS MY LUNCH.
[THINKING] HE WENT TO ALL THAT
TROUBLE TO BRING THIS TO ME.
HOLD ON, INUYASHA.
>> HUH?
>> WHY DON'T WE SHARE THIS?
UH...I SEE YOU ALREADY SHARED.
>> [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
>> I WON'T BE ABLE TO
CONCENTRATE AT HOME.
I'LL STAY IN THE LIBRARY
UNTIL SUPPERTIME.
I HAVE TO STUDY HARD,
OR I'M DOOMED!
>> HMM. OH, HI, KAGOME.
>> UH, HI, YOURSELF.
>> HOW IS THAT NEURALGIA
OF YOURS DOING?
>> NEVER FELT BETTER.
>> YOU'VE GOT TO TAKE CARE
OF YOURSELF.
YOU'RE STILL SO YOUNG.
>> HEH HEH HEH.
>> HERE.
I PUT TOGETHER SOME HEALTHY
RECIPES FOR YOU.
PROMISE YOU'LL GIVE THEM
A TRY, OK?
>> GEE, THANKS A LOT.
>> SEE YOU LATER.
>> [SIGH]
HE'S SURE THOUGHTFUL.
I'LL GIVE HIM THAT MUCH.
[GASP]
WAIT A SECOND.
[THINKING] WHY DIDN'T I
THINK OF IT EARLIER?
I CAN ASK HIM
FOR THE NOTES I NEED.
[PANTING]
I'VE GOT TO CATCH UP TO HIM.
HOJO, DON'T GO YET!
FOUND YOU.
>> OH, I JUST REMEMBERED.
A COUPLE MINUTES IN THE BLENDER,
AND THESE SHOULD WORK WONDERS
ON ALL KINDS OF AILMENTS.
>> [GASP]
HOW CONSIDERATE OF YOU.
>> LISTEN, KAGOME,
LIKE THEY SAY,
HEALTH IS MIND OVER MATTER.
LIVE A WHOLESOME LIFE,
AND MAKE SURE YOU EAT
3 SQUARE MEALS A DAY.
>> YEAH. RIGHT.
>> BYE!
MAKE SURE YOU EAT THOSE UP,
KAGOME!
>> I HAVE TO ASK YOU SOMETHING.
PLEASE COME BACK!
[SIGH]
HE'S GONE.
I'M HOME.
[THINKING] I COULDN'T BORROW
ANYONE'S NOTES.
>> HEY, KAGOME,
COME AND SEE SOMETHING.
>> HUH?
>> HA HA!
>> WHAT'S EVERYONE LOOKING AT?
>> ACCORDING TO REPORTS,
A STRANGE-LOOKING YOUTH IN A RED
KIMONO SINGLE-HANDEDLY CAPTURED
A BANK ROBBER.
>> WHAT'S THIS STORY ABOUT?
>> ON TOP OF THAT,
THIS STRANGE YOUNG MAN RESCUED
A CHILD TRAPPED IN A LOCAL
APARTMENT FIRE.
>> INUYASHA'S SO COOL.
>> HERE IS A DRAWING OF
HIS LIKENESS DONE BY THE CHILD.
>> [TOGETHER] HUH?!
>> HEY, THAT'S THE CAP
I WAS WEARING TODAY.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT. IT IS.
>> WHAT EXACTLY DID HE DO
ON THE WAY TO SCHOOL?
>> THIS IS THE STRANGEST BOX
I'VE EVER SEEN.
HMM.
>> [SIGH]
>> [SNIFFING]
HMM.
>> OH, YEAH, THIS IS HELPING
MY CONCENTRATION.
SIT, BOY.
SOTA, COME HERE A SEC.
>> WHAT IS IT, KAGOME?
>> KEEP INUYASHA COMPANY.
>> SURE THING.
I'LL SCRUB YOUR BACK
IF YOU'LL SCRUB MINE.
>> THANKS, SOTA.
NOW, THEN.
>> AAH! IT'S BOILING!
WHAT'S HE TRYING TO DO TO ME?
>> AAH!
>> COME ON.
YOU HAVE TO RINSE OFF THE SUDS.
>> I'M NOT GOING BACK IN THERE!
>> GET OUT!
GET OUT OF HERE!
UHH!
>> HEY! UHH!
>> OHH...
OH, NOW I'VE FORGOTTEN
EVERYTHING.
OH!
>> HUH?
>> WOULD YOU LIKE SOMETHING
TO EAT?
>> IT'S SURE QUIET
ALL OF A SUDDEN.
>> AAH! WHAT WAS THAT?
MY TONGUE'S ON FIRE!
>> I GAVE HIM SOME CURRY,
BUT MAYBE IT WAS TOO SPICY.
>> THAT'S SURPRISING,
COMING FROM A GUY WHO BLOWS OFF
A GAPING HOLE IN HIS GUT.
[SIGH]
YOU KNOW...
>> WHAT IS IT?
I'M KEEPING QUIET.
>> [THINKING] YEAH, BUT HOW AM I
SUPPOSED TO CONCENTRATE WITH YOU
STARING AT ME?
WHY DON'T YOU LIE DOWN?
>> NOT LIKELY.
NOW, TURN AROUND AND GET BACK
TO YOUR STUDIES.
WE'RE GOING BACK TOMORROW.
NO EXCUSES.
>> HA HA! OK.
[THINKING] IS HE ACTUALLY GONNA
SIT THERE AND WATCH OVER ME
ALL NIGHT?
I WOULDN'T PUT IT PAST HIM.
HE'S ALWAYS GOT ENERGY TO BURN.
HUH? HE'S ASLEEP.
>> [SNORING]
>> [THINKING] HUH!
WHAT'S WITH HIM?
HE BUGS ME CONSTANTLY,
AND HE CHOOSES NOW OF ALL TIMES
TO FLAKE OUT ON ME.
I'VE NEVER SEEN INUYASHA SLEEP
SO SOUNDLY.
I GUESS HE'S MORE TIRED
THAN THE REST OF US.
HAVE A GOOD SLEEP,
IF ONLY FOR THE NIGHT.
>> KAGOME AND INUYASHA ARE BACK.
>> OH.
SO, YOU SPENT THE NIGHT
AT KAGOME'S HOUSE, DID YOU?
>> WHAT'S WRONG, KAGOME?
WHERE ARE THE SMILES?
>> WHERE DO YOU THINK?
YOU WERE HOGGING THE WHOLE BED,
AND I DIDN'T GET A MINUTE'S
SLEEP.
ON TOP OF WHICH,
THE TEST WAS A KILLER.
MAN, MY LIFE STINKS!
>> A-AT LEAST IT'S SUNNY.
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
♪ EVERY HEART ♪
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> HERE'S A QUESTION.
BESIDES THE JEWEL SHARDS
NARAKU HAS IN HIS POSSESSION,
WHO ELSE HAS SOME,
AND HOW MANY DO THEY HAVE?
>> WELL, KOHAKU HAS ONE.
KAGOME HAS 3.
LET'S SEE.
>> TIME'S UP.
YOU FORGOT ABOUT KOGA,
WHO HAS ONE IN EACH LEG.
>> THAT MEANS NARAKU
WILL GO AFTER KOGA, TOO.
>> YES, EXCEPT THAT NARAKU
HAS DISAPPEARED.
>> THEN WHAT'S THAT?
>> NEXT TIME, "THE FEMALE
WOLF-DEMON AND THE LUNAR
RAINBOW PROMISE."
>> A FEMALE WOLF-DEMON? HA!
KOGA IS QUITE THE LADIES' MAN.