>> IT ALL STARTED WITH THE
SACRED TREE.
>> FIGHTING AND SEARCHING FOR
OUR DREAMS.
>> A STRONG BOND FORMS BETWEEN
US.
>> A NEW HOPE, A BRIGHT FUTURE
BEGINS NOW.
>> MIROKU AND SANGO VOWED TO
MARRY ONCE THE BATTLE AGAINST
NARAKU WAS FINISHED.
BUT IT'S NOT LONG BEFORE
MIROKU'S RELATIONSHIP WITH SANGO
WAS ON THE ROCKS.
ARE YOU GONNA LET IT END THIS
WAY, SANGO?
>> THE FINAL JEWEL SHARD GUIDES
US.
>> ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE
WELL, A NEW DAY AWAITS.
>> FEUDAL FAIRY TALE:
"INUYASHA."
>> MIROKU'S STILL DEPRESSED BY
THE SOUNDS OF IT.
>> WHAT, JUST BECAUSE A
PICKPOCKET STOLE HIS MONEY?
>> OH, HOW COULD I HAVE LET THIS
HAPPEN?
>> MIROKU...
I WISH YOU WOULDN'T TAKE IT SO
HARD.
>> SANGO...
I DON'T DESERVE SUCH KINDNESS.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT--
OH!
>> I JUST CAN'T HELP THE WAY I
AM SOMETIMES, SANGO.
>> MIROKU...
>> HMM.
>> DOESN'T LOOK TOO DEPRESSED TO
ME.
>> WHAT HE SAYS AND WHAT HE DOES
ARE OPPOSITES, AS USUAL.
>> THIS CHARM WAS GIVEN TO ME BY
A MAN OF HIGH PERSONAGE.
PLEASE ACCEPT THIS AND FIND
PEACE.
[GRUNTING]
>> IS THAT AN EARTHQUAKE?
>> MORE THAN THAT.
>> A DEMONIC AURA.
>> WE'D BETTER GO.
>> PLEASE FORGIVE US, MASTER.
HAVE MERCY!
>> WHAT SEEMS TO BE THE MATTER?
>> HUH?
>> YOU AND YOUR FRIENDS SEEMS TO
BE TROUBLED BY SOME KIND OF EVIL
PRESENCE.
IS THERE ANYTHING WE CAN DO TO
BE OF HELP?
>> MONK MIROKU, IS THAT YOU?
>> HMM?
>> OH, MONK MIROKU, HAVE YOU
COME TO FULFILL YOUR PROMISE TO
MARRY MY DAUGHTER AND MOVE IN?
>> MOVE IN AND MARRY?
>> MONK MIROKU HAS RETURNED!
BEGIN THE PREPARATIONS!
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> GOOD QUESTION.
>> YOU MEAN YOU DON'T REMEMBER?
>> HA!
HE'S MADE WAY MORE PROMISES THAN
HE COULD POSSIBLY REMEMBER.
>> MASTER MIROKU!
I'VE WAITED SO LONG TO SEE YOU.
>> OH!
>> HELLO, SHIMA.
HOW LOVELY YOU'VE BECOME.
>> THANK YOU.
>> STAY CALM.
>> THIS ALL HAPPENED IN THE
PAST, RIGHT?
>> YES.
BOTH MY WIFE AND I HAD GIVEN UP
HOPE, BELIEVING IT WAS A THING
OF THE PAST.
OUR DAUGHTER SHIMA WAS ALWAYS
SICKLY AND FRAIL.
THERE WAS NEVER A DAY WHEN SHE
COULD EVEN LIFT HER HEAD FROM A
PILLOW.
THAT'S WHEN MIROKU PASSED
THROUGH THE VILLAGE.
THIS WAS 2 YEARS AGO NOW.
>> NOW BOIL THESE MEDICINAL
HERBS IN CLEAN WATER AND DRINK
THE LIQUID EVERY DAY.
>> AND, AS ONE WOULD EXPECT FROM
SUCH COSTLY MEDICINE, IT
COMPLETELY CURED HER!
>> IT CERTAINLY WAS EXPENSIVE
MEDICINE, THOUGH.
>> HE SWINDLED THEM.
>> AND THE 2 OF YOU BECAME FAST
FRIENDS?
>> NO.
>> MIROKU GAVE US THE MEDICINAL
HERBS THEN VANISHED ALMOST AS
SUDDENLY AS HE HAD APPEARED.
>> HEAR THAT?
INNOCENT OF ANY WRONG DOINGS.
>> EXCEPT...
>> EXCEPT?
I HOPE WHEN YOU ARE WELL, YOU
WOULD CONSIDER BEARING MY CHILD,
SHIMA.
>> YES!
2 THINGS KEPT ME GOING.
THE EXPENSIVE MEDICINAL HERB AND
THE PROMISE I MADE TO MONK
MIROKU.
THAT'S HOW I COMPLETELY
RECOVERED.
>> SEE?
YOU WERE TRYING TO SEDUCE HER!
>> IT'S OK.
AFTER ALL, IT WAS A THING OF THE
PAST.
>> SO BIG DEAL.
IT DIDN'T MATTER THEN AND IT
DOESN'T MATTER NOW.
>> IT IS A BIG DEAL.
>> ISN'T THE EVIL SPIRIT THE
REASON WE'RE HERE?
>> HE'S RIGHT.
TELL US MORE ABOUT THE INCIDENT
EARLIER AT THE SHRINE.
>> FEELS LIKE ANOTHER
EARTHQUAKE.
>> MIROKU, I'M SO SCARED.
>> HUH?
I'M SCARED, TOO, BUT FOR A WHOLE
DIFFERENT REASON.
>> MIROKU, PLEASE DO WHATEVER
YOU CAN TO HELP US.
>> IF NOTHING IS DONE, OUR
DAUGHTER WILL END UP THE WIFE OF
A DEMON.
>> SHIMA'S TO MARRY A DEMON?
>> YES, YES!
THE SHRINE YOU SAW IS DEDICATED
TO THE MASTER OF THE LAKE, AND
MASTER HAS DEMANDED SHIMA TO BE
HIS WIFE.
>> I'VE TRIED TO EXPLAIN TO HIM
THAT I AM BETROTHED, BUT HE
REFUSES TO BELIEVE ME.
>> HMM.
SO SHIMA, WHO WOULD YOUR
BETROTHED BE?
>> THAT'D BE YOU; WHO ELSE?
>> HUH.
>> MIROKU, I'M SO DELIGHTED THAT
YOU REMEMBERED OUR PROMISE AND
RETURNED TO THE VILLAGE AFTER
ALL THIS TIME.
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW I'VE WAITED
FOR THIS DAY TO COME.
>> AH.
RIGHT, I UNDERSTAND.
IN ANY CASE, WE WON'T HAND YOU
OVER TO BECOME THE BRIDE OF THIS
DEMON.
>> YOU MEAN YOU WILL HELP US?
>> CERTAINLY I'LL HELP.
>> THEN LET US PREPARE THE
CEREMONY RIGHT AWAY.
>> I THOUGHT THEY WANTED MIROKU
TO DESTROY THE DEMON.
>> THAT'S JUST PART OF THE DEAL.
THE OTHER IS THAT SHE SEEMS SET
ON HAVING MIROKU'S CHILD.
[LAUGHING]
>> SHIMA!
TONIGHT IS OUR PROMISED NIGHT.
>> ACHOO!
>> IT'S FREEZING.
>> HOW COME MIROKU IS THE ONLY
ONE WHO GETS TO BE INSIDE?
IT'S NOT FAIR.
>> DON'T KNOW.
HE SAID HE WAS GOING IN TO
SETTLE THIS WHOLE THING.
>> DOES THAT MEAN HE'S GONNA
TURN DOWN THE MARRIAGE?
>> HE'D BETTER TURN IT DOWN.
HE'S ALREADY PROMISED TO
MARRY SANGO, RIGHT?
>> YOU SURE YOU CAN TRUST HIM IN
THERE?
YOU KNOW WHAT HE'S LIKE.
ONLY A FOOL REFUSES A WOMAN WHO
OFFERS HERSELF.
>> INUYASHA, SIT!
FIRST OF ALL, WHERE DID YOU GET
SUCH A FILTHY SAYING?!
AND SECOND, CAN'T YOU BE A
LITTLE MORE CONSIDERATE OF
OTHERS?
>> I'M SECOND?
>> I'D LIKE YOU TO MARRY MY
DAUGHTER AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
THE FEWER DELAYS, THE BETTER.
>> BUT THE MASTER OF THE LAKE
WHO DESIRES SHIMA AS HIS BRIDE
IS A DEMON, CORRECT?
IF THAT'S THE CASE, HE'LL COME
AFTER HER WHETHER SHE'S MARRIED
OR NOT.
I CAN'T SEE HOW A WEDDING WILL
CHANGE THINGS.
>> NO, THAT'S JUST IT.
>> HUH?
>> THE MASTER OF THE LAKE WANTS
A VIRGIN TO TAKE AS HIS BRIDE.
SO IF A MARRIAGE CEREMONY IS
HELD, WE THINK HE'LL MOST LIKELY
GIVE UP ON HER.
>> REALLY?
HOW VERY NOBLE OF HIM.
>> PLEASE DO AS MY FATHER WISHES
AND MAKE ME YOUR WIFE BEFORE THE
DEMON COMES FOR ME.
>> HMM?
BUT SHIMA...
>> ONLY A FOOL REFUSES A
WOMAN WHO OFFERS HERSELF.
>> HA HA.
GOOD POINT.
HA HA.
[ROARING]
>> MIROKU.
>> IT'S--IT'S A GHOST!
>> SHIPPOU, WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
>> HUH?
NO!
I WAS JUST TRYING TO LET HIM
KNOW HOW YOU WERE FEELING.
I DIDN'T MEAN ANYTHING.
>> I'M NOT UPSET ABOUT IT.
>> HUH?
>> SORRY TO INTERRUPT YOU.
I KNOW YOU'RE BUSY.
DROP DEAD, IDIOT.
>> IT WAS AS THOUGH HER EYES
WERE SAYING TO ME, "DROP DEAD,
IDIOT."
>> MIROKU, PLEASE TELL ME.
>> WHO WAS THAT WOMAN JUST NOW?
>> WELL, ACTUALLY...
>> ANOTHER EARTHQUAKE.
>> HA, AND SOMETHING THAT REEKS
LIKE FISH IS COMING.
LOOKS LIKE THIS MASTER OF THE
LAKE IS ABOUT TO MAKE HIS GRAND
ENTRANCE.
>> OK.
>> GREETINGS.
I AM THE MASTER OF THE LAKE.
I HAVE COME FOR SHIMA, AS WE
AGREED SOME TIME BACK.
>> THAT'S WHAT HE SAYS.
>> HE'S THE MASTER OF THE LAKE?
>> YEP, STRAIGHT FROM THE FISH'S
MOUTH.
>> HMM.
>> GET OUT OF HERE.
>> YOU!
WHY DO YOU INTERFERE?
>> THE GIRL SAYS SHE DOESN'T
WANT YOU.
>> MASTER, IT'S YOU!
>> MIROKU, I'M FRIGHTENED.
>> YOU'RE ACTUALLY AFRAID OF
THAT?
>> SHIMA!
>> STOP!
>> SEE?
GIVE IT UP, FISH.
>> I DON'T GET IT.
SHE PROMISED TO BE MY BRIDE!
SO WHY IS SHE BACKING OUT NOW?
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN PROMISED?
>> I NEVER PROMISED YOU
ANYTHING.
>> PLEASE FORGIVE US, MASTER OF
THE LAKE.
>> FATHER, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> TO BE HONEST, IN ORDER TO
MAKE THAT EXPENSIVE HERB TEA...
>> NOT BOIL THESE MEDICINAL
HERBS IN CLEAN WATER AND DRINK
THE LIQUID EVERY DAY.
>> I USED THE WATER FROM THE
LAKE.
AND AT THE SAME TIME EVERY DAY,
I PRAYED AT THE SHRINE BY THE
LAKE.
MASTER OF THE LAKE, I BEG OF
YOU, PLEASE BRING MY DAUGHTER
BACK TO HEALTH.
I WILL DO ANYTHING IN RETURN.
I NEVER IMAGINED THAT YOU WERE
ACTUALLY LISTENING TO MY
PRAYERS.
>> OH, THAT'S WHY HE ASKED FOR
SHIMA AS HIS BRIDE, IN RETURN
FOR CURING HER.
>> I THINK THERE'S AN APOLOGY
COMING MY WAY?
HUH?
>> I FEEL A BIT SORRY FOR THE
GUY, ACTUALLY.
>> I HAD NO IDEA.
MY DEAR FATHER, YOU DID THAT FOR
ME?
>> SHIMA, FORGIVE ME.
>> OF COURSE.
YOU DID WHAT YOU FELT YOU HAD TO
DO OUT OF A DESIRE TO SAVE ME.
BUT STILL, IT'S TOO LATE TO
CHANGE THINGS.
EVEN IF YOU DIDN'T KNOW HE WAS
LISTENING, A PROMISE IS A
PROMISE.
>> OHO!
LET'S DO IT!
>> SHIMA, NO!
>> COME ON, YOU'RE NOT SERIOUS.
YOU'RE GONNA BE A DEMON'S BRIDE?
>> MASTER.
[GIGGLING]
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
I AM NOT FIT TO BECOME YOUR
WIFE.
>> WHY?
>> IF WHAT I HAVE HEARD IS TRUE,
IT IS A VIRGIN YOU WISH TO TAKE
AS YOUR BRIDE, MASTER.
I MUST ADMIT SOMETHING THAT
HAPPENED 2 YEARS AGO.
I GAVE MYSELF TO MIROKU, THE
MONK STANDING BEFORE YOU.
>> ARE YOU TELLING US THE TRUTH,
SHIMA?
>> I'M SO SORRY, FATHER.
BUT I JUST COULDN'T BRING MYSELF
TO TELL YOU.
>> I FIGURED AS MUCH.
>> WE ALL DID, BUT IT'S STILL A
SHOCK WHEN SOMEBODY ADMITS IT.
>> IT'S OK.
IT'S ALL IN THE PAST, AFTER ALL.
>> PLEASE, MASTER, AS YOU HEARD,
MY DAUGHTER'S UNFIT.
>> PLEASE RELEASE ME FROM THIS
ARRANGEMENT.
>> YOU PEOPLE!
YOU DECEIVED ME!
[CRYING]
>> HUH?
AHH!
>> A CATFISH?
>> NOW YOU WILL FEEL MY WRATH!
>> OUR HOUSE WILL BE CRUSHED.
>> MIROKU, PLEASE SAVE US.
>> DON'T WORRY.
WE'LL DEAL WITH THE FISH DEMON.
LET'S DO IT, SANGO.
>> DEAL WITH THIS ON YOUR OWN.
IT WAS YOUR INDISCRETION THAT
CAUSED THIS.
>> OH, MIROKU, IS THIS LADY
GONNA TRANSFORM, TOO, LIKE THE
MASTER OF THE LAKE DID?
>> NO.
THIS LADY'S NOT A DEMON.
>> COME ON.
THIS IS NO TIME TO FIGHT.
>> NOT OUR HOME!
>> OVER HERE, SLIMY.
I'LL TAKE YOU ON.
>> I'LL SWALLOW YOU WHOLE!
>> SANGO, LET ME EXPLAIN.
>> DON'T COME NEAR ME.
I DON'T THINK THINGS ARE
GOING TO WORK OUT.
>> NOT WORK OUT?
>> WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN TO THE 2
OF THEM THIS TIME?
>> EXCUSE ME, KAGOME.
SHOULDN'T WE BE PAYING ATTENTION
TO INUYASHA AND THE GIANT
CATFISH?
>> YOU MADE A FOOL OUT OF ME!
>> TELL SOMEONE WHO CARES!
>> WHO ARE YOU?
>> HAVEN'T HAD ENOUGH?
FINE BY ME.
[GROANING]
>> SHIMA.
I HAD FAITH IN YOU.
>> HE'S CALMED DOWN.
>> HE STOPPED, BUT WHAT DOES IT
MEAN?
HAS THE MASTER GIVEN UP ON THE
IDEA OF TAKING ME AS HIS BRIDE?
>> THAT WAS EASY.
>> YEAH.
AND I WOULDN'T SLEEP IF I KILLED
A DEMON LIKE THAT.
>> YEAH, BUT GUYS, THINGS ARE
REALLY STARTING TO HEAT UP WITH
THE LOVEBIRDS.
>> WHAT?
ARE THOSE 2 STILL AT IT?
>> SANGO...
WON'T YOU EVEN LISTEN TO WHAT I
HAVE TO SAY?
>> I DON'T KNOW ANYMORE.
>> COME ON.
>> HUH?
>> YOU MAKE IT SEEM LIKE
MIROKU'S WOMANIZING IS SOMETHING
THAT JUST STARTED HAPPENING
RECENTLY.
>> INUYASHA!
>> WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
>> JEEZ!
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND ANYTHING,
DO YOU?
IMAGINE HOW BAD SHE FEELS SEEING
THE WOMEN FROM HIS PAST.
OF COURSE SHE'S GONNA BE UPSET.
WHO COULD BLAME HER?
>> EXCUSE ME, BUT I WISH YOU'D
STOP FIGHTING.
>> OH, SHIMA.
>> THIS WHOLE THING IS ALL MY
FAULT.
PLEASE DON'T BLAME MIROKU FOR
ANY WRONGDOING.
>> SANGO!
>> DON'T FOLLOW ME.
>> MIROKU, AREN'T YOU GONNA GO
AFTER HER?
>> SHE WOULDN'T LISTEN TO ME
RIGHT NOW, NO MATTER WHAT I HAD
TO SAY.
IT'S SAD.
DEEP DOWN, SHE DIDN'T TRUST ME.
IT'S GUT WRENCHING REALIZING
THAT YOU'RE NOT BELIEVED.
MY HEART IS SET ON ONE PERSON,
AND ONE PERSON ALONE.
>> HUH?
>> IF I DIDN'T KNOW ANY BETTER,
I'D THINK HE'D BEEN FALSELY
ACCUSED.
>> I WAS FALSELY ACCUSED.
>> AAH, HELP ME!
>> SHIMA, I STILL WANT YOU!
>> HE'S TAKEN HER.
>> PLEASE LET ME GO!
>> NEVER!
WE WILL LIVE TOGETHER AT THE
BOTTOM OF THE LAKE.
>> DAMMIT.
I KNEW I SHOULD HAVE FINISHED
HIM OFF WHEN I HAD THE CHANCE.
>> WE HAVE TO SAVE HER.
>> MIROKU ISN'T COMING AFTER ME.
WHAT'LL I DO NOW?
HUH?
>> AAH!
>> YOU'LL MARRY ME NO MATTER
WHAT!
>> WHY?
I TOLD YOU THAT I GAVE MYSELF TO
MIROKU.
YOU HEARD ME!
>> I'LL FORGIVE YOU.
I'LL FORGET ABOUT YOUR PAST.
>> NO!
HEY, YOU'RE WOMAN THAT WAS WITH
MIROKU.
>> SANGO!
>> MIROKU, IT'S YOU!
>> IT'S NOT ME THAT HE'S COMING
AFTER.
>> KILALA, QUICKLY TAKE THE GIRL
AWAY TO SOMEPLACE SAFE.
HIRIKOS!
>> HE DEFLECTED THE HIRIKOS.
[LAUGHING]
>> WOMAN.
I'LL TAKE YOU TO THE BOTTOM OF
THE LAKE, TOO, MAKE YOU MY
MISTRESS.
>> THE HELL YOU WILL!
THERE'S NO WAY YOU'LL TAKE MY
WOMAN FOR YOUR MISTRESS.
>> SILENCE!
>> HA.
WE'RE IN THE WATER, FOOL.
DO YOU HONESTLY THINK YOU CAN
CATCH ME?
>> OH, I DON'T NEED TO CATCH
YOU.
GET A TASTE OF THIS.
WIND TUNNEL!
[GROANING]
>> HUH?
>> THE WATER.
IT'S DISAPPEARING.
>> WATER.
>> CURSE YOU!
>> LISTEN UP, CATFISH.
DON'T YOU DARE MESS WITH MY GIRL
AGAIN, YOU GOT THAT STRAIGHT?
>> WHAT?
YOU MEAN SHE IS ONE OF YOUR
WOMEN, TOO?
OH, I'M SO VERY SORRY.
>> QUIET YOU.
SANGO, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
HEY, SANGO!
COME ON, SANGO, WAIT.
PLEASE.
SANGO.
HELLO?
I KNOW YOU CAN HEAR ME.
COME ON, SANGO.
>> GUESS I'M NOT NEEDED HERE...
FOR ONCE.
>> MIROKU.
I SUPPOSE IT TURNED OUT TO BE A
CASE OF UNREQUITED LOVE.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
I'M SORRY I LIED.
>> YOU LIED ABOUT THE WHOLE
THING?
ABOUT GIVING YOURSELF TO MIROKU?
>> YES.
I GUESS I DIDN'T WANT TO WED THE
CATFISH, SO...
>> IT WAS THE ONLY THING SHIMA
COULD THINK OF TO DISSUADE HIM
AT THE TIME.
>> IF THAT'S THE CASE, WHY
DIDN'T YOU JUST TELL ME THE
TRUTH RIGHT FROM THE VERY
BEGINNING?
YOU COULD HAVE.
>> WELL, I SUPPOSE I WAS TOO
NAIVE, SANGO.
I THOUGHT YOU'D KNOW WITHOUT MY
EXPLAINING IT.
>> OH, MIROKU...
>> NO, IT'S MY FAULT FOR BEING
SUCH A WOMANIZER ALL THE TIME.
I'M SORRY I HURT YOU SO BADLY,
SANGO.
HONESTLY.
>> NEVER MIND.
BESIDES, WHEN YOU CAME TO MY
RESCUE...
I DON'T KNOW, I WAS JUST SO
GLAD.
>> WILL YOU FORGIVE ME THEN,
SANGO?
>> I SHOULD BE ASKING YOU THAT.
>> AND THAT'S IT?
>> YOU KNOW, SANGO REALLY DOES
HAVE A BIG HEART.
>> IN SOME WAYS, IT'S BIGGER
THAN YOURS, KAGOME.
>> HUH?
HMM.
YOU 2 MAKE A FINE MATCH.
>> HMM.
>> I WAS JUST THINKING, IF HE
HAD ONLY TOLD HER THE TRUTH
SOONER, NONE OF THIS WOULD HAVE
HAPPENED.
>> JUST A SECOND.
HEY, MIROKU.
MAYBE IT JUST TOOK YOU A LONG
TIME TO REMEMBER WHAT WAS WHAT.
>> THAT'S A BULL'S EYE.
>> IS THAT TRUE?
WELL?
IS THAT IT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
IT JUST HAPPENED SO LONG AGO.
[MUSIC]
>> WHAT'S WRONG, JACQUES?
>> RENNE'S...BY A DEMON!
>> A GROUP OF MONKS WHO
SPECIALIZE IN SLAYING DEMONS
WENT TO SAVE HER, BUT...
>> THOSE MONKS...
THINGS COULD GET UGLY IF THEY
COME ACROSS SESSHOMARU.
>> IF THE HUMANS TRY THEIR
HALF-BAKED SPELLS, SESSHOMARU
WILL TEAR THEM APART.
>> I'M NOT SCARED.
>> NEXT TIME, "FOREVER WITH LORD
SESSHOMARU."
>> LORD SESSHOMARU, PLEASE
DON'T FORGET ME, EVEN IF I DIE.