>> HERE WE COME!
IT'S THE START OF "INUYASHA."
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL THE
SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY NARAKU
WITH MY TETSUSAIGA.
>> AS WE SEARCH FOR THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARDS, IT'S AS IF WE'RE
ALL BEING LURED TOGETHER.
MEANWHILE, SESSHOMARU IS
ASSAILED BY JAKOTSU AND
SUIKOTSU, AND BANKOTSU AND
KIKYO MEET.
>> IT'S UP TO ALL OF US.
>> TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FEUDAL FAIRY TALE.
>> "INUYASHA."
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> MT. HAKUREI.
I KNOW FOR CERTAIN
THAT NARAKU IS THERE.
THE QUESTION IS, WHY?
[SWALLOWING]
>> AHH.
KYOKOTSU,
MUKOTSU, HOW DOES IT FEEL TO BE
BACK IN THE OTHER WORLD AGAIN?
>> THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
ONCE YOU'RE DEAD, YOU'RE DEAD.
THAT'S THE END OF IT.
THERE'S NO SUCH THING AS AN
AFTERLIFE.
>> HMM?
THAT MAN.
>> WOMAN, ARE YOU THE
ONE THEY CALL KIKYO?
>> AND YOU ARE WITH THE
BAND OF 7?
>> [CHUCKLES]
>> WAIT!
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT OF ME?
>> JUST CURIOUS.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO KILL ME,
ARE YOU NOT?
>> HA HA HA HA.
I DON'T KNOW.
NARAKU NEVER GAVE ME ORDERS
TO DO SO.
AHH.
I'VE HEARD THE RUMORS ABOUT YOU.
STILL, I WOULD NEVER HAVE
GUESSED YOU'D BE SO BEAUTIFUL.
YOU WANT TO TAKE ME ON, DO YOU?
ALL RIGHT, THEN, LET'S DO IT.
I ACCEPT YOUR CHALLENGE.
>> HIS SACRED JEWEL
SHARDS EMIT A TAINTED BLACK
LIGHT, UNLIKE SUIKOTSU'S
CLEAR ONE.
DOES THAT MEAN HE HAS BEEN
COMPLETELY OVERTAKEN
BY THE DARKNESS?
>> WHAT'S STOPPING YOU?
COME ON, TAKE THE FIRST SHOT.
>> I WANT TO KNOW WHAT IT IS
YOU'RE AFTER.
WHY DO YOU CONTINUE TO KILL,
EVEN AFTER BEING RESURRECTED?
WHAT REASON COULD YOU POSSIBLY
HAVE FOR DOING SO?
>> NOW THAT'S A STRANGE
QUESTION.
I DON'T NEED ANY REASON FOR
KILLING PEOPLE.
I HAVE ALWAYS BEEN THIS WAY,
BEFORE MY DEATH AND AFTER BEING
REVIVED.
>> IN THE WORLD WE LIVE IN, IT'S
SOMETIMES NECESSARY TO KILL IN
ORDER TO SURVIVE, BUT YOU DIED
ONCE, SO WHY NOT STOP
YOUR EVIL WRONGDOINGS?
>> HA!
I'M A MERCENARY THROUGH AND
THROUGH, AND WHAT I DO IS
THOROUGHLY ENJOYABLE.
PEOPLE TALK ABOUT HEAVEN AND
HELL ALL THE TIME, BUT ONCE A
MORTAL IS DEAD,
THAT'S THE END OF IT.
I HAVE NO INTERESTS IN THE
SO-CALLED OTHER WORLDS.
I DO AS I PLEASE WITH NO FEAR OF
THE AFTERLIFE.
>> YOU SAY THAT TO CONVINCE
YOURSELF, DON'T YOU?
IT'S PATHETIC.
TRYING TO MAKE EXCUSES FOR YOUR
WICKED ACTIONS.
>> I KNOW ONE THING, KIKYO.
DEAD PEOPLE LIKE YOU AND I WILL
PROBABLY SHARE THE SAME FATE.
YOU SHOULD WORRY ABOUT YOURSELF.
DON'T BE SO CONCERNED ABOUT THE
CHOICES I MAKE.
WELL, IT DOESN'T REALLY MATTER.
LET'S JUST BOTH ENJOY THE TIME
WE HAVE HERE ON EARTH.
>> SO WE SHARE THE FATE
OF THE DEAD, DO WE?
THEN I WILL SEE WHERE IT GOES.
>> I ASSUME YOU'RE ONE
OF NARAKU'S FOLLOWERS.
>> [CHUCKLES]
HOW VERY PERCEPTIVE OF YOU.
>> JUST LIKE THAT POISON USER.
YOU REEK OF A DEAD MORTAL.
>> MY, WHAT A KEEN SENSE OF
SMELL, JUST WHAT I'D EXPECT FROM
INUYASHA'S OLDER BROTHER!
>> HM!
>> [GASPS] AAH!
UHH.
THAT WAS A CLOSE CALL.
>> [LAUGHS] SILLY MORTAL!
SPARE YOURSELF THE SUFFERING,
AND LET HIM SLAY YOU QUICKLY!
>> AAH!
>> YOU TALKING TO ME, IMP?
WELL?
>> WHO ARE YOU CALLING IMP?
>> HA HA HA HA.
WATCH THIS.
>> JAKEN.
>> YES, ME LORD?
THIS WAY, RIN, HURRY.
>> WAIT! WHAT ABOUT--
>> THERE'S NOTHING WE CAN DO
HERE...EXCEPT
STAY OUT OF LORD SESSHOMARU'S
WAY!
>> HMM, SO YOU DON'T WANT THE
LITTLE GIRL TO GET IN HARM'S
WAY.
WELL, AREN'T YOU JUST THE
KINDEST THING AROUND.
>> HA.
YOU TALK A GREAT DEAL FOR A
DEAD MORTAL.
>> I'M GETTING TIRED OF YOU
HARPING ON ME ABOUT BEING DEAD!
OH, NEVER MIND.
WITH THE GIRL GONE, AT LEAST
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO CONCENTRATE
ON OUR BATTLE.
COME ON, LET'S DO IT!
>> I'M WORRIED ABOUT LORD
SESSHOMARU.
THINK HE'LL BE ALL RIGHT?
>> FOOL, HE WOULD NEVER SUCCUMB
TO THE ATTACKS OF A MERE MORTAL.
>> YOU MIGHT, THOUGH, MASTER
JAKEN.
>> WATCH YOUR TONGUE, LITTLE
GIRL.
I AM A DEMON, TOO, REMEMBER?
I WOULD NEVER FALL AT THE HANDS
OF A HUMAN!
HMM. HUH?
>> HUH?
>> HUH? WHAT'S THIS?
OH! [MOANING]
HE LOOKS TERRIBLY STRONG.
>> HERE'S MY [INDISTINCT].
HANG ON TO YOUR HAT,
OR I'LL LOP IT OFF.
HA HA HA HA!
>> AAH!
>> YOU WON'T BE ABLE
TO ESCAPE ME.
>> RIN?
FLEE AT ONCE!
>> [GRUNTING]
>> LORD SESSHOMARU
WOULD KILL ME IF ANYTHING
WERE TO HAPPEN TO RIN.
I MUST PROTECT HER.
STAFF OF TWO HEADS.
>> [GASP]
>> [MOANING]
>> HA HA HA, SO MUCH FOR
THAT THREAT!
>> YES, BUT THE BRIDGE,
MASTER JAKEN.
THE WHOLE THING'S
GOING TO COLLAPSE!
>> OOH, HURRY UP, BACK TO THE
CLIFF!
>> UHH!
>> HUH?
HE'S ALIVE!
>> YOU CAN'T GET RID OF ME
THAT EASILY.
>> [MOANING]
>> DON'T JUST STAND THERE, RIN,
MOVE IT!
BACK, BACK!
>> [YELLING]
>> OH.
>> HMM.
>> I HEARD THAT GIRL WAS HIS
WEAKNESS.
MY PLAN WAS TO KIDNAP THE KID
AND USE HER AS A HOSTAGE.
I NEVER THOUGHT HE'D LEAVE
HIMSELF WIDE OPEN FOR ME.
>> AAH!
HA!
IT'S ONLY JUST THE BEGINNING!
NOW I'VE GOT YOU!
YES!
[GASP]
HE DEFLECTED MY JAKOTSU
SWORD AND FLUNG IT BACK AT ME.
>> HMM, THAT WAS CLOSE, BUT NOT
CLOSE ENOUGH.
>> [GASP]
OH!
HE'S DEADLY.
KILLED BY HIS BROTHER ON MY WAY
TO KILL INUYASHA.
I COULDN'T LIVE WITH MYSELF
IF THAT HAPPENED.
OH, WE WOULDN'T WANT THAT,
WOULD WE, INUYASHA?
>> UHH. UHH.
>> HOW FAR ARE WE GOING, ANYWAY?
HELLO!
COULD YOU AT LEAST ANSWER ME?
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW FAR.
I'M JUST GOING TO KEEP GOING
UNTIL I FIND A SAFE PLACE TO
TAKE THIS MANGY WOLF.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING THAT FOR?
>> THE BAND OF 7 IS AFTER THE
SHIKON JEWEL SHARDS IN KOGA'S
LEGS.
WHO KNOWS WHEN THOSE FREAKS ARE
GOING TO COME AFTER HIM AGAIN?
>> YEAH, I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE SHOULDN'T HANG AROUND.
>> COME ON, HURRY UP, WILL YA?
>> YOU HEAR THAT, KIRARA?
[SNARLS]
>> UHH.
>> SHE MUST HAVE BEEN
CARRIED DOWNSTREAM.
THE WATER HAS WASHED AWAY HER
SCENT.
>> [MOANING]
[MOANING]
>> JAKEN.
>> [MOANING]
ARE YOU PRETENDING TO BE DEAD,
JAKEN?
>> [STAMMERING]
PLEASE FORGIVE ME,
LORD SESSHOMARU!
I PROMISE I SHALL FIND RIN,
EVEN IF IT COSTS MY LIFE!
HUH?
MY LORD?
[STAMMERING]
WAIT FOR ME, MY LORD.
I'M COMING!
YOU ARE ANGRY, AFTER ALL.
>> [MOANING]
>> WELL, NOW.
I SEE THAT YOU'RE AWAKE.
>> HUH?
[MOANING]
>> WHAT IS IT?
WHY DO YOU RUN?
DO NOT FEAR ME, CHILD.
I AM A PHYSICIAN.
>> HUH?
HE'S NOT LIKE THE OTHER MAN.
HE'S CHANGED.
>> I SEE.
YOU WERE WITH COMPANIONS.
>> YES.
I'M SURE THEY'LL COME LOOKING
FOR ME, THOUGH.
THAT'S WHY I DON'T THINK IT'S A
VERY GOOD IDEA TO MOVE TOO FAR
AWAY FROM HERE.
>> THIS FOREST IS DANGEROUS.
YOU SHOULD STAY WITH ME UNTIL WE
MEET UP WITH YOUR FRIENDS.
>> ALL RIGHT.
HE DOESN'T SEEM LIKE A BAD MAN.
>> THERE'S NOTHING HERE.
>> NO, I DON'T SENSE ANY DEMONIC
AURA, EITHER.
>> DO YOU REALLY THINK NARAKU
IS AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE?
>> I CAN'T SAY FOR SURE, BUT OUR
ONLY CHOICE IS TO KEEP SEARCHING
FOR HIM.
>> HMM.
>> BEING SEPARATED FROM INUYASHA
LIKE THIS, YOU REALLY DO FEEL
GRATEFUL FOR HIS PRESENCE.
>> HE'S CONVENIENT TO HAVE
AROUND, ESPECIALLY HIS SENSE OF
SMELL.
>> IF WE LET HIM, HE'D SPEND THE
ENTIRE NIGHT RUNNING AROUND
SEARCHING FOR NARAKU.
HUH?
HEY, SANGO, SEE THAT
CAVE UP THERE?
>> YEAH.
LET'S CHECK IT OUT.
>> HER AGAIN.
I HOPE SHE LEAVES WITHOUT
NOTICING ANYTHING.
I DON'T WANT TO HAVE TO
FIGHT HER.
>> HUH?
YOU'RE A DOCTOR IN THE VILLAGE?
>> YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
I LIVE IN A HOUSE AT THE BASE OF
MT. HAKUREI.
I THINK YOU'LL LIKE IT THERE.
THERE ARE MANY CHILDREN ABOUT
YOUR AGE IN THE VILLAGE, AND
THEY DON'T HAVE PARENTS, EITHER.
>> OH.
>> THERE IT IS OVER THERE.
THAT'S WHERE I LIVE.
>> I SENSE THE PRESENCE
OF A JEWEL SHARD.
IT'S APPROACHING THE VILLAGE.
THE SHARD SEEMS DIFFERENT FROM
THE MAN I MET EARLIER.
IT'S...
IT'S SUIKOTSU, BUT THIS PRESENCE
IS DIFFERENT.
>> ♪ PURE HAS BECOME IMPURE,
IMPURE HAS NOW BECOME PURE,
GOOD HAS NOW BECOME BAD ♪
HMM?
>> I HAVE RETURNED.
>> [GASP] DR. SUIKOTSU!
>> HUH?
>> I HOPE YOU CAN ALL FORGIVE
ME.
I WAS GONE A LONG TIME.
>> DR. SUIKOTSU,
IS THAT REALLY YOU?
>> OF COURSE IT IS.
WHY, IS SOMETHING THE MATTER?
>> MMM.
>> OH, HOW RUDE OF ME.
THIS GIRL WITH ME IS NAMED RIN.
BE NICE TO HER AND SHOW HER
AROUND, WOULD YOU?
SHE'S OUR SPECIAL GUEST.
>> OH, THIS ISN'T WORKING OUT.
THAT DAMN SUIKOTSU, HE'S
RETURNED TO HIS FORMER SELF.
GOOD THING I DECIDED
TO STICK AROUND.
MY HUNCH WAS RIGHT.
OH, WELL, THEN.
I'LL JUST HAVE TO OPEN HIS EYES.
HUH?
>> I TOLD YOU IT WAS DR.
SUIKOTSU.
>> HE REALLY HAS RETURNED.
>> MY GOOD MEN,
WHAT BRINGS YOU HERE?
>> DOCTOR, WE BEG YOU TO LEAVE
THE VILLAGE.
>> HUH?
>> WASN'T IT YOUR FAULT THAT THE
BAND OF 7 ATTACKED THE VILLAGE
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
>> I'LL NEVER FORGET YOUR FACE
THAT NIGHT.
YOU LOOKED JUST LIKE A DEMON.
>> HUH.
AAH! UHH.
>> [NEIGH]
>> OH!
>> HMM?
>> [NEIGH]
>> OH.
>> [MOANING]
>> QUITE THE INGRATE,
WOULDN'T YOU AGREE?
AND AFTER ALL MY MINISTRATIONS
AS HIS PHYSICIAN.
>> [MOANING]
>> HEY, WHAT'S YOUR HURRY?
>> I KNEW IT.
HE IS THE SAME MAN THAT WAS
AFTER US ON THE BRIDGE!
>> [MOANING]
>> AAH!
>> I HAVE TO GET AWAY!
[MOANING] HUH?
>> HELLO.
>> [WHIMPERING]
>> THERE IT IS.
THE SCENT OF THE WALKING DEAD.
THEY'RE SOMEWHERE AT THE BASE
OF MT. HAKUREI.
>> I DON'T FEEL SO GOOD,
MY LORD.
IS IT MY IMAGINATION, OR HAS THE
BARRIER BECOME QUITE A LOT
STRONGER THAN BEFORE?
OH, HE'S STILL NOT
TALKING TO ME.
OH, THIS FUR FEELS SO SOFT
AND WONDERFUL.
[GIGGLES]
>> THE BATTLE CONTINUES.
THE FACT THAT I WALK THIS PATH
ONCE MORE ONLY SERVES TO CONFIRM
MY WRETCHED FATE AND WHAT AWAITS
ME BEYOND THIS DARKNESS.
ONCE MORE, JUST ONCE
MORE, I MUST ASCERTAIN THE
WHEREABOUTS OF THOSE MORTALS
RESURRECTED FROM THE GRAVE.
>> SUIKOTSU, WHAT'S
GOTTEN INTO YOU?
>> JAKOTSU, YOU'RE HERE.
>> BEFORE, WHEN YOU HAD THAT
FACE, YOU WERE HARMLESS.
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN ABLE TO
HURT A FLY.
SO WHICH SUIKOTSU ARE YOU?
>> HARD TO SAY.
ALL I KNOW IS THAT I FEEL BETTER
THAN EVER.
HALF OF ME USED TO WALK AROUND
IN A DAZE ALL THE TIME.
I WAS NEVER SURE WHEN I WOULD
LOSE MYSELF.
NOW THINGS ARE DIFFERENT.
I AM MYSELF NOW.
>> OH, YEAH?
I DON'T FOLLOW, BUT NO MATTER.
DOES IT MEAN THAT YOU WON'T TURN
INTO A SAINT NEXT TIME YOU
APPROACH THE BARRIER?
>> RIGHT.
THAT'S WHY I CAME TO THE BASE OF
MT. HAKUREI, JUST TO MAKE SURE
THAT FOOL DOCTOR
HASN'T APPEARED.
I AM ALL RIGHT NOW.
>> WHAT'S HAPPENED TO THE
DOCTOR?
>> HE'S NOT DR. SUIKOTSU.
HIS FACE IS RIGHT.
HE LOOKS THE SAME,
BUT IT'S NOT HIM.
>> HURRY!
RUN FOR IT!
>> [MOANING]
>> AHH. BUNCH OF SCRAWNY-
LOOKING ORPHANS.
I'LL PUT YOU OUT OF YOUR MISERY!
>> [YELLING]
>> FORGIVE ME,
MY SOUL COLLECTORS.
I MUST HURRY.
THAT SACRED JEWEL SHARD IS
COMPLETELY ENSHROUDED IN
BLACK LIGHT.
SUIKOTSU'S HEART
HAS CLOSED SHUT.
HE WILL LIKELY HARM THE
CHILDREN.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> [YELLING]
>> [MOANING]
>> HUH?
>> [GRUNTING]
DAMN IT.
>> SUIKOTSU, YOU GOT A PROBLEM
OVER THERE?
>> SAVE IT!
>> ♪ PURE HAS BECOME IMPURE,
IMPURE HAS NOW BECOME PURE ♪
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHY HAVE I LOST CONTROL OF MY
BODY?
IT'S THOSE KIDS.
[GRUNTING]
OH, DAMN IT.
WHY IS HER FACE COMING TO MIND?
>> [MOANING]
>> [GRUNTING]
CURSE IT ALL! [ECHOING]
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> SESSHOMARU CAN BARELY STAY
ON HIS FEET.
SUIKOTSU, MAKE SURE HE DOESN'T
ESCAPE.
>> JUST HURRY AND DO AWAY
WITH HIM.
I'M ITCHING TO KILL THIS GIRL.
>> AT THE BASE OF MT.
HAKUREI, INUYASHA'S BROTHER
SESSHOMARU ENGAGES IN A BATTLE
TO THE DEATH WITH THE BAND OF 7.
NEXT ON "INUYASHA," THE EXPOSED
FACE OF TRUTH.
>> NOW I REMEMBER.
I DIED ONCE BEFORE.