>> WE CONTINUE OUR JOURNEY
HOPING TO GATHER THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARDS BEFORE NARAKU GETS
TO THEM.
WE HEAR ABOUT A VILLAGE OF DEMON
WOMEN, AND SOON FIND A PLACE
OCCUPIED ONLY BY WOMEN.
BUT WE SEE NOTHING SUSPICIOUS
AND DECIDE TO LEAVE RIGHT AWAY.
THAT IS, UNTIL MIROKU'S BAD
HABITS SURFACE AGAIN,
AND WE END UP STAYING ONE NIGHT.
OR AT LEAST THAT WAS THE PLAN.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> I'M GOING TO FOLLOW THEM.
>> HEY, WAIT!
I'LL GET INUYASHA AND MIROKU
TO COME ALONG, TOO.
THEY'RE PROBABLY CLOSE BY,
SO IT'LL JUST TAKE A SEC--
>> NEVER MIND, THERE'S NO TIME
TO LOOK FOR THEM.
>> WAIT, SANGO.
>> AAH!
>> [MOANING]
UHH--
AAH!
UHH...UH...
>> HA HA HA.
>> WHERE AM I?
>> AND NOW WE SHALL MAKE YOU
ONE OF US.
HERE, SWALLOW IT.
SWALLOW IT WITHOUT BITING,
AND VERY SOON THE EGG WILL HATCH
INSIDE YOUR STOMACH AND YOU,
TOO, SHALL BECOME ONE OF US.
>> NO WAY, YOU'RE NOT GONNA
MAKE ME SWALLOW THAT THING.
>> UHH!
TELL ME, WHAT KIND OF DEMON
ARE YOU?
>> HA HA HA!
I WANT YOUR FLESH!
GIVE ME YOUR FLESH!
>> WAKANA!
WAKANA, HOW I'VE SEARCHED
FOR YOU, MY DEAREST.
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> OH, NO--
KAGOME, GET BACK!
HEY, YOU, WHAT'D YOU DO WITH
SANGO?
IF YOU HID HER SOMEWHERE,
YOU BETTER TELL ME.
>> INUYASHA, WAIT!
THERE'S SOME KIND OF DEMONIC
VAPOR SEEPING OUT OF THEIR
MOUTHS.
>> UHH!
>> HMM, SO THIS IS THE VILLAGE
OF DEMON WOMEN WE WERE LOOKING
FOR ALL ALONG.
AND WE DIDN'T EVEN KNOW IT.
>> YOU WANT ME TO GIVE YOU
MY FLESH?
>> HA HA HA.
>> I HEARD THE RUMORS ABOUT
A VILLAGE OF DEMON WOMEN WHO
WERE SKINNING THEIR POOR VICTIMS
ALIVE.
SO, YOU'RE THE ONE WHO HAS
POSSESSED THESE INNOCENT WOMEN.
>> EXACTLY.
I NEEDED TO FIND MALE FLESH
IN ORDER TO RETURN TO MY
FORMER SELF.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
YOUR FORMER SELF?
>> I SUPPOSE THERE'S NO HARM
IN EXPLAINING...
SINCE YOU'RE GOING TO DIE
VERY SOON ANYWAY.
I WAS ONCE THE DEMON THAT RULED
OVER THE NEARBY MARSH.
ONE DAY, I WAS EXORCISED
BY A MONK AND SEALED WITHIN
A SCROLL.
AND NOT SATISFIED WITH THAT,
THOSE HUMANS TORE AWAY MY FLESH
AND PAINTED A KANNON ON THE
SCROLL.
THEY COMPLETELY RESTRICTED
MY MOVEMENTS.
THE FOOLS.
THEY SEALED ME UP, BUT MY SOUL
DID NOT DIE.
I'VE WAITED PATIENTLY FOR THE
MOMENT OF MY RESURRECTION,
AND NOW YOU SHALL BECOME A PART
OF ME!
>> UHH!
SACRED SUTRA!
>> AAH!
AAH!
TRY AND RUN, YOU CANNOT
ESCAPE ME.
HUH?
>> YOU CAN'T IMAGINE HOW GLAD
I AM TO FIND YOU'RE ALIVE.
>> I, TOO, AM GLAD, SHINOSUKE.
>> HA HA HA HA.
EXCELLENT, WAKANA.
WE'LL LEAVE THE BOTHERSOME MONK
FOR LATER.
RIGHT NOW, I SHALL TAKE THAT
YOUNG MAN'S FLESH INSTEAD.
>> UHH!
AAH!
>> INUYASHA, PLEASE TAKE IT EASY
ON THEM.
THEY'RE NOT ACTUALLY EVIL,
THEY'RE BEING CONTROLLED
BY SOMEONE.
>> I KNOW THAT.
I'M NOT IN THE HABIT OF HITTING
WOMEN.
I DON'T KNOW HOW I'M GOING
TO KEEP THEM OFF.
THERE ARE TOO MANY OF THEM,
DAMN IT ALL.
>> NOT GOOD.
THE GIRL'S GONE MISSING, MAYBE
SHE RETURNED TO THAT SHRINE.
I'M GUESSING THAT ALL THE
WOMEN IN THE VILLAGE ARE BEING
CONTROLLED BY THAT DEMON,
WHATEVER IT IS.
THE QUESTION IS, HOW DO I GET
THEM BACK TO NORMAL?
HEY, THAT'S...
>> WAKANA?
WHERE ARE YOU TAKING ME?
>> OH, INSIDE THE KANNON SHRINE.
>> WAKANA, THE FIANCEE THAT
SHINOSUKE WAS SEARCHING FOR.
WAIT, SHINOSUKE, YOU MUSTN'T
GO WITH HER!
SHINOSUKE!
>> HUH?
>> RUN FOR IT!
>> IT'S THE MONK MIROKU.
>> GET AWAY FROM THERE!
>> MIROKU SEEMS CONCERNED, BUT
I CAN'T HEAR WHAT HE'S SAYING.
>> RUN AWAY!
>> UHH, OH, NO!
UHH!
CURSE IT ALL, MY SPELL
IS BROKEN.
>> OH.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON, WAKANA?
WHAT ON EARTH IS THAT THING?
>> SHINOSUKE, LISTEN TO ME,
TAKE WAKANA AND ESCAPE.
>> BUT WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> HURRY!
>> UHH, RIGHT!
>> I'LL HAVE TO USE MY
WIND TUNNEL.
DAMN, I CAN'T USE IT WITH HER
IN THE WAY.
UHH!
REPENT!
>> AAH!
[SCREAMS]
>> UHH...I ALMOST HAD IT.
HUH?
SUTRA SANS.
IT'S WORTH TRYING.
FORGIVE ME FOR DOING THIS
BUT YOU MUST AWAKEN.
>> HUH!
UHH...BLEH...
>> A SALAMANDER?
SO THAT'S WHAT'S BEEN BEWITCHING
THE WOMEN.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS, MONK,
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHAT AM I DOING HERE?
>> IT'S OK, YOU DON'T NEED
TO TRY AND REMEMBER.
FORGIVE ME.
>> UHH...
>> WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
>> REST ASSURED, SHINOSUKE,
YOU'RE FIANCE WILL BE FINE.
>> OH.
>> WHAT WAS THAT?
>> A HANGING SCROLL?
>> HUH?
[EXPLOSIONS]
>> OHH!
>> WHAT'S HAPPENING?
>> IT LOOKS LIKE A SALAMANDER
DEMON.
>> HOW FORTUNATE FOR ME,
A HALF DEMON'S FLESH JUST READY
FOR THE TAKING.
>> HUH, WHAT ARE YOU GOING
ON ABOUT, TOAD FACE?
>> HA HA HA.
THE FLESH OF A HALF DEMON
IS WORTH THAT OF 5 HUMANS.
NO, MORE LIKE 10, I'D SAY.
I SHALL DEVOUR YOU AND COMPLETE
RESURRECTING MYSELF.
>> HAH, I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT,
BUT NOBODY MESSES WITH ME!
HUH?
AAH!
>> WHOA!
>> KAGOME!
>> AAH!
>> THE DEMON HAS FINALLY SHOWN
ITS TRUE FORM.
>> MIROKU, IT'S YOU.
>> INUYASHA, DON'T WORRY,
I CAN TAKE CARE OF THOSE GIRLS.
>> SURE.
YOU THINK YOU CAN DO SOMETHING?
>> LEAVE IT TO ME.
>> ALL RIGHT, THEY'RE ALL YOURS.
>> FORGIVE ME.
>> UHH...BLEH!
>> [COUGH]
>> YOU SEE THAT, THEY SPIT UP
SALAMANDERS.
>> SO THAT'S WHAT WAS
MANIPULATING ALL OF THE WOMEN.
>> HA HA HA, IT WAS SIMPLE,
ALL WOMEN ARE WEAK.
>> WHAT DID YOU SAY?
>> I'M SICK AND TIRED OF HEARING
YOUR STUPID LECTURES.
YAH!
AAH!
ALL BRAWN, NO BRAINS.
>> THESE WOMEN ARE ALL
UNFORTUNATE SOULS WHO LOST
LOVED ONES IN THE WAR.
UHH!
THEY NEEDED TO BE COMFORTED.
THEY PROBABLY LOOKED TO THE
KANNON HANGING SCROLL
FOR GUIDANCE AND COMFORT.
UHH!
>> OHH!
>> SADLY, THEY WENT TO THE WRONG
PLACE.
THEY DIDN'T KNOW THAT THE
SALAMANDER DEMON WAS SEALED
IN THE HANGING SCROLL.
>> HANGING SCROLL?
THE THING THAT FLEW PAST
A WHILE AGO?
>> HMM.
>> SO WHY'D YOU SHOW UP NOW,
AFTER ALL THESE YEARS INSIDE
THE SCROLL?
>> HA HA HA, I DON'T REALLY KNOW
ALL THAT'S HAPPENED WHILE I WAS
SEALED UP.
HOWEVER...
>> UHH--
AAH!
UHH.
>> INUYASHA!
>> WHAT I DO KNOW IS THAT
THE EVIL AURA THAT IS PERMEATING
THE WORLD HAS GIVEN ME ENORMOUS
POWER.
>> THE EVIL AURA THAT'S
PERMEATING THIS LAND, HUH?
SO NARAKU'S INFLUENCE HAS
REACHED EVEN THIS FAR,
TO THIS FILTHY SWAMP.
WELL, I HOPE YOU'RE READY
TO DIE, 'CAUSE NOW I'M SERIOUS.
>> UHH--
HUH!
THERE'S TOO MANY OF THEM
TO HANDLE ON MY OWN!
SANGO, CAN YOU LEND ME A HAND
HERE?
>> WHAT ARE YOU SAYING, MIROKU?
SANGO'S NOT EVEN HERE.
>> HUH?
>> YOU MEAN YOU HADN'T NOTICED?
>> UHH!
HUH!
WHERE IS SHE THEN, WHAT IS
SANGO DOING?
>> I DON'T KNOW,
SHE DISAPPEARED.
>> HUH?
>> YOU WERE TOO BUSY FOOLING
AROUND WITH THE WOMEN TO NOTICE.
SANGO GOT UPSET AND WENT
TO DEAL WITH THE WOMEN ALONE.
>> SHE WENT ALONE?
[WHIMPERING]
>> KIRARA, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
HER FUR'S ALL WET.
>> UHH.
>> HERE I COME, DEMON!
>> NOW, HALF DEMON,
I'LL DEVOUR YOU!
>> WIND SCAR!
>> HE DID IT!
NOW THE WOMEN WILL--
HUH?
>> UHH...HUH!
UHH!
>> I DON'T GET IT.
WE DESTROYED
THE SALAMANDER DEMON.
HOW COME THE WOMEN
ARE STILL POSSESSED?
>> LOOKS LIKE WE'LL HAVE
TO EXORCISE THE DEMONS FROM EACH
ONE OF THEIR BELLIES BEFORE
THIS IS OVER.
HUH?
[WHIMPERING]
KAGOME, I NEED YOU TO HANDLE
THESE WOMEN.
INUYASHA, YOU KNOW WHAT YOU
HAVE TO DO, RIGHT?
YOU WRAP THINGS UP HERE.
>> HUH?
>> THERE'S SOME URGENT BUSINESS
I NEED TO TAKE CARE OF.
LET'S GO, KIRARA.
SANGO.
PLEASE BE SAFE, SANGO.
>> HE DOVE INTO THE WATER!
>> YEAH.
>> HEY, WOULD YOU QUIT DAWDLING,
I COULD USE SOME HELP OVER HERE.
>> HIRAIKOTSU?
HUH?
HUH--WAIT, SANGO!
I GET IT, YOU WERE FORCED
TO SWALLOW A DEMON, TOO.
DON'T WORRY, I'LL SAVE YOU.
HUH!
UHH.
SANGO!
SHE WON'T BE AS EASY TO DEAL
WITH AS THE WOMEN FROM
THE VILLAGE.
I HAVE TO FIND SOME WAY TO GET
CLOSE TO HER.
UHH!
HERE'S MY CHANCE.
>> HUH?
>> WHAT IS IT, INUYASHA?
>> THE SMELL OF BLOOD.
>> BLOOD?
>> UHH.
[WHIMPERING]
DON'T YOU WORRY ABOUT A THING,
KIRARA.
I'LL BE ABLE TO SAVE SANGO,
YOU CAN COUNT ON THAT.
>> SANGO, DON'T WORRY, I'M GOING
TO PURGE THAT SALAMANDER DEMON
FROM YOUR BELLY.
HUH!
UHH!
>> UHH!
HUH!
>> AAH!
>> UHH!
>> I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN AS MUCH.
YOU ARE TRULY FEARSOME
AS AN OPPONENT.
I'M GLAD WE'RE USUALLY
ON THE SAME SIDE.
>> [COUGHING]
>> HMM?
SANGO?
I THOUGHT I WAS A GONER.
>> MIROKU!
>> IS SANGO ALL RIGHT?
>> YES, WELL, MORE OR LESS.
>> MIROKU, YOUR FACE!
YOU'VE BEEN WOUNDED.
>> I KNOW.
>> WHAT'S THIS WEIRD LITTLE EGG?
>> IT'S A DEMON SALAMANDER EGG.
IF IT HAD HATCHED, I'D BE IN
A LOT WORSE SHAPE THAN I AM NOW,
BELIEVE ME.
>> SANGO WAS POSSESSED AS WELL?
>> SHE WAS BEWITCHED LIKE
THE VILLAGE WOMEN?
HOW'D SHE LET SUCH A STUPID
THING HAPPEN?
>> SHE WAS UPSET WHEN SHE
TOOK OFF.
SHE OBVIOUSLY WASN'T
THINKING STRAIGHT.
AND NONE OF THIS WOULD HAVE
HAPPENED IF MIROKU DIDN'T KEEP
FLIRTING WITH THE GIRLS.
>> HUH?
ARE YOU SUGGESTING THIS
IS MY FAULT?
>> OF COURSE!
WHO'D YOU THINK WAS TO BLAME?
>> YOU BROUGHT IT ON YOURSELF.
>> [SIGHING]
>> OH, I SEE.
SO YOU'RE RETURNING TO YOUR
HOMELAND?
>> YES.
>> THANK YOU FOR ALL YOUR HELP.
>> WE TRULY ARE INDEBTED.
>> NOT AT ALL.
>> TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH, WE
DIDN'T REALLY DO ALL THAT MUCH.
>> SPEAKING OF WHICH,
I WOULD LIKE TO THANK THE MONK.
>> MAYBE ANOTHER TIME.
>> HUH?
>> HE'S KIND OF BUSY RIGHT NOW,
I WOULDN'T INTERRUPT HIM.
>> I'M SO SORRY ABOUT THIS.
IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
>> NO NEED TO APOLOGIZE, SANGO.
BESIDES, I'M AS MUCH TO BLAME.
KAGOME INFORMED ME THAT
MY BAD HABIT OF FLIRTING WITH
WOMEN WAS THE CAUSE OF ALL THIS.
I'M REALLY SORRY, SANGO.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TO APOLOGIZE.
I WAS CARELESS, THAT'S ALL.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO DO WITH IT.
>> SANGO, I WANT YOU TO HEAR
MY FEELINGS.
YOU DON'T NEED TO SAY ANYTHING,
JUST PLEASE HEAR ME OUT.
>> HMM?
>> YOU'RE NOT LIKE THE OTHERS,
SANGO.
YOU'RE A VERY SPECIAL WOMAN
TO ME.
>> HUH?
>> "SPECIAL," HE SAYS,
WHAT A JERK.
HE'S FLIRTING WITH SANGO LIKE
HE DOES WITH EVERY OTHER WOMAN
HE SEES.
>> SHH!
>> SOMEHOW, IT'S DIFFERENT
WITH US.
YOU SEE, SANGO, I'VE NEVER HAD
SUCH STRONG FEELINGS FOR A WOMAN
AS I DO FOR YOU.
EXCEPT...THERE'S ONE PROBLEM.
I FEEL AS IF I CANNOT LOVE YOU
AS AN ORDINARY WOMAN.
>> OH!
>> YOU'RE MY COMRADE,
THE WOMAN I FIGHT ALONGSIDE.
>> SO HE'S SAYING THEY'RE JUST
GONNA BE FRIENDS?
>> THAT'S TERRIBLE!
HE'S NOT GETTING AWAY WITH THIS.
>> OH, I KNOW THAT.
YOU DIDN'T NEED TO TELL ME.
I KNEW HOW YOU FELT.
IT'S NOT AS IF--
AS IF I HOPED YOU WOULD LOVE ME.
I NEVER THOUGHT THAT.
>> SANGO?
>> WE'VE SAID IT ALL, RIGHT?
I'M GOING.
>> I'M JUST GETTING STARTED.
IF THIS BATTLE WITH NARAKU EVER
COMES TO AN END AND THE CURSE
OF MY WIND TUNNEL IS BROKEN...
IF I MAKE IT OUT ALIVE...
IF WE MADE IT THAT FAR,
WOULD YOU COME LIVE WITH ME?
WOULD YOU BEAR MY CHILDREN,
SANGO?
>> OH, WOW--HE PROPOSED TO HER!
>> HE POSES A WHAT?
>> SANGO?
>> YES!
>> YOU'LL HAVE MY CHILDREN?
10 BABIES, OR MAYBE EVEN 20?
>> YES.
MIROKU, DOES THIS MEAN YOU'LL
STOP WOMANIZING?
>> HUH?
UHH...
>> YOU WILL STOP FLIRTING,
RIGHT?
>> UHH...
>> I'LL TAKE THAT AS A NO.
>> OHH.
>> DOES THIS MEAN THEY'RE
NOT FIGHTING ANYMORE?
>> HA, THEY WON'T LAST MORE
THAN A DAY OR TWO.
>> OHH.
>> THE WRATH OF THE SEA DEMON!
>> SOMETHING'S FISHY ABOUT HER.
>> SARA, THE BEAUTIFUL AND
MYSTERIOUS WOMAN,
STEALS THE TETSUSAIGA.
>> I KNEW YOU WERE BEHIND THIS.
>> I WILL NOT ACCEPT HELP
DEFEATING INUYASHA, ESPECIALLY
NOT FROM SOMEONE LIKE YOU.
>> LORD SESSHOMARU,
WHAT'S GOING ON WITH HER?
>> SHE SURE WAS PRETTY.
>> THAT WAS NO HUMAN.
>> NEXT TIME, ON A SPECIAL
EPISODE OF "INUYASHA."
>> THE WOMAN WHO LOVED
SESSHOMARU.
>> I WILL FULFILL YOUR WISH
NO MATTER WHAT IT TAKES.