- MMM. THAT HITS THE SPOT.
- KAGOME, ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE BACK TO NORMAL ALREADY?
- YES.
FOR THE TENTH TIME TODAY,
I FEEL PERFECTLY FINE AGAIN.
I CAN HARDLY BELIEVE
THE OLD DEMON MANAGED
TO SUCK MY SOUL OUT OF ME,
BUT I'M BACK
TO MY OLD SELF NOW.
- I WISH I COULD SAY THE SAME
FOR INUYASHA, THOUGH.
SINCE HIS RUN-IN WITH KIKYO,
HE'S BEEN SPENDING
A LOT OF TIME
JUST STARING INTO SPACE.
- I JUST DON'T KNOW ANYMORE.
SO I GATHER UP ALL THE SHARDS
OF THE SHIKON JEWEL
TO BECOME A FULL-FLEDGED DEMON,
AND THEN WHAT?
EVEN IF I DO
FULLY BECOME A DEMON,
WILL THAT MAKE ME
STRONGER INSIDE?
CAN I EVER TRULY FORGET KIKYO?
- LOOK AT HIM.
I'VE NEVER SEEN HIM
ACT THIS WAY BEFORE.
- NO. NEITHER HAVE I.
- TAKE THAT!
- BAD MOVE.
- WHAT'D YOU DO THAT FOR,
SHRIMP?
- TO KNOCK SOME SENSE
INTO YOU.
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BE LOOKING
FOR THE JEWEL SHARDS.
- GET OFF MY BACK.
EVEN A GUY LIKE ME
NEEDS SOME TIME TO THINK
ONCE IN AWHILE.
- YEAH, THAT'S
WHAT'S WORRYING ME.
- WORRY ABOUT THIS!
COME BACK HERE,
YOU LITTLE PIPSQUEAK!
- CAN'T CATCH ME,
CAN YOU, BIG OAF?
- NOW YOU'VE DONE IT.
- THE SHIKON JEWEL
IS ENSHROUDED
WITH SUCH MISERY.
KIKYO CLAIMS THAT
INUYASHA BETRAYED HER,
AND INUYASHA SAYS THAT IT WAS
THE OTHER WAY AROUND.
HOW COULD TWO VERSIONS
OF THE SAME STORY
BE SO DIFFERENT?
I ONLY HOPE THAT
THE PUZZLE WILL BE SOLVED
ONCE WE'VE FOUND
ALL THE SHARDS OF THE JEWEL.
- SO I SHOULD GO RIGHT.
- HAVE YOU HEARD ABOUT
THE NEW WOMAN
WORKING AT THE REST HOUSE
UP AHEAD?
THEY SAY HER FAIR COMPLEXION
AND BEAUTIFUL EYES
ARE UNPARALLELED,
AND I UNDERSTAND
SHE'S UNATTACHED.
- I COULD USE
A BITE TO EAT.
- JUST WHAT I WAS THINKING.
- DIVINE INTERVENTION.
- SURELY THEY CAN'T BE
SPEAKING OF
THE SAME YOUNG WOMAN
I RECALL.
- YOUR SWEETS ARE READY.
- UH, THANKS.
SHOULD HAVE STUCK
TO THE RIGHT.
- JUST BETWEEN US,
I UNDERSTAND THE DAUGHTER
OF THE LORD IN THIS REGION
HAS BEEN POSSESSED BY
SOME SORT OF EVIL SPIRIT
AND HAS TAKEN TO HER BED.
- HE'LL REQUIRE THE AID
OF A SKILLED PRIEST, THEN.
- ARE YOU CERTAIN
THIS MONK IS VIRTUOUS
AND TRUSTWORTHY?
- IF ONE IS TO BELIEVE
HIS CLAIMS,
THEN, AYE, MY LORD.
- MONK, YOU MUST DRIVE AWAY
THE EVIL SPIRITS
POSSESSING MY CHILD
OR YOU'LL RECEIVE NOTHING.
- MY, LIVING IN OPULENCE
IN SUCH TURBULENT TIMES
AS THESE.
SURELY YOUR VASSALS
MUST RESENT YOUR WEALTH.
- IMPUDENCE!
PRINCESS, A MONK HAS COME
TO OFFER HIS BLESSINGS.
- PARDON ME.
ALLOW ME TO SEE HER.
HER FACE IS TERRIBLY SWOLLEN.
- IT IS ALWAYS SO.
ARE YOU CERTAIN
YOU'RE TRULY A MONK?
- HUH?
TELL ME ABOUT THAT STATUE.
- I RECEIVED IT
FROM AN IMPOVERISHED NOBLEMAN.
THEY SAY IT IS
A BLESSED IDOL.
- HMM.
I AM PREPARED TO BEGIN.
LEAVE THE PRINCESS
HERE WITH ME
AND TAKE EVERYONE ELSE
ON THE GROUNDS
OUTSIDE THE RESIDENCE GATES.
- HUH?
- AND MILORD, MARK MY WORDS,
NO MATTER HOW ALARMING
THE SOUNDS FROM WITHIN,
YOU MUST NOT PEER INSIDE.
- OH.
HMM.
- NOW THEN,
I SHALL COMMENCE
THE EXORCISM.
VERY WELL, COME OUT AT ONCE
AND SURRENDER PEACEFULLY
AND I SHALL SHOW YOU MERCY.
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN
YOU WOULD NOT GIVE IN EASILY.
A WEASEL DEMON,
HOW VERY BEFITTING.
- THAT GLOW--
A SHARD OF THE SHIKON JEWEL.
- THE BEAST SOUNDS
FEARSOME INDEED.
- IT CERTAINLY DOES.
- WE SHOULD TAKE
A LOOK INSIDE, MILORD.
- NO. WE'LL WAIT.
HE SAID WE MUST NOT PEER INSIDE
UNTIL HE GAVE US THE WORD.
BESIDES, I WANT TO MAKE SURE
THE DEMON IS LONG GONE.
- IT SOUNDS LESS LIKE
AN EXORCISM
AND MORE LIKE THE MANSION
IS BEING PILLAGED.
- I STILL SAY WE SHOULD WAIT.
- SO THIS WEASEL
WAS THE CULPRIT.
AND THIS SMALL ANIMAL
TURNED INTO A DEMON
AND POSSESSED YOU?
- YES.
- AND WHAT OF
THAT YOUNG MONK?
- HE GAVE ME NO NAME,
BUT LEFT WITH MY HEART.
- MY LORD, I REGRET
I HAVE TERRIBLE NEWS
TO BRING YOU.
[GASPING]
ALL OF YOUR VALUABLES
HAVE BEEN STOLEN.
- INCLUDING 3
OF THE BEST HORSES.
- I'VE BEEN HAD.
- NOW THEN,
I MUST FIND A PLACE
TO PAWN THESE OFF.
[SIGHS]
HOW DISAPPOINTING.
AN ENTIRE CARTLOAD OF SPOILS
AND THEY FETCHED
BUT A SMALL PRICE.
EVEN SO, THIS SHARD
OF THE SHIKON JEWEL
MADE IT WORTH MY WHILE.
- OH, YEAH.
NOW THIS IS WHAT I CALL
A HOT SPRING.
- AHH.
- A GIRL?
SHE WEARS A SHARD
OF THE SHIKON JEWEL.
AND THEY'RE--
I MEAN, IT'S HUGE.
- DON'T YOU EVEN THINK
ABOUT PEEKING AT ME.
- DON'T FLATTER YOURSELF.
I GOT NO INTEREST
IN LOOKING.
- OH, IS THAT SO?
WELL, FINE THEN.
- HEY, WHY ARE YOU
GETTING UNDRESSED?
- GIVE YOU ONE GUESS.
- OH, NO YOU DON'T.
- OOPS, SORRY.
YOU WANT TO COME?
WAIT, COME TO THINK OF IT,
HOW COME YOU AND KAGOME
SPEND SO MUCH TIME TOGETHER
AND YET YOU NEVER SEEM
TO BATHE AT THE SAME TIME?
THINK OF ALL
THE FUN THINGS YOU CAN DO
WHEN THERE'S TWO OF YOU.
- LISTEN, KID--
- MOM, DAD, AND I
ALWAYS TOOK BATHS TOGETHER,
AND WE HAD
A REALLY GREAT TIME.
- REMIND ME TO EXPLAIN IT TO YOU
WHEN YOU'RE A BIT BIGGER.
- I GUESS THAT MEANS
YOU HAVEN'T GOTTEN VERY FAR
WITH KAGOME YET, RIGHT?
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANS,
BUT NO ONE SEEMS
TO BE WILLING TO ANSWER.
I WONDER WHY.
- I'LL TELL YOU WHY--
IN ABOUT 50 YEARS
WHEN YOU'RE OLD ENOUGH
TO UNDERSTAND IT!
- JUST AN INNOCENT QUESTION.
WHAT DID I SAY?
- AHH.
- OK, SO MAYBE I'M NOT
THE BEAUTY THAT KIKYO WAS.
[GASPS]
AAH!
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- I'M FINE, OK?
JUST GO AWAY.
SHOO!
SHOO, MONKEYS!
- SHE'S WITH ANOTHER MAN.
TOO BAD.
I HATE HAVING
TO RESORT TO VIOLENCE.
- ALLOW ME TO EXPLAIN.
I MERELY WISH
FOR A GUARANTEE.
- I TOLD YOU
THAT YOU'D BE COMPENSATED.
- YES.
- COME ON,
CAN'T YOU TRY AND SEE
THE HUMOR IN IT?
SO I BONKED YOU ON THE HEAD.
YOU SAW ME NAKED,
SO CAN'T WE SAY WE'RE EVEN?
- I SAW NOTHING!
- HE DID, RIGHT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
I WAS LOOKING
SOMEWHERE ELSE.
- SO IT'S THE FELLOW IN RED
YOU WANT ME TO ATTACK?
- RIGHT.
- MEANWHILE,
I SHALL MAKE OFF
WITH THE GIRL.
- I STILL DON'T GET IT.
WHY GO TO ALL THIS TROUBLE
WHEN YOU COULD USE
YOUR POWERFUL RIGHT HAND
AND HAVE THE JEWEL
IN A MATTER OF SECONDS?
- DON'T BE A FOOL.
SURELY YOU KNOW
BETTER THAN THAT.
IF I USE THIS HAND,
EVERYONE IN
THE VICINITY WOULD DIE.
- HOW COULD I HAVE FORGOTTEN?
I HOPE YOU REMEMBER
WHO YOUR FRIENDS ARE
IF THIS SHOULD SOMEHOW
GET OUT OF CONTROL.
- YOU CAN COUNT ON IT,
MY FRIEND.
- HUH?
- I HAVE COME FOR YE!
- INUYASHA!
WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
- FEAR NOT, YOUNG LADY.
YOU HAVE NO REASON
TO DOUBT MY INTENTIONS.
I AM NOTHING MORE
THAN A SIMPLE MONK--
A MONK WHO DESIRED
A JEWEL SHARD
AND GOT HIMSELF A YOUNG WOMAN
IN THE PROCESS.
- WHAT AM I,
A CONSOLATION PRIZE?
- KAGOME!
WHO'S THE GUY?
WHERE'S HE TAKING HER TO?
DON'T TAKE THIS PERSONALLY,
BUT I GOT BETTER THINGS
TO DO.
- AAH!
DON'T KILL ME.
I'M BUT AN INNOCENT BADGER.
- YOUR FRIEND
IS A VIOLENT ONE.
- EXPLAIN YOURSELF!
WHY DID YOU ATTACK ME?
- INUYASHA!
LET ME GO.
- GLADLY.
SEEING AS I HAVE
WHAT I DESIRE.
HMM.
- HEY, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- THAT CREEP.
WHO THE HECK
WAS THAT GUY, ANYWAY?
- HE DID MENTION SOMETHING
ABOUT BEING A MONK,
BUT WHAT WAS THE DEAL
WITH HIS RIGHT HAND?
- YEAH, I'VE NEVER SEEN
SUCH A STRONG STORM
COME FROM OUT OF NOWHERE.
IT WAS LIKE
THE WIND FROM HIS HAND
WAS PULLING IN
EVERYTHING FROM ITS PATH.
[GASPS]
- OH, NO!
THAT MONK TOOK OFF
WITH MY BIKE.
YOU CREEP!
- LIKE THAT MATTERS.
YOU WERE BEING KIDNAPPED.
DON'T YOU THINK
THAT'S MORE IMPORTANT?
I CAN'T TURN MY BACK
ON YOU PEOPLE FOR A SECOND.
- YOU WERE WORRIED ABOUT ME.
SORRY.
- SORRY FOR WHAT?
I NEVER SAID
I WAS WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
I WAS ONLY THINKING
ABOUT THE JEWEL SHARD.
- SPEAKING OF WHICH,
HE TOOK MORE THAN THE BIKE.
HE GOT THE JEWEL, TOO.
- WHAT?
[GASPING]
[CHATTER]
- LOUSY THIEF.
I'LL FIND HIM YET.
HE COULD NOT
HAVE GOTTEN TOO FAR.
I'LL HUNT THE FRAUD DOWN.
- COME ON, INUYASHA.
WHAT'S TAKING YOU?
- GET OFF MY BACK.
THERE'S A LOT OF SMELLS
TO SIFT THROUGH, ALL RIGHT?
- WELL, HURRY UP.
PEOPLE ARE STARING.
- I'M WITH KAGOME.
THEY DON'T LOOK VERY FRIENDLY.
- WHERE DID THAT
MISERABLE THIEF GO?
- WHAT,
IS HE SOME MANNER OF BEAST?
- SEE WHAT I MEAN?
- THE YOUNG MAN AND THE BOY
ARE ODD ENOUGH,
BUT LOOK AT
THAT STRANGE GIRL.
- IS SHE ALSO A DEMON?
- WHO, ME?
- SEE HOW IT FEELS?
- HEY, MAYBE HE NEVER
EVEN CAME THROUGH HERE.
- HE WAS HERE, ALL RIGHT.
I CAN SMELL HIM.
- EVEN IF HE DID PASS THROUGH,
A THIEF WOULDN'T
JUST BE HANGING AROUND
IN A PLACE LIKE--
[GASPS]
- WOULD ANYONE
LIKE TO DANCE?
- SO MUCH FOR THEIR CLAIM
OF HAVING BEAUTIFUL GEISHAS.
I WOULD'VE HAD
A BETTER TIME
IF I'D GONE DRINKING
WITH THE BADGER.
- GOTCHA!
- BUSTED, BICYCLE THIEF.
- I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
IT'S TOO GOOD TO BE TRUE.
YOU'RE A REAL SIGHT
FOR SORE EYES.
- HEH.
I'LL GIVE YOU SORE EYES!
- BEAST! YOU AGAIN.
I SHOULD HAVE
FIGURED AS MUCH.
- YEAH, YOU SHOULD HAVE.
FUNNY, THAT'S JUST
WHAT I WAS THINKING.
BUT I GUESS NOT ALL OF US
ARE BLESSED WITH GOOD LOOKS
AND BRAINS.
DON'T SUPPOSE
YOU'D BE INTERESTED
IN HANDING OVER
THAT JEWEL FRAGMENT
YOU STOLE FROM US.
- A GEM SUCH AS THIS
DOES NOT BELONG
IN THE HANDS OF A DEMON.
- WE'LL SEE ABOUT THAT.
OH, NO, YOU DON'T.
COME BACK
AND FIGHT LIKE A MAN.
- I WILL NOT FIGHT
A SENSELESS BATTLE.
- ALL A MATTER OF OPINION.
HE BLOCKED THE
TETSUSAIGA.
I KNEW IT.
HE'S NO ORDINARY MORTAL.
- YOU'LL BE PUNISHED,
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU INSIST.
- HMM.
I DON'T KNOW WHO YOU ARE,
BUT YOU'RE NO MONK.
- I GO BY THE NAME MIROKU.
AND YES, I AM A MONK,
WHO WORKS TO AID
THE COMMON MAN.
[CHATTER]
- BEWARE, VILLAGERS!
A MONK IS ABOUT
TO SLAY THE DEMON!
- "WORK TO AID
THE COMMON MAN."
YOU'RE NOTHING
BUT A SLEAZY ROBBER.
NOW GIVE US BACK
OUR SHARD OF THE SHIKON JEWEL.
WE WENT TO A LOT
OF TROUBLE TO GET IT,
AND WE'RE NOT
GONNA LOSE IT NOW.
- TOUCHING SPEECH.
I KNOW YOU WENT TO GREAT PAINS
TO COLLECT THIS GEM,
BUT TRUST ME,
IT'S IN BETTER HANDS
WITH ME, INUYASHA.
- HUH, SO YOU KNEW
WHO I WAS ALL ALONG.
- NOT AT ALL.
WAS IT THAT BEAUTIFUL
COMPANION OF YOURS
WHO CALLED YOU BY NAME
OR THE YOUNG FOX?
- UH, HE CAN'T BE ALL BAD
IF HE HAS SUCH GOOD TASTE.
- SNAP OUT OF IT, KAGOME.
HE STOLE YOUR JEWEL
FROM UNDER YOUR NOSE.
- ENOUGH TALKING.
LET ME AT YOU!
- STRONG,
BUT NOT STRONG ENOUGH.
- CURSE HIM!
HE BLOCKS EVERY STRIKE.
I'LL HAVE THAT JEWEL SHARD
BACK FROM YOU NOW,
UNLESS YOU'D RATHER DIE,
THAT IS.
- HMM.
- AS YOU WISH.
VILLAGERS, TAKE HEED!
DISTANCE YOURSELF
FROM THIS PLACE,
I WARN YOU.
IT'S FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY.
[MURMURING]
- HUH?
- END OF THE LINE.
THIS TIME VICTORY IS MINE.
- HMM.
- HE'S HOLDING OUT
HIS HAND.
- THIS MAY COME
AS SOMETHING OF A SURPRISE,
BUT I'M A VERY SORE LOSER.
WIND TUNNEL!
- IT'S JUST LIKE
BACK AT THE CLIFF.
WHERE'S THE
WIND COMING FROM?
HIS RIGHT HAND'S
DRAWING IT IN.
- LET'S SEE HOW LONG
YOU CAN WITHSTAND ME.
- RUN AWAY!
QUICKLY!
- HIS HAND'S JUST LIKE
A BLACK HOLE.
IT'S SUCKING UP EVERYTHING
THAT ISN'T NAILED DOWN.
- WE'D BETTER
ESCAPE FROM HERE
WHILE WE CAN.
- WE HAVE TO STOP HIM.
- HUH?
- HOW DO WE DO THAT?
- VILLAGERS, TAKE HEED!
DISTANCE YOURSELF
FROM THIS PLACE.
- HE WARNED THE VILLAGERS
BECAUSE HE DOESN'T WANT
TO HURT HUMANS.
- CAN'T LET GO.
- SURRENDER WHILE YOU CAN.
IF YOU GET SUCKED IN,
YOU'LL NEVER COME OUT ALIVE.
- NO CHANCE.
I'LL BE TOO BUSY
HACKING YOUR RIGHT HAND OFF
TO SURRENDER.
- MY HAND WILL PULL YOU IN,
SWORD AND ALL.
- KAGOME!
KAGOME!
- OH, MY HEAD.
HUH?
- THOSE PRAYER BEADS.
THEY'RE WHAT SEALS OFF
THE POWER OF HIS HAND.
HE STOPPED THE ASSAULT
ON HIS OWN,
MEANING HE CAN'T BE
ALL THAT BAD.
- KAGOME, ARE YOU CRAZY?
YOU COULD'VE GOTTEN
YOURSELF KILLED.
- I WOULDN'T HAVE DONE IT
IF I'D HAD ANY DOUBTS.
WITH A HAND THAT POWERFUL,
HE COULD HAVE KILLED US
A LONG TIME AGO
IF HE'D WANTED TO.
LET'S AT LEAST
GIVE HIM A CHANCE.
MAYBE HE CAN LEND US A HAND.
- I WAS WRONG.
KILL HIM!
- YOU JUST BLEW
YOUR LAST CHANCE.
- SETTLE DOWN, WILL YOU?
LET ME EXPLAIN THINGS.
I, TOO,
AM IN SEARCH OF THE SHARDS
OF THE SHIKON JEWEL.
MY PURPOSE IS TO FIND
AND ELIMINATE A DEMON--
A TERRIBLE DEMON
THAT GOES BY THE NAME OF NARAKU.
- NARAKU?
- YES, AND IT WAS
THIS SAME DEMON
WHO LEFT ME
WITH THIS CURSED HOLE
IN MY RIGHT HAND.
- WHAT SORT OF DEMON
IS THIS THING?
- I KNOW LITTLE OF HIM
EXCEPT THAT HE IS VERY WICKED
AND THOUGHT TO DEVOUR PEOPLE.
- YEAH, GO ON.
- ACCORDING TO FATHER,
MY GRANDFATHER
BATTLED NARAKU LONG AGO
IN HIS YOUTH.
IT WAS OVER 50 YEARS AGO.
THEIR BATTLE ENSUED
FOR SEVERAL YEARS,
AND EACH TIME NARAKU
APPEARED BEFORE MY GRANDFATHER,
HE TOOK ON THE FORM
OF A DIFFERENT HUMAN.
- HE WAS A SHAPE-SHIFTER,
SERIOUSLY?
- THEY SAY THAT
THE LAST TIME HE APPEARED
BEFORE MY GRANDFATHER,
HE TOOK ON THE FORM
OF A BEAUTIFUL WOMAN.
MY GRANDFATHER
HAD GREAT SPIRITUAL POWERS,
BUT UNFORTUNATELY,
AS FATE WOULD HAVE IT...
- DON'T TELL ME.
HE WAS A LECHER.
- REMARKABLE INTUITION.
- NARAKU PIERCED
MY GRANDFATHER'S RIGHT HAND
WITH HIS SACRED
RELIGIOUS SEALS
AND MANAGED TO ESCAPE.
- THE ABYSSAL HOLE
THAT I HAVE CURSED YOU WITH
SHALL BE PASSED DOWN
TO YOUR CHILDREN,
AND THEIR CHILDREN,
SO LONG AS I LIVE.
EACH GENERATION
SHALL THUS BE CURSED
UNTIL NO ONE REMAINS.
- EACH YEAR,
THE HOLE IN MY HAND
BECOMES BIGGER
AND THE WIND
EVER MORE POWERFUL.
UNLESS I CAN DEFEAT NARAKU,
I MYSELF WILL EVENTUALLY
BE DEVOURED BY THE HOLE.
- SO IN OTHER WORDS,
YOU MEAN IT WOULD KILL YOU?
- YES, AND I AM PREPARED
TO ACCEPT THAT FATE
IF SUCH IS TRULY MY DESTINY.
BUT IN THE MEANTIME,
I MUST CONTINUE TRYING
TO STOP NARAKU.
THE SACRED JEWEL OF THE 4 SOULS
VANISHED 50 YEARS AGO
AND NOW ITS SCATTERED
INTO MANY TINY SHARDS.
KNOWING NARAKU,
HE IS CERTAIN
TO ATTEMPT TO GATHER
THE FRAGMENTS
IN ORDER TO STRENGTHEN
HIS OWN MALICIOUS POWER.
I'M SURE OF IT.
I KNOW BECAUSE
NARAKU ONCE CAME CLOSE
TO GETTING THE JEWEL
50 YEARS AGO.
IN DOING SO,
HE SLEW THE PRIESTESS
PROTECTING IT.
- YOU SAY HE KILLED
A PRIESTESS?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- HE MUST BE THE DEMON
WHO DISGUISED HIMSELF AS ME
AND STRUCK DOWN KIKYO!
IT MUST BE HIM!
MIROKU, YOU SAY THIS NARAKU
TAKES ON ALL KINDS
OF DIFFERENT FORMS, RIGHT?
WHAT ABOUT NOW?
WHAT DOES HE LOOK LIKE NOW?
- CALM DOWN.
IF I HAD THAT INFORMATION,
I WOULD HAVE SLAIN HIM
LONG AGO MYSELF.
- NARAKU LAID A TRAP
FOR KIKYO AND ME.
HE MADE US BELIEVE
WE DECEIVED EACH OTHER.
THE DEMON WHO KILLED KIKYO
IS STILL ALIVE
AND IS AFTER
THE SACRED JEWEL FRAGMENTS.
I WILL HUNT DOWN
KIKYO'S KILLER
AND AVENGE HER DEATH.
- IF WE KEEP LOOKING
FOR THESE JEWEL FRAGMENTS,
WE'RE SURE TO RUN INTO
NARAKU OURSELVES
SOONER OR LATER.
- HOW DID YOU GET THAT BACK?
- LET'S SEARCH
FOR THE JEWEL SHARDS TOGETHER.
- UH...
- UNLESS YOU PLAN
ON GIVING UP, INUYASHA.
- I'M NEVER GIVING UP.
- WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- I'VE ALWAYS BEEN MORE
OF A SOLITARY MAN,
PREFERRING TO WORK ON MY OWN
THAN IN THE COMPANY OF OTHERS.
- YEAH, BUT IF
WE DON'T ACT FAST,
YOU WON'T EVEN HAVE
YOUR OWN COMPANY TO ENJOY.
- DEAR KAGOME,
ARE YOU TROUBLE BY
THIS WRETCHED FATE OF MINE?
- SORT OF.
- THEN DO ME THIS GOOD TURN,
WILL YOU?
I WISH FOR YOU
TO BEAR ME A SON.
- HEKE?
- HUH?
- AND WHY WOULD I DO THAT?
- IF FOR SOME
UNFORESEEABLE REASON
I SHOULD FAIL
TO DESTROY NARAKU,
I SHOULD LIKE MY SON TO CARRY ON
THE FAMILY'S MISSION.
[SIGHS]
- HANDS OFF, PRIEST.
YOUR ONLY FAMILY MISSION
IS LECHERY.
- I'M A MONK, NOT A PRIEST.
- DON'T EVER CONSIDER
LAYING A HAND ON KAGOME AGAIN.
- INUYASHA?
- OH, I BEG YOUR PARDON.
I THOUGHT YOU NO MORE
THAN A COMPANION.
BUT APPARENTLY
YOU ARE IN LOVE WITH KAGOME.
- UH...
- MY, THIS IS AWKWARD.
- WELL, YOU'VE GOT IT ALL WRONG.
SHE'S JUST A JEWEL DETECTOR.
- HUH?
IS THAT ALL I AM TO YOU?
OH, HOW COULD I FORGET,
YOU GOT A THING FOR DEAD GIRLS.
- HUH?
- WHO SHOULD I HELP OUT?
MIROKU'S A LOT NICER
THAN INUYASHA.
- YOU WOULDN'T DARE
BETRAY ME!
- YOU CAN'T REALLY BLAME HER.
YOU COULD TREAT HER
MORE KINDLY.
- HA! WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
- WELL, SO MUCH
FOR EVERYONE COMING
TO A PEACEFUL SOLUTION.
I NEVER WANT TO GROW UP.
- YES! EXACTLY!
BE MORE GENTLE!
- LIKE THIS.
- AAH!
GET YOUR HANDS OFF ME!
- I TOLD YOU
NOT TO TOUCH HER!
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- WE NOW KNOW THAT NARAKU
WAS THE DEMON
WHO CAUSED INUYASHA
AND KIKYO TO HATE EACH OTHER.
WHILE TRAVELING WITH MIROKU,
WE DISCOVERED THE SCENT OF INK
ON AN OLD BATTLEFIELD.
WE FOLLOWED THE SCENT
TO A MYSTERIOUS ARTIST,
AND BEFORE WE KNOW IT,
DEMONS ESCAPE FROM THE DRAWING
AND ATTACK US.
WHY HAS THE DRAWING
COME TO LIFE?
NEXT TIME...
SEE YOU SOON!