- I WAS SO WORRIED.
I THOUGHT YOU WEREN'T COMING
BACK ANYMORE, KAGOME.
- SORRY ABOUT THAT, SHIPPO.
- HEY, INUYASHA,
HAVE YOU ASKED FOR
KAGOME'S FORGIVENESS?
- BUTT OUT!
- I WONDER HOW ON EARTH
THOSE TWO PATCHED THINGS UP.
- HUH.
KNOWING HIM, HE PROBABLY JUST
WORE KAGOME DOWN
WITH HIS SILENCE.
- WHAT?
YOU MEAN SHE FORGAVE HIM
FOR CHEATING ON HER?
OH!
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
HOW COULD SHE PUT UP
WITH THAT KIND OF BEHAVIOR?
- SHE PROBABLY REALIZED THAT HE
WAS BACKED UP AGAINST THE WALL.
SHE MOST LIKELY DIDN'T
WANT TO PRESSURE HIM.
- YEAH, IT DOESN'T TAKE MUCH
TO PUSH HIM OVER THE EDGE.
- WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT?
- AH.
A CLEAR SIGN OF REMORSE.
GOOD, GOOD.
- [BIRDS CHIRPING]
- SO, THIS IS WHERE
NARAKU'S CASTLE USED TO BE?
- YES, THERE ARE STILL
TRACES OF NARAKU'S MIASMA.
THIS IS IT.
- HMM.
- IT DOESN'T MAKE
ANY SENSE, THOUGH.
THERE'S HARDLY ANY
SIGNS OF THE RUINS.
YOU SURE NARAKU'S CASTLE
WAS REALLY HERE?
- YOU'VE GOT A POINT.
CONSIDERING IT'S NARAKU,
IT WOULDN'T BE
THE FIRST TIME
WE'VE BEEN LURED
TO A FALSE CASTLE.
- MAYBE THE CASTLE WE SAW
BEFORE WAS JUST AN ILLUSION.
- NO, IT WAS REAL.
- HUH?
HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
- THERE'S NO MISTAKE.
NARAKU'S CASTLE
WAS DEFINITELY HERE.
- HUH?
SANGO, WHAT HAVE YOU GOT THERE?
- WHAT'S UP, SANGO?
DID YOU FIND SOMETHING?
- THIS WAS MY FATHER'S ARMOR.
THE DAY HE WAS MURDERED,
WE DEMON SLAYERS WERE
LURED TO NARAKU'S CASTLE.
[SCREAMING]
- THIS IS WHERE I COME IN.
[GRUNTING]
- MY FATHER AND ALL
THE OTHERS WERE SLAUGHTERED.
THE ASSASSIN WAS
MY YOUNG BROTHER KOHAKU.
HIS MIND WAS BEING
CONTROLLED BY NARAKU.
[GRUNTING]
A WEB!
A SPIDER WEB!
[GRUNTS]
- SANGO, WHAT HAVE I DONE?
- KOHAKU!
THEIR BODIES WERE BURIED IN
THE CORNER OF THE COURTYARD...
RIGHT WHERE WE'RE STANDING.
- I'M SORRY, SANGO.
HUH?
- HUH?
UH, MIROKU?
- WE MUSTN'T LEAVE YOUR
FATHER AND THE OTHERS HERE,
BURIED IN THIS TAINTED GROUND.
- MIROKU--
- WE SHALL BURY THEM ELSEWHERE
AND OFFER OUR PRAYERS.
IS THAT AGREEABLE, SANGO?
- OF COURSE.
MIROKU, I...
THANK YOU.
- SO, THIS IS WHERE
NARAKU'S CASTLE STOOD.
BUT WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE PEOPLE INSIDE,
LIKE SANGO'S BROTHER KOHAKU,
WHO WAS UNDER
NARAKU'S CONTROL?
WAS HE DESTROYED ALONG
WITH THE CASTLE?
- WELL, AT LEAST HERE
WILD DOGS WON'T DIG
UP THEIR GRAVES.
- LET THIS BE YOUR
RESTING PLACE
FOR THE TIME BEING.
- SOMEDAY I PROMISE
TO ERECT PROPER GRAVES
FOR YOU IN OUR VILLAGE.
THE VILLAGE IS ABANDONED NOW,
BUT KOHAKU AND I
ARE STILL ALIVE.
WE'LL BOTH WATCH
OVER THE GRAVES.
- AAH!
- IF I CAN FIND HIM.
- HA HA HA!
- HMPH!
WELL?
- OH!
- THAT'S QUITE
THE PERFORMANCE, YOUNG LAD.
- HA HA HA!
HMPH!
- YOU ARE REMARKABLE!
- I'LL SAY.
HE CERTAINLY IS.
- YOUR PERFORMANCE HAS
BEEN TRULY ENTERTAINING.
- ON TOP OF WHICH,
YOU'VE DONE A FINE JOB
CUTTING OUR FIREWOOD.
- DON'T MENTION IT.
- YOU MUST BE TIRED
AFTER ALL THAT WORK.
COME INSIDE AND REST A LITTLE.
- THANK YOU.
- WELL?
DID YOU REMEMBER ANYTHING?
- NO...
NOT REALLY.
- HOW ABOUT...
WHERE YOU CAME FROM?
OR YOUR NAME?
- WAIT A MINUTE, NOW.
PERHAPS YOU LIVED
CLOSE TO THE CASTLE.
- CASTLE?
- ABOUT 10 DAYS AGO,
LORD HITOMI'S CASTLE SUDDENLY
VANISHED INTO THIN AIR.
AND IT WAS THE VERY NEXT DAY
THAT WE FOUND YOU
LYING UNCONSCIOUS.
PERHAPS YOU'VE SUFFERED
A FRIGHTENING EXPERIENCE,
AND THAT'S WHAT CAUSED
YOU TO LOSE YOUR MEMORY.
- WELL, NEVER MIND.
YES.
- I GUESS NOT.
MEANWHILE, YOU CAN STAY
HERE AS LONG AS YOU LIKE.
NOW, EAT UP.
THERE'S LOTS MORE.
- HMM.
THANK YOU.
- [CRICKETS CHIRPING]
- THE CASTLE.
THAT'S RIGHT.
I HAVE A FEELING I WAS THERE.
- [BUZZING]
- HUH?
AH!
[PANTING]
GRAMPS! GRANNY!
- HUH?
- I HAVE TO LEAVE YOU.
- WHERE WILL YOU GO, MY BOY?
- I CAN'T STAY HERE ANYMORE.
IT'S DANGEROUS,
SO DON'T GO OUTSIDE.
THANK YOU FOR
ALL YOUR KINDNESS.
- WAIT.
- OH, MY.
- THAT'S IT.
I REMEMBER.
I RAN AWAY FROM THE CASTLE
THE NIGHT IT DISAPPEARED.
- KOHAKU, I HAVE NO NEED TO
KEEP YOU ALIVE ANY LONGER.
GO JOIN YOUR FATHER
AND THE OTHERS.
- KOHAKU.
MY NAME IS KOHAKU?
AH!
AAH!
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
HUH?!
- [GROWLING]
- WHAT IS IT, KILALA?
ARE THERE DEMONS NEARBY?
- I SENSE A JEWEL SHARD!
- WHAT'S THAT?
KAGOME, IS IT THIS WAY?
- YES, IT'S JUST
BEYOND THIS FOREST.
- NARAKU'S POISONOUS INSECTS!
- SO, THEY'RE AFTER THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARD, TOO, ARE THEY?
- KOHAKU, YOU CANNOT
ESCAPE FROM ME.
SURRENDER AND GIVE ME THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARD IN YOUR BACK.
- SACRED JEWEL SHARD?
- SURRENDER THE JEWEL!
- AAH!
- [GROWLING]
- KOHAKU!
- THAT DEMON IS TRYING
TO GET THE SHARD
EMBEDDED IN KOHAKU'S BACK!
- WHAT?
THE SACRED SHARD EMBEDDED
IN KOHAKU'S BACK
IS HIS LIFELINE.
IF THE SHARD IS REMOVED,
HE'LL DIE.
HYAH!
- [GROWLING]
- [GROANING]
HUH?
- KOHAKU.
YOUR MIND WAS
UNDER NARAKU'S CONTROL,
AND YOU WERE IN NARAKU'S CASTLE.
SO, WHY ARE YOU HERE NOW?
- WHO ARE YOU?
DO YOU KNOW ME?
- [GASP]
- HUH?
- YOU'VE HURT YOUR ARM.
LET ME SEE IT.
- UH...EXCUSE ME.
- HMM?
- HAVE WE, YOU KNOW,
UH, MET BEFORE?
- MM-HMM.
- THINK, KOHAKU.
ARE YOU SURE YOU DON'T
REMEMBER ANYTHING AT ALL
FROM BEFORE YOU
ESCAPED THE CASTLE?
- HMM.
NO.
- YOU DON'T REMEMBER NARAKU?
- NARAKU?
- KOHAKU, I HAVE NO NEED
TO KEEP YOU ALIVE ANY LONGER.
GO JOIN YOUR FATHER
AND THE OTHERS.
- WAIT A MINUTE.
COULD HE HAVE BEEN NARAKU?
- I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK THE KID IS JUST
PUTTING ON AN ACT FOR US.
- IT DOESN'T APPEAR
THAT WAY TO ME.
- YOU MEAN YOU TRUST HIM?
- I DIDN'T SAY THAT.
LAST TIME WE SAW KOHAKU,
HE WAS VIRTUALLY A PUPPET...
LIKE A HUMAN WITHOUT A SOUL.
NOW WE HAVE THIS BOY.
- HMM?
- DO YOU THINK IT'S SAFE TO
LEAVE THEM ALONE, KAGOME?
- SANGO WANTED IT THAT WAY,
SO I WASN'T GONNA
ARGUE WITH HER.
- THE SLAYERS' VILLAGE?
- YES.
THAT'S WHERE WE USED
TO LIVE, KOHAKU.
- HMM?
THEN YOU MEAN I WAS
A DEMON SLAYER, AS WELL?
- YOU WERE STILL AN APPRENTICE.
- REST YOURSELF, SANGO.
WE'LL BE NEEDING YOU
AGAIN IN A SHORT TIME.
- YES, FATHER.
- KOHAKU, YOU, TOO,
MUST PREPARE FOR BATTLE.
- WHO? UH, ME?
- YES, YOU ARE 11 NOW,
PLENTY OLD ENOUGH
TO GO INTO BATTLE.
- MM-HMM.
- SANGO?
- YES?
- DO DEMONS BREATHE FIRE
AND TOXINS, AS THEY SAY?
- SOMETIMES.
- THEN IT'S TRUE.
- KOHAKU, WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU SCARED?
- NO, I NEVER SAID
I WAS SCARED.
- YOU'LL BE FINE.
WE EXTERMINATE
SNAKES AND SPIDERS
AND OTHER SUCH LARGE BEASTS.
AS FATHER SAYS,
THE MOST FRIGHTENING DEMON
IS ONE THAT MASQUERADES
AS A HUMAN BEING.
HE SAYS THAT IF
THAT TYPE OF DEMON
COMES TO POSSESS JEWEL,
THEN IT'S TROUBLE.
THE DAY WE WERE
LURED IN BY NARAKU
WAS KOHAKU'S VERY FIRST
EXPERIENCE IN BATTLE.
- SAY, TELL ME EVERYTHING
YOU KNOW ABOUT ME.
- UH...
- I FEEL SO EMPTY
'CAUSE I DON'T KNOW
HOW I GOT HERE.
- HE'S JUST LIKE
THE KOHAKU I REMEMBER--
QUIET AND A BIT COWARDLY.
- HUH?
- DON'T RUSH IT.
IT'LL TAKE TIME TO REMEMBER.
WE'LL HAVE ALL THE TIME
IN THE WORLD TOGETHER NOW.
- UH...
EXCUSE ME?
- HMM?
- YOU'RE EMBRACING ME.
IT'S KIND OF EMBARRASSING.
- WHY ARE YOU SO SHY?
WE'RE SIBLINGS.
KOHAKU HAS COME BACK TO ME.
HE'S ESCAPED FROM
NARAKU'S GRASP.
THAT'S WHAT I WANT TO BELIEVE.
- [SIGHS]
- HUH?
- [CLICKING]
- WELL, I'M SURE
A COUPLE GOOD PUNCHES
WOULD KNOCK THE TRUTH
OUT OF HIM.
- COME ON NOW.
YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
- KAGOME IS RIGHT.
IT'S NOT AS SIMPLE AS ALL THAT.
I CAN'T SAY WHETHER
OR NOT IT'S A TRAP,
BUT THE FACT IS,
SANGO'S BEEN REUNITED
WITH HER YOUNGER BROTHER.
- YEAH, AND IF IT IS A TRAP,
THEN SANGO WILL
BE HEARTBROKEN.
- WE HAVE TO KEEP
IN MIND THAT NARAKU
LOVES TO TOY WITH
PEOPLE'S FEELINGS.
HUH?
- HMM!
- INUYASHA?
- IF YOU TWO WON'T TELL HER,
THEN I WILL.
- HOLD ON!
DON'T DO IT, INUYASHA!
- HUH?
WHAT?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- LISTEN, SANGO,
IT'S ABOUT KOHAKU.
IT'S OBVIOUSLY ONE
OF NARAKU'S TRAPS.
- [GASPS]
YOU'RE WRONG!
I TRUST KOHAKU.
- THAT'S WHAT NARAKU WANTS.
- WHAT CHOICE DO I HAVE,
EXCEPT TO TRUST
MY YOUNGER BROTHER?
- THIS WHOLE THING
REEKS OF NARAKU.
- IF WE HADN'T COME TO HIS AID,
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD
WOULD HAVE BEEN REMOVED,
AND MY BROTHER REALLY
WOULD HAVE DIED.
- THAT'S THE TRAP.
THAT'S WHAT HE
WANTS YOU TO THINK.
- IT'S NOT A TRAP!
- THAT NICE LADY
WILL BECOME UNHAPPY,
AND IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
I CAN'T STAY.
- YOU'RE BEING BLINDED BY
LOVE FOR YOUR KID BROTHER!
- ENOUGH!
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW I FEEL!
- OPEN YOUR EYES!
- FAREWELL, THEN.
- LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING--
- HMM?
- HUH?
- [RUMBLING]
- THEY'RE COMING.
- HUNDREDS OF THEM.
- [BUZZING]
- NARAKU'S POISONOUS INSECTS!
- NARAKU'S ADVANCE GUARD.
- IT'S KOHAKU THEY'RE AFTER.
- FORGET ABOUT HIM, SANGO!
[GRUNTING]
- KOHAKU?
KOHAKU?
- SANGO, I CAN SENSE THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARD IS ON THE MOVE.
LET'S GO, SANGO.
WE'VE GOTTA PROTECT KOHAKU.
- YES, RIGHT.
- [GRUNTS]
- AAH!
- HUH?
- [CHUCKLING]
- KAGURA, WHAT DO YOU
WANT THIS TIME?
- I KNOW YOU'RE HIDING KOHAKU.
INUYASHA, LET ME HAVE HIM.
- WHAT?
- DON'T PLAY INNOCENT WITH ME.
HAND OVER NARAKU'S KEPT BOY.
YOU SEE, KOHAKU WENT BERSERK
AND RAN OFF FROM THE CASTLE
WITH A SACRED JEWEL SHARD
EMBEDDED IN HIS BACK.
- AND THAT'S THE REASON
YOU'VE COME FOR HIM?
- NARAKU ALWAYS GOES OVERBOARD.
IMAGINE DISPATCHING
THIS ENORMOUS ARMY
SIMPLY BECAUSE
HE WANTS THE SHARD.
- SO, YOU'RE AFTER THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARD, ARE YOU?
- CORRECT.
ALTHOUGH ONCE IT'S REMOVED,
KOHAKU WILL DIE.
WE'RE UNDER ORDERS TO LET
SANGO HAVE HIM AFTER THAT.
- HUH?
HOW DARE YOU?!
- [PANTING]
- [BUZZING]
- [GASPS]
AAH!
- [PANTING]
- [BUZZING]
- AAH!
- [GASPING]
- JUST IN THE NICK OF TIME.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY DID YOU COME?
IT WAS ME THAT THEY WERE AFTER.
HUH?
UH...
- KOHAKU, STAY HERE.
DON'T LEAVE ME ANYMORE.
- WHY?
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS FOR ME?
HUH?
- YOU'RE MY BROTHER, THAT'S WHY.
KOHAKU, YOU'RE MY ONE
AND ONLY LITTLE BROTHER.
- [GROWLING]
- KILALA?
- PROTECT KOHAKU FOR ME,
AND I'LL GO STOP THOSE DEMONS.
- SURE THING. GOOD LUCK!
- KILALA!
- [ROARS]
- KOHAKU, YOU MUST LIVE!
- COME ON, LET'S GO!
- HUH?
[PANTING]
- [GROWLING]
- HOW WILL WE STOP THEM?
- I CAN DO IT.
- [SNARLING]
- I'M OUT OF ARROWS.
LET'S HIDE IN THAT HOLE.
- [BUZZING]
- WE'LL WAIT UNTIL INUYASHA
AND THE OTHERS COME.
- THAT LADY.
- HUH?
- I HOPE SHE'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
- OH, YOU MEAN SANGO.
SHE CAN HANDLE HERSELF.
SHE'S STRONG.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT HER.
SANGO'S YOUR OLDER SISTER.
CAN'T YOU REMEMBER HER?
OR ARE YOUR MEMORIES
STILL LOCKED UP
INSIDE OF YOU, KOHAKU?
- HMM.
I DO SEEM TO KNOW HER.
I MEAN, SHE SEEMS SO FAMILIAR.
- I'M SURE SHE DOES.
YOU KNOW, SANGO HAS
BEEN SO WORRIED ABOUT YOU
EVER SINCE THE TWO OF
YOU WERE TORN APART.
SHE TRIES TO PUT
ON A CHEERFUL FACE,
BUT SOMETIMES HER SADNESS
STILL GETS THE BETTER OF HER.
SO, I'M GLAD YOU'VE RETURNED,
FOR YOUR SAKE AND FOR HERS.
- [SIGH]
DO YOU REALLY THINK
IT WOULD BE ALL RIGHT
IF I STAY WITH HER, THEN?
- OF COURSE IT IS.
AND THAT WAY, YOU'LL EVENTUALLY
START TO REMEMBER HER.
- MM-HMM.
I WANT TO REMEMBER HER
AND EVERYTHING ELSE.
STILL, WHY DO I FEEL THIS WAY?
IT'S LIKE I'M SCARED.
THERE'S SOMETHING
I DON'T WANT TO REMEMBER.
- KILL HER.
KILL KAGOME.
- [GASPS]
- WHAT'S KEEPING HIM?
HURRY, INUYASHA.
- WHAT A SHAME THAT YOU'RE
ALL OUT OF ARROWS.
- HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
KOHAKU?
- [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- NARAKU IS STILL CONTROLLING
THE AMNESIA-RIDDEN KOHAKU,
WHO'S ABOUT TO CARRY OUT
HIS ORDERS TO KILL KAGOME.
SANGO FINDS OUT AND RESOLVES
TO KILL KOHAKU, THEN HERSELF.
MIROKU RECOGNIZES IT'S A TRAP
AND USES HIS WIND TUNNEL
TO SUCK IN THE DEMONS,
POISON INSECTS AND ALL.
HURRY, INUYASHA!
YOU HAVE TO STOP SANGO!
NEXT TIME,
"THAT UNFORGETTABLE FACE."
SEE YOU SOON!