>> IN A STRANGE TURN OF EVENTS
DURING OUR PURSUIT OF NARAKU,
WE END UP HELPING
AN OLD EXORCIST.
>> IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
>> HOWEVER, CONSIDERING THAT SHE
CAN'T EVEN SENSE A DEMONIC AURA,
THE EXORCIST'S TALENTS ARE A BIT
SUSPECT.
THROUGH HER, WE ARE HIRED TO
SLAY THE DEMON THAT HAS BEEN
TERRORIZING THE DEMON'S HEAD
CASTLE, AND WE LEARN OF THE
CLAN'S STRANGE LORD AND MEET
HIS DAUGHTER--A DAZZLING BEAUTY
OF A PRINCESS.
AT THE PRINCESS' REQUEST, I WILL
PERSONALLY SLAY THIS DEMON AND
FREE THE DEMON'S HEAD CASTLE.
>> UHH!
WIND SCAR!
>> ON THE NIGHT THAT THE GIANT
DEMON HEAD APPEARS, THOUGH,
INUYASHA'S WIND SCAR
HAS NO EFFECT.
THE DEMON HEAD MUST BE AN
ILLUSION, MEANING ITS TRUE FORM
HAS TO BE SOMEWHERE ELSE.
>> [GROANING]
>> AAH!
>> [GROWLING]
>> OH!
>> LOOK! THE LORD!
>> LET HIM GO.
HUH!
SO, THIS IS THE TRUE FORM
OF THE DEMON.
>> [PANTING]
>> OHH!
DAMN YOU!
>> I MADE SURE I BROUGHT THE
EXORCIST'S PURIFICATION SALT.
ADDING MY OWN SPIRITUAL POWER
MADE IT WORK.
[THINKING] I'M IN TROUBLE.
THIS DEMON IS POWERFUL,
AND THIS DEMONIC AURA
HAS LEFT ME PARALYZED.
>> HA HA HA HA!
MONK, THERE'S NO HELP
FORTHCOMING.
BESIDES, THAT HALF-DEMON IS
PROBABLY FIGHTING THE LORD
BACK AT THE CASTLE.
I USED MY DARK MAGIC TO
MANIPULATE THAT FOOLISH
PUPPET LORD.
HA HA HA HA!
>> [THINKING] WHAT?
INUYASHA, HELP ME!
>> [ROARING]
>> [PEOPLE WHIMPERING]
>> DEAR GOD.
>> YOU'VE GOT SOME NERVE
SHOWING YOUR TRUE SELF,
HUH, DEMON?
>> [ROARING]
>> PREPARE TO DIE!
>> [WOMAN SCREAMING]
>> HE'S USING HER AS A SHIELD!
>> INUYASHA, DON'T USE
THE TETSUSAIGA.
>> DAMN.
IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
>> [GRUNTING]
>> HUH.
NOT TOO STRONG, ARE YOU?
HUH?
OH, NO, YOU DON'T!
>> HE'S GONE. SAFE AT LAST!
>> DON'T BE SO FOOLISH.
IT'S TOO EARLY TO REST AT EASE.
YOU WOMEN PROTECT THE PRINCESS.
>> I'M AFRAID THAT WE CANNOT.
>> IS SOMETHING THE MATTER?
>> YES, THERE IS.
>> THE UNDERGROUND BURIAL SITE
OF THE DEMON HEAD?
>> YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
SHE WANTED TO SHOW IT
TO THE MONK.
>> SANGO!
>> I'M GOING TO GET MIROKU!
>> I'M COMING WITH YOU.
IT'S SAFER THAN STAYING HERE.
>> MADAM EXORCIST,
WHAT ARE YOU...
>> THAT TURNED OUT QUITE WELL,
DON'T YOU THINK?
>> HUH?
>> YOU MUST HAVE BEEN QUITE
WORRIED, KNOWING THAT THE MONK
AND THE PRINCESS WERE IN
EACH OTHER'S ARMS.
BUT AT AN UNDERGROUND BURIAL
SITE, OF ALL PLACES.
NOTHING ROMANTIC COULD EVER
HAPPEN THERE.
>> PLEASE.
THIS IS HARDLY THE TIME
FOR SUCH NONSENSE.
>> YOU'RE VERY FOND OF HIM.
I CAN TELL THE MONK MEANS
QUITE A LOT TO YOU.
HMM.
IT'S WRITTEN ALL OVER YOUR FACE.
>> IT'S NOT LIKE THAT,
OLD WOMAN.
WHERE DID SHE GO?
>> HURRY IT UP,
OR I'LL LEAVE YOU BEHIND.
>> GRRRR!
>> [MEOW]
>> HA HA HA HA!
YOU CANNOT MOVE, I SEE.
NO ONE CAN OVERCOME THE GRIP
OF MY DEMONIC AURA.
>> YOU INTEND TO CONSUME ME?
>> ALL THE MONKS AND PRIESTESSES
WHO CAME TO SLAY THE DEMON
WERE DEVOURED BY ME.
HA HA HA HA!
LUCKY MONK.
YOU ARE EXACTLY MY 100th VICTIM.
I SHALL DEVOUR YOU
AND YOUR SPIRITUAL POWERS.
THEN I WILL BE COMPLETELY
REBORN, AND I SHALL DISCARD
THIS EMPTY SHELL.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> HA HA HA HA!
SUCH A FINE COUNTENANCE,
SWEET MONK.
>> [GROANING]
>> DON'T WORRY.
YOU'RE NOT FATALLY WOUNDED.
>> I HAVE TO STOP THE BLEEDING.
>> MISS, THANK YOU FOR HELPING.
>> DON'T TRY TO TALK.
THIS IS GONNA STING A BIT,
BUT IT WON'T LAST LONG.
>> THEY'VE ALL BEEN KILLED
BY THE DEMON.
>> LET'S GO.
WE MIGHT FIND SOMEONE
WHO'S STILL ALIVE.
IS ANYONE IN HERE?
[THINKING] THIS IS IT.
THIS IS THE ROOM THE LORD
REFUSED TO LEAVE.
>> OH!
KAGOME, LOOK AT THAT!
>> HUH?
A WOMAN'S IN THERE, ASLEEP.
EXCUSE ME.
[GASP]
[THINKING] THE PRINCESS?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
THE PRINCESS IS SUPPOSED TO BE
UNDERGROUND AT THE BURIAL SITE.
[GASP]
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS!
>> HUH?
>> SHE'S DEAD.
>> HAH!
>> UHH!
>> [BOTH GRUNTING]
>> DAMN YOU!
ENOUGH OF THIS ALREADY!
HUH?
>> [MOANING]
>> WHAT'S HE DOING BACKING OFF?
>> [GROWLING]
>> WHAT WAS THAT?
THE DEMON WAS TRANSPARENT
FOR A SECOND THERE.
SOMETHING'S WRONG HERE.
THIS DEMON KEEPS BACKING AWAY
AND NEVER ATTACKS,
ALMOST AS IF--
[GASP]
ALMOST AS IF HE'S BUYING TIME.
>> HUH?
WHO WAS THAT?
SOMEONE HAS TOUCHED
THE HOST BODY!
>> [GRUNTS]
>> MIROKU!
UGH!
WHY, YOU...
[GASP]
[THINKING] I CAN'T MOVE!
>> [SNARLING]
>> [THINKING] KIRARA,
YOU CAN'T, EITHER!
>> UHH!
>> HA HA HA HA!
STAND STILL AND WATCH
MY EVERY MOVE.
I WILL DEVOUR
THIS DELECTABLE MONK!
>> [GRUNTING]
[THINKING] DAMN HER.
HUH?
>> THE EXORCIST!
>> DISPERSE TO THE WIND,
EVIL POWERS THAT PREVAIL!
UHH!
A LITTLE PURIFICATION SALT.
>> WHY DOES MY DEMONIC AURA
NOT WORK ON THIS EVIL WOMAN?
>> [GRUNTING]
EXORCIST, USE IT ALL!
THROW ALL THE PURIFICATION SALT
ON HER!
>> HUH?
TAKE THAT!
>> AAH!
>> MM-HMM.
>> [SCREAMING]
DAMN YOU TO HELL, MONK!
YOU PUT A SPELL
ON THE PURIFICATION SALT!
>> HUH?
MIROKU!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> I DIDN'T THINK I WAS GONNA
MAKE IT.
UH, MADAM EXORCIST?
>> YES? WHAT IS IT NOW?
>> HOW DID YOU OVERCOME THE GRIP
OF THAT DEMONIC AURA?
>> OH? WHAT AURA?
I DIDN'T SENSE ANYTHING UNUSUAL.
>> [THINKING] HUH?
>> [THINKING] YOU REALLY
DON'T SENSE IT?
>> [THINKING] I SUPPOSE
SHE'S SPECIAL IN SOME WAYS.
>> WE CAN'T AFFORD TO SIT HERE
WASTING PRECIOUS TIME.
THE DEMON HEAD FLEW OFF
AND IS STILL ALIVE.
>> HUH?
[THINKING] WHAT'S THIS?
THE PRESENCE IS GROWING
STRONGER.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
>> [GROWLING]
>> WHAT WAS THAT?
>> I FEEL SOMETHING.
>> [BOTH WHIMPERING]
>> [THINKING] THE DEMONIC AURA'S
RISING FROM THE DEMON'S HEAD
CASTLE.
>> [ROARING]
>> [THINKING] THIS DEMON IS JUST
A DIVERSION TO SIDETRACK ME.
THE REAL DEMON IS INSIDE
THE CASTLE.
BETTER HURRY.
WHY DON'T YOU GET BACK INSIDE
THE CASTLE WHERE YOU BELONG,
DEMON?
>> [PANTING]
>> SO THE DEMON TOOK THE GUISE
OF THE PRINCESS AND DEVOURED
THE MONKS AND PRIESTESSES WHO
CAME TO EXORCISE THE CASTLE?
>> SHE SAID THAT I WAS TO BE
THE 100th VICTIM.
>> HMM. MAKES NO SENSE.
WHY DID THE DEMON COME AFTER YOU
AND NOT ME?
AFTER ALL, I'M THE STRONGER ONE.
>> [TOGETHER] UH...
>> THAT DEMON DEVOURS
SPIRITUAL POWER.
ONCE IT CONSUMED THE POWERS
OF 100, IT WAS GOING TO BE
COMPLETELY REBORN.
>> I UNDERSTAND NOW.
THAT MEANS I MUST HAVE BEEN
NUMBER 101.
OTHERWISE, THERE'S NO WAY
IT WOULD HAVE IGNORED SOMEONE
WITH MY EXTRAORDINARY POWERS.
HUH?
ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME?
>> A...A DEMON HEAD?
>> [GROWLING]
>> [THINKING] WHAT ARE
THOSE THINGS COMING OUT OF
THE PRINCESS' BODY?
>> [ROARING]
>> LOOK!
WHAT ARE THOSE THINGS
IT'S EATING?
>> HA HA HA HA!
I BURIED THE SPIRITUAL POWERS
OF 99 VICTIMS INSIDE THAT BODY.
I NEED JUST ONE MORE.
THAT MONK WOULD HAVE BEEN
MY LAST.
HUH?
YOUNG WOMAN, WHAT IS THAT?
WHAT IS THAT YOU CARRY WITH YOU?
>> HUH?
[THINKING] THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARDS!
>> HA HA HA HA!
THIS MIGHT BE BETTER
THAN CONSUMING THE POWERS
OF A MERE HUMAN.
>> [THINKING] SHE'S GOING TO
EAT ME!
>> AAH!
>> [ROARING]
>> I'M NOT GONNA BE YOUR DINNER,
YOU HEAR?
TAKE THAT!
>> [SCREAMING]
>> HURRY, SHIPPO. YOUR FOXFIRE!
>> RIGHT.
FOXFIRE!
>> NOW'S OUR CHANCE.
>> MM-HMM.
>> STOP! NOT SO FAST!
>> [TOGETHER] AAH!
>> AAH!
>> YOU WON'T ESCAPE.
SURRENDER, AND GET IT OVER WITH.
>> [GASP]
>> AAH!
>> YOU WON'T ESCAPE.
SURRENDER, AND GET IT OVER WITH!
>> [GASP]
>> UHH!
NO, YOU DON'T!
>> [SCREAMING]
>> SO SHE'S FINALLY SHOWING
HERSELF.
>> INUYASHA!
>> YOU'RE LATE.
>> HUH?
>> A SECOND LATER, AND SHE WOULD
HAVE BEEN DEMON FOOD!
>> SHUT UP!
YOU SHOULD BE THANKING ME
FOR EVEN SHOWING UP.
>> WHAT DID YOU SAY?
>> COME ON, YOU GUYS.
>> WHY, YOU...
OH!
HOW DARE YOU?
YOU FIEND!
MY BEAUTIFUL FACE IS SCARRED!
YOU'VE RUINED ME!
YOU'LL PAY WITH YOUR LIFE!
>> LIKE THEY SAY,
IT'S ONLY SKIN-DEEP.
>> [SCREAMING]
>> YOU'VE CAUSED ENOUGH TROUBLE
AROUND HERE.
TIME TO PUT AN END TO THIS.
>> OH, YOU HALF-BREED!
>> THIS TIME YOU'RE GOING DOWN.
PREPARE TO DIE!
>> THE DEMON!
>> IS IT UNCONSCIOUS?
>> HUH?
>> OH!
>> LOOK. MY LORD!
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> [ALL TALKING AT ONCE]
>> HUH.
>> DIE!
HUH?
STAY STILL, WOULD YOU?
>> HA HA HA HA!
>> WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
>> THE OCCUPANTS OF THIS CASTLE
BURIED MY HEAD UNDERGROUND.
THEY HOPED THAT IT WOULD
WARD OFF EVIL.
THOSE FOOLISH HUMANS!
THAT'S WHY I CURSED THE PRINCESS
TO DEATH, THEN ASSUMED
HER APPEARANCE.
AND INTO HER CORPSE, I HID THE
SPIRITUAL POWERS THAT I STOLE
FROM THOSE I DEVOURED.
>> SO THE LORD WAS MERELY
GUARDING THE PRINCESS' BODY
AND ACTING AS A DECOY IN CASE
THE TRUTH WERE EVER LEARNED.
HUH.
WELL, THAT'S TOO BAD FOR YOU,
DEMON HEAD.
YOU'RE MESSING WITH THE WRONG
PEOPLE THIS TIME.
>> HA HA HA HA!
DO YOU THINK SO?
>> I KNOW SO!
>> WAIT. STOP!
>> HMM?
>> MIROKU!
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT, MIROKU?
QUIT INTERFERING!
>> I HAVE TO ASK THE DEMON
SOMETHING BEFORE IT'S DESTROYED.
>> LIKE WHAT?
>> MONK?
>> TELL ME, WHY DIDN'T YOU MAKE
YOUR ESCAPE SOONER?
YOU HAD EASILY OVERPOWERED ME.
WITH SUCH AN OBVIOUSLY POWERFUL
DEMONIC AURA, YOU COULD HAVE
ESCAPED ANYTIME YOU WANTED.
>> HA HA HA HA!
UNTIL NOW, I HAD TO BE CAREFUL
ABOUT APPEARING.
I KNEW THAT THERE WAS A STRONGER
PRESENCE--ONE THAT COULD TAKE
COMPLETE CONTROL OF ME.
>> [TOGETHER] HUH?
>> HUH?
A STRONGER PRESENCE?
>> CORRECT.
NARAKU AND THE DEMONIC AURA
HE CONTROLLED.
HOWEVER, NARAKU IS NO LONGER
AROUND, AND I DON'T HAVE TO
HIDE MYSELF IN THIS CASTLE
ANY LONGER!
>> IT'S ESCAPING!
>> HA HA HA HA!
NOW I CAN HAVE MY FILL OF MONKS
AND PRIESTESSES!
>> NOT HAPPENING, UGLY.
WIND SCAR!
>> HUH?
[SCREAMING]
>> HE DID IT!
>> [GRUNTS]
>> IT'S STILL ALIVE.
>> THE WIND SCAR DIDN'T WORK.
>> HA HA HA HA!
IT'S JUST A START.
I'LL RESTORE MY BODY
AND WREAK HAVOC ON THIS LAND!
WHAT?!
>> WIND TUNNEL!
>> [SCREAMING]
>> [GRUNTING]
IT'S ALL OVER, FINALLY.
>> ABOUT TIME.
WHAT A PAIN THAT WAS.
>> LOOK!
>> THE SKY IS RETURNING
TO NORMAL.
>> THE DEMON'S DESTROYED,
AND THE DEMONIC AURA OVER
THE CASTLE HAS DISAPPEARED.
>> SO IT'S ALL BECAUSE THIS
DEMON NAMED NARAKU HAS VANISHED?
AND THAT'S WHY THE DEMONS
IN THIS REGION ARE ACTING UP
SO MUCH?
>> IT SEEMS SO.
>> AH.
THEN I CAN SEE THAT I'LL BE
GETTING VERY BUSY.
BUSINESS WILL SOON BE BOOMING.
>> HUH?
>> OLD WOMAN, I HAVE ONE PIECE
OF ADVICE FOR YOU.
RETIRE.
YOU'RE NOTHING BUT A FAKE
EXORCIST ANYWAY.
>> INUYASHA, DON'T BE SO BLUNT.
>> SHUT YOUR MOUTH.
IF IT WEREN'T FOR ME
AND MY PURIFICATION SALT,
THE MONK WOULD BE NOTHING
BUT A MEMORY NOW.
>> AND I'M GRATEFUL TO YOU.
>> HUH. WOULD YOU LISTEN TO HER?
>> I THINK THIS EXPERIENCE
HAS MADE HER OVERCONFIDENT.
>> AND UNFORTUNATELY FOR US,
SHE'LL PROBABLY LIVE
A LONG LIFE.
>> YEAH, MEANING SHE WON'T BE
EASY TO GET RID OF.
>> HUH? DID YOU SAY SOMETHING?
>> [TOGETHER] UH, NOPE.
>> HEY, COME ON.
LET'S GET GOING.
>> GOOD IDEA.
>> IF ANYTHING COMES UP,
I'D BE HAPPY TO HELP
YOU YOUNGSTERS.
>> THANKS.
WE MIGHT TAKE YOU UP ON THAT.
>> TAKE CARE! THANKS AGAIN!
>> WELL, PEOPLE, THIS IS
BECOMING A REAL PROBLEM.
WITH NARAKU'S DISAPPEARANCE,
EVEN THE DEMONS WHO WERE IN
HIDING ARE STARTING TO LOOK FOR
THE JEWEL SHARDS.
>> HUH.
THEY'RE NOTHING BUT A BUNCH
OF PUNY DEMONS WHO WERE SCARED
OF NARAKU.
I COULD TAKE CARE OF EVERY
SINGLE ONE OF THEM.
[THINKING] BESIDES, IT'S NOT
LIKE NARAKU HAS COMPLETELY
VANISHED OFF THE FACE
OF THE EARTH.
I WILL DEFINITELY FIND HIM.
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> WHY AM I LIVING
IN THIS WORLD?
JUST WHAT AM I?
AND WHERE AM I GOING?
WHAT WAS IT THAT CAUSED MY FATE
TO GO AWRY?
THAT TIME THAT I SPENT WITH
INUYASHA, WHEN I SAVED ONIGUMO.
NEXT TIME,
"KIKYO'S LONELY JOURNEY."
IS THAT MOUNT HAKUREI-SAN?