- MY ETERNAL LIEGE,
THE ULTIMATE DEMON WITHOUT
RIVAL, LORD SESSHOMARU.
HIS FATHER'S HEIRLOOM,
THE TETSUSAIGA,
IS ABLE TO FELL 100 DEMONS
WITH ONE SWEEP OF
ITS MIGHTY BLADE,
AND ONLY MY LORD IS WORTHY
OF ITS MAGNIFICENCE.
SUCH A SWORD IS WASTED ON
LORD SESSHOMARU'S YOUNGER
BROTHER INUYASHA,
THAT DESPICABLE HALF-DEMON
WITH A MORTAL FOR A MOTHER.
- HMM!
[GASPS]
[WOLF HOWLS]
[GROWLING]
- HUH?
- RIN.
- YES? WHAT IS IT,
MY LORD?
- IF YOU'RE HUNGRY, YOU MUST
FEND FOR YOURSELF.
- ALL RIGHT.
I'M OFF.
- OH, MY GOODNESS.
LORD SESSHOMARU'S INSTRUCTED
RIN TO FEND FOR HERSELF.
SO WHY DID HE THEN DEMAND
THAT I ACCOMPANY HER?
- HOW FAR ARE WE GOING,
MASTER JAKEN?
- UNTIL WE FIND FOOD!
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- HMM.
MASTER JAKEN,
HOW EXACTLY ARE YOU
OF ANY SERVICE
TO LORD SESSHOMARU?
- MMM!
I SERVE HIM IN
INNUMERABLE WAYS!
- YOU DO?
- YES!
FOR INSTANCE, UH...
[GASPS]
INUYASHA'S TETSUSAIGA
TURNED BRILLIANT RED.
- [GROWLING]
- I CAN'T BEGIN TO FATHOM
HOW LORD SESSHOMARU FEELS,
BUT INUYASHA'S SWORD HAS
BECOME EXTREMELY DANGEROUS.
IT CAN EVEN BREAK
THROUGH A DEMON BARRIER.
IT'S TRUE THAT MY LORD
HAS HIS OWN SWORD,
THE TOKIJIN,
AS WELL AS THE TENSEIGA,
BUT NO GOOD CAN COME
OF INUYASHA WIELDING
SUCH A DEADLY WEAPON.
I KNOW.
I SIMPLY HAVE TO TAKE
THE SWORD AWAY FROM HIM.
[CHUCKLES]
- MASTER JAKEN?
- LISTEN HERE, RIN!
TODAY YOU SHALL WITNESS
THE GREAT LENGTH
I GO TO SERVE OUR LORD!
NO VASSAL HAS EVER SERVED
HIM AS I AM ABOUT TO!
- COME ON,
LET'S DO IT AGAIN.
- READY?
- ROCK, PAPER, SCISSORS!
- YEAH!
WE WIN AGAIN!
- [CHUCKLES]
NOTHING BEATS THE SWEET
SMELL OF VICTORY, RIGHT?
- LET'S SEE.
IRON REAPER,
SOUL STEALER.
- OK, READY TO LOSE AGAIN?
- CAN YOU HEAR US
BACK THERE, SANGO?
- LOUD AND CLEAR.
- [SIGH]
- I WISH YOU WOULD STOP
SIGHING ALL THE TIME.
IT'S MORE IRRITATING
THAN LOSING THE GAME.
- WE WOULD HAVE HAD
ANOTHER CHANCE AT A DRAW
IF ONLY YOU HADN'T SHOWN
THE SAME SCISSORS HAND I DID.
OH, I UNDERSTAND.
YOU WANTED TO
LOSE ON PURPOSE
SO THAT YOU COULD STAY
BEHIND THE OTHERS WITH ME.
[GRUNTS]
- NO SUCH THING.
WE SIMPLY LOST,
AND NOTHING ELSE.
- THE CURSE OF THIS DAMN HAND
RUNS DEEPER THAN I EXPECTED.
- IT'S YOUR PERSONALITY
THAT'S CURSED.
- ROCK, PAPER, SCISSORS!
- WE DID IT!
WE BEAT THOSE
GUYS AGAIN!
- AND WE DID IT
WITH PAPER.
THAT MAKES IT
THE WIND TUNNEL.
- ♪ WIND TUNNEL! ♪
- NOW, LISTEN, ARE YOU SURE
YOU WEREN'T CHEATING?
- STOP BEING SUCH A POOR LOSER.
- ROCK, PAPER, SCISSORS!
HA HA HA!
OH, THEY'RE COMING
THIS WAY AT LAST!
NOW, HURRY UP
AND COME OUT, NOMAN!
WHAT'S TAKING
YOU SO LONG?
- [GRUMBLING]
YOU SUMMONED?
- NOMAN, INUYASHA AND HIS
FRIENDS ARE COMING,
SO GET CLOSE TO THEM
AND STEAL THE TETSUSAIGA.
YOU ARE A DEMON BORN
FROM THE REGRETS OF MAN,
SO YOU SHOULD BE ABLE
TO GRASP THE SWORD.
NOW, SET OUT AND STEAL IT!
- THE TETSUSAIGA?
- IT'S INUYASHA'S
PRECIOUS TREASURE.
- IS IT VALUABLE?
- MM-HMM.
FIND IT AND BRING
IT BACK TO ME.
- ROCK, PAPER, SCISSORS!
- HOW ABOUT THAT?
WE WON AGAIN!
- YOU'RE GOOD
AT THIS, KAGOME.
- YEP.
THIS IS ONE OF
MY SPECIALTIES.
WE WON WITH SCISSORS,
SO THAT MAKES IT...
♪ HERE I COME! ♪
- I CAN HARDLY
SEE THEM ANYMORE.
- IF WE CAN'T SEE THEM,
HOW ARE WE GONNA
KNOW IF THEY CHEAT?
- THERE YOU GO AGAIN.
- [CHIRPING]
- MIROKU.
- INUYASHA,
SOMETHING IS COMING.
- WHAT?
WHAT IS THIS?
- A MIST?
- NOT REALLY.
IT'S MORE LIKE SMOKE.
- THINK IT'S A MOUNTAIN FIRE?
- NO, NOT LIKELY.
WHAT WAS THAT?
- GET YOUR HANDS OFF ME!
- AH! NO, IT WASN'T
ME, SANGO.
- [COUGHING]
- AH!
SOMETHING'S
TOUCHING ME!
- KAGOME!
- WHY, YOU--
[COUGHING]
- [GASP]
THEY'RE GONE!
THE JEWEL SHARDS
ARE MISSING!
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
MISSING?
- WHAT'S TAKING THAT
BUMBLING FOOL SO LONG?
HUH?
- MASTER JAKEN, I'VE
BROUGHT YOUR TREASURES.
- EXCELLENT!
DID YOU GET
THE TETSUSAIGA?
- HERE.
- THAT'S NOT IT!
THAT'S NOT IT, EITHER!
I HAVE NO NEED
FOR THOSE!
- WHAT ABOUT THESE
TREASURES?
- YOU FOOL!
THESE AREN'T TREASURES!
WHY DIDN'T YOU BRING ME
BACK THE TETSUSAIGA?
- TETSUSAIGA?
- IT'S INUYASHA'S SWORD!
- ALL HE HAD WAS
A RUSTY OLD THING.
- FOOL, THAT'S THE--AAH!
- IT DIDN'T LOOK NEARLY AS
VALUABLE AS THESE TREASURES.
- STOP YOUR BABBLING
AND GO GET ME THE SWORD!
- [GRUMBLES]
- WHAT A DIMWIT!
- MASTER JAKEN,
ARE YOU CERTAIN
THAT THE DEMON
CAN HANDLE THIS?
- IF ONLY I HAD
SOME HENCHMEN,
THIS JOB WOULD
BE EASIER.
AH, FOR THE OLD DAYS...
WHEN I WAS THE COMMANDER
AND HAD MANY
SERVING UNDER ME.
BACK THEN, I HAD
HUNDREDS OF DEMONS
AND CONTROLLED
THE PLAINS OF MUSASHI.
WE WERE AT BATTLE
WITH THE DEMONS
THAT CONTROLLED
THE EASTERN MOUNTAINS.
THEIR LEADER WAS BIKUNI,
WHO, DESPITE BEING SEVERAL
HUNDRED YEARS OLD,
WAS A FORMIDABLE FOE.
AAH!
- [SNARLING]
- JUST THEN...
- YOU'RE IN MY WAY.
STEP ASIDE.
- WHO IS THAT?
- I SAID, YOU'RE IN MY WAY.
UNDERSTAND?
- WHO IS HE?
STAND DOWN!
CLEAR THE PATH FOR HIM!
- [MURMURING]
OHH!
HE'S BEAUTIFUL!
LOOK AT HIM.
HE'S SO DASHING!
- MASTER JAKEN!
- FORGET ME AND LIVE
ON YOUR OWN ACCORD!
- MASTER JAKEN!
- DON'T!
- COME BACK!
- FORGIVE ME FOR
FOLLOWING YOU.
IT MAY NOT HAVE
BEEN YOUR INTENTION,
BUT YOU SAVED MY LIFE.
IT WOULD BE AN HONOR
TO BECOME YOUR SERVANT.
HMM?
HUH?
A MOMENT OF YOUR TIME!
- HERE.
- HMM?
AH! AH!
OH!
THANK YOU.
WHAT IS IT?
- I WILL ENTRUST IT TO YOU
IF YOU'RE ABLE TO USE IT.
- [GASP]
I AM MOST HONORED.
TELL ME, WHAT IS YOUR NAME?
I MUST KNOW!
- SESSHOMARU.
- OH, SESSHOMARU?
SEVERAL DECADES HAVE
PASSED SINCE THAT DAY,
AND I HAVE LONG THOUGHT
TO REPAY MY DEBT
OF GRATITUDE.
I CANNOT LEAVE THIS
TO THAT BUMBLING DEMON.
- HE SURE FINDS WAYS
TO KEEP HIMSELF BUSY.
- HMPH!
- HMM?
- SO, YOU'RE THE THIEF,
ARE YOU?
- HAND OVER THE JEWEL SHARDS
BEFORE YOU MAKE
US REALLY ANGRY.
- YOU GOT SOME NERVE
STEALING FROM US
IN BROAD DAYLIGHT
LIKE THAT.
- THE SWORD.
THE SWORD.
OH, THERE IT IS.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
- GIVE ME THAT TETSUSAIGA.
- HA HA HA!
HE BOUNCED RIGHT OFF
THE TETSUSAIGA'S BARRIER.
- THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN A DEMON TRIES
TO TOUCH YOUR SWORD.
- IN THIS AGE OF CIVIL WAR,
MANY MEN HAVE GONE OFF
TO FIGHT BATTLES
AND HAVE RETURNED TO FIND
THEIR LAND, THEIR FARMS,
AND EVEN THEIR HOMES
DESTROYED OR STOLEN.
THE COMBINED SADNESS
AND BITTERNESS
OF THEIR LOSSES GAVE RISE
TO THIS DEMON'S BIRTH.
- HOW TRAGIC.
I FEEL SORRY FOR HIM.
- LISTEN, WHAT DO YOU
SAY WE LET HIM GO
IF HE RETURNS
OUR BELONGINGS?
- THERE'S MY BOTTLE
WITH THE SHARDS.
- AND MY SPINNING TOP.
- AND MY THINGS, TOO.
- DON'T DO ANYTHING
I WOULDN'T DO.
- OK.
- IF YOU DO,
WE'LL HAVE TO SLAY YOU.
- IF YOU LIKE,
I'LL READ A SUTRA
TO CALM YOUR SPIRIT.
- TOOK THAT PRETTY EASILY.
- STRANGE DEMON.
- TAKES ALL KINDS, EVEN
WHEN IT COMES TO DEMONS.
- CURSE THAT BLASTED DEMON!
UH, WHO'S COOKING?
OH, THAT'D BE ME.
I'M BURNING UP!
HELP!
WATER! WATER!
WATER, WATER, WATER,
WATER, WATER!
WHERE'S THE--AAH!
HELP, HELP!
HELP! HELP! HELP!
HELP! AH!
AH!
AAH!
GOING DOWN!
- HMM?
DID YOU GUYS HEAR
A VOICE JUST NOW?
- HUH?
YOU SURE YOU WEREN'T
JUST IMAGINING IT?
- WE'VE TAKEN CARE
OF THE DEMON,
SO LET'S KEEP
MOVING AHEAD.
- I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
- [PANTING]
CURSE YOU, INUYASHA,
YOU WRETCH!
- THAT MUST HURT, MASTER JAKEN.
- OF COURSE IT DOES!
- WELL, I SUPPOSE YOU'RE
GIVING UP THEN.
- NEVER!
NOW, WOULD YOU
STOP INTERFERING
AND QUESTIONING
MY EVERY MOVE?
NOW, BE OFF!
- BUT I THOUGHT YOU
SAID YOU WANTED ME
TO SEE YOU IN ACTION.
- I SAID NO SUCH THING!
JUST YOU WAIT,
INUYASHA.
I WILL TAKE THE TETSUSAIGA
AWAY FROM YOU,
JUST YOU WAIT AND SEE!
- WELL, THAT TOOK A BIG
BITE OUT OF THE DAY.
- GREETINGS,
YOUNG TRAVELERS.
- HMM?
- WHAT'S THIS ABOUT?
"IN TRAINING, OFFERING FREE
ADVICE AND WEAPON SHARPENING."
- I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT YOU GUYS,
BUT I DON'T LIKE
THE LOOKS OF THIS OLD GUY.
- KEEP IT COMING,
SONNY.
YOU'RE BUILDING
MY CHARACTER.
HEH HEH HEH!
THIS INCENSE HAS DULLED
INUYASHA'S SENSE OF SMELL,
AND HE HAS
NO IDEA WHO I AM.
WHAT WILL IT BE?
CAN I SHARPEN YOUR
LIVES OR YOUR KNIVES?
- SHARPEN A LIFE?
- SO, WHY DON'T YOU
LET HIM WORK ON YOUR
SWORD, INUYASHA?
- ON MY SWORD?
- YES, SON.
I'D BE HONORED.
- HUH.
HOW UNUSUAL TO FIND
A SWORD-SHARPENING MONK.
- HE MUST BE A CRAFTSMAN
OF THE FEUDAL ERA.
MAYBE I'LL GIVE IT A GO.
NO CHARGE, RIGHT?
- HUH?
- HOW GENEROUS OF YOU.
- DO A GOOD JOB.
- DON'T FORGET THIS.
- JUST A MOMENT.
- THAT'S ABOUT ALL THAT
NEEDS SHARPENING.
WE'LL STOP BY LATER
AND PICK THEM UP.
- DO A GOOD JOB, OLD MAN.
- DAMN THAT INUYASHA!
ALL RIGHT!
I'LL SHARPEN THEM!
SO, IF I CAN DO A GOOD
JOB ON THESE WEAPONS,
THEN HE'LL WANT ME TO
SHARPEN HIS SWORD, AS WELL.
AND IT WILL BE
THE PERFECT OPPORTUNITY
TO STEAL IT FROM HIM!
[GRUNTING]
RIN!
BE OFF WITH YOU, YOU PEST!
- HMPH! ALL RIGHT.
I'LL STAY AWAY IF
THAT'S WHAT HE WANTS.
HUH?
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
COME WITH ME.
- THIS IS EXCELLENT.
- YES. THIS IS NICELY DONE,
MONK-IN-TRAINING.
- MY WEAPONS NEVER
LOOKED SO GOOD.
- NEITHER HAVE MINE.
- GUESS I SHOULD HAVE LEFT
MY SWORD WITH THE OLD GUY.
- TOO BAD.
HE'S WORKED SO HARD,
HE'S FALLEN ASLEEP.
- LET'S JUST LET HIM REST.
- AFTER ALL, HE DESERVES
NOT TO BE AWOKEN.
- OH, WELL.
MY LOSS, I GUESS.
- [SNORING]
HUH?
THEY'RE GONE!
WHAT HAPPENED?!
THE WEAPONS ARE GONE!
THEY'RE GONE!
I'VE BEEN HAD!
I'VE BEEN DUPED!
INUYASHA WAS SUPPOSED
TO LEAVE HIS SWORD
HERE SO I COULD
SHARPEN IT!
I--I MEAN, STEAL IT!
[CRYING LOUDLY]
WAIT.
THERE MIGHT STILL BE A WAY.
[GRUNTING]
JUST YOU WAIT, INUYASHA,
FOR TONIGHT,
YOU WILL LOSE POSSESSION
OF YOUR PRECIOUS SWORD!
[LAUGHING]
- I'VE PICKED ALL THESE
FLOWERS FOR LORD SESSHOMARU.
I'D BETTER GO.
- [GROWLING]
- UH-OH.
I CAN'T REMEMBER
WHICH WAY TO GO.
I MUST HAVE GONE TOO FAR.
I THINK I'M LOST.
CAN YOU SMELL ANY TRACE
OF LORD SESSHOMARU?
- [GROWLS]
- OH.
THEN WE REALLY ARE LOST.
I'LL HAVE TO GO
BACK TO JAKEN.
- AH!
MY LEGS ARE KILLING ME.
- MINE ARE, TOO.
[JINGLING]
- HUH? WHAT'S THAT?
A HOT SPRING?
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- WOW!
THIS LOOKS FANTASTIC!
- THAT WAS LUCKY.
- I GUESS YOU WANT
TO BATHE WITH ME.
- HMM.
- ON SECOND THOUGHT,
MAYBE NOT.
- WE'RE GOING IN FIRST!
- HEH HEH HEH!
I'LL SNEAK INUYASHA'S
SWORD AWAY
WHILE HE BATHES
IN MY HOT SPRING.
- THIS FEELS TERRIFIC.
- AHH!
- AW, NO INUYASHA.
MAYBE DOG DEMONS
DON'T LIKE WATER.
- GUESS I SHOULD HAVE
ASKED HIM, TOO.
- HUH?
- THE SHARPENING MONK,
YOU MEAN?
- YEAH.
IT SEEMS LIKE HE KNEW
WHAT HE WAS DOING.
- IF HE'S LOOKING
FOR THE SHARPENER,
I CAN MAKE THAT HAPPEN.
THEN I CAN TAKE HIS
SWORD AWAY FROM HIM.
OH, VERY WELL!
- WE'RE ALL DONE. YOUR TURN.
- COMING.
- LET'S BE ON OUR WAY, THEN.
- THEY'RE GOING IN?
MAKE UP YOUR MIND!
- AHH!
- NO PEEKING!
- SORRY. DIDN'T MEAN TO.
- WHO'D WANT TO LOOK AT YOU?
- OOPS.
I GUESS HE WASN'T
TALKING TO ME.
- THIS REALLY HITS THE SPOT.
- YEAH.
- HEH HEH HEH!
TAKE YOUR TIME AND HAVE
A NICE LONG BATH.
HUH?
[GASP]
I FOUND THE SWORD!
YES!
[SCREAMING]
IT'S MY FAULT.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE BEEN SO HASTY.
WAIT, I KNOW!
I'LL GO LIKE THIS.
- [GASPS]
- MY INTELLIGENCE
IS TRULY FORMIDABLE.
- [SIGH]
- HUH?
- WHAT'S THAT?
- SESSHOMARU!
- OH, MAN...CAN'T STAND...
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
[GROANING]
- INUYASHA!
AH!
GROSS! COVER UP!
- SESSHOMARU IS...
- I'LL GO AND TRY
TO SLOW HIM DOWN.
YOU TAKE CARE OF THESE TWO.
LET'S MOVE, KILALA.
- YEAH, SURE.
THAT'S EASIER SAID THAN DONE.
- OVER THERE, OVER THERE.
MY CLOTHES--GET MY CLOTHES.
- THERE'S BOTH
OF THEIR KIMONOS,
BUT WHERE'S
THE TETSUSAIGA?
- HA HA HA!
- MASTER JAKEN,
I FOUND YOU!
- HUH?
RIN, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING HERE?
- I CAN'T SEEM TO
FIND MY WAY BACK.
- STOP RIGHT THERE!
- HUH? I'VE BEEN FOUND OUT!
HANG ON, RIN IS HUMAN,
SO SHE SHOULD BE ABLE
TO HOLD THE TETSUSAIGA.
RIN, HURRY AND TAKE THIS
TO LORD SESSHOMARU AT ONCE!
- BUT HOW?
- [SCREAMING]
- HURRY AND GO TO HIM WHILE
I HOLD OFF THIS DEMON SLAYER!
- [GROWLING]
- YOU'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
[GRUNTS]
LET'S CUT HIM OFF, KILALA.
- NOT SO FAST!
- AH!
AAH!
- THAT'S FAR ENOUGH, JAKEN!
- HMM
HUH?
- GIVE ME BACK
MY TETSUSAIGA.
- I DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT IT.
- WHAT?
- MASTER JAKEN!
- RIN, YOU FOOL!
WHY DID YOU RETURN?
- INUYASHA,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- WAIT A MINUTE.
A GIRL?
- COME ON. TAKE MY HAND.
- RIN!
HOLD ON TIGHT.
I'VE GOT YOU.
- [GRUNTING]
- RIN, BUT WHY DID
YOU COME BACK?
- HUH?
BECAUSE I COULDN'T HELP
BUT WORRY ABOUT YOU, JAKEN.
- HUH?
UH...
OH, RIGHT.
WHERE'S THE TETSUSAIGA?
- HUH?
[GASP]
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS!
[GASPING]
- HELLO?
IS SOMETHING THE MATTER?
JAKEN?
- DAMN THAT JAKEN.
HE'S GONNA PAY FOR THIS
NEXT TIME I SEE HIM.
- IT SEEMS THAT HE WAS AFTER
THE SWORD AND NOT YOU.
- STRANGE THAT THERE'S
NO SIGN OF SESSHOMARU.
- JAKEN MUST HAVE COME UP WITH
THIS PLAN ALL ON HIS OWN.
- KAGOME, YOU LOOK PALE.
- HUH?
HE DIDN'T STEAL
ANYTHING FROM YOU, TOO?
- MM-MM.
NOT AT ALL.
NO ONE ELSE SEEMED TO NOTICE.
SESSHOMARU IS SUPPOSED
TO DESPISE HUMANS,
YET IT WAS A HUMAN GIRL
WHO CAME TO SAVE JAKEN.
WHAT'S THE MEANING
OF THIS, I WONDER?
- ALL THAT WORK FOR NOTHING!
- THEY ALL LOOK DELICIOUS.
WHICH ONE SHOULD
I CHOOSE, MASTER JAKEN?
- WHO CARES?
LEAVE ME ALONE!
- MAYBE I'LL HAVE TWO OR 3.
- LORD SESSHOMARU
AND HIS WHIMS.
WHY DOES HE INSIST ON KEEPING
A HUMAN GIRL AT HIS SIDE?
- THIS ONE IS SWEET, TOO.
WATCH OVER THE OTHER ONES
FOR ME, OK, JAKEN?
- OH, WELL.
NO SENSE COMPLAINING.
- I COULDN'T HELP
BUT WORRY ABOUT YOU.
- IF RIN HADN'T RETURNED
AT JUST THAT MOMENT,
I WOULD HAVE SUFFERED
A TERRIBLE BEATING
AT INUYASHA'S HANDS.
IT'S YOU AGAIN!
- SESSHOMARU CAN
BE SO CARELESS,
TAKING HIS EYES
OFF HIS WARD.
- AAH!
[GROANING]
RIN!
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
LORD SESSHOMARU,
RIN HAS BEEN ABDUCTED!
- NARAKU DID THIS.
- BUT WHY?
- FOOL.
DID HE THINK THAT I WOULD
TAKE ANY ACTION
OVER A MERE MORTAL?
- AND YET YOU WALKED
STRAIGHT INTO NARAKU'S DEN.
MY LORD, YOU'RE
SO RESERVED ABOUT
SHOWING YOUR
FEELINGS FOR OTHERS.
- NEXT TIME, "SESSHOMARU
AND THE ABDUCTED RIN."
- WAIT, MY LORD!