- [PANTING]
- AFTER HIM!
HE HAS A FRAGMENT
OF THE SHIKON JEWEL.
- OH, NO!
- HE CAN'T BE FAR.
FIND HIM AT ONCE.
WE MUSTN'T LET HIM FLEE
WITH THE JEWEL FRAGMENT.
- HUH?
- [SCREAMING]
- HELP.
PLEASE SAVE ME.
- THESE DEMONS ARE INDEED
THIRSTY FOR THEIR FILL OF BLOOD.
[LAUGHS]
THEY SHALL DRINK
TO THEIR CONTENT.
- [SCREAMING]
- UGH!
I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER SEEN
SO MANY BODIES.
MUST HAVE BEEN SOME BATTLE.
HATE TO SEE WHAT
THE OTHER GUYS LOOK LIKE.
- [SIGHS]
WHAT A SURPRISE.
ANOTHER BATTLEGROUND
FULL OF BODIES
IN THE WARRING STATES ERA.
- YOU'RE MISTAKEN.
THIS WAS NO BATTLE.
- HUH?
- SOMETHING'S NOT RIGHT.
NO BLOOD.
I CAN'T PICK UP
THE SCENT OF BLOOD.
- IT MUST BE THE WORK
OF SOME DEMON,
AND A VERY STRONG ONE TO HAVE
WROUGHT THIS DESTRUCTION,
WHICH MUST MEAN IT POSSESSES
A SHARD OF THE SHIKON JEWEL.
- MIROKU, LET'S GET
ONE THING STRAIGHT.
I HAVE NO INTENTION
OF TEAMING UP WITH YOU
OR OF SHARING ANY
JEWEL SHARDS WITH YOU.
- EACH MAN FOR HIMSELF?
THAT'S WHAT
YOU'RE TRYING TO SAY?
- GLAD WE'RE ON
THE SAME TRACK.
- THEN I SHALL TAKE
MY LEAVE OF YOU NOW.
BETTER FOR US
TO COMPETE FROM AFAR.
- TOO BAD. HE WAS STARTING
TO GROW ON ME.
ARE YOU SURE YOU WANT HIM
TO LEAVE, INUYASHA?
HMM?
WHERE'D HE GET TO?
- HELP! A DEMON!
- AAH!
- PLEASE RETURN
THAT LETTER AT ONCE!
I MUST DELIVER IT
BEFORE THE SUN GOES DOWN!
- IS THIS THE SCENT
THAT I WAS PICKING UP?
- ...BE IN GRAVE DANGER!
- SIT, BOY.
- [GRUNTING]
WHAT'D YOU DO THAT FOR?
- 'CAUSE YOU WERE PESTERING
THE POOR GUY.
WHY WERE YOU PICKING ON HIM?
- HE WAS GIVING OFF THE SAME
SMELL OF INK AS THE BATTLEFIELD.
- HMM?
- IF I CAN TRACK
DOWN THE SOURCE,
IT'LL PROBABLY LEAD US
TO THE DEMON.
- THE DEMON--OR ANYONE
WHO HAPPENS TO HAVE
A LETTER ON HAND.
- DO YOU WANT TO COME UP
WITH A BETTER PLAN,
OR SHOULD WE USE MINE AND FIND
THE JEWEL BEFORE MIROKU?
- [SIGHS]
WHAT DO YOU HAVE
AGAINST HIM, ANYWAY?
- SO NOW YOU'RE TELLING ME
THAT YOU LIKE THAT LECHER?
- YEAH. I DO.
- HUH?
- AS IF.
IT WAS OBVIOUSLY
A JOKE. HMM?
- SHE LIKES HIM?
WHAT COULD SHE POSSIBLY SEE
IN THAT GUY?
- CAN'T YOU PAY ATTENTION
FOR MORE THAN 3 SECONDS?
- HE'S SUCH AN IDIOT.
- INCREDIBLE.
YOU MOWED DOWN
THAT ARMY OF MEN?
ON YOUR OWN, NO LESS?
IF IT IS THE TRUTH YOU SPEAK,
I WOULD BE HONORED TO HAVE YOU
JOIN MY MILITARY FORCES.
- MILORD, I HAD HEARD
THAT THOSE MERCENARY SOLDIERS
WERE BECOMING
A NUISANCE TO YOU.
I THOUGHT IT THE PERFECT
OPPORTUNITY TO DISPLAY
MY CAPABILITIES.
- MILORD,
I MUST SPEAK WITH YOU.
- HUH?
[GULPS]
- OH?
- [GRUNTING]
- YOUR CLAIMS OF POWER
ARE UNFOUNDED.
YOU'RE NOTHING BUT
A WANDERING ARTIST
FROM THE CAPITAL.
- HUH? NO.
I SPOKE ONLY THE TRUTH.
I AM POWERFUL.
I AM NOT A WANDERING ARTIST.
PLEASE ALLOW ME TO SPEAK
WITH YOUR MASTER AGAIN.
- LIAR!
- YOU WERE SELLING YOUR
PAINTINGS AT THE MARKET!
- [GRUNTING]
- GIVE HIM ANOTHER ONE.
- YEAH. TAKE THAT.
- YOU--
- GO EASY ON THE POOR MAN!
- HUH?
- OF COURSE, PRINCESS.
UH, FORGIVE US.
WE DIDN'T SEE YOU THERE.
- WE'RE NOT
THROUGH WITH YOU YET.
- [GASPS]
THE LADY IS STUNNING.
- [PANTING]
HOPE YOU CAN SWIM.
- AAH!
- [LAUGHS]
GOOD RIDDANCE!
- SAFE JOURNEY TO YOU.
[LAUGHING]
- [GRUNTS]
CURSE THEM ALL.
THEY'LL REGRET THIS.
I CAN SUMMON
MY DEMON BRIGADE
AND DEFEAT ALL
THAT STAND IN MY WAY.
I DESERVE TO BECOME A WARLORD.
NO ONE WILL BE ABLE TO CRITICIZE
ME ONCE THEY WITNESS MY POWER.
I SHALL POSSESS MY OWN CASTLE
AND BE SURROUNDED IN RICHES.
AYE, AND I SHALL MARRY
A PRINCESS.
THERE IS NOTHING
I CANNOT ACHIEVE.
[LAUGHS]
- EXCUSE ME.
MIND ANSWERING
A FEW QUESTIONS?
- WHAT?
- GREAT. HE'S PICKING ON
SOME GUY AGAIN.
- 6 INNOCENT PEASANTS DOWN,
HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS TO GO.
- WHO ARE YOU?
I WARN YOU I'M POWERFUL.
I MEAN, I'M NOTHING MORE THAN
A MERE SECOND-RATE ARTIST.
- AN ARTIST?
THEN ANSWER ME THIS,
LITTLE MAN.
WHY IS IT YOU REEK OF INK
AND FRESH HUMAN BLOOD?
HUH?
- RELEASE ME!
FREE ME AT ONCE!
- COME BACK!
- [GROWLING]
- HUH?
- WHAT IS IT?
- A DEMON!
- [GROWLING]
HEY, YOU, COME BACK HERE!
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
IS THAT GUY A DEMON?
NO. I'M SURE
HE'S JUST A HUMAN.
- THEY SAY SIZE
ISN'T EVERYTHING.
- LOOK!
- HIS BLOOD'S BLACK!
- [COUGHING]
WHAT THE HELL?
THIS IS BLOOD
AND BLACK INK.
- INUYASHA,
GET AHOLD OF YOURSELF.
- HIS NOSE IS SO SENSITIVE.
THE SMELL OF INK
AND BLOOD GOT TO HIM.
- CAN YOU HEAR ME?
SAY SOMETHING.
- [PANTING]
- WHAT MANNER
OF BEAST WAS HE?
AND HOW DID HE DETECT THE SCENT
OF BLACK INK AND BLOOD?
YET IT IS HE
WHO SHOULD BE AFRAID.
I HAVE AN ENDLESS STREAM
OF DEMON BATTALIONS PREPARED
TO BACK ME ON MY COMMAND.
- [LAUGHS]
AN EXORCISM?
- YES.
I SENSE AN EVIL SHADOW HANGING
OVER THIS MANSION.
I COULD DRIVE OUT THE DEMONS
IN A SINGLE NIGHT.
- SOME CLAIM.
THIS MANSION IS NOT CURSED
WITH DEMONS.
EVERY YEAR A REPUTED PRIEST
OF MUCH GREATER STANDING
THAN YOURSELF
COMES TO BLESS
THE GROUND HERE.
- LEAVE THIS PLACE AT ONCE!
THE ONLY CURSE WE HAVE
IS BEING PLAGUED WITH VISITS
FROM ROGUES LIKE YOU!
EVIL SHADOW, HE SAYS. HA!
- HUH!
- THERE YOU HAVE IT.
[SIGHS]
I SUPPOSE I MUST RETIRE
IN THE WOODS TONIGHT.
- [RUMBLING]
- HUH?
MY PREDICTION IS TRUE.
RUN! THE EVIL SHADOW
I SPOKE OF IS UPON US!
- LISTEN TO HIM.
HIS ARROGANCE
GOES UNBRIDLED.
[SCREAMING]
- WHAT?!
RUN!
[SCREAMING]
- THE BOLD DEMON
AND DRAGON DEMON.
I'VE ONLY SEEN THOSE
IN PAINTINGS OF HELL.
- AAH! HELP!
SOMEONE RESCUE THE PRINCESS!
- COMING!
- PRINCESS.
PRINCESS.
- [WHIMPERING]
[WHIMPERING]
- PRINCESS!
[GASPS]
PRINCESS,
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
YOUR EYES GLOW RED!
- I WANT YOUR BLOOD.
GIVE ME YOUR BLOOD.
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
- STOP THIS MADNESS!
RELEASE ME!
STOP THIS!
- HUH?
HUH?
WHAT--WHAT HAPPENED?
- STOP THIS!
[PANTING]
THE SKIES
ARE RAINING BLACK INK?
THE INK MUST HAVE SPRUNG
INTO ACTION OF ITS OWN ACCORD
WHILE I LAY SLEEPING.
- [LAUGHING]
- I'M INDEBTED TO YOU
FOR SAVING MY DAUGHTER.
MONK, I HOPE YOU WILL FIND IT
IN YOUR HEART TO FORGIVE MY MEN
FOR THEIR EARLIER RUDENESS.
- YOU NEED NOT THANK ME, AND I
BEAR NO GRUDGE TOWARDS YOUR MEN.
BUT I FEAR THE DANGER
HAS YET TO PASS.
THE DEMONS
WILL SURELY ATTACK AGAIN.
COME TO THINK OF IT,
THE PRINCESS
WILL UNDOUBTEDLY BE SAFER
IF SHE WERE TO STAY
HERE WITH ME--
HERE IN THE SAME ROOM,
SHARING THE SAME BEDDING.
- HE'S AT IT AGAIN,
AND I SUPPOSE YOU'LL NEED
TO SEARCH HER ROBES
WHILE YOU'RE AT IT,
TOO, YOU PERVERT.
- IF IT ISN'T MY OLD, DEAR
FRIENDS KAGOME AND INUYASHA.
- DAMN. WE MUST HAVE
JUST MISSED HIM.
- TELL US, MIROKU,
DID THE INK DEMONS
PASS THROUGH HERE?
- I SUPPOSE, BUT I DIDN'T
REALIZE THEY WERE MADE OF INK.
SO AN ARTIST IS CAPABLE
OF MANIPULATING THOSE DEMONS?
- YES, BUT HE ISN'T A DEMON;
HE'S HUMAN.
- VERY TROUBLING.
FOR A HUMAN
TO HAVE SUCH STRENGTH,
HE MUST BE DRAWING ON THE POWER
OF THE JEWEL SHARD.
- YEAH. THAT'S JUST WHAT
WE'VE BEEN THINKING, TOO.
- SO HOW DO WE STOP AN ARTIST
WHO HAS THE POWER
TO BRING HIS DEMONS
TO LIFE?
- [CHEWING]
I'VE SEEN THE SHIKON JEWEL
GIVE PEOPLE
SOME INCREDIBLE
POWERS BEFORE,
BUT BRINGING PAINTINGS
TO LIFE?
WHY DO YOU SIT THERE?
DON'T YOU WANT TO JOIN
THE OTHERS IN FORMING A PLAN?
- HMPH!
- GET OFF IT.
DON'T TELL ME
YOU'RE STILL SULKING.
- IS SOMETHING
THE MATTER, INUYASHA?
- LEAVE ME ALONE.
- CAN'T YOU GET OVER IT
AND WORK WITH MIROKU THIS ONCE?
WHAT CAN I SAY?
THE GUY IS SO JEALOUS.
- HARDLY.
WHY WOULD I BE JEALOUS?
- HUH?
- YOUR FAITH IN ME IS STRONG,
SO YOU AT LEAST CAN SENSE
MY PURE INTENTIONS.
- SURE.
THAT AND THE FACT THAT
YOU HAVE SOME JEWEL SHARDS.
THERE'S TWO.
OH, NO.
LOOKS LIKE 3.
- YOU HAVE THE POWER
TO SEE THE SHARDS.
- SIT!
- WOULD YOU STOP WITH THAT?
- I COLLECTED
THESE SHARDS ON MY OWN.
TAKING THEM WOULD MAKE
YOU A THIEF.
- THANKS FOR
SPELLING IT OUT.
ANYWAY, WHO ARE YOU
TO CALL ME A THIEF?
I HAPPEN TO REMEMBER
A CERTAIN SOMEONE
THAT MADE AWAY
WITH KAGOME'S SHARDS.
- HMM.
YOUR POWERS OF RECALL
ARE GREATER THAN
I WOULD HAVE IMAGINED.
- WHAT?
THAT ARTIST WAS MANIPULATING
THE DEMONS?
- YES, MILORD.
IT SEEMS THE SHIKON JEWEL SHARD
HE POSSESSES
GRANTS HIM THAT POWER.
- HE POSSESSES A FRAGMENT
OF THE JEWEL?
I HAVE HEARD RUMORS
OF ITS POWERS.
THEY CLAIM THAT A SINGLE SHARD
OF THE SACRED JEWEL
CAN INCREASE ONE'S NATURAL
POWERS AT LEAST A HUNDREDFOLD.
- PERHAPS WE SHOULD LIBERATE IT
FROM THE ARTIST.
- HMM.
- MILORD, IT SEEMS THE MONK
ALSO POSSESSES ONE.
- THAT YOUNG MONK DOES?
- AAH!
YOU TRICKED US!
- WHAT IS THIS ABOUT?
I REMEMBER DOING NOTHING
TO WARRANT THIS VIOLENT
AND TRAITOROUS ATTACK.
NOT YET.
- LISTEN, MONK.
HAND OVER THE JEWEL SHARD.
- HUH?
- [SCREAMING]
- YOU ALL RIGHT, MIROKU?
- LOOK.
THESE MEN ARE VASSALS
TO THIS LORD.
- NOW, WHAT WERE YOU SAYING
ABOUT A JEWEL FRAGMENT?
WHICH ONE OF YOU
WANTS TO GO FIRST?
- IT ISN'T OUR FAULT.
OUR LORD DEMANDED THAT
WE SEIZE YOUR JEWEL SHARD.
- THE MASTER HIMSELF WENT TO
TAKE THE SHARD FROM THE ARTIST.
- YOU KNOW THE WHEREABOUTS
OF THIS ARTIST.
WHERE IS HE?
TELL ME AT ONCE.
KAGOME, LEND ME YOUR
CONTRAPTION FOR A BIT.
- WAIT UP.
I'LL COME WITH YOU.
- ME, TOO!
- KEEP GOING!
I'LL CATCH UP!
THESE DEMONS ARE CREATED BY
THE POWER OF A JEWEL FRAGMENT.
- MERE MORTALS CANNOT
POSSIBLY DEFEAT THEM.
- MOVE IN.
- [SCREAMING]
- [LAUGHS]
- I HAVE AN INFINITE NUMBER
OF SOLDIERS AT HAND,
AND WHEN ANY ARE DESTROYED,
THEY CAN BE IMMEDIATELY REPLACED
WITH THE STROKE OF A BRUSH.
COME FORTH,
MY LOYAL DEMONS OF HELL!
[GRUNT]
- [SCREAMING]
- HALT! COME BACK!
SOMEBODY HELP ME GET MY
HORSE UNDER CONTROL! AAH!
- YOU MUSTN'T SLAY THEM,
OR THE NOXIOUS FUMES
WILL OVERCOME YOU AGAIN.
- JUST WATCH.
- AAH!
- YOU SAVE ME, YOUNG MAN.
YOU SHALL BE COMPENSATED.
- [SCREAMING]
- PHEW!
SOMEONE NEEDS A BATH.
- INUYASHA?
WHOA!
DON'T SAY I DIDN'T WARN YOU.
- HUH? INUYASHA!
MIROKU SAVED US.
- STAY BEHIND ME, FRIENDS.
THIS IS DANGEROUS.
I'M GOING TO UNLEASH
THE WIND TUNNEL!
- [SCREAMING]
- WHAT'S THIS?
HE'S DRAWING IN ALL MY DEMONS!
- [GRUNTING]
- MIROKU.
- I'VE NEVER BEFORE DRAWN IN SO
MANY DEMONS ALL IN ONE ATTEMPT.
IF I MIGHT JUST REST A BIT.
- OH, GREAT.
I KNEW WE COULDN'T
DEPEND ON HIM.
HUH?
- HERE'S THE SECOND FEATURE.
HE MUST HAVE MADE
ANOTHER DEMON.
- I'LL GET HIM.
KAGOME!
CAN YOU TELL ME
WHERE THE FRAGMENT IS?
- THERE. IN THE BAMBOO
INK POT ON HIS WAIST.
- I'M ALL OVER IT.
OH, RIGHT.
HOW COULD I
HAVE FORGOTTEN THIS?
HEY, MIROKU, YOU'LL
NEVER IMPRESS ANYONE
WITH THOSE FLASHY ANTICS.
- MISERABLE WRETCH.
BEHOLD THE DEMONS OF DEATH!
- [GROWLING]
- ISN'T THAT TRICK
GETTING OLD?
- MY, WHAT DO YOU CALL
THAT TECHNIQUE HE'S USING?
- IT'S CALLED
WHALING ON THEM.
- ALL RIGHT,
I FINISHED THAT GROUP OFF.
NOW HAND OVER THE JEWELS
BEFORE I LOSE IT.
- [SCREAMING]
- YOU UNDERESTIMATE ME.
THE FLAMES OF MY HELLFIRE
SHALL BURN YOU TO THE BONE.
- [SCREAMING]
- THIS IS IT.
TAKE YOUR LAST CHANCE
TO SURRENDER.
- AAH!
- MAYBE ONE DAY
I'LL DIE AT THE HANDS
OF SOMEONE STRONGER ME,
BUT THEY WON'T BE HUMAN.
- STAY BACK.
YOU CANNOT HAVE THE JEWEL.
IT IS MY LAST CHANCE
AT HAPPINESS.
- IT'S OVER!
[SCREAMS]
- MY INK!
MY INK HAS ALL BEEN SPILT!
- HERE, MY INK.
I GIVE YOU MY BLOOD.
DRINK WELL
AND FILL YOURSELF.
COME TO LIFE.
FEAST ON MY LIFEBLOOD!
- HUH?
THAT FOOL!
- YOU ARE MINE.
I SHALL NEVER LET ANYONE ELSE
TAKE AHOLD OF YOU.
[LAUGHING]
MY BLOOD.
THE INK DID NOT FUSE
WITH MY BLOOD.
IT DEVOURED IT!
AAH!
[MOANING]
HELP ME!
- THE FOOL.
THE INK DEVOURED HIM.
- WHAT A TERRIBLE WAY
TO END.
- YOU'RE TELLING ME.
THE ARTIST'S AMBITIONS MUST HAVE
TURNED THE INK INTO A PARASITE.
IMAGINE. HE'D RATHER HAVE
HIS BLOOD SUCKED DRY
THAN TO PART
WITH THE JEWEL FRAGMENT.
AND HE PAID FOR HIS
FOOLISHNESS WITH HIS LIFE.
- IRONIC.
THE JEWEL SHARD I WORKED
SO HARD TO WIN IS EVIL.
SO EVIL THAT I FEAR
I MUSTN'T TOUCH IT.
WHAT?
- SO, WHO WANTS THIS?
- WELL, IT'S OBVIOUSLY MINE.
- MIROKU DID HIS SHARE
OF WORK, TOO, REMEMBER?
- WHY DON'T YOU KEEP IT,
KAGOME?
- HUH?
- YEAH?
- MM-HMM.
- DONE AND DONE.
- GOOD THING
SOMEONE'S GROWN UP.
- AMAZING.
KAGOME PURIFIED THE EVIL SHARD
JUST BY PICKING IT UP.
- REALLY, MIROKU?
YOU'LL COME WITH US?
- GLADLY.
JOURNEYING IN THE COMPANY
OF A PRETTY WOMAN IS
SO MUCH MORE ENJOYABLE.
- [GIGGLES]
- HMPH!
- AND DESPITE
INUYASHA'S APPEARANCE,
HE'S REALLY NOT
SUCH A BAD FELLOW.
- HMM.
- MIROKU IS RIGHT.
INUYASHA COULD HAVE KILLED
THE ARTIST
AND ENDED THE TROUBLE
WITH ONE BLOW,
BUT INSTEAD HE SPARED
THE MAN'S LIFE AND WENT
STRAIGHT FOR THE INK POT.
YEAH.
I GUESS INUYASHA'S
ALL RIGHT.
HE JUST DOESN'T KNOW IT YET.
I MIGHT TELL HIM ONE DAY
IF THE TIME'S EVER RIGHT.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- IT'S BEEN QUITE A WHILE
SINCE INUYASHA TOOK POSSESSION
OF THE TETSUSAIGA,
THE SWORD FORGED
FROM HIS OWN FATHER'S FANG.
I THOUGHT HE'D LEARNED
ALL THERE WAS TO KNOW
ABOUT THE SWORD,
BUT APPARENTLY NOT.
ONE DAY HE RECALLS THE WORDS
OF HIS BROTHER SESSHOMARU,
WHO TOLD HIM
THE TETSUSAIGA'S SECRET
IS THAT IT HOLDS THE POWER TO
SLAY 100 DEMONS WITH ONE STROKE.
CAN THAT BE TRUE?
NEXT TIME, NARAKU
AND SESSHOMARU JOIN FORCES.
SEE YOU SOON.