[GRUNTING]
- WHERE ARE KAGOME
AND THE OTHERS?
HUH?
UGH!
- I SURE HOPE
INUYASHA'S ALL RIGHT.
- AN INDIVIDUAL SUCH AS HE
WOULD NOT EASILY BE SLAIN.
- MIND GETTING OFF ME?
- AH, WELL!
SPEAK OF THE DEVIL.
- HUH. HAVEN'T HAD
YOUR FILL OF ME YET, I SEE.
[GROWLING]
TETSUSAIGA!
THE OLD WITCH HAS
KIDNAPPED KAGOME?
- YEAH, SHE PULLED HER OFF
THE BRIDGE AS WE WERE FALLING.
- WELL, AT LEAST KAGOME
DIDN'T FALL TO HER DEATH.
- THEIR SOULS ARE ASCENDING.
- KAEDE!
WHAT ARE THESE
STRANGE ORBS OF LIGHT?
- URASUE MUST HAVE
IMPRISONED HUMAN SOULS
TO ANIMATE THESE CLAY SOLDIERS.
I FEAR IT GETS WORSE.
HUMAN BONES ARE
BAKED IN WITH THE CLAY.
- HUMAN BONES?
- IT IS WORSE THAN I THOUGHT.
URASUE'S MAGIC IS FIENDISH,
USING THE BONES
AND SOULS OF THE DEAD,
AND NOW SHE POSSESSES
MY SISTER'S REMAINS
AND HOLDS KAGOME
IN CONFINEMENT.
[GROANS]
- YOU'RE WOUNDED, OLD WOMAN.
YOU WAIT HERE, AND I'LL GO
AND RECOVER KIKYO'S REMAINS.
- I WORRY THAT TIME
IS NOT ON OUR SIDE.
WE MAY SHORTLY FIND OURSELVES
FACE TO FACE WITH MY SISTER.
- WHAT?
BUT KIKYO'S DEAD!
- URASUE HAS ALL
SHE NEEDS TO REVIVE HER,
AND IF SHE SUCCEEDS,
WE SHALL FACE A FORMIDABLE FOE.
WE MUST FIND SOME WAY
TO STOP THIS.
- STOP! WHAT DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE PULLING HERE?
- YOU ARE AN INSOLENT ONE,
ARE YOU NOT?
THAT SHOULD DO IT. GOOD.
- WHAT'S IN THIS WATER?
IT SMELLS DISGUSTING!
HUH?
WHO IS THAT?
- SO, YOU'RE DRESSED.
THE ATTIRE OF A PRIESTESS
IS MOST FITTING.
IT FLATTERS YOUR GOOD LOOKS.
I HAVE DONE WELL
TO RESHAPE YOUR BODY
WITH HUMAN BONES
AND GRAVEYARD SOIL.
NOW, ALL THAT YOU REQUIRE
IS A HUMAN SOUL.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- MY MAGICAL, HERBAL
POTION WILL SOON
SUCK THE SOUL
FROM YOUR VERY BODY.
KIKYO SHALL HAVE HER SOUL,
AND YOU SHALL BE AMONG
THE LIVING DEAD.
- [THINKING]
KIKYO'S SOUL?
THEN THIS GIRL IS KIKYO?
[GRIMACING]
- SHOW SOME MERCY!
CAN'T YOU SEE GRANNY KAEDE'S
IN A LOT OF PAIN?
- FASTER, SLOWER--WILL SOMEBODY
MAKE UP THEIR MIND?
- I BEG OF YE
TO PROCEED QUICKLY.
FLY LIKE THE DEVIL'S
AT YOUR HEELS.
- IF WE DON'T HURRY,
KAGOME'S SOUL WILL BE STOLEN.
KAEDE IS RIGHT.
THERE'S NO TIME TO LOSE.
- I CAN'T BREATHE.
I CAN HARDLY EVEN MOVE.
- THIS YOUNG LASS
DIFFERS SOMEHOW.
MOST OF MY VICTIMS WOULD HAVE
FALLEN FAINT BY THIS POINT.
[MOANING]
- THAT LIGHT!
THE GIRL POSSESSES A FRAGMENT
OF THE SHIKON JEWEL!
HOW VERY FORTUITOUS FOR ME!
HA HA HA HA HA!
AAH!
DOES THIS LIGHT SHINE
FROM THE JEWEL ITSELF?
OH!
THE SOUL APPEARS TO BE ANGRY.
KIKYO'S SOUL FLASHES WITH
AN INEXPLICABLY VIOLENT
AND ANGRY LIGHT!
- I'M GOING TO THROW UP!
OH, GROSS!
- AAH!
THE SOUL IS SEEKING REVENGE.
I SUSPECT SHE MUST
HAVE EXPERIENCED
A TREMENDOUS BETRAYAL
IN HER FORMER LIFE.
[GASPS]
- KIKYO IS THERE.
- HELP! INUYASHA!
- YOU SURVIVED THE FALL?
- IT IS HER!
- DO NOT CALL OUT FOR ME.
DO NOT CALL OUT MY NAME.
- KI-KIKYO.
- HER SOUL IS EMERGING!
- KA-KAGOME!
- THE INSTANT
YOU CALLED HER NAME,
HER HEART MISSED A BEAT,
AND KIKYO'S SOUL SPRANG FORTH!
- KAGOME'S SPIRIT
HAS ENTERED KIKYO'S BODY!
- KAGOME!
DON'T LEAVE US!
WAKE UP, KAGOME!
- YOU WASTE YOUR TIME SPEAKING
TO A SOULLESS LUMP OF FLESH,
BUT I HAVE NO BONES ABOUT
HAVING HER LATER FOR DINNER.
- YOU FIEND, URASUE!
HOW DARE YE DESECRATE MY SISTERS
GRAVE AND USE HER REMAINS?
- MY CREATION IS WONDROUS,
IS IT NOT?
I USED HER REMAINS
AND GRAVESITE SOIL
TO RECREATE HER
AS LIVING FLESH AND BLOOD.
AS SUCH, I AM HER CREATOR--
NAY, HER BIRTHMOTHER,
AND AS PROOF OF HER
ALLEGIANCE TO ME,
SHE SHALL FOLLOW
MY EVERY COMMAND.
NOW COME AND USE
YOUR POWERS TO RID US OF--
AAH!
[GROANING]
- HUH?
- INUYASHA,
WHY ARE YOU STILL ALIVE?
I BOUND YOU TO A TREE
WITH A SACRED ARROW.
[GRUNTS]
- YEAH, YOU SURE DID,
AND I STAYED THERE FOR 50 YEARS,
BUT AS YOU CAN SEE, I'M ALIVE
AND READY TO TAKE YOU ON AGAIN.
[GROWLS]
- YOU VILE BEAST!
I DESPISE YOU!
YOU LOATHSOME HALF-MAN!
UGH!
- HUH?
GOT A PROBLEM, KIKYO?
[MOANS]
- WHY DID YOU BETRAY ME,
INUYASHA?
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHERE'S ALL THAT BLOOD
COMING FROM?
- LOOK CLOSER, INUYASHA.
IS THAT NOT THE FATAL WOUND
YE INFLICTED ON KIKYO?
- I INFLICTED?
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
THAT I WAS THE ONE
WHO KILLED KIKYO?
- YES.
IT WAS YOUR WOUNDS
THAT SEALED HER FATE
AND ENSURED HER DEMISE.
- THERE MUST BE
A MISTAKE OF SOME KIND.
I DIDN'T KILL HER.
I DON'T EVEN REMEMBER
WOUNDING HER.
- CAN YE BE CERTAIN?
THESE WOUNDS DID NOT
COME FROM YOUR HAND?
THINK HARD!
TRY TO REMEMBER!
IF--IF NOT YOU,
THEN WHO SLEW MY SISTER?
- YOU ARE EVEN MORE VILE
THAN I THOUGHT--
INVENTING SUCH FEEBLE EXCUSES.
PLEASE. IT IS MOST
UNFLATTERING, INUYASHA.
STOP IT!
[SIGHS]
[GROANS]
INUYASHA, DO YOU NOT
REMEMBER WHEN YOU TOLD ME
THAT YOU WISHED TO BECOME HUMAN?
- IMPOSSIBLE!
HE WISHES TO BECOME A DEMON.
- YOU SAID
YOU WOULD BECOME HUMAN.
I BELIEVED YOUR WORDS.
THAT DAY, I CARRIED THE SHIKON
JEWEL AND WENT TO YOU.
[RUNNING]
- OH!
[GROANING]
HUH?
[MOANING]
- FOOL!
I HAD NO DESIRE WHATSOEVER
TO BECOME HUMAN.
- HUH?
- BUT I SHALL TAKE
THE SHIKON JEWEL NONETHELESS.
THANKS.
THIS JEWEL IS ABOUT
TO ABSORB A GREAT DEAL
OF PAIN AND SUFFERING
WHEN I USE IT TO
SLAUGHTER THE VILLAGERS.
[SIGHS]
- YOU TRAITOR!
TRAITOR!
- BUT, KIKYO,
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT INUYASHA COULD HAVE
COMMITTED SUCH A HEINOUS CRIME.
- ARE YOU SUGGESTING THAT
I WAS THE ONE WHO BETRAYED YOU?
- YOU KNOW IT'S TRUE.
THAT IS WHY I SUMMONED UP
THE LAST VESTIGES OF MY STRENGTH
AND BOUND YOU TO THE TREE
WITH MY SACRED ARROW.
[GASPS]
INUYASHA.
- KIKYO.
[SIGHS]
YOU AND I WERE FATED
NEVER TO MEET AGAIN.
- AAH!
- STOP THIS ASSAULT, KIKYO!
- WHO ARE YOU?
- I AM YOUR YOUNGER
SISTER, KAEDE.
MY LOOKS HAVE ALTERED,
BECAUSE 50 YEARS HAVE
PASSED SINCE YOUR DEMISE.
- THEN EXPLAIN WHY YOU WOULD
SPEAK ON INUYASHA'S BEHALF.
GIVE ME THIS!
- OH!
- AAH! UGH!
[MOANS]
- KAEDE!
- YOU MUST STOP
THIS MADNESS.
INUYASHA IS NOT YOUR ENEMY.
- OPEN YOUR EYES!
YOU, TOO, HAVE BEEN TAKEN IN
BY THIS DECEITFUL MONSTER.
- YOU ARE MISTAKEN!
- HAND ME YOUR ARROWS.
- I'LL DO NO SUCH THING!
- KAEDE! SHOW LOYALTY
TO YOUR FLESH AND BLOOD!
NOT TO SOME DEVIOUS,
LYING, HALF-BREED.
NOW, HEAR THE DEMANDS
OF YOUR ELDER SISTER
AND GIVE ME THOSE ARROWS!
- SISTER!
- MOVE!
YOU TOLD ME YOU WISHED
TO BECOME HUMAN.
- YOU TOLD ME
YOU WISHED TO BE WITH ME.
[GROWLING]
- WHAT WILL HAPPEN TO KAGOME?
- KIKYO'S SOUL WILL NOT
FIND ANY MANNER OF PEACE
AS LONG AS SHE HARBORS
THIS HATRED OF INUYASHA.
AND UNTIL KIKYO'S SOUL
RETURNS TO KAGOME'S FLESH,
KAGOME IS DOOMED.
- AAH! OH, NO!
- WAIT! KIKYO!
I MEANT EVERY WORD.
- LIAR!
I WAS A FOOL BEYOND COMPARE FOR
BELIEVING YOUR FARFETCHED TALES
AND WISHING TO LIVE
TOGETHER WITH YOU.
I DESPISE YOU
WITH MY LAST BREATH.
MY SPIRIT WILL NOT FORGET
THAT ALL-CONSUMING HATRED.
SO LONG AS YOU LIVE,
MY SPIRIT CANNOT BE FREED.
- INUYASHA, YOU MUST DESTROY
MY SISTER'S BODY AT ONCE.
THIS REBIRTH IS NOTHING
BUT A DECEIT OF MAGIC.
DESTROY HER BODY AND RELEASE
THE SOUL FROM WITHIN.
- IT'S FUTILE.
I SHALL NOT RETURN TO THAT BODY
UNTIL I'VE CARRIED OUT MY
REVENGE ON THE TRAITOROUS BEAST!
INUYASHA, YOU ARE
THE ONE WHO SHALL DIE!
- IT HAS OVERCOME
THE TETSUSAIGA!
RUN, INUYASHA!
[GRUNTING]
AAH!
- HUH?
[GRUNTING]
OH, NO!
- IT IS KAGOME.
SHE IS TRYING TO CALL BACK
THE SOUL TO HER OWN BODY.
- NO! NOT YET!
THIS CANNOT BE!
MY REVENGE!
- AAH!
[GROANING]
- HUH?
WHERE--WHERE IS SHE?
[GASPS]
KIKYO!
SOME PART OF THE SOUL
MUST REMAIN INSIDE!
- THAT WHICH KEEPS KIKYO MOVING
IS NO MORE THAN HER DEEP HATRED.
IT SEEMS MOST OF THE SOUL
HAS RETURNED
TO THE YOUNG GIRL
FROM WHENCE IT CAME.
KIKYO'S HATRED FOR YOU AND HER
NEED FOR REVENGE MUST HAVE
ABSORBED INTO HER BONES
AND THE GRAVE SITE SOIL ITSELF.
THE ONCE PURE MAIDEN
IS NOW A MONSTER.
A MONSTER FEEDING
ON ITS HATRED OF YOU!
LOVELY IMAGE, IS IT NOT?
- INUYASHA!
- I MUST DISTANCE MYSELF
FROM THE GIRL,
OR SHE WILL STEAL BACK
THE REMAINDER OF MY SOUL.
I MUST MOVE AWAY.
OH!
[GASPS]
INUYASHA!
- KIKYO, YOU CAN'T GO ON
LIKE THIS ANY LONGER.
YOU MUST RETURN
TO KAGOME'S BODY.
- YOU ARE SAYING YOU WISH ME
TO DIE, IS THAT IT?
[GASPS]
FOR IF MY SOUL WERE
TO RETURN TO THE GIRL,
THEN I WILL CEASE
TO EXIST FOREVER.
YOU MUST KNOW THAT.
IS THAT WHAT YOU
DESIRE, INUYASHA?
I REFUSE TO DIE.
- AAH!
- MY SPIRIT CANNOT REST IN PEACE
UNTIL I SEE YOU DEAD!
[GROANING]
MY SPIRIT CANNOT REST IN PEACE
UNTIL I SEE YOU DEAD!
- DON'T DO THIS!
AAH!
KIKYO!
[GASPS]
- AAH!
- WHY? WHY DID IT
HAVE TO COME TO THIS?
[GROWLING]
- [VOICE-OVER]
KIKYO HAD USED
HER SPIRITUAL POWERS
TO PROTECT THE SACRED
SHIKON JEWEL FROM DEMONS.
[SCREECHING]
I, TOO, NEEDED
THE SHIKON JEWEL
SO THAT I COULD BECOME
A FULL-FLEDGED DEMON.
- UGH! UGH! UGH!
[GROWLING]
WILL YOU STOP IT?
WHY DO YOU NEVER
FINISH ME OFF?
- STOP COMING AFTER THE JEWEL.
I HAVE NO WISH
TO WASTE MORE ARROWS.
- [VOICE-OVER]
I MERELY WANTED
THE JEWEL FOR MYSELF.
I HAD NO INTENTION
OF KILLING KIKYO.
IT BECAME CLEAR THAT KIKYO DID
NOT INTEND TO KILL ME EITHER.
- HUH?
- INUYASHA, I KNOW
YOU'RE WATCHING ME.
PLEASE, COME JOIN ME.
IT IS THE FIRST TIME
WE HAVE SPOKEN LIKE THIS.
- WHAT'S YOUR POINT?
- INUYASHA,
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF ME?
DO I SEEM ORDINARY?
- HUH? WHERE ARE YOU
GOING WITH THIS?
- I MUST NEVER REVEAL
MY WEAKNESSES TO ANYONE.
I MUST NEVER WAVER.
IF I DID, A DEMON WOULD
GET THE BETTER OF ME.
INSIDE, I AM AN ORDINARY WOMAN,
YET I CANNOT REVEAL
MYSELF AS SUCH.
IN MANY WAYS, WE ARE
SIMILAR, BOTH OUTSIDERS.
THAT IS WHY I WAS
UNABLE TO KILL YOU.
- HMM!
QUIT WHINING.
WE'VE ALL GOT OUR CROSS TO BEAR.
HMM!
HUH?
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
I SHOULDN'T COMPLAIN.
- [VOICE-OVER]
WHEN I SAW KIKYO'S SAD
AND LONELY EXPRESSION,
I FELT GUILTY FOR THE VERY
FIRST TIME IN MY LIFE.
AFTER THAT, I COULDN'T
GET HER OUT OF MY MIND.
SHE WAS ALWAYS BY MY SIDE...
AND I...BY HERS.
- ME? BECOME A HUMAN?
- IT'S POSSIBLE.
IT'S TRUE THAT
YOU ARE HALF DEMON,
BUT YOU ARE ALSO HALF HUMAN.
IF THE SACRED JEWEL
OF THE 4 SOULS
FELL INTO THE HANDS OF A DEMON,
THEIR POWERS WOULD
UNDOUBTEDLY INCREASE.
HOWEVER, IF IT WERE USED
TO TURN YOU INTO A HUMAN,
IT WOULD BE PURIFIED.
THE JEWEL OF THE 4 SOULS
WOULD PROBABLY CEASE TO EXIST.
- AND THEN WHAT?
WHAT WOULD HAPPEN TO YOU?
- MY DUTY IS
TO PROTECT THE JEWEL.
WITHOUT IT, I COULD LIVE
THE LIFE OF AN ORDINARY WOMAN.
[GASPS]
- UGH!
[SIGHS]
- [VOICE-OVER]
I HAD NO SECOND THOUGHTS.
I KNEW I COULD LIVE
WITH KIKYO, AS A HUMAN.
I'D LONGED FOR SUCH A LIFE.
BUT THE DAY SHE WAS
TO BRING ME THE JEWEL...
- HUH?
UGH!
HUH?
- DIE, INUYASHA!
- [VOICE-OVER]
SHE BETRAYED ME!
KIKYO BETRAYED ME!
AS SOON AS I LET DOWN MY GUARD,
SHE TRIED TO SLAY ME.
I MANAGED TO DODGE THE ARROWS
AND WENT TO THE VILLAGE
TO STEAL THE JEWEL.
AND THAT'S WHEN
SHE BOUND ME TO THE TREE.
[GROANING]
- WHY DID YOU
BETRAY ME, INUYASHA?
- HOW DID IT COME TO THIS?
AAH!
HOW DID IT GO SO WRONG?
IT WASN'T SUPPOSED
TO BE LIKE THIS!
KIKYO!
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- APPARENTLY, KIKYO DIES AGAIN,
BURYING HER HATRED OF INUYASHA,
AND OUR JOURNEY IN SEARCH
OF THE JEWEL SHARDS CONTINUES,
BUT NOT WITHOUT MORE
DEMONS TRYING TO STEAL
THE ONES WE ALREADY HAVE.
WAIT.
THIS GUY ISN'T A DEMON.
WELL, WHATEVER HE IS,
HE SURE HAS A LOT OF POWER
IN HIS RIGHT HAND.
IS HE AN ALLY, A FOE,
OR JUST A DIRTY LECHER?
NEXT TIME, "MYSTICAL HAND
OF THE AMOROUS MONK, MIROKU."
SEE YOU SOON!