- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- I AM SOMEONE WHO,
LIKE YOURSELF,
DESPISES INUYASHA.
- I SHOULD KNOW THE NAME
OF THE ONE I MAKE A PACT WITH.
- MY APOLOGIES.
CALL ME NARAKU.
- WELL, I'M NOT AFRAID.
NARAKU'S A TERRIBLE DEMON.
WE'VE GOT TO DO WHAT WE CAN
TO DESTROY HIM.
- TRYING TO BUY TIME IN ORDER TO
SAVE THE LIVES OF YOUR FRIENDS.
[GRUNTING]
- AAH!
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- I WAS AFRAID.
- HMM?
AH--
AAH!
- UHH!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING
THAT FOR, INUYASHA?
UHH.
- LAY OFF!
- IF YOU SEAL UP THE WELL,
KAGOME WILL NEVER BE ABLE
TO RETURN TO THIS ERA.
DON'T FOOL YOURSELF.
YOU NEED HER AS MUCH AS
THE REST OF US DO.
- I CAN'T HAVE HER
HANGING AROUND.
OTHERWISE, I'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO FIGHT THE WAY I WANT TO.
[GRUNTING]
WHOA.
[GROWLS]
LET'S GO, MIROKU.
- GO?
TO WHERE?
- HOW CAN YOU ASK SUCH A THING?
WE'LL FIND NARAKU AND CRUSH HIM
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
- LET'S BE GOING, SHIPPO.
- NOT ME.
I DESPISE INUYASHA.
[SNIFFLING]
- FINE WITH ME.
STAY HERE.
- I UNDERSTAND THAT YOU FORCED
KAGOME TO LEAVE FOR HER SAFETY,
BUT DO YOU NOT THINK YOU
COULD HAVE ACHIEVED THE SAME END
THROUGH LESS AGGRESSIVE METHODS?
- LEAVE ME ALONE!
I DID WHAT I HAD TO!
- SO HOW DO YOU RECOMMEND WE
GO ABOUT SEARCHING FOR NARAKU?
YOU'VE COME ACROSS SOME
NEW LEADS, I SUPPOSE?
- NO, NOT EXACTLY.
- YOU HAVE NOTHING TO GO ON.
- QUIET!
- YOU SENT KAGOME BACK
OF YOUR OWN VOLITION.
I'D APPRECIATE IT IF YOU DIDN'T
TAKE OUT YOUR FRUSTRATION ON ME.
- WILL YOU GET OFF MY BACK?!
- OUR BEST HOPE NOW
LIES IN COMPOSING OURSELVES
AND THINKING THINGS THROUGH.
- I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS!
- WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
I WANT TO CRUSH NARAKU
AS DESPERATELY AS YOU, INUYASHA.
50 YEARS AGO,
HE FORMED A WIND TUNNEL
ON THE HAND OF MY GRANDFATHER,
AND NOW THE CURSE HAS CARRIED
OVER THE GENERATIONS TO ME.
- MIROKU...
TAKING ACTION IS MORE MY STYLE,
NOT STRATEGIZING.
YOU THINK OF SOMETHING.
- WORK WITH ME, INUYASHA.
LET'S GO BACK TO WHEN
THIS ALL STARTED.
YOU MENTIONED THAT YOU FELL INTO
NARAKU'S TRAP 50 YEARS AGO
IN THIS VERY SAME VILLAGE,
CORRECT?
- YEAH.
- SO THEN YOU'VE MET NARAKU
IN PERSON, HAVE YOU?
- NOT EXACTLY.
- INUYASHA, YOU CAN BECOME
FULLY HUMAN
IF YOU USE THE SACRED JEWEL.
I SHALL BRING IT TO YOU TOMORROW
AT THE BREAK OF DAWN
TO THIS VERY PLACE.
- HUH?
UH?
- DIE, INUYASHA!
[GRUMBLES]
- I MAY HAVE MET HIM,
BUT IF I DID,
HE WAS DISGUISED AS KIKYO,
SO I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT HE LOOKS LIKE.
- IT MAKES NO SENSE.
YOU DON'T KNOW NARAKU,
AND YET HE DESPISED YOU ENOUGH
TO DISGUISE HIMSELF AS KIKYO
AND LEFT YOU FOR DEAD.
COULD YOU HAVE DONE SOMETHING
IN THE PAST
TO CAUSE HIM TO BE EMBITTERED?
- HOW DO I KNOW?
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT HE LOOKS LIKE.
- HMM.
ONE THING WE DO KNOW IS THAT
KIKYO WAS A PRIESTESS.
[SOBBING]
PERHAPS IT WAS SHE AND NOT YOU
THAT NARAKU HAD
A DEEP GRUDGE AGAINST,
ESPECIALLY SINCE YOU DON'T THINK
YOU KNOW HIM.
- YOU MEAN, IT'S KIKYO HE HATES?
- KAGOME!
- HUH?
- HI.
LONG TIME, NO SEE.
SO HOW'S YOUR RHEUMATISM?
- YEAH, AND YOUR
PLANTAR'S WARTS?
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
- YOU'RE WEARING CIVVIES.
UNIFORM IN THE WASH?
- MM-HMM.
I'M STILL TRYING
TO GET THE STAINS OUT.
THE FRONT WAS COVERED IN BLOOD.
[GASPS]
- NOW YOU'RE A HEMOPHILIAC?
- OH, YEAH.
I'LL BE 6 FEET UNDER
IN NO TIME AT ALL.
INUYASHA'S BLEEDING
HADN'T STOPPED.
I WAS SO WORRIED ABOUT HIM.
BUT MAYBE HE HAD
OTHER THINGS ON HIS MIND
WHEN HE HELD ME IN HIS ARMS.
- I'LL HANG ON TO THE JEWEL.
- MAYBE HE HUGGED ME
TO GET THE SACRED SHIKON JEWEL.
THAT CREEP'S GONNA PAY!
- KAGOME.
TAKE IT INTO THE HALL
IF YOU DON'T MIND.
- IT WAS THE FIRST TIME
A GUY HUGGED ME LIKE THAT.
I COULDN'T HELP IT
IF I GOT A BIT FLUSTERED.
HE'S A GUY, AFTER ALL, RIGHT?
I MEAN, HE'S HALF-DEMON,
BUT HE'S ALSO HALF-HUMAN.
[SIPS]
- THESE INJURIES ARE SERIOUS.
YE WON'T BE SEEING ANY BATTLES
FOR SOME TIME YET.
- THEY WON'T HOLD ME BACK
ANY LONGER THAN 2 OR 3 DAYS.
- NOT SURPRISING THAT YE WOULD
PUT ON A BRAVE FACE.
THERE.
- AAH!
WHAT'D YOU DO THAT FOR?!
- IF YE CAN MUSTER
THAT MUCH VIGOR,
THEN PERHAPS IT WON'T
TAKE TOO LONG TO RECOVER.
I NEED TO SPEAK TO YE.
I HAVE GIVEN MUCH THOUGHT
TO THIS,
EVER SINCE MY SISTER KIKYO
WAS REVIVED BY
THE EVIL WITCH URASUE.
- HMM.
- KIKYO HAD TOLD ME
IT WAS YE, INUYASHA,
WHO HAD STOLEN HER
SACRED SHIKON JEWEL.
DO YE NOT THINK IT STRANGE?
THE ONE WHO
DISGUISED HIMSELF AS YE
COULD HAVE MADE OFF
WITH THE JEWEL,
YET HE DID NOT.
HE TRICKED YE INTO
TERRORIZING THE VILLAGE
AND PURSUING THE SACRED JEWEL.
THEN KIKYO BOUND YE TO A TREE
WITH HER SACRED ARROW.
WAS THE TRICKSTER ATTEMPTING
TO PIT YE AGAINST EACH OTHER?
OR WAS IT KIKYO WHO WAS
THE TRUE OBJECT OF HIS MALICE?
WAS HE TRYING TO FILL HER HEART
WITH HATRED AND BITTERNESS?
- WHAT?
- IN KIKYO'S POSSESSION,
THE SACRED JEWEL OF THE 4 SOULS
REMAINED PURE,
BUT WHEN HER HEART
BECAME TAINTED AND HATEFUL,
THE JEWEL ALSO BECAME SULLIED,
AND IT FILLED
WITH A MALEVOLENT POWER.
AT THE TIME, THERE WAS
BUT A SINGLE PERSON
WHO WISHED FOR
SUCH A TERRIBLE OUTCOME.
SHALL I TAKE YE TO SEE THE PLACE
WHERE THIS MAN ONCE RESIDED?
KIKYO HAD COME
TO HER OWN DECISION.
- SHE WAS HARBORING A THIEF.
- BECAUSE SHE PITIED HIM.
HE WAS UNABLE
TO MOVE ON HIS OWN.
THIS IS THE CAVE.
THE MAN WENT BY
THE NAME OF ONIGUMO.
HE SUFFERED FROM TERRIBLE BURNS,
AND HIS FACE WAS
ESPECIALLY SCARRED.
I KNOW NOT IF
HE FELL FROM A CLIFF
OR HOW HE SUSTAINED
HIS INJURIES,
BUT BOTH LEGS WERE BROKEN.
YET DESPITE HIS SEVERE WOUNDS,
ONIGUMO CONTINUED TO ENDURE.
HE DID NOT MOVE AGAIN,
BUT HE RECOVERED HIS STRENGTH
ENOUGH TO CONVERSE,
AND, GRADUALLY,
HIS TRUE NATURE EMERGED.
- YOU...
YOUNG LASS.
- IT'S KAEDE.
- YES.
YOUR SISTER POSSESSES WHAT IS
KNOWN AS THE SHIKON JEWEL,
DOES SHE NOT?
- WHAT WOULD YE KNOW
ABOUT THE JEWEL?
- ALL WHO ARE WICKED
KNOW OF IT AND PURSUE IT.
- YE INCLUDED?
- I UNDERSTAND THAT
THE MORE EVIL THE JEWEL ABSORBS,
THE MORE EVIL IT BECOMES.
OUTSTANDING.
- MY SISTER HAS IT
UNDER HER CONTROL.
IT WON'T BE CORRUPTED.
- KIKYO'S MANNER
IS SELF-RIGHTEOUS.
FOR ONCE, I SHOULD
LIKE TO SEE HER
APPREHENSIVE AND FRIGHTENED.
THAT WOULD BRING ME
TRUE PLEASURE.
[CHUCKLING]
- I SEE.
ONIGUMO SAID THAT, DID HE?
- BIG SISTER, I DON'T CARE FOR
THAT MAN.
- BEAR HIM NO GRUDGE.
GIVE HIM PITY.
HIS INJURIES ARE GREAT.
HE SHALL NEVER MOVE
FROM THERE AGAIN.
- IT WAS NOT LONG AFTERWARD
THAT KIKYO BOUND YE TO A TREE
WITH HER ARROW.
SEVERAL DAYS LATER, WHEN I WENT
TO VISIT ONIGUMO AT THE CAVE,
I FOUND IT HAD BEEN BURNED OUT.
JUDGING BY WHAT I SAW,
THE FLAMES MUST HAVE
BEEN INTENSE,
FOR ONIGUMO WAS UNABLE TO MOVE
AND WOULD HAVE PERISHED
IN THE CAVE,
YET HIS BONES WERE
NOWHERE TO BE FOUND.
THEY, TOO, MUST HAVE
GONE UP IN FLAMES.
- WHAT DOES THIS
HAVE TO DO WITH ME?
I'M LOOKING FOR NARAKU,
AND NARAKU IS A DEMON,
NOT A HUMAN,
SUCH AS THIS ONIGUMO PERSON.
- NO MISTAKING THAT.
ONIGUMO MAY HAVE BEEN EVIL,
BUT HE WAS HUMAN--
A SCOURGE TO HUMANITY.
- LET'S GO INSIDE
AND TAKE A LOOK, SHALL WE?
[GRUNTING]
- OH!
WHOA!
OH, I CAN'T PULL IT
OUT OF THE WELL,
AND UNLESS I DO,
KAGOME WILL NEVER RETURN TO US.
I'M STARTING
TO MISS HER ALREADY.
- I CAN'T HAVE HER
HANGING AROUND.
OTHERWISE, I'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO FIGHT THE WAY I WANT TO.
- UNH!
HE'S MORE STUBBORN THAN A MULE!
THAT DOES IT!
I'M NEVER SPEAKING
TO INUYASHA AGAIN!
- DID YOU SAY THE NAME INUYASHA?
[WHIMPERING]
I ASKED YOU A QUESTION.
- WHOA!
- HUH.
LADY KAEDE.
- HMM?
- LOOK THERE.
THIS ONE SIDE ALONE
IS FREE OF GRASS AND MOSS
OF ANY KIND.
- OH.
IT'S THE SAME PLACE.
THIS IS THE VERY SITE
WHERE ONIGUMO LAY INJURED.
- HMM.
HUH?
AH!
UNH!
I'M SENSING THE EVIL SPIRIT
OF A DEMON,
AN ENTITY WHICH HAS BEEN
LEFT BEHIND HERE FOR DECADES.
- IMPOSSIBLE.
- COULD IT BE A HUMAN THAT
LEFT THIS FOUL SPIRIT BEHIND,
HERE WHERE EVEN
GRASS REFUSES TO GROW?
- THE SPIRIT IN THIS CAVE
BELONGS TO NO HUMAN.
IT'S DEFINITELY THAT OF A DEMON.
- HMM.
BUT IF ONIGUMO WAS HUMAN,
HOW COULD HE HAVE POSSESSED
THE SPIRIT OF A DEMON?
- HELP!
- HUH?
- SOMEBODY HELP ME!
AAH! AAH!
- [DOGS BARKING]
- SHIPPO!
UHH!
[GRUNTING]
AAH!
- [SNARLING]
- IRON REAPER SOUL STEALER!
UHH!
UHH.
- ARE YOU STILL IN PAIN?
OH--YOUR CHEST!
YOU'RE BLEEDING!
- NO.
MY WOUND MUST HAVE REOPENED.
HUH?
- MIGHT YOU BE INUYASHA?
- THAT DEPENDS WHO'S ASKING!
- I AM ROYAKAN,
THE GUARDIAN OF HAOWA.
- ROYAKAN.
ARE YE NOT THE GENTLE CREATURE
THAT GUARDS THE FOREST?
- THAT WAS BEFORE I WAS REBORN.
INUYASHA, I HAVE COME
TO SLAY YOU!
ARRGGH!
- GOOD LUCK, IS ALL I CAN SAY.
- ROYAKAN SEEMS TO KNOW
THAT INUYASHA'S
IN NO CONDITION TO FIGHT.
[GRUNTING]
FIGHT AS YOU MAY,
YOU CAN NEVER DEFEAT ME!
ARRGGH!
- THAT LEAVES ME
WITH ONE CHOICE.
- AAH!
- INUYASHA!
QUICKLY, THIS WAY!
ARRGGH!
[GRUMBLES]
[CHUCKLING]
- I MUST CONGRATULATE MYSELF.
IT WAS A BRILLIANT IDEA, INDEED,
EMBEDDING A JEWEL SHARD
IN ROYAKAN'S BODY.
- IRON REAPER!
UNH...
- YOU OK?
- MY VISION IS STARTING
TO BECOME BLURRY.
- MONK, INUYASHA IS IN DANGER.
- I'M MOVING AS FAST
AS I'M ABLE.
BUT FIRST--UNH!--
I MUST STOP ROYAKAN.
[GROWLING]
[GRUNTING]
IT CAN BE DONE!
[GROWLING]
HE ESCAPED.
HUH?
- HOW UNFORTUNATE.
PERHAPS I SHOULD HAVE MADE
ROYAKAN MORE POWERFUL.
- INUYASHA, SHOW ME YOUR WOUNDS.
- WHERE IS ROYAKAN?
- HE HAS FLED.
- INUYASHA, I SENSE THAT
NARAKU IS NEAR.
- WHAT?
- MOST LIKELY,
ROYAKAN HAS A JEWEL FRAGMENT
AND, THROUGH IT, IS BEING
MANIPULATED BY NARAKU.
- THAT WOULD EXPLAIN
SUCH A GENTLE CREATURE
TURNING EVIL.
[GRUNTING]
INUYASHA!
- NARAKU, WHERE ARE YOU?
COME OUT AND FACE ME,
ONE-ON-ONE!
[GRUNTING]
- INUYASHA!
- ROYAKAN MAY RETURN
FOR ANOTHER ATTACK.
WE SHOULD FLEE
TO THE VILLAGE AT ONCE
AND CONTEMPLATE OUR NEXT MOVE.
- INUYASHA.
[SIGH]
- IT'S BEEN 3 WHOLE DAYS.
WHY DOESN'T HE COME AND GET ME?
- KAGOME!
- HUH?
- GUESS WHAT--
HOJO HAS BEEN LOOKING
ALL OVER THE PLACE FOR YOU.
- HOW HAVE YOU BEEN
FEELING THESE DAYS, KAGOME?
ANY BETTER?
- YEAH, I GUESS.
- HEY, GREAT.
THEN HOW ABOUT SEEING A MOVIE
WITH ME THIS SATURDAY?
- THIS SATURDAY?
- YEAH.
I'LL BRING A THERAPEUTIC
BACK PAD FOR YOU.
OR HAVE YOU MADE
OTHER PLANS ALREADY?
- WELL, NOT EXACTLY.
INUYASHA WILL COME FOR ME
BY THEN, WON'T HE?
- JUST SAY YES.
- YOU TOTALLY BLEW HIM OFF
LAST TIME YOU HAD A DATE, RIGHT?
- HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
- EXCUSE US.
WON'T BE LONG.
- AAH!
UNH!
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
- YOU'VE GOT THE HOTS
FOR SOME OTHER GUY,
DON'T YOU, KAGOME?
- UH...
- THAT EXPLAINS ALL THE SIGNS
COMING FROM YOU LATELY.
- I DIDN'T THINK YOU WERE
MEMORIZING CHEMISTRY EQUATIONS.
- HANG ON A MINUTE.
HOW WAS I SUPPOSED TO ACT?
- AHA!
YOU LOVE HIM,
BUT HE DOESN'T LOVE YOU.
- OH, GIVE ME A BREAK!
WHO COULD EVER LOVE
THAT SELFISH, ARROGANT MONSTER?
- WHO'S SHE TALKING ABOUT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- HMPH!
YOU'RE ON.
I'LL GO TO THE MOVIES WITH YOU.
- THAT'S GREAT!
ALL RIGHT!
[SIGH]
- WHO DOES INUYASHA THINK HE IS,
TRYING TO CONTROL MY LIFE?
I'LL TAKE THINGS
INTO MY OWN HANDS.
THAT'LL SHOW HIM.
UHH.
[GRUNTS]
I PULLED A MUSCLE THAT TIME.
I HOPE INUYASHA'S
GETTING A GOOD REST.
- OPEN UP!
LET ME OUT OF HERE!
- YOU'RE WASTING YOUR TIME,
INUYASHA.
THIS HUT IS COVERED
WITH SACRED SEALS
TO KEEP THE DEMONS OUT
AND YOU IN.
- YEAH, BUT WHO SAYS
I NEED TO BE SEALED INSIDE?
OPEN UP!
- PLEASE STOP, INUYASHA.
BE STILL AND REST.
YOUR INJURIES STILL HAVEN'T
HAD ENOUGH TIME TO HEAL.
- KAGOME.
[GIGGLING]
- I COULD LIE WITH YOU
IF YOU LIKE.
- SHIPPO, YOU CREEP!
LAUGH IT UP, FUZZBALL!
- I WAS ONLY TRYING
TO CHEER YOU UP!
UNH! UNH! OOH! OOH! OW!
- YOU'VE BEEN KNOCKING AROUND
INSIDE THIS PLACE
FOR HOURS ALREADY.
- YEAH!
SO HURRY UP AND UNTIE ME!
- THEN THE DEMONS WOULD GET YOU.
THUS THE SEALED HUT
WOULD BE MEANINGLESS.
- UNH!
LET ME OUT OF HERE!
UNH!
AH!
- KAEDE, SEAL THE DOOR
WITH THE SACRED ENCHANTMENT.
- CONSIDER IT DONE.
- YOU MUSTN'T RUSH THINGS,
INUYASHA.
I AM INCLINED TO WANT
TO RUSH AFTER NARAKU, AS WELL,
BUT FIRST YOU MUST
RECOVER FROM YOUR INJURIES.
- HE SPEAKS THE TRUTH.
NARAKU'S STRENGTH IS ALWAYS
BEYOND COMPREHENSION.
ISN'T THAT PRECISELY WHY
YE BANISHED KAGOME
TO HER OWN WORLD?
- IT IS?
HE SENT HER AWAY OUT OF CONCERN?
- WE NEED YOU
TO RECOVER QUICKLY,
FOR WE MUST FACE NARAKU
AT OUR STRONGEST.
OTHERWISE, I FEAR THAT
OUR FATES WILL BE SHORT-LIVED.
- UHH.
ARE YOU A MAN OR A MOUSE?
I, FOR ONE, AM PREPARED
TO FIGHT NARAKU HERE AND NOW!
- PUT YOUR HEAD DOWN
AND GET YOURSELF SOME
MUCH-NEEDED SLEEP, MY GOOD MAN.
LIE DOWN!
BE SILENT!
SLEEP!
REST!
HOW MANY TIMES
DO I HAVE TO TELL YOU?
- MIROKU, AIM FOR
THE OLD INJURIES.
- INUYASHA, YOU AWAKE?
- UH...WHY?
- I WAS THINKING ABOUT KAGOME
AND WONDERING IF SHE MISSES US.
- YOU WOKE ME UP FOR THAT?
FORGET ABOUT KAGOME.
SHE'S A THING OF THE PAST.
I MEAN, THE FUTURE.
- HMM?
- AS LONG AS SHE'S
ALIVE AND WELL,
THAT'S ALL I HOPE FOR.
I CAN'T BEAR TO SEE
ANOTHER WOMAN DIE.
[WHIMPERING]
- I'VE BEEN
SEARCHING FOR YOU, ROYAKAN.
- NARAKU?
GO AWAY!
I REFUSE TO BATTLE
WITH INUYASHA AGAIN.
- WHY DO YOU TREMBLE SO?
- I HAVE NO DESIRE TO BE
DRAWN INTO A WIND TUNNEL.
[CHUCKLING]
- I SHALL TAKE AWAY YOUR FEAR
AND STOP YOUR TREMBLING.
- [INDISTINCT]
[SCREAMING]
AAAH!
[ROARING]
[CHUCKLING]
- A SINISTER WIND BLOWS OUR WAY.
LADY KAEDE, STAY ON GUARD,
FOR A MALEVOLENT SPIRIT
APPROACHES.
- AYE.
[DOG BARKING]
WE SHALL STOP HIM HERE.
- HMM.
- INUYASHA, WHERE ARE
YOU HIDING?
- HE'S COME BACK!
AND HE'S EVEN LARGER THAN
LAST TIME!
- REVEAL YOURSELF, INUYASHA.
- AS LONG AS OUR SPELL
IS UNBROKEN,
INUYASHA'S HUT SHALL REMAIN
INVISIBLE TO THE DEMON.
- WHAT HAS CAUSED
THIS TRANSFORMATION?
THE BEAST IS EVEN MORE
FRIGHTFUL THAN BEFORE.
I'LL WAGER THAT ANOTHER SHARD
OF THE SACRED SHIKON JEWEL
HAS BEEN EMBEDDED IN HIS BODY.
- WHAT A PITIFUL DEFENSE.
HUH!
- NO!
- DON'T MOVE.
- I HAVE NO CHOICE!
- THERE YOU ARE!
[ROARS]
- INUYASHA!
- UHH.
- I OWE YOU ONE, ROYAKAN,
FOR GETTING ME OUT OF THAT HUT,
WHERE MY SO-CALLED FRIENDS,
THE MONK AND THAT HAG,
SEALED ME INSIDE.
- FOR YOUR PROTECTION,
I MIGHT ADD.
- GRATITUDE DOESN'T
COME NATURALLY TO HIM.
- I HAVE HEARD ENOUGH!
- LET'S GET AT IT!
[GRUNTING]
AAH!
UNH!
UHH.
- INUYASHA'S BEEN THROWN
TO THE GROUND.
- HE MAY HAVE THE WILL TO FIGHT,
BUT HIS STRENGTH HASN'T
HAD TIME TO RECOVER YET.
- I'M NO MATCH FOR HIS MIGHT.
HUH?
- [INDISTINCT]
THE SACRED JEWEL.
- I HAVE TO GET IT
BEFORE HE DOES.
- HANDS OFF, DEMON!
- SHIPPO!
- YOU WON'T ESCAPE.
[ROARS]
- AAH!
AH! AH!
- SHIPPO, MOVE!
I'LL OPEN MY WIND TUNNEL!
[GASP]
- LOOK!
- NARAKU'S VENOMOUS INSECTS.
[GRUMBLES]
- IT FIGURES.
NOW, HOW DO WE GET OURSELVES
OUT OF THIS ONE?
[SCREAMING]
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- 50 YEARS EARLIER,
INUYASHA AND KIKYO
WERE DECEIVED INTO THINKING
THEY HAD BETRAYED ONE ANOTHER,
AND IT WAS THE DEMON NARAKU
WHO HAD STAGED THE TREACHERY.
WHY HAD HE DONE SUCH A THING?
WHAT WAS HIS PURPOSE?
INUYASHA'S WRATH AND HIS
BURNING MEMORIES OF KIKYO
FINALLY LEAD HIM
TO NARAKU'S HIDDEN LOCATION.
THERE, INUYASHA FINDS OUT
THE HORRIBLE TRUTH
BEHIND THE LONG-AGO BETRAYAL.
NEXT TIME...
SEE YOU SOON.