>> KIKYO.
IT'S YOU.
>> YES.
I BROUGHT SOME GRUEL FOR YOU.
>> FORGET ME.
DON'T EVEN BOTHER COMING.
GO AWAY.
>> KIKYO WAS SECRETLY HARBORING
A BANDIT NAMED ONIGUMO.
>> WHY CAN'T I TELL INUYASHA
ABOUT IT?
>> KNOWING HIM, HE'LL PROBABLY
JUST BECOME JEALOUS.
>> JEALOUS?
>> INUYASHA, I NEED YOUR HELP.
>> HOW COME?
WHAT'S THIS ABOUT?
>> I'VE BEEN ASKED TO SLAY
A DEMON FROM ANOTHER COUNTRY,
BUT EVEN FOR ME IT WILL BE
A DIFFICULT MISSION.
>> OH, ALL RIGHT,
BUT IT'S GONNA COST YOU.
>> INUYASHA, IT'S COMING
YOUR WAY!
>> LEAVE HIM TO ME.
IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
KIKYO, THAT'S THE DEMON'S
TRUE FORM.
>> RIGHT.
>> HA, RIGHT ON TARGET.
>> YOU--
YOUNG LASS.
>> IT'S KAEDE.
>> YES.
YOUR SISTER POSSESSES WHAT
IS KNOWN AS THE SHIKON JEWEL,
DOES SHE NOT?
>> WHAT WOULD YE KNOW ABOUT
THE JEWEL?
>> ALL WHO ARE WICKED KNOW OF IT
AND PURSUE IT.
>> YE INCLUDED?
>> I UNDERSTAND THAT THE MORE
EVIL THE JEWEL ABSORBS,
THE MORE EVIL IT BECOMES.
OUTSTANDING.
>> MY SISTER HAS IT UNDER HER
CONTROL.
IT WON'T BE CORRUPTED.
>> KIKYO'S MANNER IS
SELF-RIGHTEOUS.
FOR ONCE, I SHOULD LIKE TO SEE
HER APPREHENSIVE AND FRIGHTENED.
THAT WOULD BRING ME TRUE
PLEASURE.
HEH HEH HEH.
>> I SEE.
ONIGUMO SAID THAT, DID HE?
>> BIG SISTER, I DON'T CARE
FOR THAT MAN.
>> BEAR HIM NO GRUDGE.
GIVE HIM PITY.
HIS INJURIES ARE GREAT.
HE SHALL NEVER MOVE FROM THERE
AGAIN.
>> THAT IS WHAT KIKYO HAD TO SAY
ABOUT THE INCIDENT, BUT I FELT
A STRONG FOREBODING ABOUT
HER KINDNESS.
>> WHAT A LOVELY SIGHT.
HOWEVER, I UNDERSTAND IF YOU
REMAIN BENEATH THE CHERRY TREES
FOR TOO LONG, YOU WILL GO
INSANE.
IS IT THE TREES THAT ARE
CHANGING YOU?
YOU SEEM LIKE A COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT PERSON FROM WHEN
I LAST SAW YOU.
AND WHAT OF YOUR PITIFULLY WEAK
POWERS?
SPECTERS AND DEMONS ARE IN THEIR
HEYDAY, ALL OF THEM BREAKING
THROUGH YOUR BARRIER.
>> I SEE.
SO YOU WERE THE ONE UNLEASHING
DEMONS AROUND ME.
>> I WARNED YOU NOT TO LET
YOUR HEART GO TO A MAN.
HE IS THAT WORTHLESS HALF-DEMON,
IF I'M NOT MISTAKEN.
GIVE ME THE SACRED JEWEL.
I SHALL PURIFY IT IN YOUR PLACE.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE THE POWER TO.
>> HA!
DIE, KIKYO!
AAH!
DAMN YOU, KIKYO.
>> NOW LEAVE, AND I WILL SPARE
YOUR LIFE.
>> ONIGUMO.
ONIGUMO.
YOUR EVIL THOUGHTS HAVE BROUGHT
US HERE.
>> A DEMON.
>> TELL ME, WHAT IS IT YOU WANT?
>> I MUST POSSESS MY FORMER
MOBILITY, THEN THE JEWEL
WILL BE MINE, NOT TO MENTION
THE LOVELY MAIDEN KIKYO.
>> DONE.
BUT IN RETURN, WE WILL TAKE
YOUR SOUL.
>> HEH HEH.
MY SOUL IS RANCID TO THE CORE,
YET IT STILL HOLDS VALUE.
FEAST ON MY FLESH.
FEAST ON ME, DEMONS.
DEVOUR ME!
AND IN EXCHANGE, BESTOW ME WITH
YOUR MOBILITY AND STRENGTH!
[SCREAMING]
>> YOU'VE IMPROVED CONSIDERABLY.
>> THANKS.
>> NEXT IS THE ARROW OF SEALING.
>> ARROW OF SEALING?
>> THAT WAS THE ARROW
OF SEALING.
WE USE IT FOR DEMONS WHO ARE
OTHERWISE INVINCIBLE.
>> AND THEN WHAT HAPPENS
TO THE DEMON?
>> THEY FALL INTO AN ETERNAL
SLEEP.
THEY WILL ONLY AWAKEN
WHEN THE ONE WHO SHOT THE ARROW
DEEPLY WISHES FOR THE DEMON
TO REVIVE.
I WARN YOU, THOUGH,
BEWARE OF THIS TREE.
>> HUH?
THE SACRED TREE?
>> IT'S KNOWN AS THE TREE
OF AGES.
IT HAS THE POWER TO TRANSCEND
TIME.
>> TREE OF AGES?
>> IF YOU SEAL A DEMON ONTO THIS
TREE, THE DEMON'S BODY WILL
REMAIN PERFECTLY INTACT.
HUH?
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> THERE ARE SO MANY OF THEM.
OH, HOW COULD I NOT HAVE NOTICED
SUCH A STRONG AURA?
>> GO, DEMONS.
GO AND TAKE THE SACRED JEWEL.
THE SACRED JEWEL WILL GIVE YOU
IMMENSE DEMONIC POWER.
BECOME THE GREATEST DEMONS
OF THEM ALL AND DESTROY
THE PRIESTESS KIKYO.
>> IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
>> INUYASHA!
>> TOOK YOU LONG ENOUGH, KIKYO.
>> FORGIVE ME.
MY SPIRITUAL POWERS
HAVE WEAKENED.
>> OK, LET ME TRY.
>> COME AND GET ME!
BLADES OF BLOOD!
>> INUYASHA!
>> WATCH OUT, KIKYO!
AAH!
>> KAEDE!
>> AAH!
>> FORGIVE ME, KAEDE.
>> IT--IT'S OK.
I THINK I'M ALL RIGHT.
[SQUAWKS]
>> HOW'S YOUR, UH, SISTER'S EYE?
>> I'VE DONE A TERRIBLE THING
TO HER.
I'M ENTIRELY THE ONE TO BLAME.
IF ONLY I HADN'T BEEN SO
CARELESS.
>> HMM, COME ON.
DON'T BLAME YOURSELF TOO MUCH.
THINGS LIKE THIS ARE BOUND
TO HAPPEN WHEN YOU'RE FIGHTING
ALL THE TIME.
>> INUYASHA, ARE YOU UNABLE
TO BE YOURSELF UNLESS YOU
ARE FIGHTING?
>> YOU ASKED ME SOMETHING LIKE
THAT BEFORE.
>> WOULDN'T YOU LIKE TO STOP
FIGHTING?
>> HUH, WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> STOP FIGHTING ALL THE TIME.
STOP AND BECOME HUMAN.
>> ME, BECOME A HUMAN?
>> IT'S POSSIBLE.
IT'S TRUE THAT YOU ARE
HALF-DEMON,
BUT YOU ARE ALSO HALF HUMAN.
>> HMM.
>> IF THE SACRED JEWEL OF
THE 4 SOULS FELL INTO THE HANDS
OF A DEMON, THEIR POWERS WOULD
UNDOUBTEDLY INCREASE.
HOWEVER, IF IT WERE USED TO TURN
YOU INTO A HUMAN, IT WOULD BE
PURIFIED.
THE JEWEL OF THE 4 SOULS WOULD
PROBABLY CEASE TO EXIST.
>> AND THEN WHAT?
WHAT WOULD HAPPEN TO YOU?
>> MY DUTY IS TO PROTECT
THE JEWEL.
WITHOUT IT, I COULD LIVE
THE LIFE OF AN ORDINARY WOMAN.
[GASPS]
>> KIKYO.
KIKYO, I WILL BECOME A HUMAN.
I SWEAR I'M NOT JUST SAYING
THIS.
I WILL BECOME A HUMAN...
>> INUYASHA.
>> SO YOU CAN BECOME A NORMAL
HUMAN, TOO, AND BE MY--
>> ENOUGH.
STOP.
THAT'S ALL I NEED TO HEAR.
>> KIKYO, I TRULY AM IN--
>> INUYASHA, ARE YOU SURE
ABOUT THIS?
>> ABOUT WHAT?
>> ABOUT ME.
ARE YOU SURE?
>> DO YOU EVEN HAVE TO ASK?
>> TOMORROW AT NOON.
IN FRONT OF THE SACRED TREE
IN THE WESTERN FOREST.
WAIT FOR ME THERE.
I'LL BRING THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> I'LL BE THERE.
>> THAT WON'T HAPPEN.
I'LL NEVER ALLOW IT.
>> WHO IS IT?
>> KIKYO, IT'S ME.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER?
HAS SOMETHING HAPPENED?
>> I CAN'T STAND ALL THIS
WAITING.
KIKYO, CAN YOU MAKE ME HUMAN
RIGHT NOW?
>> YOU KNOW I CAN'T.
THE NIGHTTIME IS FILLED
WITH EVIL.
IF WE ARE TO USE THE SACRED
JEWEL, IT MUST BE AFTER SUNRISE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THEN DO IT RIGHT AFTER THE DAY
BREAKS, AGREED?
>> YOU ARE SO HOPELESS.
HMM?
INUYASHA?
>> KIKYO, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
>> HUH?
OH.
JUST OUT.
>> [YAWNS]
>> IT'S EARLY.
GO BACK TO SLEEP.
>> BUT--
>> YOU DON'T NEED TO WORRY,
KAEDE.
I'M ONLY GOING OUT TO FIND
MEDICINAL HERBS FOR YOUR
WOUNDED EYE.
>> MEDICINAL HERBS?
THERE'S ALREADY LOTS RIGHT HERE.
>> UH, UM, THERE MAY BE
SOMETHING MORE EFFECTIVE.
I'M GOING TO TAKE ANOTHER LOOK
AROUND.
>> THANK YOU.
I APPRECIATE IT.
>> KAEDE, DOES YOUR EYE HURT?
>> NO.
IT'S MUCH BETTER TODAY.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
I WON'T BE VERY LONG.
>> AT THAT MOMENT, I FELT
LONELIER THAN I'D EVER FELT
BEFORE.
I WANTED MY SISTER TO STAY
WITH ME FOREVER.
NEVER BEFORE THAT MORNING HAD
I FELT SO STRONGLY HOW MUCH
I WANTED HER TO STAY.
>> I'M RUNNING SO LATE.
INUYASHA?
HE HASN'T EVEN ARRIVED YET.
THAT INUYASHA.
MAYBE HE OVERSLEPT.
HMM.
>> HEH HEH HEH.
>> [MOANS]
>> YOU CAN TRY TO PRETTY
YOURSELF UP WITH THIS, BUT YOU
CAN'T HIDE YOUR TRUE NATURE.
>> WHAT?
>> THIS ROUGE DOESN'T BECOME YOU
AT ALL.
DEMON BLOOD IS GOOD ENOUGH
FOR YOU.
>> INUYASHA?
>> FOOL.
I HAVE NO DESIRE WHATSOEVER
TO BECOME HUMAN.
>> UH?
>> BUT I SHALL TAKE
THE SHIKON JEWEL NONETHELESS.
THANKS.
THIS JEWEL IS ABOUT TO ABSORB A
GREAT DEAL OF PAIN AND SUFFERING
WHEN I USE IT TO SLAUGHTER
THE VILLAGERS.
>> OH, YOU TRAITOR.
TRAITOR!
SO YOU INTENDED TO TRICK ME FROM
THE VERY START.
WAS EVERYTHING YOU TOLD ME
A LIE?
>> I SWEAR I'M NOT JUST SAYING
THIS.
I WILL BECOME A HUMAN...
SO YOU CAN BE A HUMAN, TOO.
>> I HATE YOU.
I HATE YOU!
>> NOW, ON TO THE NEXT ONE.
THE HALF-DEMON.
>> KIKYO?
SHE'S NOT HERE YET.
>> AH, HA HA.
SO YOU'VE COME, HALF-DEMON.
>> WH--WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY,
KIKYO?
>> I SAID, "HALF-DEMON."
CAN'T THOSE UGLY DOG EARS
OF YOURS HEAR WHAT I SAY?
>> UGLY DOG?
>> I CAN'T LET A HALF-DEMON
LIKE YOU HAVE THE SACRED JEWEL.
I WILL DESTROY YOU HERE AND NOW.
DIE, INUYASHA!
BE GONE, HALF-DEMON!
>> DAMN IT!
>> HEH HEH HEH.
NOW THE SACRED JEWEL WILL
BE TAINTED WITH HATRED
AND BITTERNESS.
>> DAMN.
YOU MEAN ALL THIS TIME YOU WERE
JUST USING ME?
>> THEN TELL ME YOUR NAME,
AND I SHALL NEVER CALL YOU
HALF-DEMON AGAIN.
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU SAID,
AND YET--WHY NOW?
>> AAH!
>> HA HA.
HMM.
HEH, SO THERE.
FINALLY, A WAY FOR ME TO BECOME
ALL DEMON AT LAST.
HA, I WON'T LET ANYONE CALL ME
A HALF-DEMON AGAIN!
>> DIE, INUYASHA!
I BELIEVED IN YOU.
I TRUSTED YOU.
>> I NEVER DOUBTED YOU,
NOT FOR A MINUTE!
YET YOU DECEIVED ME.
>> INUYASHA!
>> KI--KIKYO.
HOW COULD--I THOUGHT--
>> SISTER KIKYO!
>> KIKYO!
>> WHO DID THIS TO YOU, KIKYO?
>> AM I GONNA DIE LIKE THIS?
>> STOP, THAT'S ALL I NEED
TO HEAR.
>> I GUESS THAT'S OK.
KIKYO, EVEN THOUGH IT ENDED LIKE
THIS, I STILL LOVE--
>> THE SACRED JEWEL.
IT WAS ALL BECAUSE OF THIS.
LISTEN TO ME, KAEDE.
TAKE THE SACRED JEWEL
AND BURN IT WITH MY BODY.
THAT WAY IT WILL NEVER FALL INTO
THE HANDS OF EVIL AGAIN.
>> KIKYO!
KIKYO!
>> I WILL TAKE THE SACRED JEWEL
WITH ME TO THE NETHERWORLD.
>> IT HAS BEEN 50 YEARS SINCE
INUYASHA WAS SEALED TO
THE SACRED TREE.
HE LOOKS EXACTLY THE SAME
AS HE DID THEN.
50 YEARS AGO, MY SISTER KNEW
THAT SHE WAS GOING TO DIE.
SO WHY DID SHE CHOOSE TO USE
THE ARROW OF SEALING RATHER THAN
A SACRED ARROW TO DESTROY HIM?
WHY DID SHE SEAL INUYASHA TO
THE SACRED TREE--A TREE OF AGES
SAID TO BE ABLE TO TRANSCEND
TIME?
AND IF INUYASHA WAS FILLED WITH
HATRED TOWARD MY SISTER,
WHO TOOK BACK THE SACRED JEWEL
AND SEALED HIM TO THE SACRED
TREE, THEN WHY DOES HE WEAR SUCH
A PEACEFUL EXPRESSION?
IT SEEMS I UNDERSTAND
VERY LITTLE AFTER ALL.
I WONDER SOMETIMES IF
I EVER WILL.
>> [CRYING]
>> OH, IT'S A BABY!
MY FIRST GRANDCHILD!
A BEAUTIFUL BABY GIRL!
>> IT'S OK.
GOOD GIRL.
OH, WE'RE GOING TO CALL
YOU KAGOME.
KAGOME.
>> [CRIES]
>> IT'S NICE TO FINALLY SEE YOU,
KAGOME.
>> KAGOME?
YOUR FRIEND'S ON THE PHONE.
>> THE NOTES FOR PRACTICE?
SURE, I'LL BRING THEM TODAY.
I KNOW, I KNOW.