[BIRDS CHIRPING]
- MM.
[SLURPING]
KAGOME, PASS THE SOY SAUCE!
- IS YOUR ARM BROKEN?
GET IT YOURSELF!
- YEESH. FORGET IT.
I'LL EAT IT PLAIN.
[GRUMBLES]
ENOUGH OF YOUR SNIPPY MOOD AT
THE DINNER TABLE, YOUNG LADY.
MAYBE THEY DIDN'T ALL
HAVE GOOD TABLE MANNERS
BACK IN THE FEUDAL ERA,
BUT IN THIS HOUSE WE DO.
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
IN A WHILE
WE'VE ALL HAD DINNER TOGETHER,
SO BE CHEERFUL.
- I DON'T THINK
THAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
- UH? HMM.
- EXCUSE ME.
[SIGHS]
GOOD LORD,
WHAT'S WRONG WITH HER?
- SHE'S A TEENAGER.
BET ANY MONEY IT'S BOY TROUBLE.
[KIDS TALKING INDISTINCTLY]
[SIGHS]
SEEMS LIKE FOREVER
SINCE I WAS LAST IN SCHOOL.
- KAGOME!
- HUH?
OH, YUKA, ERI, GOOD MORNING!
HI, AYUMI!
- OH, YOU WON'T BE SO CHEERFUL
WHEN YOU HEAR THE NEWS.
- YOU'VE GOT A PROBLEM
ON YOUR HANDS.
- HUH?
- THERE'S BEEN A NEW DEVELOPMENT
WHILE YOU WERE
ABSENT FROM SCHOOL
WITH YOUR INFERIORITY COMPLEX.
[SIGHS]
- NOW I'VE GOT
PSYCHOLOGICAL DISORDERS.
GRANDPA MUST HAVE
RUN OUT OF DISEASES.
- HEY, HOJO! WAIT UP!
- HI!
- GOOD MORNING, HOJO.
- CHECK THAT OUT!
SHE'S ONLY A SEVENTH-GRADER.
THAT JANE DOE HAS BEEN TAGGING
AFTER HOJO LIKE A LOST KITTEN.
- IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE HOJO
IS COMPLAINING TOO MUCH, EITHER.
- WHAT WILL YOU DO, KAGOME?
- DO WHAT?
IF SHE LIKES HIM, GO AHEAD.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN, HUH?
- SHE'S TRYING TO STEAL HIM
AWAY FROM YOU.
- YOU'RE BEING ONE-UPPED
BY A SEVENTH-GRADER.
SHE'S ALL LIKE,
"OH, HOJO, YOU'RE SO COOL,"
MAKING HIM THINK HE'S A REAL
HIPSTER WITH THE CHICKLETS.
- I'M NOT EXACTLY SURE
WHAT YOU JUST SAID,
BUT I'M NOT GOING OUT WITH HOJO,
SO WHAT DO I CARE?
- KAGOME, SPILL IT!
- I BET YOU'RE SEEING SOMEONE
NEW, AND YOU DIDN'T TELL US!
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
- THAT EXPLAINS IT.
- YEAH, OTHERWISE YOU WOULDN'T
BE ACTING SO BLASE ABOUT THIS.
SO WHO IS IT?
- TELL US!
- WHO IS HE? 'FESS UP!
- THERE'S NOTHING TO TELL.
HE'S A JERK.
HE'S NOT WORTH TALKING ABOUT.
I NEVER WANT TO SEE HIM AGAIN.
- SO THERE IS SOMEONE?
- THERE NEVER WAS!
[BELL DINGING]
- SAVED BY THE BELL!
I DON'T WANT TO BE LATE.
SEE YOU IN CLASS!
- KAGOME, GET BACK HERE!
- WAIT UP!
- OH, I CAN'T STAND THIS.
INUYASHA! WHAT DO YOU
TAKE ME FOR ANYWAY?
I HAVE SOME SELF-RESPECT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'D EVEN ASK ME THAT.
- UGH! WELL, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO BITE MY HEAD OFF.
I WAS JUST WONDERING.
- YOU JERK!
DON'T YOU GET ANYTHING?
- IF I'M SUCH A JERK,
THEN STOP TAGGING ALONG
AND GETTING IN THE WAY.
I'M TIRED OF WASTING MY TIME
RESCUING YOU.
- I SEE. SANGO!
- HUH! SHE MISSES
HER WOLF BOY ALREADY.
- I'M GOING BACK HOME, STUPID!
YOU'RE SUCH A JERK!
[BIRDS SINGING]
- HMM. IT LOOKS LIKE
AN ORDINARY OLD WELL.
YET THIS PASSAGE CAN ACCESS
KAGOME'S WORLD?
- YEP. BUT THE ONLY ONES WHO ARE
ABLE TO TRAVEL THROUGH THE WELL
ARE KAGOME AND INUYASHA.
HE'S THE ONLY ONE WHO CAN
GO BACK AND GET KAGOME.
BUT THAT STUBBORN DOLT IS
TOO PROUD TO EVER DO THAT.
HE'D CUT OFF HIS NOSE
TO SPITE HIS FACE.
[SNEEZES]
- EVERYBODY'S TAKING A SHOT
AT ME TODAY. I CAN FEEL IT.
MY EARS ARE BURNING.
- INUYASHA,
STUPID IS AS STUPID DOES.
YE NEED TO LEARN TO BE MORE
CAREFUL WITH YOUR SPEECH.
- ARE YOU CALLING ME STUPID,
YOU OLD HAG?
WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT IT?
YOU WEREN'T EVEN THERE!
- I KNOW THIS, UNGRATEFUL DOG:
IN ORDER TO FIND
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS,
KAGOME'S SPIRITUAL POWER
IS ESSENTIAL,
YET YE MADE HER UPSET WITH YOUR
WORDS AND SENT HER RUNNING HOME.
- THAT WAS HER IDEA!
SHE CHOSE TO GO HOME.
I NEVER FORCED HER.
SHE SAID,
"I'M GOING HOME, STUPID!"
- INUYASHA?
- YEAH, WHAT?
- THAT IMITATION WAS PATHETIC.
- UNH!
I'M A DEMON, NOT A COMEDIAN.
[WOMEN CHATTERING
AND LAUGHING]
- ALL RIGHT, ONE AT A TIME.
LINE UP.
OH, THIS IS A FINE PALM.
YOU'LL LIVE A LONG LIFE
AND HAVE MANY CHILDREN.
- THANK YOU, MONK.
ARE YOU SURE?
- I'M SURE THAT THE FATHER
OF YOUR FIRST CHILD
COULD BE A MAN OF THE CLOTH.
- WHAT ABOUT
YOUR VOW OF CHASTITY?
- YOU JUST GAVE HER THE EXACT
SAME FORTUNE YOU GAVE ME.
- TRUE. BUT I DON'T HAVE TO MAKE
YOU FORTUNATE AT THE SAME TIME.
WE CAN TAKE TURNS.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
THINK IT OVER CAREFULLY.
DENYING YOUR DESTINY NOW
COULD THROW YOU OFF COURSE
FOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
- OH, YOU'RE SO NAUGHTY!
- HA HA HA HA!
- HUH? OH!
- HE'S ACTING LIKE
A DIRTY OLD MAN.
- I AGREE COMPLETELY.
I'M JUST AS EAGER AS YOU ARE
TO CONTINUE OUR QUEST
FOR THE JEWEL SHARDS,
BUT THERE'S NO USE
GETTING IMPATIENT.
UNTIL INUYASHA COOLS DOWN
AND GOES AFTER KAGOME,
WE'RE STUCK HERE
AT A STANDSTILL.
- INUYASHA IS SO STUBBORN
SOMETIMES.
HE'S GOT ENOUGH PRIDE
TO CHOKE A HORSE,
AND HE CAN NEVER ADMIT
WHEN HE'S WRONG.
- THAT'S EXACTLY WHY THE THREE
OF US SHOULD NEVER BE SEEN
ANYWHERE NEAR THE WELL.
- BUT WHY NOT?
- THINK OF INUYASHA'S
PERSONALITY.
EVEN IF HE WANTED
TO GO GET KAGOME,
HE NEVER WOULD
IF SOMEONE ELSE WAS WATCHING.
HE'S NOTHING BUT A BIG SOFTIE
UNDERNEATH THAT HARD-NOSED
EXTERIOR.
[SIGHS]
- APPEARANCES
CAN BE SO DECEIVING.
- I DON'T KNOW
WHO HAS THE BIGGER EGO.
- OH! UH!
ALL RIGHT. NOBODY'S LOOKING.
KAGOME'S NOT GETTING OFF
THAT EASILY
WITHOUT APOLOGIZING TO ME.
OH!
- OK, CLASSES ARE OVER.
TIME FOR YOU TO START TALKING.
- SO, WHAT KIND OF A GUY
ARE YOU SEEING, KAGOME?
- A STUPID CREEP!
HE'S RUDE AND MOODY AND SELFISH
AND DOWNRIGHT IGNORANT.
AND HE GETS SO JEALOUS,
IT'S JUST RIDICULOUS.
- WELL, IF HE'S JEALOUS,
THEN AT LEAST THAT'S A SIGN
HE HAS FEELINGS FOR YOU
AND WANTS YOU FOR HIMSELF.
STILL AT
THE "DOES HE LIKE ME" STAGE?
CALL ME WHEN YOU GET
FURTHER INTO THE STORY LINE.
- MAYBE HE'S MOODY AND JEALOUS
BECAUSE HE'S UNSURE ABOUT
YOUR FEELINGS FOR HIM?
- IF THAT WERE TRUE, I'D BE
THRILLED. BUT THE DEAL IS,
HE'S STILL TOTALLY HUNG UP
OVER HIS FIRST GIRLFRIEND
AND DOESN'T HAVE
THE TIME OF DAY FOR ME.
WAIT A MINUTE,
THAT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
IF HE DIDN'T HAVE
THE TIME OF DAY FOR ME,
THEN HE WOULDN'T GET JEALOUS,
ESPECIALLY IF HE'S
STILL HUNG UP OVER KIKYO.
- SOUNDS LIKE THE GUY'S
REALLY PASSIONATE
AND FULL OF
CONFLICTING EMOTIONS.
- YOU GOT THAT RIGHT.
HE ACTUALLY TRIED TO KILL SOME
GUY FOR TRYING TO COME ON TO ME.
- KILL HIM?
- THAT'S WAY PSYCHO.
- BUT YOU DIDN'T TELL US THAT
THE GUY WAS MENTALLY UNBALANCED.
- YOU GOT TO DITCH THIS DUDE.
HE COULD TURN INTO A STALKER.
- UH, BUT...
- THERE'S A DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN MOODY AND BIPOLAR.
- DOES HE HAVE TOTALLY
HARD-CORE FITS OF RAGE?
- HE'S COME A LONG WAY,
CONSIDERING HIS DIFFICULT PAST.
HE'S STRONG AND COURAGEOUS
AND HAS MOMENTS WHERE
HE'S EVEN ALMOST NICE TO ME.
- KAGOME...
- YEAH?
- YOU SOUND LIKE YOU'RE
IN LOVE WITH THIS NUT BAR.
- HUH?
I DON'T LOVE INUYASHA.
THAT'S...IMPOSSIBLE.
- COME ON, YOU MUST
LOVE HIM, KAGOME.
IT'S WRITTEN ALL OVER YOUR FACE.
HEH HEH.
- IT IS? ME?
WITH INUYASHA?
[WHOOSHING]
- HMM. HMM?
WHAT?
WHY ISN'T SHE HERE?
[GRUNTS]
[SNIFFS]
I CAN SMELL KAGOME'S SCENT
ALL OVER THIS ROOM.
[SIGHS]
- WHAT DO YOU KNOW!
IT'S INUYASHA.
[SCREAMS]
- WHAT?
- DON'T YOU REMEMBER ME FROM
THE LAST TIME YOU WERE HERE?
I'M KAGOME'S KID BROTHER SOTA.
- YEAH.
- DID YOU COME TO VISIT HER?
- WELL, SORT OF.
- OH, GOOD. BECAUSE I WAS
WORRIED MAYBE THE TWO OF YOU
HAD A FIGHT OR SOMETHING.
- HUH...
- YOU KNOW, KAGOME.
WHEN SHE'S IN A BAD MOOD,
YOU GOT TO STAND CLEAR.
- HMM.
- HEY, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
[SIGHS]
- SHE'S STILL ANGRY AT ME?
MAN, CAN SHE EVER HOLD A GRUDGE.
- I'M EXHAUSTED.
WHAT A DAY.
HI, I'M HOME.
- KAGOME IS HOME. HEY, SIS,
GUESS WHO JUST SHOWED UP? UGH!
- QUIET! AND DON'T TELL
KAGOME THAT I CAME,
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS.
YOU GOT THAT, KID?
- UH-HUH.
- UNH!
IT'S A PROMISE BETWEEN US,
MAN TO MAN, OK?
- MAN TO MAN? YOU BET.
MM-HMM.
[STRAINS]
[DOOR CREAKS]
- SOTA?
- HI, HOW ARE YOU DOING?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN MY ROOM?
- UH...I CAN'T TELL YOU.
IT'S A MAN-TO-MAN PROMISE.
- HUH?
[WATER RUNNING]
- NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT IT,
INUYASHA DID COME ALL THAT WAY
TO RESCUE ME FROM THE WOLVES,
AND INSTEAD OF SAYING THANK YOU,
I TURNED AROUND
AND HELPED KOGA ESCAPE.
NO WONDER HE WAS SO UPSET.
I CAN'T REALLY BLAME HIM.
- I DON'T CARE
IF KAGOME IS ANGRY.
I'LL DROP DEAD
BEFORE I APOLOGIZE.
UH! UH! UH!
- IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
HE ACCOMPLISHED ANYTHING.
- THERE IS NO END
TO HIS TROUBLE-MAKING.
- MIROKU, I THOUGHT YOU TOLD US
NOT TO GO ANYWHERE NEAR THE WELL
IN CASE INUYASHA SEES US.
- YEAH, I KNOW,
BUT I COULDN'T RESIST
WATCHING INUYASHA
MAKE A TOTAL FOOL OF HIMSELF.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
- HEY, KAGOME!
- HUH?
- NICE TO SEE YOU
BACK AT SCHOOL.
I HOPE THAT MEANS
YOU'RE FEELING BETTER.
- A MOVIE?
YEAH, I'D LIKE TO CATCH UP A
BIT. I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU IN AGES.
- I WAS THINKING OF CROSSING
OVER TO THE FEUDAL ERA
THIS WEEKEND, BUT HOW WOULD I
EXPLAIN THAT ONE?
- IS SATURDAY A GOOD DAY
FOR YOU TO GO OUT?
- WELL, I DON'T REALLY--
- SATURDAY IS PERFECT.
- HUH?
- SHE'D LOVE TO GO.
- REALLY?
- WAIT. I WOULD?
- GREAT. I'LL PICK YOU UP
AROUND 6:00, OK?
- WHY DID YOU SET ME UP
LIKE THAT?
- HOJO IS A NICE GUY.
HE'S PERFECT FOR YOU
AND HE TREATS YOU WITH RESPECT.
SOME DANGEROUS BAD BOY MIGHT
SEEM LIKE A THRILL FOR NOW,
BUT YOU CAN GET REALLY MESSED UP
GETTING INVOLVED
WITH SOMEONE LIKE THAT,
AND YOU DESERVE BETTER,
SO DON'T EVER SETTLE FOR LESS.
- THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT
INUYASHA, AREN'T THEY?
- YOU ARE GOING TO THE MOVIE.
- OK.
[SIGHS]
INUYASHA IS PROBABLY
STILL MAD AT ME.
HE'S THE TYPE TO HOLD A GRUDGE.
- I'M TIRED OF WASTING MY TIME
RESCUING YOU.
[SIGHS]
- IT'S HOPELESS.
IF I GO BACK NOW,
WE'LL ONLY FIGHT.
[BIRDS SINGING]
- YOU KNOW KAGOME.
WHEN SHE'S IN A BAD MOOD,
YOU GOT TO STAND CLEAR.
[SIGHS]
- INUYASHA!
- AAAH!
DON'T POP OUT AT ME LIKE THAT!
YOU SCARED THE LIFE OUT OF ME!
- SWALLOW YOUR PRIDE
AND GO BACK.
I'M SURE KAGOME
WILL FORGIVE YOU.
- WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY?
DO YOU THINK THIS IS
ALL MY FAULT?
SHE'S TO BLAME, TOO, YOU KNOW.
- YEAH,
BUT YOU WERE ACCUSING KAGOME
OF BEING INVOLVED WITH KOGA!
- HUH?
- YOU'RE NOT GOING TO BE DEALING
WITH ANYTHING, YOU UNDERSTAND?
KOGA'S HURT.
THIS IS NO TIME FOR POSTURING.
- OH...
- I KNOW KAGOME PROTECTED KOGA
AND HELPED HIM ESCAPE,
AND I UNDERSTAND THAT
KOGA IS YOUR SWORN ENEMY.
WHAT I DON'T UNDERSTAND
IS WHY KAGOME HELPED HIM
AFTER HE KIDNAPPED HER.
SHE WAS TERRIFIED WHEN
HE THREW HER OVER HIS SHOULDER
AND LEAPT OVER CLIFFS AND
DRAGGED HER INTO THE WOLF DEN,
SO WHY DID SHE TAKE HIS SIDE?
INUYASHA, DO YOU THINK
IT'S POSSIBLE
THAT KAGOME REALLY MIGHT HAVE
FALLEN IN LOVE WITH KOGA?
- ARGH! WHAT ARE YOU
ASKING ME FOR?
ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR MIND? THERE
IS NO WAY KAGOME LOVES KOGA.
IF YOU'RE GOING
TO REASON WITH ME,
COME UP WITH
SOMETHING REASONABLE!
- HELP!
I'M SORRY, INUYASHA,
YOU'RE RIGHT.
KAGOME DOESN'T LOVE KOGA.
SHE'S JUST KINDHEARTED.
- SHUT UP, ALREADY!
YOU NEVER CHANGE
YOUR TUNE, DO YOU?
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE TRYING TO DO.
YOU WANT ME TO GO AFTER HER,
BUT I'M NOT GONNA!
FORGET IT!
- BUT YOU WANT TO GO AFTER HER,
AND YOU KNOW IT,
SO JUST HEAR ME OUT.
YOU DON'T KNOW THE MIND OF
A WOMAN AND NEITHER DO I,
SO MAYBE WE SHOULD
TAKE THE ADVICE
OF SOMEONE OLDER AND WISER
LIKE KAEDE. IT CAN'T HURT.
- THIS IS NONE OF HER BUSINESS.
- JUST RELAX. I WON'T TELL HER
THIS IS ABOUT YOU AND KAGOME.
I'LL PRETEND I'M ASKING ADVICE
FOR A FRIEND OF MINE, OK?
- HUH! DO YOU THINK
IT'LL WORK?
I GUESS IT CAN'T HURT
TO HEAR HER OUT
AS LONG AS
SHE DOESN'T KNOW IT'S ME.
- RIGHT ON! LET'S GO!
HA HA HA!
- ONLY FOR A FEW MINUTES.
- KAEDE, DO YOU HAVE
ANY EXPERIENCE WITH DOGS?
- DOGS?
- YEAH. THIS ISN'T ABOUT ME, OK?
- ALL RIGHT, THEN.
TELL ME MORE
ABOUT YOUR DOG FRIEND.
- HERE'S THE DEAL.
IT'S A LITTLE COMPLICATED.
THERE ONCE WAS A DOG.
HE HAPPENED TO BE FRIENDS
WITH A CAT,
BUT THEN A WOLF APPEARED
AND FELL IN LOVE WITH THE CAT.
THE DOG WAS
VERY PROTECTIVE OF THE CAT,
AND HE FOUGHT WITH
THE WOLF CONSTANTLY.
ONE DAY, THE WOLF STOLE THE CAT
AND WHISKED HER AWAY.
BUT THEN SOME BIG, UGLY BIRD
SWOOPED DOWN FROM THE SKY
AND PECKED AT THE WOLF
AND HURT HIM VERY BADLY.
MEANWHILE, THE DOG CAME
TO RESCUE THE CAT,
BUT WHEN HE GOT THERE,
HE NOTICED ALL THESE UGLY BIRDS,
SO HE KILLED THEM.
THE DOG WANTED TO KILL
THE INJURED WOLF NEXT,
BUT THE CAT PRACTICALLY
SCRATCHED HIS EYES OUT
IN ORDER TO PROTECT THE WOLF
AND LET HIM ESCAPE.
YOU SEE, THE CAT WAS ONLY TRYING
TO HELP THE INJURED WOLF,
BUT THE DOG SUSPECTED
THAT THE CAT
HAD ACTUALLY FALLEN IN LOVE
WITH THE WOLF.
SO, THE DOG WAS
A REAL JERK ABOUT IT,
AND THE CAT HISSED AT HIM
AND RAN DOWN A WELL BACK HOME.
SO THAT'S THE BASIC STORY
FOR YOU, KAEDE.
I WANT TO KNOW
HOW WE CAN GET THE CAT AND DOG
BACK TOGETHER AS FRIENDS AGAIN.
- FIRST THE DOG MUST ACKNOWLEDGE
THAT HE MADE A MISTAKE.
- WHAT MISTAKE?
- WHY ARE YE WHINING?
THIS IS ABOUT SHIPPO'S
DOG FRIEND, IS IT NOT?
- UH...FINE, CONTINUE.
- CATS ARE COY. SHE IS
PROBABLY LONGING FOR THE DOG
TO COME AFTER HER
AND MAKE AMENDS.
THE DOG AND THE CAT HAVE
MISUNDERSTOOD ONE ANOTHER.
THAT IS WHY THEY WILL BE
AT LOGGERHEADS
UNTIL THE AIR IS CLEARED.
HENCE, THE DOG MUST
GO AND SEE THE CAT,
AND THEY MUST SPEAK
ABOUT THE MATTER FRANKLY.
THAT IS THE MOST
EXPEDIENT SOLUTION.
[BOTH LAUGH]
- KAGOME, HOW LONG ARE YOU
GOING TO STICK AROUND HERE?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
THIS IS MY HOME.
I'VE GOT HOMEWORK
AND EXAMS TO STUDY FOR.
I CAN'T GO RACING OFF
TO THE FEUDAL ERA
WHENEVER I WANT TO, YOU KNOW.
- WELL, THAT NEVER
STOPPED YOU BEFORE.
- I'LL LEAVE WHEN INUYASHA
COMES TO GET ME.
- MAYBE HE WON'T COME FOR YOU.
[PENCIL TIP SNAPS]
- HOW DARE YOU SAY
SOMETHING LIKE THAT!
GET OUT OF MY ROOM!
[CAT MEOWS]
- WHY WOULD HE WANT
TO COME GET YOU
IF YOU'RE ALWAYS
BITING PEOPLE'S HEADS OFF?
- I'M BITING
PEOPLE'S HEADS OFF, HUH?
OH.
I'LL GET UP EARLY AND STUDY.
I CAN'T CONCENTRATE TONIGHT.
[SIGHS]
I'VE MISSED MY BED.
IT SURE BEATS SLEEPING
ON THE COLD GROUND OUTSIDE.
THAT'S NOT TRUE. YOU LOVE
SLEEPING UNDER THE STARS,
KNOWING INUYASHA
IS WATCHING OVER YOU.
I WONDER WHAT STAR
HE'S UNDER TONIGHT.
[CLOCK TICKING]
[GRUNTS]
- DAMN! SHE'S ASLEEP ALREADY.
- INUYASHA.
- OH! SHE'S TALKING
IN HER SLEEP.
IS SHE DREAMING ABOUT ME?
- SIT!
- UGH! UH!
HER DREAM IS MY NIGHTMARE.
[ALARM RINGING]
[WHIMPERING]
- HMM? MY ALARM CLOCK IS GONE.
HUH?
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
- MAYBE IT WAS INUYASHA?
OH!
HUH?
OH! HE WAS HERE.
[BIRDS SINGING]
- SOMETHING BIG CAME UP?
- UH-HUH.
SO I WON'T BE ABLE TO GO
TO THE MOVIES ON SATURDAY.
I'M REALLY SORRY.
- I SEE.
- NEVER MIND ME, HOJO.
PLEASE DON'T TAKE IT PERSONALLY.
YOU COULD ASK
THAT SEVENTH-GRADER.
I BET SHE'D BE THRILLED TO GO.
- HUH?
- COME ON, YOU KNOW THE ONE.
SHE'S BEEN CHASING AFTER YOU
FOR WEEKS NOW.
- KAGOME, IS THAT WHAT
THIS IS ALL ABOUT?
DON'T BE SILLY.
I'M NOT GOING OUT WITH
ANYBODY ELSE. DON'T WORRY.
WHAT A RELIEF. I THINK
IT'S KIND OF SWEET OF YOU.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU ACTUALLY
GET JEALOUS OVER ME!
- WELL...
- DON'T WORRY.
THERE'S ALWAYS NEXT WEEK. CIAO!
- NOTHING FAZES HIM, DOES IT?
IF ONLY INUYASHA HAD CONFIDENCE
LIKE YOU, HOJO!
[SIGHS]
- HUH? K-KAGOME?
- HI, I THOUGHT I'D DROP BY.
THERE'S NO WAY
HE'S GOING TO APOLOGIZE FIRST,
SO I MIGHT AS WELL GET THIS OVER
WITH AND MOVE ON WITH LIFE.
WELL, UH, INUYASHA--
- OK, I'M SORRY.
- HUH?
- WHY ARE YOU
STARING AT ME LIKE THAT?
YOU'RE STILL HOLDING A GRUDGE,
AREN'T YOU?
- OH, NO, I'M NOT MAD ANYMORE.
I'M JUST SHOCKED
THAT YOU ACTUALLY CAME OUT
AND APOLOGIZED TO ME FIRST.
I REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
[MUMBLES]
- ARE YOU SURE?
- IS THAT WHAT
YOU'RE APOLOGIZING FOR?
FOR BREAKING MY ALARM CLOCK?
- I'VE GOT NOTHING ELSE
TO APOLOGIZE FOR.
[GRUMBLES]
- KAGOME, WAIT!
- KAGOME!
- HE'S DOING HIS BEST.
TRY TO CALM DOWN.
- HOW LONG HAVE YOU GUYS
BEEN WATCHING US?
- BELIEVE ME,
HE REALLY IS SORRY.
- YES, HE WENT TO
GO GET YOU TWICE.
AND SINCE YOU LEFT FOR HOME,
ALL HE'S DONE IS SIGH
HEAVILY AND MOPE AROUND.
- HE CAME OVER TWICE?
- ENOUGH, ALREADY.
GIVE ME A BREAK!
HOW DID YOU KNOW I WENT?
CAN'T A GUY HAVE ANY PRIVACY
AROUND HERE, YOU BUNCH OF SPIES?
- JUST RELAX, INUYASHA.
- SHE CAME BACK.
THAT'S THE IMPORTANT THING.
SWALLOW YOUR PRIDE FOR ONCE
AND APOLOGIZE NICELY.
[GRUMBLES]
- SHUT UP!
[EVERYBODY SCREAMING]
- PLEASE FORGIVE US, INUYASHA!
- NEVER!
- WE WERE WORRIED ABOUT YOU!
- I DON'T CARE!
BUTT OUT OF MY LIFE, STUPID!
[SCREAMING CONTINUES]
- COME ON, INUYASHA!
- YE MUST FORGIVE HIM.
KAGOME, HE IS JUST HAPPY
THAT YE CAME BACK.
[INUYASHA AND FRIENDS
SCREAMING]
- GET BACK HERE!
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- I FEEL THE WIND.
IT'S A GHOSTLY HOWL.
THE GALES SUDDENLY
TURN INTO BLADES,
SLICING THROUGH ANYTHING
AND EVERYTHING.
AT MIROKU'S CASTLE, WE COME
ACROSS A MOUNTAIN OF CORPSES.
THEY'RE THE BODIES
OF KOGA'S DEMON WOLF TRIBE.
THE WOLF PACK RISES UP
AND ATTACKS INUYASHA!
STOP, KOGA! IT'S A TRAP!
INUYASHA WASN'T THE ONE
WHO KILLED YOUR FRIENDS!
NEXT ON "INUYASHA"...
SEE YOU SOON!