>> HERE WE COME.
IT'S THE START OF "INUYASHA."
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL
THE SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY NARAKU WITH
MY TETSUSAIGA.
>> EVERYONE PURSUING NARAKU
CONVERGES ON MOUNT HAKUREI,
BUT BANKOTSU, THE LAST
AND STRONGEST OF THE BAND OF 7,
IS THERE WAITING TO FIGHT
INUYASHA.
>> IT'S UP TO ALL OF US.
>> TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FEUDAL FAIRYTALE.
>> "INUYASHA!"
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> IT HAS TO BE NARAKU.
>> LORD SESSHOMARU, WHAT IS IT?
>> JUST AS I THOUGHT.
>> "FINAL BATTLE:
THE LAST AND STRONGEST
OF THE BAND OF 7."
>> [GROWLING]
>> [GRUNTING]
>> KOGA!
>> KAGOME!
AAGH!
>> YOU GUYS ARE TOO SLOW.
>> HEY, THERE, YOU GUYS!
>> KOGA!
[PANTING]
>> THANK GOODNESS WE FINALLY
CAUGHT UP.
>> YOU TWO JUST GOT UP AND LEFT.
>> YEAH, SORRY.
BUT I'M GLAD YOU'RE OK.
KIRARA?
>> YOU, TOO, SHIPPO?
>> I FEEL A LOT BETTER.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY YET,
BUT IT SEEMS THE SACRED BARRIER
HAS BEEN DISSOLVED.
AND I CAN SMELL SOMETHING COMING
FROM THAT MOUNTAIN.
IT'S NARAKU'S SCENT.
AND IT'S A WHOLE LOT MORE
POWERFUL THAN IT WAS BEFORE.
>> HERE THEY COME AGAIN!
>> KEEP THEM AWAY FROM ME!
>> MAYBE THEY'RE HUNGRY OR
SOMETHING!
[GRUNTING]
>> LORD SESSHOMARU, NO!
EXCELLENT SWORDSMANSHIP,
AS ALWAYS.
NOW, IT'S TIME FOR MY STAFF OF
TWO HEADS!
HA HA HA HA HA!
COME ON, YOU PATHETIC DEMONS!
>> YOU TELL 'EM, MASTER JAKEN.
>> HA HA!
>> [GRUNTING]
LET'S GO!
>> BUT WHERE DO WE GO TO?
>> TO GO GET NARAKU,
WHERE ELSE?
>> [GASPS]
>> LET'S GO, KAGOME.
>> KIRARA, LET'S GET GOING!
[ROARS]
>> HEY!
WAIT UP!
>> NOT AGAIN!
>> I REALLY HOPE EVERYONE'S OK.
>> I'M SURE THEY'RE JUST FINE,
SHIPPO.
>> [GROWLS]
BANKOTSU...
ARE YOU PLANNING TO BLOCK MY
WAY?
>> YOU'RE DAMN RIGHT.
YOU KILLED ALL MY BAND OF 7
BROTHERS.
SO, NOW I'M GOING TO AVENGE
THEIR DEATHS.
>> YEAH, WELL, 6 OUT OF 7 AIN'T
ALL THAT BAD.
BUT IF KILLING YOU IS THE ONLY
WAY I CAN GET TO THAT BASTARD
NARAKU, THEN IT'S TIME FOR A
LITTLE REUNION!
WIND SCAR!
>> FOOL!
YOU THINK THAT'LL WORK ON ME?!
WELL, THINK AGAIN!
[GRUNTS]
>> A BLAST OF HEAT?
[GRUNTING]
>> SO...
WE'RE EVENLY MATCHED.
HA.
>> LAST TIME WE FOUGHT AT
HIJIRI ISLAND, HE ALSO MANAGED
TO COUNTER MY WIND SCAR.
AND NOW HE'S EVEN STRONGER.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE UP TO.
YOU'RE USING THE OTHER 6 SACRED
JEWEL SHARDS!
>> OF COURSE.
AND I USE THEM WITH PRIDE.
I THINK OF THEM OF KEEPSAKES
FROM MY FALLEN BROTHERS.
KYOKOTSU...
MUKOTSU...
SUIKOTSU...
GINKOTSU...
JAKOTSU...
RENKOTSU.
ADD MY OWN JEWEL SHARD TO ALL
THOSE, AND IT TOTALS 7.
SO, YOU SEE, I HAVE MORE THAN
ENOUGH POWER TO DEFEAT YOU!
>> WIND SCAR!
[GRUNTING]
I DON'T HAVE TIME TO MESS
AROUND.
[GROWLING]
[GRUNTING]
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER, INUYASHA?!
THAT'S INTERESTING.
WERE YOU ALWAYS THIS WEAK,
INUYASHA?
OR IS IT THAT I'VE BECOME WAY
TOO POWERFUL FOR YOU?
>> [PANTING]
ARE YOU SAYING THAT YOU HAVE
THE 7 JEWEL SHARDS, BANKOTSU...
AND THAT'S THE BEST YOU CAN DO?
>> I GOTTA SAY, YOU SURE DO KNOW
HOW TO TALK TOUGH.
BUT UNFORTUNATELY FOR YOU, A BIG
MOUTH WON'T BE ENOUGH.
>> HA.
I'LL CARVE OUT EVERY ONE OF
THOSE JEWEL SHARDS.
SO, GET READY TO MEET YOUR
MAKER, BANKOTSU!
[GROWLING]
YOU SHOULD BE ROTTING IN YOUR
GRAVE LIKE A GOOD CORPSE.
AND I'M GONNA BE THE ONE THAT
MAKES SURE THAT YOU DO.
>> THAT'S VERY HIGH AND MIGHTY
FOR ONE SUCH AS YOU...
A PATHETIC LITTLE DEMON WHO WAS
NAILED TO A TREE.
>> OH, YOU SON OF A...
>> MY MISTAKE.
YOU'RE NOT A REAL DEMON--
JUST A HALF-DEMON.
NARAKU TOLD ME ALL ABOUT YOU AND
THAT DEAD PRIESTESS KIKYO.
>> [GROWLS]
WHY, YOU...
[GRUNTING]
>> A MEASLY HALF-DEMON WHO WAS
PINNED TO A TREE FOR 50 YEARS
HAS NO BUSINESS CRITICIZING
THOSE OF US WHO WERE
RESURRECTED.
>> WHAT'S THAT?
[GRUNTING]
HA.
SEEMS LIKE YOU AND NARAKU HAVE
BEEN TALKING QUITE A LOT, HUH?
>> ACTUALLY, THIS IS THE SECOND
TIME I'VE RUN INTO NARAKU.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
>> THE FIRST TIME WE MET WAS
BEFORE THE BAND OF 7 WAS FORMED.
LOOKING BACK, IT WAS KIND OF A
STRANGE COINCIDENCE.
>> SO, YOU'RE OLD PALS THEN?
>> HA!
I DON'T BEFRIEND DEMONS.
BACK THEN, I WAS ALWAYS LOOKING
FOR A CHALLENGE, ALWAYS LOOKING
FOR STRONG OPPONENTS TO BEAT.
[GRUNTING]
I DIDN'T CARE IF THEY WERE
DEMONS, AS LONG AS THEY WERE
STRONG.
[GROWLING]
ONE DAY, I HEARD ABOUT A
FRIGHTENING, POWERFUL DEMON AND
ENTERED THE LIFELESS FOREST IN
WHICH HE WAS SUPPOSED TO DWELL.
[DISTANT ROARING]
I'VE COME TO FIGHT THE DEMON
WHO RULES THIS FOREST.
>> PERHAPS IT WAS HIM.
>> DID YOU KILL HIM?
>> HMM.
ARE YOU A DEMON-SLAYER
OR SOME KIND OF MONK?
>> I AM NEITHER ONE OF THOSE.
IF YOU'RE TELLING ME YOU'RE
STRONG, THEN I WISH TO FIGHT
YOU.
>> OH.
YOU WANT TO TEST YOUR STRENGTH?
>> ONE LIKE YOU--WHO POSSESSED
DEMONIC POWERS FROM THE MOMENT
HE WAS BORN--COULDN'T POSSIBLY
UNDERSTAND!
[GRUNTS]
HUH?
>> HA HA HA HA HA.
FROM THE MOMENT I WAS BORN.
>> WHAT'S SO FUNNY?!
>> YOU DESIRE DEMONIC POWERS,
DO YOU?
>> SO, THEN YOU ADMIT THAT
YOU'RE A DEMON?
>> I HAVE BEEN WANDERING THE
LAND SEARCHING FOR A POWER WHICH
I HAVE BEEN UNABLE TO ACQUIRE.
>> THE SHIKON JEWEL, YOU SAY.
>> I DO NOT KNOW IF OR WHEN IT
WILL MANIFEST ITSELF IN THIS
WORLD AGAIN.
>> HEY, BIG BROTHER.
OH, YOU'RE KIDDING.
YOU DESTROYED IT ALREADY?
OH.
YOU COULD AT LEAST LEAVE ME
ONE TO KILL, OK?
SO, YOU HUNGRY?
>> HEY, JAKOTSU,
LET'S GO TO WAR.
>> HUH?
BUT WHAT FOR?
I THOUGHT YOU SAID YOU'D NEVER
TAKE ORDERS FROM THE SAMURAI.
>> AND I WON'T.
WE'LL BE MERCENARIES AND
SLAUGHTER EVERYONE.
THE SAMURAI WON'T BE ABLE TO
COMPLAIN TO THE LEADER OF AN
ELITE BAND OF MERCENARIES.
>> YES, BUT THERE'S ONLY
YOU AND ME.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
I GUESS WE NEED TO RECRUIT SOME
MORE COMRADES.
[SIGHS]
>> WAIT UP, BIG BROTHER.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> I WONDER HOW MANY MEN WE
SHOULD HAVE IN OUR MERCENARY
BAND.
>> HUH?
WELL, YOU CAN COUNT ME IN,
I SUPPOSE.
BUT MAKE SURE THERE'S SOME
GOOD-LOOKING GUYS.
>> DON'T BE SILLY.
WHAT'S MOST IMPORTANT IS THAT
THEY'RE STRONG.
>> HUH?
HMM.
YEAH, I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
IF WE RECRUITED GOOD-LOOKING
WARRIORS, I'D JUST WANT TO CUT
THEM UP.
WHAT WAS I THINKING?
HA HA HA HA.
>> HA HA HA HA.
HA HA HA HA HA.
NARAKU AND I MET AGAIN AFTER
THAT, AND HE TOLD ME MUCH MORE
THAN HE DID AT OUR FIRST
MEETING.
>> NARAKU DIDN'T RESURRECT YOU
JUST TO HAVE SOMEONE TO TALK TO.
YOU MUST BE A REAL IDIOT,
BANKOTSU.
>> YOU'RE THE ONLY IDIOT AROUND
HERE.
>> WHAT?
>> YOU CAN TELL FROM A GLANCE
WHAT KIND OF MAN HE IS.
A SHARPER PERSON WOULD SEE THAT.
>> [GROWLS]
WATCH YOUR MOUTH, BANKOTSU.
NARAKU'S JUST TAKING ADVANTAGE
OF YOU AND MAKING YOU DO HIS
DIRTY WORK.
>> WELL, IT DOESN'T MATTER!
I'M A BUSY MAN, AND I'VE GOT
THINGS TO DO--LIKE SETTLING
THE SCORE WITH YOU!
>> COME ON!
[GRUNTING]
>> I'VE BEEN GIVEN THIS SECOND
CHANCE AT LIFE, AND I'M NOT
GONNA WASTE IT.
>> WIND SCAR!
>> [GRUNTING]
>> AWAKEN, BANKOTSU.
AWAKEN.
AWAKEN, BANKOTSU, AWAKEN.
I GRANT YOU LIFE ONCE AGAIN.
>> [GROANING]
WHO ARE YOU?
>> TO THINK THE MAN I MET ALL
THOSE YEARS AGO WAS BANKOTSU OF
THE BAND OF 7.
>> [GRUNTING]
I REMEMBER NOW.
YOU'RE THAT DEMON I MET IN THE
FOREST.
>> MY NAME IS NARAKU.
>> NARAKU?
WAIT?
WHAT IS THIS?
THE 7 OF US WERE BEHEADED.
>> YOU ARE QUITE RIGHT.
WE ARE INSIDE YOUR GRAVE
RIGHT NOW.
>> HUH?
[SIGHS]
>> I EMBEDDED A SHARD OF THE
SACRED JEWEL INSIDE YOUR BODY.
THAT IS THE POWER YOU FEEL.
>> AH.
SACRED JEWEL SHARDS CAN BE VERY
USEFUL, CAN'T THEY?
>> I WANT YOU TO SERVE ME,
BANKOTSU.
IF YOU DO, THEN THIS RENEWED
LIFE OF YOURS WILL BE
EVERLASTING.
NOW, GO FORTH WITH YOUR 6
COMRADES...
AND DESTROY MY ENEMIES.
>> [GRUNTING]
I'M NOT DOING THIS BECAUSE OF
HIS ORDERS.
[GROWLS]
>> [GRUNTING]
>> SO, YOU SURVIVED.
THAT'S GOOD!
'CAUSE NOW I CAN KILL YOU!
>> ONE OF US IS GONNA DIE TODAY,
BUT IT ISN'T GONNA BE ME!
[RUMBLING]
>> IT'S COLLAPSING!
>> IT SEEMS THE BARRIER AROUND
THE SACRED MOUNTAIN HAS BEEN
TOTALLY DISSOLVED.
AN EVIL AURA IS POURING OUT.
>> IS IT NARAKU'S AURA?
>> YES.
AND IT'S MUCH STRONGER THAN
BEFORE.
WAIT.
IT'S A DEMONIC AURA...
AND IT'S GETTING STRONGER.
[PANTING]
>> HEY, WAIT!
IS THIS THE SHAFT WE WERE IN
BEFORE?
[CRASH]
>> HUH?
>> MIROKU?
>> YES.
I SENSE IT, TOO.
[GASPS]
NARAKU!
>> IT IS HIM!
HEY, WAIT!
>> [GASPS]
>> THAT HAS TO BE...
>> KEEP LOOKING DOWN AND YOU'LL
LOSE YOUR HEAD.
>> KAGURA.
>> HMM.
>> MIROKU, NARAKU HAS
DISAPPEARED.
>> HE WAS THERE,
BUT THEN IT SEEMED LIKE HE RAN
AWAY.
NOW I GET IT.
NARAKU IS STILL INCOMPLETE,
ISN'T HE, KAGURA?
>> HUH?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, MONK?
>> NARAKU TOOK REFUGE INSIDE
MOUNT HAKUREI BECAUSE HIS
BARRIER WAS BROKEN BY INUYASHA'S
RED TETSUSAIGA.
ISN'T THAT THE CASE?
>> [GRUNTING]
>> [GROANS]
HE'S BROKEN THROUGH MY BARRIER.
>> THAT'S WHY NARAKU HID HIMSELF
IN HERE, ISN'T IT?
TO REFORM HIS BARRIER AND
RESTORE HIS POWERS.
>> I'M SORRY TO DISAPPOINT YOU,
BUT NARAKU DOESN'T TELL ME
ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
I SUPPOSE HE DOESN'T TRUST ME
ALL THAT MUCH.
IT WOULD BE BETTER TO ASK
KANNA ABOUT NARAKU,
THOUGH SHE PROBABLY WON'T SAY
MUCH.
>> TELL US EVERYTHING YOU KNOW
RIGHT NOW, KAGURA!
>> IF YOU REALLY WANT TO KNOW
ALL THIS SO BADLY, WHY NOT ASK
NARAKU?
I'LL EVEN HELP YOU FOLLOW HIM!
>> [GASPS]
>> [SCREAMS]
[SCREAMING]
>> HA.
>> COME AND GET IT, BANKOTSU!
>> [SCREAMING]
>> [GRUNTING]
DAMN IT.
I'M NOT GETTING ANYWHERE.
IF ONLY BANKOTSU WERE A DEMON
MY BACKLASH WAVE WOULD TAKE CARE
OF HIM.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER, INUYASHA?
ARE YOU OUT OF BREATH?
>> BUT HE'S HUMAN...
EVEN IF HE IS AN EVIL SPECTER,
HE DOESN'T HAVE A DEMONIC AURA.
TAKE THIS!
WITHOUT THE OPPONENT'S DEMONIC
AURA TO ENTRAP AND SEND BACK AT
HIM, I CAN'T USE MY BACKLASH
WAVE.
DAMN THAT NARAKU.
THAT'S WHY HE WENT TO THE
TROUBLE TO RESURRECT THESE 7
SPECTERS TO FIGHT HIS BATTLES.
>> WELL, WELL.
YOU LOOK DEEP IN THOUGHT.
ARE YOU THINKING ABOUT WHERE
YOU'D LIKE TO BE BURIED?
>> HA!
I WAS THINKING ABOUT HOW I'D
INTENDED TO KILL YOU RIGHT AWAY.
BUT I CHANGED MY MIND...
'CAUSE I'M HAVING
WAY TOO MUCH FUN!
>> [PANTING]
WHAT'S GOING ON, KOGA?
>> ALL THE GREENERY AROUND
MOUNT HAKUREI IS DEAD!
>> IT WAS ALL DESTROYED BY
NARAKU'S MIASMA.
>> I SENSE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
THEY'RE COMING FROM TWO
DIFFERENT PLACES--
FROM BELOW THE MOUNTAIN
AND NEAR THE CENTER.
>> HUH?
TWO PLACES?
>> BELOW THE MOUNTAIN IS
STRONGER.
>> THAT'LL BE NARAKU.
>> MOST LIKELY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LEAD THE WAY, KAGOME.
>> HUH?
HOW CAN SHE LEAD YOU ANYWHERE
WHEN YOU TAKE OFF LIKE THAT.
>> KIRARA, LET'S GET MOVING.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
>> DON'T LEAVE US!
>> AAGH!
>> HEY!
WATCH IT!
WHERE ARE YOUR MANNERS?!
[GRUNTING]
>> HOW'D YOU LIKE THAT!
>> THAT'LL TEACH YOU TO MESS
WITH US.
>> HUH?
>> KOGA!
>> KAGOME!
[GRUNTING]
>> OH, NO!
WE'VE BEEN LEFT BEHIND!
>> MIROKU, SANGO, INUYASHA--
EVERYONE, PLEASE HANG ON.
[CLANGING]
>> [GRUNTING]
[GROWLS]
DAMN.
NARAKU'S JUST AHEAD.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER, INUYASHA?
I THOUGHT YOU SAID YOU WERE
HAVING FUN.
>> WHAT WILL I DO?
I CAN'T BEAT BANKOTSU LIKE THIS.
>> COME ON.
I CAN'T JUST STAY HERE AND PLAY
WITH YOU FOREVER, YOU KNOW.
>> WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
[GROWLS]
>> SO, LET'S JUST END
THIS RIGHT NOW.
>> [GROWLS]
>> HA!
>> IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
>> [GRUNTS]
HOW DARE YOU?
>> HA.
I KNEW YOU HAD THE JEWEL SHARDS
IN YOUR ARM.
YOUR SWORD ARM SEEMED UNUSUALLY
STRONG, AND IT GOT ME THINKING.
>> SO, YOU TOOK A GUESS.
SEEMS LIKE YOU HAVE ALL THE
LUCK.
>> OH, IT'S MORE THAN JUST LUCK,
BANKOTSU.
I'M GONNA CUT OUT ALL THE
SHARDS.
AND THE NEXT ONE'S IN YOUR NECK!
[GRUNTING]
>> HA HA HA HA HA.
>> [GRUNTING]
HUH?
AAGH!
OH!
>> DON'T UNDERESTIMATE ME,
HALF-DEMON.
JUST WHO DO YOU THINK YOU'RE
DEALING WITH?
>> [GRUNTING]
YOU BASTARD.
>> HA.
I AM BANKOTSU,
LEADER OF THE BAND OF 7.
AND I'VE NEVER LOST A BATTLE TO
ANYONE.
>> [GROWL]
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS I
SENSE ARE BECOMING TAINTED.
WHAT'S GOING ON INSIDE
MOUNT HAKUREI?
ARE THOSE CLUMPS OF FLESH?
IT'S NOT A DEMON.
>> KILL MY ENEMIES.
>> DO YOU THINK YOU CAN DEFEAT
MY HALBEARD BANRYU, WHICH HAS
ABSORBED THE HATRED OF A
THOUSAND HUMANS AND A THOUSAND
DEMONS?
>> NEXT TIME, "THE POWER OF
BANRYU: DUEL TO THE DEATH ON
MOUNT HAKUREI."
>> A WEAPON INFUSED WITH A
DEMONIC AURA?
DAMN, IT'S SO POWERFUL!