>> YOU WON'T BELIEVE WHAT
I FOUND.
LOOK AT THE WIFE'S NAME OF MY
ANCESTOR--AKITOKI HOJO, WHO
LIVED 500 YEARS AGO DURING
THE FEUDAL ERA.
>> HIS WIFE?
HOJO'S ANCESTOR, HUH?
WHAT IF I COULDN'T RETURN TO
THE MODERN AGE AND ENDED UP
MARRYING THIS HOJO?
NAH.
>> SOMEONE IS AFTER THE BLADE,
AND IT'S NONE OTHER THAN THE
LEADER OF THE DEMON NINJAS
HOSHIYOMI.
AND HOSHIYOMI IS THE ONE WHO
MADE KAIJINBO FORGE THE NAGINATA
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
>> COME ON.
WE'VE GOTTA KEEP GOING.
[SCREAMING]
>> KAGOME, AKITOKI!
>> [SCREAMING]
>> KAGOME!
KAGOME!
I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THE LIKES
OF YOU.
>> [GROWLS]
>> WHO THE HELL ARE YOU FREAKS?
>> GENBU OF THE DARKNESS.
>> BYAKKO OF THE SNOW.
>> SEIRYU OF THE MOON.
>> SUZAKU OF THE FLOWER.
LET'S SEE HOW YOU COUNTER OUR
DEMON NINJA DOPPELGANGER
TECHNIQUE.
>> HUH?
WHY THE HELL ARE THEY
CIRCLING US?
>> SANGO AND I WILL HANDLE
THEM.
>> INUYASHA, YOU GO AFTER KAGOME
AND AKITOKI.
>> GOOD LUCK.
>> WE'LL TAKE YOU ON,
WHOEVER YOU ARE.
>> HIRAIKOTSU!
>> YOU BETTER BE SAFE, KAGOME.
>> MR. HOSHIYOMI!
>> SO YOU'RE HOSHIYOMI, HUH?
>> GET OUT OF MY WAY!
>> THAT WAS TOO EASY.
HUH?
>> [LAUGHS]
DEMON NINJA.
SHADOW INCARNATION.
>> SAVED BY THE KEN BLADE.
IT'S MY FIRST BIT OF GOOD LUCK.
WAIT.
WHERE'S KAGOME?
KAGOME?
KAGOME!
>> HOJO!
>> KAGOME!
KAGOME, GRAB ONTO THIS.
DON'T WORRY, KAGOME, YOU'RE
SAFE, AND WE'RE GOING TO BE OK.
>> THANK YOU, HOJO.
>> MISFORTUNE HAS BROUGHT ME
EVEN MORE FORTUNE.
FIRST I WAS SAVED, AND NOW THIS.
COULD THIS MEAN THE END OF ALL
MY BAD LUCK?
>> HEY, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, HOJO?
>> OH, JUST ANOTHER MISFORTUNE.
I'M QUITE USED TO IT.
BELIEVE ME.
>> HUH?
>> AH!
A WATERFALL!
[SCREAMING]
>> DAMN YOU!
>> STOP ALREADY.
YOU'RE WASTING YOUR ENERGY.
I AM IMMORTAL.
>> WHO THE HELL IS THIS GUY?
>> MASTER HOSHIYOMI.
>> WHY ARE YOU STILL HERE?
HURRY AND GO AFTER THE
KEN BLADE.
>> YES, MASTER.
>> WHICH IS THE REAL ONE?
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE TO TELL.
>> DAMN.
YOU'RE ANNOYING.
>> IT DIDN'T WORK.
>> YOU HAVEN'T LEARNED YOUR
LESSON.
>> HE SEEMS A LOT STRONGER THAN
WE FIRST THOUGHT.
>> I'LL DEAL WITH HOSHIYOMI.
YOU FIND KAGOME AND HOJO.
>> I'M ON MY WAY.
>> QUICKLY, MIROKU.
>> KIRARA, TAKE US THERE.
>> OH, NO, YOU DON'T.
HOSHIYOMI, I'M YOUR ONLY
OPPONENT HERE.
>> I ONCE HEARD OF A HALF-DEMON
WHO FOUGHT KAIJINBO AND HIS
SWORD TOKIJIN.
HIS NAME WAS INUYASHA.
>> OH, YOU HEARD ABOUT KAIJINBO.
I REMEMBER HIM, UNFORTUNATELY.
>> WHY DO YOU FEEL YOU MUST
PROTECT THE NAGINATA OF KENKON
WHICH WAS FORGED BY KAIJINBO?
I'M QUITE CERTAIN IT HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH YOU.
>> THAT'S WHERE YOU'RE ALL
WRONG, 'CAUSE NOTHING GOOD'S
GONNA COME OF LETTING THE LIKES
OF YOU POSSESS A DEMON BLADE.
>> SO WHAT WILL YOU DO?
>> THIS.
WIND SCAR!
HAH!
THAT'S WHAT YOU GET FOR THINKING
YOUR DEMON NINJA TRICKS WOULD
WORK ON ME.
HOPE YOU LEARN FROM THIS.
>> [CHUCKLES]
>> HUH?
>> I'LL CONCEDE THAT THE SWORD
TRICK YOU USED TO DEFEAT
KAIJINBO LIVES UP TO ITS
REPUTATION INDEED.
>> SO THAT'S WHERE YOU ARE.
>> HOWEVER, I SHALL PROVE
SOMETHING IRREFUTABLE TO YOU
TODAY.
YOU ARE NO MATCH FOR ME.
>> SHUT UP!
I'LL BLOW YOU AND YOUR LOUSY
SHADOWS OUT OF HERE.
>> DEMON NINJA, SHADOW HOLD!
>> HUH?
WHAT THE HELL?
I CAN'T MOVE MY BODY.
>> [CHUCKLES]
>> KAGOME AND AKITOKI FELL FROM
THIS WATERFALL?
>> YES.
THEY WERE PROBABLY SWEPT AWAY
BY THE RAPIDS.
>> IF THEY FELL FROM THAT
DISTANCE, THERE'S NO WAY THEY
COULD POSSIBLY HAVE SURVIVED.
>> COME ON, HOW ABOUT A LITTLE
OPTIMISM?
>> HUH?
>> THIS CLOTH BELONGS TO KAGOME.
>> USE YOUR FOX FIRE, SHIPPO.
>> YEAH.
SURE.
FOX FIRE!
>> SANGO!
>> MIROKU, I'M GOING TO CHECK
THE BOTTOM OF THE FALLS.
>> BE CAREFUL, SANGO.
WATCH OUT FOR WHIRLPOOLS IN
THE WATERFALL'S BASIN.
>> I WILL.
>> THE AURA OF THE KEN BLADE IS
COMING FROM THAT A WAY, BOYS.
>> STOP ACTING LIKE THAT,
SUZAKU.
YOU'RE GIVING ME THE CREEPS.
>> SORRY!
I JUST CAN'T HELP MYSELF.
>> HUH?
HUH?
>> WHAT DO YOU HAVE THERE?
>> BEATS ME.
HMM.
>> [GRUNTING]
HOW'S YOUR LEG, KAGOME?
DOES IT STILL HURT?
>> NO.
IT FEELS A LOT BETTER SINCE YOU
PUT ON THOSE MEDICINAL HERBS.
>> OH?
THAT'S GOOD.
GLAD TO HEAR IT.
>> SORRY I'M SUCH A BURDEN.
I KNOW YOU MUST BE TIRED, TOO.
>> I CARRY THE ENTIRE WEIGHT
OF THE HOJO FAMILY NAME ON MY
SHOULDERS.
YOU'RE NOT THAT HEAVY IN
COMPARISON.
>> HUH.
>> WAIT, THAT DIDN'T QUITE COME
OUT THE WAY IT WAS SUPPOSED TO.
YOU'RE REALLY NOT HEAVY, KAGOME.
OW!
>> HOJO, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> JUST ANOTHER SLIGHT
MISFORTUNE.
HUH?
[SCREAMING]
UH, SORRY ABOUT THAT.
[SCREAMS]
>> HOJO!
>> I'M ALL RIGHT.
IT'S JUST ANOTHER BIT OF
BAD LUCK.
>> DOESN'T LOOK LIKE WE'RE BEING
FOLLOWED.
LET'S STOP HERE AND REST UP
FOR A WHILE.
WHAT DO YOU SAY, HOJO?
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> I HOPE WE CAN MEET UP WITH
INUYASHA AND THE OTHERS, 'CAUSE
WE COULD SURE USE THEIR HELP.
BUT IF WORSE COMES TO WORSE,
WE'LL HAVE TO GO TO FURAI SHRINE
BY OURSELVES AND SEAL
THE KEN BLADE.
>> I'M DEFINITELY NOT AS STRONG
AS YOUR FRIEND INUYASHA.
BUT I GUARANTEE I CAN BE OF
SERVICE IN TIMES OF TROUBLE.
NOT ON AN EMPTY STOMACH THOUGH.
I'LL GO SEARCH THE WOODS AND
FIND US SOMETHING TO EAT.
>> ALL RIGHT!
THE STUFF IN MY BACKPACK WASN'T
WASHED AWAY.
>> AH.
>> SORRY, IT'S NOT VERY MUCH,
BUT HERE YOU ARE.
>> AH, I'M HONORED TO HAVE YOUR
HOME COOKING AND IN THESE
SURROUNDINGS, NO LESS.
>> DON'T GO OVERBOARD, NOW.
IT'S ONLY INSTANT NOODLES.
WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU DON'T LIKE IT?
>> NO SUCH THING!
IT'S DELICIOUS!
SUCH A DELICACY.
WHEN I THINK OF THE MAN WHO WILL
BE ABLE TO EAT YOUR COOKING
EVERY DAY, I'M SO JEALOUS
I CAN'T STAND IT.
>> I, UH...
>> HAH.
>> I DON'T HAVE A GUY LIKE THAT.
>> OH, I SEE.
WELL, I KNOW YOU'RE TRAVELING
WITH A MONK AND A HALF-DEMON,
BUT OF COURSE, I CAN'T SAY
WHETHER OR NOT THEY'RE SUITABLE
PARTNERS FOR YOU.
SOMEWHERE UNDER THIS ENORMOUS
SKY, THERE'S A MAN WHO WAS BORN
TO SHARE HIS DESTINY WITH YOU.
OF THAT MUCH, I'M CERTAIN.
>> DESTINY, HUH?
HOJO, HAVE YOU FOUND SOMEONE?
I MEAN, ARE YOU ENGAGED?
>> NO, ESPECIALLY NOT WITH THE
BAD LUCK MY FAMILY SUFFERS FROM.
>> I GUESS THAT MAKES SENSE.
SO MANY THINGS ARE HAPPENING IN
THIS ERA IT MUST BE HARD TO FIND
A BRIDE.
>> KAGOME, I'D JUMP AT THE
CHANCE TO MARRY YOU.
UH...NEVER MIND.
FORGET THAT!
IT'S NOTHING!
HMM?
>> HERE, HAVE MINE.
>> THANKS.
>> LET'S REST A BIT LONGER.
THEN WE'LL HEAD TO THE FURAI
SHRINE AND...
>> [SNORING]
>> HEY, WHAT AM I THINKING ABOUT
THAT FOR?
THEN AGAIN...
>> DEMON BLADES CAN ONLY BE
HANDLED BY DEMONS OR HALF-DEMONS
LIKE ME.
NOT BY HUMANS LIKE YOU GUYS.
HUMANS SHOULDN'T GET INVOLVED
IN THINGS LIKE THIS.
YOU GUYS JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND.
HUMANS SHOULDN'T GET INVOLVED
IN THINGS LIKE THIS.
YOU GUYS JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND.
>> MAYBE THERE IS A DEEP RIFT
BETWEEN DEMONS AND HUMANS.
ONE THAT'S SO BIG IT SIMPLY
CAN'T BE CROSSED.
HUH?
>> OH, KAGOME.
>> COULD THE KAGOME THAT WAS
WRITTEN ON THAT SCROLL REALLY
BE ME?
>> LOOK.
THOSE HUMANS ARE DEFENSELESS.
THIS IS OUR CHANCE TO ATTACK
THEM AND TAKE THE KEN BLADE.
>> DON'T BE HASTY.
>> WHAT?
>> CAN YOU NOT SENSE IT?
THE AURA EMANATING FROM THE
BLADE IS SO STRONG WE WOULDN'T
BE ABLE TO CONTROL IT, LET ALONE
HOLD IT.
>> JUST WHEN I WAS STARTING
TO HOPE I'D TASTE HUMAN BLOOD
AGAIN.
>> WE'LL HAVE TO WAIT UNTIL
MASTER HOSHIYOMI GETS HERE,
UNLESS, OF COURSE--
>> SUZAKU?
>> HMM?
>> THAT DRAWING YOU FOUND.
>> THIS THING?
>> YES.
THAT JUST MIGHT COME IN HANDY.
>> DAMN.
>> THIS IS THE KON BLADE.
THE AURA IS MAGNIFICENT,
IS IT NOT?
>> WHY DID YOU HAVE KAIJINBO
MAKE SUCH A BLADE ANYWAY?
AND WHAT MAKES YOU WANT
THE OTHER ONE SO BADLY?
>> THAT IS NONE OF YOUR
BUSINESS.
I'LL SAY IT AGAIN.
WHILE THIS BLADE MEANS
EVERYTHING TO ME, IT HAS
ABSOLUTELY NO VALUE TO YOU
OR YOUR FRIENDS.
IF YOU BACK OFF, I'LL SPARE YOU
AND THE OTHER HUMANS, TOO.
OR DO YOU PLACE NO VALUE ON
YOUR LIFE?
>> WHAT?
I CAN MOVE.
DOES THE POWER OF THE
SHADOW HOLD FADE AS MY SHADOW
DISAPPEARS?
>> SO WHAT'S YOUR DECISION?
>> I AIN'T ABOUT TO WASTE MY
LIFE OVER SOME LOUSY DEMON
BLADE.
>> YOU'RE SMARTER THAN I
EXPECTED.
>> [CHUCKLES]
YOU ARE A FOOL, THEN.
>> OH, YEAH?
JUST WHAT THE HELL DOES THE
NAGINATA OF KENKON MEAN TO YOU?
>> I OWE YOU NO EXPLANATION.
>> KAGOME IS AS BEAUTIFUL
AS BODHISATTVA.
IF SHE WERE TO MARRY INTO THE
HOJO FAMILY, ALL WOULD BE WELL
AGAIN.
>> [LAUGHING]
>> AHH, KAGOME HOJO.
THAT HAS A NICE RING TO IT.
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING, HONESTLY.
HUH?
>> HUH?
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
>> [LAUGHING]
WE'RE FROM A SMALL VILLAGE
NOT TOO FAR FROM HERE.
>> DON'T TELL ME THESE ARE THEIR
ANCESTORS.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING WALKING
ABOUT AT THIS HOUR?
>> WE WERE GATHERING FIREWOOD
FOR TOMORROW MORNING, AND WE SAW
YOU HERE THROUGH THE TREES.
>> YOU BECAME LOST IN THE
FOREST, I IMAGINE?
>> COME, THEN.
WHY DON'T YOU RETURN TO THE
VILLAGE WITH US?
>> YOU'D SHOW US THE WAY?
THAT WOULD BE A GREAT HELP.
>> WAIT.
HOJO, GIVE ME THAT.
I THOUGHT MAYBE THE DEMON NINJAS
HAD DISGUISED THEMSELVES.
INUYASHA'S ONLY A HALF-DEMON,
YET HE WAS NEARLY OVERCOME BY
THE POWER OF THE BLADE'S AURA.
THESE GIRLS DON'T SEEM TO BE
EFFECTED AT ALL.
>> IS SOMETHING THE MATTER?
>> NO, NOT REALLY.
>> GOOD.
IF YOU LIKE, I'D BE HAPPY
TO CARRY YOU TO THE VILLAGE.
>> I'LL PACK YOUR BELONGINGS
FOR YOU.
>> THAT'S QUITE ALL RIGHT.
THIS IS VALUABLE TO ME,
ACTUALLY.
>> I CAN WALK ON MY OWN.
THANKS.
>> DEMON NINJA DARKNESS PUPPET.
THE PUPPETS WON'T BE AFFECTED BY
THE AURA, AND THEY'LL BE ABLE
TO STEAL THE BLADE.
>> I ALMOST HAD IT!
HE WAS ABOUT TO HAND IT OVER
TO ME!
>> I KEEP TELLING YOU TO CUT OUT
THAT STUPID ACT.
>> RELAX, WILL YOU.
WE HAVE LOTS OF CHANCES LEFT.
WE'LL CATCH THEM OFF GUARD, AND
THEN WE'LL STEAL THE KEN BLADE
AND TEAR THOSE TWO HUMANS APART.
>> OH, YOU ARE SO SCARY.
>> AH!
I SAID STOP IT!
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO
CONCENTRATE?
>> UH, IS SOMETHING WRONG?
>> NOT AT ALL.
DO YOU MIND IF I ASK WHAT YOUR
RELATIONSHIP IS?
>> WE REALLY DON'T HAVE
A RELATIONSHIP.
NOT LIKE THAT.
>> PLEASE FORGIVE US.
YOU MAKE SUCH A FINE COUPLE
WE THOUGHT YOU WERE MARRIED.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
YOU REALLY THINK WE LOOK GOOD
TOGETHER?
>> DEFINITELY.
I THINK THAT YOU WOULD MAKE
A WONDERFUL COUPLE IF YOU WERE
TO MARRY KAGOME, AKITOKI.
>> YOU HONESTLY THINK SO?
HOW ABOUT THAT.
>> HOJO, PUT ME DOWN.
>> HUH?
I'M SORRY.
I GOT CARRIED AWAY THERE.
PLEASE DON'T GET UPSET.
I DIDN'T MEAN ANYTHING BY IT.
>> THAT'S NOT IT.
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
HOW DO YOU KNOW OUR NAMES?
WE NEVER TOLD YOU.
>> FOOL!
>> IT'S YOUR FAULT FOR MAKING
ME LOSE MY CONCENTRATION!
>> THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
>> HA HA HA, LET'S JUST KILL
THEM NOW AND GET IT OVER WITH.
>> NOW, HOLD ON A MINUTE!
DON'T BE RASH!
THE ONLY THING WE'RE AFTER IS
THE KEN BLADE AFTER ALL!
>> WE KNOW THAT MUCH.
>> [LAUGHING]
>> HUH?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> THOSE ARE PUPPETS.
THAT'S WHY THE AURA OF THE BLADE
DIDN'T AFFECT THEM.
>> [SCREAMS]
>> HIT THE MARK!
HOJO, TAKE THE KEN BLADE WITH
YOU AND HURRY TO THE
FURAI SHRINE.
>> NO, KAGOME.
I CAN'T LEAVE YOU HERE ALONE
TO FACE THESE DEMON PUPPETS
BY YOURSELF.
>> BUT, HOJO...
>> AAH!
KAGOME, GET AWAY FROM HERE,
SAVE YOURSELF!
>> DON'T MOVE, HOJO.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> YOU OK, HOJO?
[SCREAMS]
>> KAGOME, NO!
>> HOJO!
>> AAH!
>> HAVEN'T YOU FIGURED IT
OUT YET?
ALL THE POWER YOU THROW AT ME
IS BEING ABSORBED BY THE BLADE.
>> WHAT?
DAMN IT.
>> WHAT IS THIS?
>> AW, THIS AURA'S FROM
HOSHIYOMI'S KON BLADE.
>> MASTER HOSHIYOMI, WE CAPTURED
KAGOME, THE GIRL WHO WAS WITH
THE GROUP.
>> YOU'RE OK?
WHERE'S KAGOME?
>> KAGOME WAS--SHE WAS...
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO KAGOME?
>> [LAUGHING]
>> KAGOME!
>> WHAT WILL YOU DO NOW?
DO YOU WANT TO PROTECT THE KEN
BLADE EVEN IF IT COSTS THIS
WOMAN HER LIFE?
>> KAGOME.
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> IF YOU WANT TO SAVE THIS
WOMAN, COME TO FURAI SHRINE
AND MAKE SURE YOU DON'T FORGET
TO BRING THE KEN BLADE.
>> IT'S ALL MY FAULT THAT KAGOME
GOT INVOLVED IN THIS AND THAT
SHE FELL INTO HOSHIYOMI'S HANDS.
>> WE DON'T HAVE TIME FOR
THAT NOW.
WE HAVE TO SAVE KAGOME FROM
THAT DEMON.
>> YEAH, BUT HOW?
>> TETSUSAIGA STILL HASN'T
TRANSFORMED!
>> NEXT TIME: THE GREAT DUEL
AT SHOUN FALLS.
>> LIKE THE SAYING GOES, WHERE
THERE'S A WILL, THERE'S A WAY.