>> THIS IS THE SPOT WHERE
INUYASHA AND I FIRST MET.
OF COURSE, THAT WAS 500 YEARS
AGO DURING THE FEUDAL ERA.
THE TREE.
THAT MEANS I'M PRACTICALLY HOME.
HUH?
IS THAT A BOY?
AND IT ALL BEGAN RIGHT HERE.
[GASPS]
>> YOU HAVE IT, DON'T YOU?
THE JEWEL.
GIVE IT TO ME!
>> THAT THING.
IT'S AFTER ME.
>> THE SACRED JEWEL!
>> WHY ARE YOU TAKING SO LONG
TO KILL IT?
JUST DO HER LIKE YOU DID ME.
>> DID HE JUST TALK?
SO YOU'RE ALIVE?
AAH!
LET GO OF ME!
>> OW, OW, OW!
YOU LET GO!
>> LET ME GO!
>> HEY, CAN YOU PULL OUT
THIS ARROW?
>> HUH?
>> LOOK.
CAN YOU PULL OUT THIS ARROW
OR NOT?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT I SHOULD
DO, BUT...
GIVEN THE CHOICE, I CHOOSE TO...
HELP!
>> AH, HA HA HA!
>> HUH?
>> WICKED CHILD.
>> NASTY HAG.
IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
HAH.
>> IF I HADN'T BEEN ATTACKED
BY THAT CENTIPEDE DEMON,
IF I HADN'T MET INUYASHA
THAT DAY, I WOULDN'T HAVE TO
STRESS OUT DURING TESTS,
AND GRANDPA WOULDN'T HAVE TO
AGONIZE OVER MY PRETEND
ILLNESSES.
>> HEY, SIS.
YOU'RE UP EARLY.
>> YEAH, I GOTTA GO
DO SOMETHING.
>> MAN, WHEN DID SHE BECOME
A MORNING PERSON?
>> MORNING, MOM.
IS MY LUNCH READY?
>> YES.
AND I MADE ENOUGH FOR YOUR
FRIENDS, TOO.
>> WOW, THANKS!
>> NO PROBLEM.
THERE'S ONE THING, KAGOME.
>> HUH?
>> DO ME A FAVOR AND ASK HOW
EVERYONE LIKES IT, OK, DEAR?
>> UH, SURE.
JUNIOR HIGH STUDENTS LIKE ME
HAVE IT TOUGH ENOUGH WITH JUST
OUR STUDIES TO WORRY ABOUT.
>> KAGOME.
>> HMM?
HEY, GOOD MORNING!
>> YEAH.
LET'S GET MOVING, OK?
>> OK.
ONCE AGAIN I'M SETTING OUT INTO
THE FEUDAL ERA.
AND ONCE AGAIN...
>> KAGOME, WELCOME BACK!
>> HI, GUYS.
>> HEY, INUYASHA,
LIGHT A FIRE UNDER IT.
>> ONCE AGAIN I'LL CONTINUE
THE JOURNEY AND DO MY BEST
TO FIND THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
>> HEY, INUYASHA,
HAVE YOU NOTICED THEM?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> WE'RE BEING WATCHED
BY SAIMYOSHO.
>> HA!
NARAKU'S STUPID BUGS ARE
PROBABLY JUST MAKING SURE THAT
WE'RE HEADING TOWARD
THE REALM OF FIRE.
COME ON, MYOGA.
THINK HARD.
ARE YOU SURE YOU DON'T KNOW
OF ANY OTHER WAY TO GET
TO THE GRAVEYARD?
>> OH, FOR THE LAST TIME,
THERE IS NO OTHER WAY TO REACH
THE GRAVEYARD, OK!
>> SO, INUYASHA...
YOU WOULD LIKE TO KNOW
WHERE THE PATHWAY IS?
>> HMM, KAGURA.
>> HAKUDOSHI IS HEADED TOWARD
THE MOUNTAIN IN THE REALM
OF FIRE.
THERE'S SUPPOSED TO BE A GATEWAY
THERE THAT LEADS THE TRAVELER
TO THE BORDER BETWEEN THIS WORLD
AND THE NEXT.
>> MOUNTAIN IN THE REALM
OF FIRE?
>> I DON'T UNDERSTAND, KAGURA.
WHY HAVE YOU COME TO TELL US
THIS?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
YOU'D HAVE TO ASK HAKUDOSHI
THAT.
>> ACTUALLY, INUYASHA,
I DON'T THINK THEY WERE SENT
TO WATCH US.
I THINK THE SAIMYOSHO WERE SENT
TO LEAD US TO THE GATE.
>> YES, I AGREE.
BUT IF THEY WERE, IN FACT,
SENT TO SHOW US THE WAY,
PERHAPS IT MEANS THAT HAKUDOSHI
DOESN'T HAVE THE POWER TO PASS
THROUGH THE GATE ALONE.
>> IF WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
THE NARAKU WE KNOW, I'M SURE
HE HAS SOMETHING UP HIS SLEEVE.
>> YEAH, BUT THIS IS HAKUDOSHI,
NOT NARAKU, REMEMBER?
>> DON'T FORGET HAKUDOSHI
IS AN INCARNATION OF NARAKU.
>> HAH, LISTEN TO YOU TWO.
WHO CARES WHICH ONE IT IS?
ALL WE HAVE TO DO IS GET TO
THE GRAVEYARD AT THE BORDER
OF THE NETHERWORLD FIRST AND GET
HOLD OF THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD
BEFORE THE BAD GUY.
SIMPLE.
>> SPEAKING OF SIMPLE--
>> HEY, COME ON.
INUYASHA CAN'T HELP HIS
LIMITATIONS, SHIPPO.
>> INUYASHA.
>> SO THIS IS THE REALM OF FIRE?
>> YES.
AND IT CERTAINLY LIVES UP TO
ITS NAME, DOESN'T IT?
>> NOW WHAT?
>> WE WAIT AND SEE.
AFTER THEM.
>> HACHI, GO DOWN.
IT WENT DOWN THERE.
>> LOOKS KIND OF CREEPY.
>> UH-HUH.
>> GOOD.
IT SHOULD DO IF IT'S
THE ENTRANCE TO A GRAVEYARD.
LET'S GET GOING.
>> MIROKU?
>> HMM, INUYASHA'S RIGHT.
>> KAGURA, APPARENTLY INUYASHA
AND HIS FRIENDS HAVE JUST
MADE IT TO THE GATE.
>> ARE YOU QUITE SURE ABOUT
LETTING THEM GO IN FIRST?
ISN'T THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD
ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THAT GATE?
>> OH, DON'T WORRY.
WE'LL GET TO THE SHARD
BEFORE THEM.
BUT IN ORDER TO DO THAT,
YOU WILL FIRST HAVE
TO DO YOUR JOB.
>> HUH, SO YOU WANT THE LAST
LAUGH, DO YOU, HAKUDOSHI?
IT SEEMS YOU'RE JUST LIKE
NARAKU.
>> HMM.
>> IT'S HUGE.
>> YEAH.
RIGHT.
WELL-SPOTTED, MIROKU.
>> HEY, KAGOME?
>> YES?
WHAT'S WRONG, SHIPPO?
>> DON'T THOSE ROCKS LOOK LIKE
THE SKULLS OF DEMONS?
>> YES, YOU'RE RIGHT.
AND LOOK.
THERE ARE EVEN MORE OF THEM
UP AHEAD.
>> WHICH PROBABLY MEANS
WE'RE GOING THE RIGHT WAY.
>> INUYASHA, UP AHEAD.
>> WELL, LOOKS LIKE WE FINALLY
MADE IT.
>> THIS IS IT.
>> SO THERE ACTUALLY IS A GATE.
>> HUH.
OH, MAN, THIS IS GONNA BE EASY.
I MEAN, THERE AREN'T EVEN
ANY GUARDS AROUND.
OK, EVERYONE, GET BACK.
I'M GONNA BREAK APART THE GATE
WITH MY WIND SCAR.
>> YOU WISH TO PASS?
>> THIS DOESN'T SOUND GOOD.
>> ANSWER.
DO YOU WISH TO PASS OR NOT?
>> WHAT A DUMB QUESTION.
>> YOU MUST NOT ANSWER,
MASTER INUYASHA!
>> HEY, IT'S MYOGA.
>> WOW.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE ACTUALLY
CAME WITH US.
>> I THOUGHT HE RAN AWAY
AGES AGO.
>> OH, I'M GOING TO IN A MOMENT.
IT'S STILL NOT TOO LATE.
PLEASE TURN BACK.
>> WHAT ARE YOU BABBLING ABOUT?
>> DO YOU WISH TO PASS OR NOT?
>> LOOK, BUDDY,
OF COURSE I WANT TO PASS!
WHY DO YOU THINK I WENT TO ALL
THE TROUBLE TO COME HERE?
>> NO, MASTER INUYASHA!
>> THEN YOU MAY PASS.
>> AH!
>> THE STONE STATUES.
>> HUH?
>> THEY'RE GOZU AND MEZU,
THE GUARDS OF THIS GATE.
>> WHAT?
I THOUGHT THEY WERE JUST
STONE DECORATIONS.
>> ONLY THE DEAD MAY PASS
THROUGH THESE GATES.
WE MAKE CERTAIN ALL THOSE
WHO WISH TO PASS ARE DEAD.
>> HUH, SO THAT'S WHAT
THE DEAL IS.
I GUESS NOW WE KNOW WHY
HAKUDOSHI LURED US HERE
AHEAD OF HIM.
OH, WELL.
I'M SURE NOT ABOUT TO TURN BACK
NOW!
UH!
HUH, THESE GUYS ARE BIG,
BUT THAT JUST MAKES THEM SLOW.
WIND SCAR!
>> AAH!
>> UH!
DID HE SUCCEED?
>> HMM.
[CRASH]
UH...
HUH?
MY WIND SCAR DIDN'T WORK!
>> IT IS USELESS.
>> WE CANNOT BE SLAIN BY BLADES
OF THIS WORLD.
>> CANNOT BE SLAIN BY BLADES
OF THIS WORLD?
>> THAT WAS BECAUSE GOZU AND
MEZU ARE NOT OF THIS WORLD.
AS YOU KNOW, THE TETSAIGA
IS A SWORD THAT SLAYS THE DEMONS
IN OUR WORLD, BUT IT ISN'T ABLE
TO HURT GOZU OR MEZU
IN THE LEAST!
>> THEN WHAT DO WE DO?
JUST STAND BY AND WATCH WHILE
INUYASHA GETS KILLED?
>> SHE'S RIGHT!
>> ISN'T THERE SOME WAY TO STOP
GOZU AND MEZU?
>> ONCE THEY ARE AWAKENED,
THEY WILL NOT REST UNTIL
THE GATE HAS BEEN OPENED
AND CLOSED AGAIN.
OR, IN OTHER WORDS, THEY WON'T
REST UNTIL MASTER INUYASHA
PASSES THROUGH THE GATE
AS ONE OF THE DEAD.
>> THAT'S TERRIBLE.
>> YOU MAY PASS...
>> ONCE YOU ARE DEAD.
>> HUH, KIND OF DEFEATS
THE PURPOSE.
>> TO PASS THROUGH THE GATE
AT THE BORDER OF THIS WORLD
AND THE NEXT, ONE MUST BATTLE
THE 2 GUARDS GOZU AND MEZU.
RIGHT ABOUT NOW, INUYASHA SHOULD
BE FIGHTING THEM IN MY PLACE.
VERY SOON THE GATE WILL OPEN,
MEANING INUYASHA'S DEAD.
>> ONLY THE DEAD CAN PASS
THROUGH THIS GATE.
SO PREPARE TO DIE BY OUR HANDS.
>> YEAH.
YOU REALLY GOTTA LEARN
A NEW LINE THERE, BUDDY BOY.
HUH?
UH!
UH, NOT EVEN A CRACK!
HUH?
AH!
>> INUYASHA!
>> WE TOLD YOU THE SWORDS
OF YOUR WORLD CANNOT HARM US.
>> OK, THEN.
IF SWORDS WON'T WORK,
THEN HOW ABOUT THIS?
WIND TUNNEL!
[GRUNTS]
>> DO YOU WISH TO PASS THROUGH
THE GATE, TOO?
>> THE WIND TUNNEL DOESN'T WORK
EITHER!
>> HOW CAN THAT BE?
>> HUH?
MIROKU, HOLD THAT WIND TUNNEL
OPEN!
>> HUH?
>> TAKE THIS!
>> HE DID IT.
>> INUYASHA!
>> I ONLY TRIPPED HIM.
>> HE'S GETTING UP.
>> OH, I KNOW.
DAMN IT.
EVEN AFTER USING THE WIND TUNNEL
TO INCREASE MY SPEED, IT DIDN'T
FAZE THEM.
>> MASTER INUYASHA?
>> HUH?
MYOGA AGAIN?
YOU MEAN YOU'RE STILL HERE?
>> JUST WHAT EXACTLY ARE YOU
INFERRING?
I'VE BEEN HERE THE WHOLE TIME.
>> RIGHT, OF COURSE YOU HAVE.
NOW HURRY UP AND SPIT IT OUT.
>> OH, YES.
HERE'S WHAT YOU NEED TO DO.
TURN MEZU AND GOZU BACK
INTO STONE.
>> WHAT?
>> THEY WILL RETURN TO STONE
AFTER THE GATE HAS OPENED
AND CLOSED.
SO WHAT YOU NEED TO DO IS AIM
FOR THE CHAINS HOLDING THE GATE
SHUT WITH YOUR WIND SCAR.
AND NOW I SHALL TAKE MY LEAVE.
>> HUH?
HAH, THERE HE GOES,
RUNNING AWAY AGAIN.
[SLAM]
HUH?
MYOGA'S RIGHT, THOUGH.
IF I BLAST THOSE CHAINS APART
AND OPEN THE GATE, IT'LL BE LIKE
KILLING 2 BIRDS WITH ONE STONE.
MY RED TETSAIGA CAN BREAK
THROUGH BARRIERS.
ALL RIGHT.
AAH!
[YELLS]
>> OH!
>> HE DID IT!
>> HUH?
HUH?
>> THANKS FOR THE GOOD WORK,
INUYASHA.
I'M GOING ON AHEAD NOW, OK?
>> DAMN YOU, KAGURA.
GET BACK HERE!
>> IT'S OPENING.
>> [GASPS]
>> DAMN YOU, KAGURA.
GET BACK HERE!
>> IT'S OPENING.
[GASPS]
>> [GASPS]
>> WHAT'S THIS?
OH, AH!
>> THE DEMONS HAVE BECOME
PETRIFIED.
>> BUT HOW CAN THAT BE?
>> HIDE, OR WE WILL, TOO!
>> AAH!
>> INUYASHA!
>> MOVE IT!
>> OH!
IT'S THERE, BEYOND THE GATE!
>> DO YOU WISH TO PASS OR NOT?
>> WHAT?
DO I LOOK LIKE I'M AN IDIOT?
>> IN THAT CASE,
WE SHALL CLOSE THE GATE.
>> HEY, KAGOME,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> UH-HUH.
>> HMM.
THEY'VE TURNED TO STONE AGAIN.
>> WHERE'S KAGURA?
>> I GUESS SHE RAN AWAY.
>> I WONDER IF HAKUDOSHI
KNEW ABOUT THIS.
THAT ONE TURNS TO STONE
ONCE YOU PASS THE GATE.
>> HMM.
I THINK HE WAS TESTING IT
BY USING KAGURA AS WELL AS US.
UH!
>> HAKUDOSHI, YOU BASTARD.
>> KAGURA, WHAT'S WRONG?
>> YOU SENT ME TO THE GATE
KNOWING THAT I WOULD PROBABLY
DIE!
>> I HEARD THAT THE LIVING
CANNOT PASS THROUGH THE GATE,
BUT I NEEDED TO SEE IF IT WAS
ACTUALLY TRUE OR NOT.
>> DON'T PLAY WITH MY LIFE,
YOU BRAT!
OH--OH!
UH, OH!
OOH...
>> DOES IT HURT, KAGURA?
THAT'S BECAUSE NARAKU JUST TOOK
HOLD OF YOUR HEART FROM WHEREVER
HE IS.
TRY NOT TO FORGET, KAGURA...
NARAKU AND I ARE STILL
CONNECTED.
SO NEXT TIME,
THINK BEFORE YOU ACT.
BESIDES, I'D NEVER LET MYSELF
BE KILLED BY THE LIKES OF YOU.
>> IS THAT TRUE, KAGOME?
>> MM-HMM.
I'M SURE OF IT.
WHEN I LOOKED THROUGH THE OPEN
GATE, I COULD FEEL IT.
I SENSED THE PRESENCE OF
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
>> HUH?
>> HMM.
>> SO IT'S THERE SOMEWHERE.
SOMEWHERE BEYOND THAT GATE
IS THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> ♪ I GET, I GET, I GET
GET THE FEELING
I GET, I GET, I GET
GET THE DREAMING ♪
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> ♪ COME MY WAY ♪
>> ♪ COME CLOSE TO ME ♪
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
♪ I'LL BE WITH YOU
I'LL BE WITH YOU
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
SO COME MY WAY
COME MY WAY
COME... ♪
>> WHILE WE'RE IN THE REALM
OF FIRE, DEMONS WREAK HAVOC.
>> SOMEONE IS USING BIRDS
TO ATTACK PEOPLE.
>> ARE YOU ANOTHER ONE OF
NARAKU'S MINIONS?
THE FACT THAT THERE ARE
SAIMYOSHO AROUND IS PROOF.
I DON'T LIKE TO FIGHT WOMEN, BUT
YOU'RE TOO EVIL NOT TO FIGHT.
>> SHE SEEMS TO HAVE SOMETHING
TO DO WITH NARAKU, BUT I DON'T
THINK SHE'S ONE OF HIS MINIONS.
NEXT ON "INUYASHA:"
THE FIERY BIRD MASTER,
PRINCESS ABI.
IMPOSSIBLE!
SHE COUNTERED THE WIND SCAR!