>> IS IT REALLY ALL RIGHT FOR ME
TO GO BACK?
>> SURE, THERE'S NOTHING FOR YOU
TO DO AROUND HERE, ANYWAY.
>> WELL, IF YOU SAY SO.
>> HMM.
>> SIS, WELCOME HOME.
>> NICE TO BE BACK.
>> KAGOME, WELCOME BACK, DEAR.
>> WELL, WELL...YOU WERE GONE
FOR SOME TIME.
IT WAS HARD COMING UP
WITH EXCUSES FOR YOUR SCHOOL.
>> I'M JUST GLAD THAT YOU'RE
SAFELY HOME AGAIN, KAGOME.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER,
YOU TIRED OR SOMETHING?
>> I'M NOT TIRED, REALLY.
OH.
HERE YOU ARE, A PRESENT.
APPARENTLY SOME KIND OF RARE
DRIED FOOD.
>> I CAN'T WAIT TO TRY IT.
>> I'M GOING TO GO REST
IN MY ROOM.
>> I AM NOT!
>> JUST WHO DO YOU THINK YOU'RE
KIDDING, INUYASHA?
AND IF YOU DO GO, THEN I'LL BE
UPSET.
BUT THAT'S TO BE EXPECTED,
RIGHT?
>> KAGOME.
>> I CAN'T KEEP PUTTING MYSELF
THROUGH ALL THIS.
OK.
>> MAYBE YOU SHOULD PACE
YOURSELF, SIS.
>> I'M GOING BACK TO SCHOOL
TOMORROW AFTER A LONG ABSENCE.
I NEED TO STORE UP ENERGY.
I THINK I'LL BE HERE FOR A WHILE
SO I'M GOING TO KNUCKLE DOWN,
AND STUDY HARD.
I DESPERATELY NEED TO CATCH UP
IN ALL MY CLASSES.
>> WELL, SHE SEEMS READY TO GO.
>> SECONDS PLEASE!
>> COMING UP.
>> UH, WHAT IS IT?
>> UH, NOTHING.
>> I'LL GET A GOOD NIGHT'S
SLEEP AND FORGET ALL ABOUT THE
FEUDAL ERA FOR A WHILE.
I'LL CONCENTRATE ON WHAT
I REALLY AM,
A JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT.
>> HUH?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> OH, KAGOME!
>> HEY, HOW'S IT GOING?
>> GREAT TO SEE YOU.
SO, YOU'RE WELL ENOUGH TO RETURN
TO SCHOOL?
>> UH, YEAH.
>> THAT'S GOOD, 'CAUSE YOU SURE
WERE GONE A LONG TIME.
>> WHAT WAS IT AGAIN?
AN INNER EAR DISEASE THAT
MADE YOU HEAR ALL KINDS
OF STRANGE THINGS?
>> UH, NEVER MIND ME,
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
>> OH, JUST MORE PREPARATIONS.
>> HEY, KAGOME HAS BEEN AWAY FOR
SUCH A LONG TIME SHE PROBABLY
DOESN'T KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT IT.
>> OH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
>> TELL ME.
>> CULTURAL FESTIVAL.
>> HUH?
>> WE'RE HAVING A
CULTURAL FESTIVAL.
>> A FESTIVAL?
YES, BUT WHAT ABOUT CLASSES?
>> CLASSES? ARE YOU KIDDING?
WE'RE TOO BUSY WITH ALL OF THIS.
>> WE JUST HAVE CLASSES
IN THE MORNING.
>> WHY DID I HAVE TO COME BACK
WHEN CLASSES AREN'T CRUCIAL?
>> ARE YOU OK?
>> I'M GOING HOME.
>> HEY, HANG ON A MINUTE.
>> I GUESS I'M NOT REALLY NEEDED
HERE OR OVER THERE RIGHT NOW.
>> WHY ARE YOU SO DEPRESSED,
KAGOME?
>> YOU'VE GOT TO TRY AND SHAKE
IT OFF.
WHAT CAN WE DO TO HELP YOU?
>> I KNOW, LET'S SING.
>> SING?
>> YES, THAT'LL CHEER YOU UP.
>> KNOW WHAT?
KAGOME, YOU SHOULD PARTICIPATE
IN THE FESTIVAL AS WELL.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
WE SURE COULD USE THE HELP.
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> [LAUGHING]
>> AN UNDERSTUDY?
>> YES, THINK OF IT AS BEING
LIKE A STAND-IN
OR LIKE A SUBSTITUTE.
>> COME ON, I MEAN HOW HARD
CAN IT BE?
>> OK, THEN...I'LL DO IT.
SO, WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
>> SING IN THE CHOIR.
>> SING?
>> HELP WITH THE FOOD.
>> THE FOOD?
>> ACTING.
>> ACTING?
>> I HAVE A SMALL ROLE FOR YOU.
THE HEROINE'S FRIEND, BRILLIANT.
>> BRILLIANT, YOU SAY?
SO, WHICH SHOULD I DO?
>> WELL, ALL OF THEM OF COURSE.
>> ALL 3?
>> YOU'RE THE UNDERSTUDY.
>> DON'T BE SO CHICKEN.
>> LOOK, KAGOME, WE'VE ALL
GONE THROUGH A LOT OF PRACTICE
AND PREPARATION.
BUT YOU'LL BE DONE WITH ALL
OF THIS IN A FEW DAYS.
DOING ALL 3 SHOULD BE EASY.
>> OK.
>> NOW.
HEY, COME ON, KAGOME,
I WANT YOU TO SING LOUDER.
SING IT FROM THE HEART.
>> I WANT TO CREATE SOMETHING
EXOTIC AND REFRESHINGLY UNIQUE.
>> WELL, I AM RATHER GOOD
AT OUTDOOR COOKING.
>> WHAT, YOU MEAN LIKE
BARBECUING?
>> GRILLED RIVER FISH OVER
A WOOD FIRE, OR FERN ROOTS
OVER A WOOD FIRE.
>> JUST STICK WITH THE PEELING
THING.
>> OK, WE'LL BEGIN WITH
BRILLIANT'S LINE IN ACT 2,
ALL RIGHT?
>> EVER SINCE MY GRANDFATHER
COLLAPSED FROM LUMBAGO, I'VE--
>> NO, NO, NO.
YOU NEED TO THROW YOUR ARMS OUT
LIKE THIS, AND SPEAK MORE
DRAMATICALLY.
FROM THE TOP.
>> MY GRANDFATHER COLLAPSED
FROM LUMBAGO!
>> SO, HOW IS IT?
>> IT'S NOT BAD, IF I MAY
SAY SO.
>> THEN I WANT SOME, TOO!
>> I'M HOME.
>> HEY, SIS, YOU'RE HOME LATE.
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO ALL THAT
ENERGY YOU STORED UP?
>> I USED IT ALL UP IN ONE
SINGLE DAY.
>> WERE YOUR CLASSES THAT HARD?
>> SCHOOL WORK WOULD'VE
BEEN EASIER.
>> KAGOME, THIS IS PRETTY GOOD.
>> HUH?
>> THE DRIED FOODS YOU BROUGHT
BACK FOR ME.
THEY GO PERFECTLY WITH SAKE.
>> GOOD.
I'M SO GLAD.
>> NARAKU TRIED TO USE
KAGOME'S EYES?
>> YES, TO HELP HIM FIND
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
>> THAT MEANS NARAKU
DOESN'T KNOW THE WHEREABOUTS
OF ALL THE REMAINING
SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
>> YES.
AND THE FACT THAT HE WENT
TO THE TROUBLE OF KIDNAPPING
KAGOME MUST SIGNIFY THAT THERE
ARE SHARDS WHICH EVEN NARAKU
CANNOT FIND.
>> HOW COME?
>> IT'S HARD TO SAY.
PERHAPS THERE IS SOMETHING
ABOUT WHERE THEY ARE HIDDEN.
>> IT MEANS NARAKU IS
NOT INFALLIBLE.
>> HEH HEH HEH.
SO, YOU'VE COME, NARAKU.
ACTUALLY I HEARD YOU COMING
FROM SEVERAL LEAGUES AWAY.
>> OH, THEN THAT WILL SAVE ME
TIME EXPLAINING MYSELF.
>> MIMISENRI, THEY SAY THAT YOU
POSSESS EARS THAT ARE CAPABLE
OF HEARING ALL THINGS IN THIS
WORLD.
>> YES, YOU ARE CORRECT,
AND I HAVE HEARD THINGS
ABOUT YOU, TOO.
DO YOU INTEND TO TAKE MY EARS
AND MAKE THEM A PART OF YOU
SO THAT YOU MAY USE THEM?
>> REST ASSURED, YOUR FILTHY
LITTLE BODY DOESN'T INTEREST
ME AT ALL.
>> WELL, TELL ME, THEN.
WHY HAVE YOU COME ALL THE WAY
HERE TO VISIT ME?
>> WHAT HAVE YOU HEARD
OF THE WHEREABOUTS OF
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS?
>> AHH, ACCORDING TO THE RUMORS
OF DEMONS, NARAKU, YOU YOURSELF
HAVE APPARENTLY OBTAINED NEARLY
ALL OF THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
>> JUST ONE.
ONE SHARD IS LEFT,
AND SOMEHOW IT HAS ELUDED MY
ATTEMPTS TO FIND IT.
>> AHH, THEN LET'S SEE WHAT
MY EARS CAN FIND FOR YOU.
HMM.
>> ALL OF OUR JEWEL SHARDS
ARE NOW IN NARAKU'S POSSESSION.
>> KOGA STILL HAS 2 SHARDS
IN HIS LEGS.
>> AND THERE'S THE ONE
WHICH KEEPS KOHAKU ALIVE.
>> OF COURSE.
>> IF NARAKU SUCCEEDS IN MAKING
THE SACRED JEWEL WHOLE AGAIN,
KOHAKU WILL DIE.
>> DON'T WORRY, SANGO.
WE'LL STOP NARAKU.
>> THANK YOU.
>> BELIEVE ME, WE'RE GOING
TO FIND THE REMAINING
JEWEL SHARDS BEFORE HIM.
>> YES, YOU'RE RIGHT INUYASHA,
WE WILL.
>> INUYASHA, I'M SURE I DON'T
NEED TO REMIND YOU, BUT YOU MUST
BE MORE CAREFUL WITH KAGOME.
MAKE SURE NARAKU NEVER CAPTURES
HER AGAIN.
>> LOOK, I KNOW ALL THAT
ALREADY, OK?
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU EATING
OVER THERE, SHIPPO?
>> WHAT, THIS?
REMEMBER THOSE VILLAGERS AND
ITINERANT PRIESTS WE SAVED
A WHILE AGO?
WELL, THEY GAVE ME SOME OF THEIR
DRIED FOOD IN GRATITUDE.
>> OH, BROTHER.
NO MATTER HOW MANY TIMES
WE DEMON SLAYERS WARN THEM,
THEY NEVER LISTEN.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> NO, KIRARA, THIS FOOD
IS MADE OUT OF DEMONS.
>> WHAT?
>> THIS IS A HYPAE OF A FUNGAL
DEMON CALLED SHIRONYUUDOU.
>> SO, IS IT SAFE TO EAT?
>> YES, LIKE THIS IT IS.
BUT IF YOU PUT IT IN WATER
AND HEAT IT...
>> YOU MEAN IF YOU BOIL IT?
>> YES, IF YOU BOIL IT,
A NEW SHIRONYUUDOU IS BORN.
>> SO IT ISN'T REALLY DEAD THEN?
>> IT'S BEST IF ALL THIS FOOD
IS DISPOSED OF.
>> HMM, BUT IT WAS SO DARN
TASTY.
>> THAT'S WHY IT'S SUCH
A NUISANCE.
>> UHH!
FORGET ABOUT THE DRIED FOOD.
IF WE CAN FIND THE REMAINING
SACRED JEWEL SHARD,
WE CAN PUT AN END TO ALL
OF THIS.
>> HMM, YOU'RE QUITE RIGHT.
THAT WAS THE START OF IT ALL.
>> WHEREVER NARAKU IS HIDING
RIGHT NOW, HE'S SURE TO APPEAR
WHERE THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD IS.
[SINGING]
>> GOOD, NEXT KEY.
HUH?
>> I'M SORRY, AYUMI,
I CAUGHT A COLD.
>> OH, NO!
>> I'M SO SORRY.
>> IT'S ALL RIGHT,
IT CAN'T BE HELPED.
KAGOME!
>> HUH?
>> YOU WILL SING HER ALTO SOLO.
>> WHAT!
YOU CAN'T REALLY BE SERIOUS.
>> UH-HUH!
>> HEY, UH, CAN YOU HAND ME
THAT TAPE PLEASE?
>> YOU MEAN THIS TAPE?
>> YEAH, THAT'S THE STUFF.
>> MOKI, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> OW!
IT HURTS.
>> TAKE HER TO THE INFIRMARY,
RIGHT AWAY.
SO, HOW IS SHE?
>> SPRAINED ANKLE.
SHE WON'T BE ABLE TO MOVE AROUND
FOR A WHILE.
>> UHH.
BRILLIANT!
>> HUH...UH, YES?
>> FROM THIS MOMENT ON,
YOU ARE NO LONGER PLAYING
BRILLIANT.
BUT THE FEMALE LEAD,
ESCARGOT PUDDING!
>> WHAT!
>> NOW, LET'S CONTINUE
WITH REHEARSAL.
ESCARGOT, GET ON STAGE.
>> NO FAIR.
I CAN'T BELIEVE ARIMI AND ERI,
AFTER ALL, I'M SUPPOSED
TO BE AN UNDERSTUDY,
NOT THE STAR ATTRACTION!
RIGHT?
>> IT'S NO GOOD.
I JUST CAN'T FIND
ANY GOOD RECIPES.
HONESTLY, ISN'T THERE ANYTHING
THAT PACKS A REAL PUNCH?
SOMETHING THAT TANTALIZES
THE PALLET, YET SOMETHING NEW,
YOU KNOW?
>> GUESS NOT.
>> WELL, CAN YOU FIND SOMETHING?
>> HUH?
BUT I--
AFTER THIS IS DONE,
I HAVE TO GO TO A PRACTICE
SINGING LESSON FOR THE CHOIR.
THEN I HAVE TO GO TO REHEARSALS
FOR THE PLAY, AND THEN I--
>> I'M COUNTING ON YOU.
>> STOP COUNTING ON ME!
>> YOU SOUND LIKE YOU'RE
RECOVERING, KAGOME.
>> HI, HOJO.
>> I HEAR YOU'VE TAKEN ON
A LOT OF WORK FOR THE FESTIVAL.
>> NOT TAKEN ON,
MORE LIKE FORCED TO.
AT FIRST IT WAS JUST HELPING OUT
A LITTLE.
THEN THE JOBS GOT BIGGER,
AND BIGGER.
>> WELL, YOU HAVEN'T BEEN
IN SCHOOL FOR A WHILE,
SO MAYBE EVERYONE JUST WANTS YOU
TO REALLY FEEL A PART
OF THIS FESTIVAL.
>> YOU THINK SO?
>> SURE.
>> SAY, HOJO, DO YOU KNOW
HOW TO COOK ANY UNUSUAL DISHES?
>> WELL, I'M NOT REALLY MUCH
OF A COOK.
>> I GUESS I'LL JUST HAVE TO ASK
MY MOM.
OH!
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> I THINK I HAVE AN IDEA.
>> KAGOME, BY THE WAY,
I WAS THINKING...
NOW THAT YOU'RE PLAYING
THE HEROINE, WE'LL HAVE QUITE
A FEW SCENES TOGETHER.
SO, HOW ABOUT WE REHEARSE
TOGETHER, TOO?
KAGOME?
WHERE'D SHE GO?
>> I'M BACK!
HERE IT IS.
JUST NEED SOME OF IT, GRANDPA.
[SINGING]
>> AND SO I, ESCARGOT PUDDING,
WILL NEITHER RUN NOR HIDE
FROM YOU.
>> GREAT!
>> SO, WHAT'S THIS?
>> SOMETHING THAT PACKS
A REAL PUNCH,
TANTALIZES THE PALLET,
YET IS NOT FAMILIAR TO ANYONE.
>> I'LL BE BACK SOON.
>> I GUESS WE NEED KAGOME
TO START LOOKING FOR THE
SACRED JEWEL SHARDS AGAIN, HUH?
>> HMM, YEAH.
KAGOME LIKES TO TAKE HER SWEET
TIME WHEN WE LEAVE HER ALONE.
SEE YA!
>> HEY, INUYASHA,
ASK KAGOME FOR MORE NINJA FOOD!
SOMEONE'S IN A HURRY.
>> MMM.
THESE THINGS ARE TASTY,
BUT I HAVE TO SAY, THEY CAN BE
A LITTLE BIT ON THE TOUGH SIDE.
MAYBE I CAN BOIL IT.
OH, LOOK AT THAT.
A FESTIVAL.
HMM, ECONOMY'S NOT GOOD.
HMM?
>> AAH!
>> OH, HELLO, IT'S BEEN A WHILE.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING!
IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
>> HUH?
WHAT'S WRONG?
>> THAT MUST HAVE BEEN THE
SHIRONYUUDOU SANGO WAS
TALKING ABOUT.
WHERE'S THE REST?
>> REST OF WHAT?
>> THE REST OF THE DRIED FOODS
KAGOME BROUGHT BACK!
>> OH, THE--THE ONE IN THE POT
IS THE LAST OF IT.
I ATE THE REST, I SUPPOSE.
>> AHH, WELL, I GUESS IT'S OK.
>> HI THERE!
WELCOME BACK.
>> HI, INUYASHA.
HAVE YOU COME FOR A VISIT?
>> I...CAN'T REALLY STAY.
>> BUT YOU'LL HAVE TO HAVE
DINNER WITH US, WON'T YOU?
COME ON, NOW.
>> UH...SURE.
>> I'M HOME!
>> WHO'S A GOOD LITTLE KITTY,
WHO'S A WITTLE KITTY CAT,
LITTLE PUSSY CAT, YES, YOU'RE--
>> HUH, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> UHH, HEY.
WE'RE GOING BACK AFTER WE EAT.
>> HOLD ON A MINUTE,
YOU NEVER SAID ANYTHING ABOUT ME
RETURNING SO SOON WHEN I LEFT.
>> GIVE IT A REST.
WE CAN'T EXACTLY FIND
THE JEWEL SHARDS WITHOUT YOU,
NOW, CAN WE?
>> THAT'S THE REASON?
>> 'COURSE IT IS.
>> IS THAT ALL?
>> HUH?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> NOTHING...
JUST FORGET IT.
THIS IS HOW THINGS USED TO BE.
>> HMM...UH...I FELT LIKE
SEEING YOU, OK.
GOT A PROBLEM WITH THAT?
>> NOT AT ALL.
>> BOY, YOU'RE SELFISH,
INUYASHA.
>> WELL, I'M SORRY
TO DISAPPOINT YOU BUT I CAN'T
GO BACK JUST YET.
>> HUH?
OH, IT'S NOT ANOTHER ONE
OF THOSE TESTS, IS IT?
>> NO, A CULTURAL FESTIVAL.
>> A CULTURAL WHAT?
>> SIS, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
IN IT?
>> OH, A BIT OF THIS AND THAT.
SINGING IN THE CHOIR, COOKING,
PERFORMING ON STAGE.
>> CAN FAMILY MEMBERS COME, TOO?
>> SURE, I GUESS.
>> OH, THAT SOUNDS GOOD.
THEN, WHY DON'T WE ALL GO.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THAT.
>> OH, NONSENSE.
I SIMPLY MUST SEE MY
GRANDDAUGHTER PERFORM.
>> HEY, CAN I GO, TOO?
>> NO WAY!
>> WHY THE HECK NOT?
>> BECAUSE IMAGINE WHAT
WOULD HAPPEN IF PEOPLE FOUND OUT
ABOUT YOU.
>> HUH.
>> I HAVE A LOT TO DO
SO I'M GOING EARLY.
>> SEE YOU!
>> WE SHOULD START GETTING
READY, TOO.
>> I'M SO EXCITED!
>> I BETTER DRESS UP FOR THIS.
NOW, WHERE DID MY KIMONO GO?
>> AHH.
>> THEY'RE SURE TAKING
A LONG TIME.
I WONDER WHAT SEEMS TO BE
HOLDING THEM UP?
HMM...
MMM!
UHH, TOO TOUGH.
FOX FIRE!
NOTHING LIKE HOME COOKING.
WHOA!
WHAT IS IT?
[GROWLING]
>> HIRAKOTSU!
>> UHH!
>> ARE YOU TWO OK?
>> I DON'T GET IT.
A DEMON IN AN AREA
FULL OF HUMANS?
>> THAT WAS A RECONSTITUTED
DEMON OF A KUROTENNUDAKE FUNGI.
>> A DEMON FUNGI?
>> UHH, HEH HEH HEH...
>> TIME TO GET RID
OF ALL THE DRIED FOOD.
TASTY OR NOT.
>> YOU STILL HAVE SOME LEFT?
>> JUST A FEW SNACKS
FOR THE ROAD.
I DON'T SEE WHAT THE BIG DEAL
IS.
>> SHIRONYUUDOU, KUROTENUDAKE,
YUMENAMAZU, WARAIASABI,
HAMADARUMA, HAMITSISUIKA,
AND THE ESEDAIKOKU.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU HAD SO MANY
LEFT STILL.
IS THIS ALL OF THEM?
>> KAGOME TOOK THE REST
BACK HOME WITH HER.
>> KAGOME TOOK THE REST?
>> BACK HOME?
>> WELL, INUYASHA IS WITH HER,
I SUPPOSE.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
I GUESS IT'S OK THEN.
>> YEAH, BUT I HEARD THAT
INUYASHA CAN'T REALLY DO
AS HE PLEASES WHEN HE'S
IN KAGOME'S WORLD.
>> HMM.
>> OOPS, EXCUSE ME, PLEASE.
>> RIGHT, LET'S PUT THE
BAKED GOODS ON THE TABLE, OK?
[GROWLING]
>> AAH!
IT'S THE DAY OF THE CULTURAL
FESTIVAL.
THE HOME EC CLASSROOM IS IN
RUINS.
>> DAMN IT!
THAT'S A KUROTENNUDAKE.
>> THERE ARE DEMONS RUNNING
ALL OVER THE SCHOOL.
WHERE DID THEY COME FROM?
>> KAGOME HAS A LOT
OF RESPONSIBILITY TODAY.
>> ON THE NEXT "INUYASHA,"
BATTLE AGAINST THE DRIED-UP
DEMONS AT THE CULTURAL FESTIVAL.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, HOJO?
THEY'RE FOR REAL!