- [ROARING]
- WHERE ARE WE NOW?
- THE PLACE WHERE A GIANT DEMON
KNOWN AS RYUKOSSEI
WAS SEALED INTO A DORMANT STATE.
STRANGE, THOUGH, THAT IT WAS
COMPLETELY DESTROYED LIKE THIS.
LORD SESSHOMARU, DO YOU
HONESTLY THINK THIS
IS INUYASHA'S DOING?
- IT'S ANYONE'S GUESS
HOW HE MIGHT HAVE
ACCOMPLISHED THIS.
- INDEED.
IMAGINE INUYASHA DEFEATING
SUCH A FORMIDABLE FOE.
IT TOOK EVERYTHING IN
YOUR FATHER'S POWER TO SEND
RYUKOSSEI INTO DORMANCY.
[SCREAMING]
DON'T LEAVE ME BEHIND,
LORD SESSHOMARU!
- HMM?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, KOGA?
- DON'T YOU TWO SMELL
THAT STENCH?
- I DON'T SMELL ANYTHING.
[SNIFFS]
WAIT. IT STINKS
LIKE A BUNCH OF CATS.
- WELL, THEY'RE NOT
FROM AROUND HERE.
- HMM. I WONDER
WHAT THEY WANT.
- WHO CARES WHAT THEY WANT?
- ARE WE LEAVING?
- ARE YOU JUST
GOING TO LET THEM GO?
- YEAH, YOU GOT IT.
WE DON'T NEED TO GO LOOKING
FOR TROUBLE.
- I GUESS NOT.
- YEAH, THEY'VE GOT
NOTHING TO DO WITH US.
- [SNORING]
WHAT ARE THEY DOING
AROUND HERE?
- UGH, SHE'S LATE!
- SHE SURE IS.
- SHE'S BEEN GONE 3 DAYS.
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING,
INUYASHA?
- WHERE ELSE?
I'M GONNA BRING KAGOME BACK.
- AH. HMM.
- [GRUNTING]
- I'M HOME, GRAMPS.
- HELLO, SOTA.
- INUYASHA, YOU'RE HERE!
- NICE TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
- WHERE'S KAGOME?
- I DON'T KNOW. I GUESS
SHE'S STILL AT SCHOOL.
- OH, WELL, SHE SHOULD BE BACK
ANY MINUTE.
- SEE YOU LATER!
- YEP, LATER!
- [MEOWING]
- [LAUGHING]
- I'M HOME!
- HUH? JUST THE PERSON
I'M WAITING FOR.
HEY! YO!
- HUH? WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
I JUST CAME TO GET YOU.
- YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO DO THAT.
- HMM! SURE I DID.
OTHERWISE, YOU'D TAKE
FOREVER TO COME BACK.
- GIVE ME A BREAK.
I HAVEN'T BEEN
BACK HERE FOR AGES.
- JUST GET READY,
AND WE'LL GO.
- HUH? YOU WANT TO GO NOW?
- WHY DON'T YOU HAVE DINNER
BEFORE YOU LEAVE?
- WE CAN EAT
WHEN WE GET BACK THERE.
- YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
IT'S STEAK.
- HUH? WHAT'S STEAK?
- SO INUYASHA WENT
BACK TO GET HER?
- IT'S FOR THE BEST.
WE NEED HER TO COME BACK.
- I WISH I COULD GO SEE
WHERE KAGOME LIVES ONE TIME.
- MASTER!
- HUH?
- PLEASE HELP ME, MY LORDS.
- IT'S THE OLD RACCOON DOG.
- HACHI, SO WHAT ARE YOU DOING
AROUND THESE PARTS?
- WELL, I--WELL, I HAD NO CHOICE
BUT TO HIDE IN HUMAN TERRITORY.
SEE, THOSE AWFUL DEMONS
FROM THE WEST ARE
IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
- WHY DON'T YOU JUST START
FROM THE BEGINNING?
- THE CATS!
- WHAT CATS?
- OK, OK, OK.
THE CAT DEMONS ARE
KILLING EVERY DEMON
THEY CROSS PATHS WITH
AND SEARCHING HIGH AND LOW
FOR THE JEWEL SHARDS.
- WHAT?
- OH, YEAH, AND I DIDN'T WANT
TO GET CAUGHT,
SO I RAN ALL THE WAY HERE.
- WHO ARE THESE DEMONS?
- I TOLD YOU, THEY'RE CATS,
AND THEY'RE NOT JUST ANY OLD
ORDINARY CAT DEMONS, EITHER.
- AM I THE ONLY ONE
WHO'S STILL CONFUSED?
- LET'S JUST GET OUT OF HERE
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
- MIROKU, LOOK.
- HUH?
- I HEAR THERE'S A PRIESTESS
IN THIS VILLAGE.
- [CRYING]
- THIS MUST BE WHERE SHE LIVES
RIGHT HERE.
- WHAT BUSINESS DO YOU HAVE
WITH ME?
- HMM? HUH?
- NO. NO. YOU CAN'T BE HER.
SHE'S YOUNG,
AND SHE WEARS SKIMPY CLOTHES.
- I WONDER IF SHE'S TALKING
ABOUT KAGOME.
- PLEASE, MY LORD, PLEASE!
- MIROKU!
- SLOW DOWN.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- YOU SMELL THAT?
IT'S THE SCENT OF CATS.
- IT'S THEM!
IT'S THE CAT DEMONS
FROM THE WEST!
- CAT DEMONS?
- HMM. MY FRIENDS AND I
ARE PANTHER DEMONS.
DON'T LUMP US TOGETHER
WITH COMMON CATS,
OR YOU'LL MAKE US ANGRY.
- AAH! AAH!
- WHOA! AAH!
- WHAT DO YOU DEMONS WANT HERE?
- WE'RE AFTER THE JEWEL SHARDS.
- [DEMONS GROWLING]
- YOU'D BETTER HAND THEM OVER.
- I'M AFRAID
WE CAN'T HELP YOU THERE.
- YEAH, THAT'S FOR SURE.
WE DON'T HAVE 'EM.
- SO, WHERE IS THIS PRIESTESS?
- WHY SHOULD WE TELL YOU THAT?
- TAKE THEM.
- [SHOUTING]
- [SCREAMING]
- HA HA HA!
BACK TO ME.
IT LOOKS LIKE WE WON'T FIND
THE PRIESTESS HERE.
BUT WE'LL BE BACK.
- AAH! HUH?
DID THEY RUN AWAY?
- YEAH, BUT I DON'T THINK
WE'VE SEEN THE LAST OF THEM.
- IT'S A GOOD THING KAGOME
DECIDED TO GO HOME WHEN SHE DID.
- BUT I'M THINKING IT MIGHT
BE BETTER IF SHE STAYS AWAY
FOR A LITTLE BIT LONGER.
- SHE'S ON HER WAY.
INUYASHA WENT TO
GET HER, REMEMBER?
- [INUYASHA LAUGHING]
OW! THAT HURT!
- THAT'S ENOUGH.
STOP TEASING THE CAT.
- I WAS JUST PLAYING WITH IT.
- BUYO DIDN'T THINK SO.
THAT'S WHY YOU GOT SCRATCHED.
NEVER GET ON THE WRONG SIDE
OF A CAT.
- WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
- THEY SAY A CAT'S CURSE LASTS
7 GENERATIONS.
A CAT'S VENGEANCE RUNS DEEP.
- HA! AS IF A CAT'S CURSE
COULD DO ANYTHING TO HURT ME.
HA HA HA HA!
- [BUYO HOWLING]
- HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
TO THE CAT?
SIT, BOY!
DINNERTIME.
- WHY DON'T YOU STAY
AND LEAVE TOMORROW?
- INUYASHA,
YOU CAN CRASH WITH ME.
- [CHOMPING]
- I HEARD THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARDS WERE KEPT
BY A STRANGE PRIESTESS,
BUT SHE WASN'T THERE.
AND BESIDES,
WE RAN INTO SOME TROUBLE.
COULD YOU COME ALONG WITH US?
- GO WITH HER, SHINRON.
- HMM. ALL RIGHT.
- WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO, SIS?
- I NEED TO TALK TO SOMEONE.
I'M GOING TO GO AND FIND HIM.
- YOU SURE ABOUT GOING ALONE?
- I'LL BE FINE.
YOU GIVE KARON A HAND.
- YES, OF COURSE.
- WE'LL ALL MEET UP
LATER AT THE ENTRANCE
TO THE VALLEY, SHALL WE?
- HERE, KAGOME. YOU OK?
- KAGOME!
- YOU KNOW, IT'S REALLY TOO BAD
THAT YOU'VE COME BACK.
- IT'S A SHAME
YOU DIDN'T STAY AWAY LONGER.
- NOW, WHAT KIND OF GREETING
IS THAT?
- DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
- TECHNICALLY SPEAKING,
IT'S ABOUT TO START.
- STOP WITH THE MUMBO JUMBO.
- DEFINITELY CATS.
- LOTS AND LOTS OF CATS.
- CATS?
- HUH?
HUH?
- HA HA! THAT'S THE WAY, JAKEN.
YOU CAN DO IT.
NO, TO THE RIGHT,
IN FRONT OF YOU.
- IN BEHIND?
- NOW LEFT. RIGHT.
ON THE SIDE. OVER THERE.
NO, THERE.
- OVER HERE?
I GOT ONE!
I CAUGHT IT WITH MY BARE HANDS!
- YOU'RE SO AMAZING, JAKEN.
YOU'RE THE GREATEST.
- I AM GREAT!
- IF IT ISN'T TORON.
- IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME,
SESSHOMARU.
- I THOUGHT YOU WERE DEAD.
- THAT'S A FINE WAY
TO GREET SOMEONE.
THIS TIME, I'M GOING
TO SETTLE THINGS
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
- WE SETTLED THINGS
A LONG TIME AGO,
BUT IF YOU INSIST.
YOU WON'T BE AS LUCKY
AS YOU WERE 50 YEARS AGO.
- YOU'RE STILL AS BOORISH
AS EVER, I SEE.
I AGREE THAT THINGS
WILL BE DIFFERENT
FROM HOW THEY TURNED OUT
50 YEARS AGO, THOUGH.
OUR MASTER IS WAITING FOR YOU.
- MASTER?
- YES, THE ONE WHO LEADS
THE PANTHER TRIBE.
I REALIZE YOUR DEAR FATHER
IS DEAD,
BUT OUR MASTER
IS GOING TO BE RESURRECTED
AT LONG LAST.
- RESURRECTED?
FOR WHAT PURPOSE?
- TO ATTACK THE LANDS
IN THE EAST ONCE AGAIN,
BUT MORE IMPORTANTLY,
TO GET OUR REVENGE
ON ALL YOUR KIND.
- I WILL PERSONALLY SEE TO IT
THAT HE NEVER BREATHES AGAIN.
- I'M GLAD TO HEAR YOU'VE
ACCEPTED MY CHALLENGE.
COME, NOW,
DON'T BE SO HASTY.
WE WON'T BATTLE IT OUT HERE.
COME TO OUR CASTLE.
THEN YOU CAN BRING
ALL THE REINFORCEMENTS
THAT YOU REQUIRE.
- LORD SESSHOMARU!
LOOK AT HOW MANY FISH JAKEN
AND I JUST CAUGHT.
- DON'T LEAVE ME BEHIND!
- LORD SESSHOMARU!
[PANTING]
SEE?
- JAKEN.
- YES?
- THE PANTHER DEMON TRIBE
IS BACK.
- AAH! WHAT ARE THEY
DOING HERE AGAIN?
- RIN, LISTEN.
- YES?
- YOU ARE TO WAIT HERE
WITH AUN.
- ALL RIGHT.
I WON'T MOVE FROM HERE.
- UH-HUH!
WAIT, MY LORD!
- DON'T FORGET TO COME BACK
AND GET US.
WE'LL BE WAITING.
- CAT DEMONS, YOU SAY?
- YOU KNOW,
I DISTINCTLY REMEMBER
SOMETHING SIMILAR TO THIS
HAPPENING 50 YEARS AGO.
- 50 YEARS AGO?
- YEAH. A TRIBE OF CATS SWARMED
IN AND ATTACKED FROM THE WEST.
- ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
SOUNDS LIKE ONE
OF YOUR TALL TALES.
- WAIT A MINUTE, INUYASHA.
DON'T YOU THINK
IT COULD HAVE HAPPENED
WHILE YOU WERE SEALED
TO THAT TREE?
- I GUESS,
BUT I WOULDN'T KNOW ABOUT IT.
- I'VE NEVER HEARD OF IT EITHER.
- MAYBE THAT'S 'CAUSE
YOU'RE JUST A BRAT.
- AM NOT! QUIT TREATING ME
LIKE A KID!
- SO, WHAT EXACTLY HAPPENED?
- I ESCAPED BEFORE
THE CAT DEMONS ARRIVED.
- NOW IT'S BELIEVABLE.
- I RETURNED AFTER I HEARD THEY
HAD ALL LEFT, AND SURE ENOUGH,
THERE WASN'T A SINGLE CAT DEMON
IN SIGHT.
- WHERE WERE THEY?
- OH, DEARIE ME, I'M AFRAID
THAT'S ALL I CAN REMEMBER.
- THE STORIES ARE TRUE. YOU ARE
A STRANGELY DRESSED PRIESTESS.
- THE CAT DEMONS!
- STOP CALLING US CATS,
YOU LITTLE RACCOON DOG.
- EXCUSE ME, I'M A FOX.
- WHO ARE YOU,
AND WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- IT'S NOT YOU
THAT WE'RE AFTER.
WE WANT THE PRIESTESS
WITH THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
- WELL, YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO GET
THROUGH ME FIRST,
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT.
- HA! YOU'RE A HALF-DEMON.
- GOT A PROBLEM WITH THAT?
- YOU WOULDN'T HAPPEN
TO BE INUYASHA?
- HUH?
- YOU KNOW THIS DEMON?
- I'VE NEVER SEEN HER BEFORE.
- YOU MUST BE HIM,
SESSHOMARU'S BROTHER.
- HUH, YEAH, WE'RE NOT EXACTLY
A CLOSE-KNIT FAMILY.
- LET ME TAKE ON INUYASHA.
SHURON, YOU HANDLE THE MONK
AND THE DEMON SLAYER.
RIGHT.
[ROARS]
- NOW BRING IT ON!
- I WON'T KILL YOU NOW,
BUT IT SURE WILL BE
A GOOD FIGHT.
JUST TRY AND COME AFTER ME.
- SURE! IT'S YOUR FUNERAL!
- AAH!
- WATCH OUT, SANGO!
WHAT'S THAT?
- [GROWLING]
- KAGOME!
WHAT DID YOU DO?
- HUH? HA HA HA!
[SHOUTING]
- AAH!
- [LAUGHS]
SHE HAS THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS,
ALL RIGHT.
- KAGOME!
- HUH. THAT GIRL SEEMS TO MEAN
A LOT TO YOU, INUYASHA.
- YEAH, AND YOU'D
BETTER LET HER GO.
- YOU'LL HAVE TO
COME TO OUR CASTLE
IF YOU WANT HER BACK--
IF YOU CAN, THAT IS.
WE'LL BE WAITING FOR YOU,
INUYASHA.
- NO! STOP!
OUT OF MY WAY!
DAMN IT! I'LL GET THEM.
- I'M GOING WITH YOU.
- WE'D BETTER GO, TOO, MIROKU.
- HOW'S KIRARA?
- SHE'S FINE. I'M SURE
SHE'LL COME TO IN A MINUTE.
- MY LORD,
I'LL BE LEAVING NOW.
- OH, NO, YOU'RE COMING WITH US.
- AAH!
- [PANTING]
WHERE ARE THEY?
WHERE'D THEY GET TO?
- CALM DOWN, INUYASHA.
THIS PLACE REEKS
OF THE CAT STENCH.
- YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
[SNIFFS]
THIS WAY.
- INUYASHA!
- HUH?
- WHERE'S KAGOME?
- I'LL FIND HER, DON'T WORRY.
THIS WAY.
- I HOPE LORD SESSHOMARU
DOESN'T INTEND TO TAKE
THOSE DEMONS ON ALONE.
NO, THAT WOULD BE TOO DANGEROUS,
EVEN FOR SOMEONE
AS STRONG AS MY MASTER.
AAH! WAIT, I KNOW HIM!
- LORD SESSHOMARU,
I, ROYAKAN,
WOULD BE HONORED TO SERVE
UNDER YOU ONCE AGAIN.
- NOT NECESSARY.
- PLEASE, MY LORD,
I BEG YOU TO RECONSIDER.
- DON'T LEAVE WITHOUT ME!
- ROYAKAN.
- YES?
- LEAVE BEFORE I LOP OFF
YOUR HEAD.
- PERHAPS YOU SHOULD CONSIDER
ACCEPTING HIS ASSISTANCE.
WE NEED HELP.
- NOT NECESSARY.
- THEN MAYBE WE CAN GET
INUYASHA'S AID THIS TIME.
- JAKEN?
- YES?
- ONLY YOU NEED ACCOMPANY ME.
- [ROYAKAN CRYING]
- LORD...SESSHOMARU!
I SHALL FOLLOW YOU
TO THE ENDS OF THE EARTH.
[CRYING]
HMM?
IF THIS TURNS OUR POORLY,
I'LL HAVE TO PAY FOR IT
WITH MY LIFE.
- ISN'T THAT KOGA UP AHEAD?
- HUH?
- HEY, MUTT, WHERE'S KAGOME?
- HUH. LIKE IT'S ANY
OF YOUR BUSINESS.
- I'VE BEEN PICKING UP
THE FOUL STENCH OF CAT DEMONS
IN THIS AREA A LOT LATELY.
SO TELL ME WHY KAGOME'S SCENT
IS MIXED UP WITH THEM NOW.
- UH!
- WHAT ARE YOU GETTING AT?
- I'D BETTER NOT FIND OUT
THAT KAGOME'S BEEN KIDNAPPED
BY CAT DEMONS, YOU MUTT.
- [GROWLS]
- YOU FOOL!
SHE WAS CAPTURED?
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
- SHUT UP! IT WASN'T LIKE
I HANDED HER OVER ON A PLATTER.
- KOGA!
- I HAVEN'T GOT TIME TO LOSE.
- AAH! KOGA, WAIT!
- HERE WE GO AGAIN.
- DAMN THAT KOGA,
ALWAYS BUTTING IN.
- WE CAN'T BE TOO PICKY ABOUT
OUR ALLIES AT A TIME LIKE THIS.
- HE'S RIGHT.
AND BESIDES, KOGA STOPS
FOR NOTHING WHEN IT
COMES TO KAGOME.
- YEAH, AND HE SURE
IS STRONG, TOO.
- SPARE ME. I'M NOT RELYING
ON KOGA'S HELP.
I'M GONNA SAVE KAGOME
ON MY OWN.
- [KAGOME GRUNTING]
LET ME GO!
PUT ME DOWN, YOU CREEP.
- WE GOT THEM.
WE GOT THE SHARDS.
- THOSE BELONG TO ME.
GIVE ME THAT BACK!
- WHO'S THIS STRANGE-LOOKING
YOUNG GIRL?
- SEEMS LIKE SHE'S
INUYASHA'S WENCH.
- INUYASHA?
THE YOUNGER SON
OF THE OLD MUTT?
- YEAH. HE'S ALIVE.
ISN'T THAT A SURPRISE?
- SHE SEEMED LIKE GOOD BAIT, SO
WE DECIDED TO BRING HER ALONG.
- TELL ME WHAT YOU WANT.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
TO INUYASHA?
- WE'RE GONNA KILL HIM.
- [GASPS]
- WHAT DO YOU THINK, TORON?
- I DON'T NEED BAIT
FOR SESSHOMARU.
HE'LL DEFINITELY COME.
- WHO ARE THESE PEOPLE?
WHAT ARE THEY PLANNING TO DO?
- KAGOME!
- KOGA!
- I'M HERE TO SAVE YOU.
- YOU'RE NOT INVITED
TO THIS LITTLE PARTY, WOLF BOY.
- AFTER THEM!
- [SHOUTING]
- NO, YOU DON'T.
WHO ASKED YOU FOR HELP, MUTT?
- I'M THE ONE WHO'S GONNA DO
THE SAVING HERE.
- NOT IF I HAVE ANY SAY IN IT!
SHE NEEDS MY HELP, DOG FACE!
- HUH?
- WHAT'S WITH THIS WALL?
- KAGOME!
[ECHOES]
- WHERE ARE YOU?
- KAGOME!
- SAY SOMETHING!
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
- KOGA, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- WHERE DID THE CATS GET TO?
- WE'VE LOST THEM.
THEY VANISHED WITHOUT A TRACE.
- I'M NOT PICKING UP ANY SCENT
OF THE CATS OR KAGOME.
- YEAH, THEIR SCENT
HAS COMPLETELY DISAPPEARED,
JUST LIKE WITH NARAKU'S BARRIER.
- HUH? BARRIER, YOU SAY?
[GRUNTS]
- WHAT ARE YOU PLANNING TO DO
WITH THAT SWORD?
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO HIS SWORD?
IT'S--IT'S GLOWING RED.
- [INUYASHA GRUNTS]
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
♪ EVERY HEART ♪
- THE PANTHER DEMON TRIBE WANTS
REVENGE ON INUYASHA'S BROTHER?
- ACCORDING TO ROYAKAN,
SOME CAT DEMONS ATTACKED HIM
50 YEARS AGO.
- AND BEFORE THAT,
THEY BATTLED INUYASHA
AND SESSHOMARU'S OLD MAN.
- NOTHING'S WORSE
THAN A CAT'S WRATH.
- DAMN IT! WHY DOES KAGOME
HAVE TO GET WRAPPED UP IN THIS?
IT'S ALL YOUR FAULT, INUYASHA.
- NEXT TIME: "TARGET:
SESSHOMARU AND INUYASHA."
- HOLD TIGHT, KAGOME!
I'LL SAVE YOU!