- KAGOME, IS IT THIS WAY?
- YES.
IT'S JUST BEYOND
THIS FOREST.
WE'RE IN SEARCH
OF SACRED JEWEL SHARDS
WHEN WE MEET UP
UNEXPECTEDLY WITH KOHAKU,
WHO'S BEING ATTACKED BY
ONE OF NARAKU'S DEMONS.
THE DEMON IS AFTER
THE SHARD EMBEDDED
IN KOHAKU'S BACK.
- HUH.
HUH?
- KOHAKU.
- SANGO IS OVERJOYED
AT BEING REUNITED WITH KOHAKU,
BUT KOHAKU'S MEMORY
HAS BEEN ERASED BY NARAKU,
AND HE REMEMBERS
NOTHING ABOUT HER.
- KOHAKU HAS COME BACK TO ME.
HE'S ESCAPED
FROM NARAKU'S GRASP.
THAT'S WHAT I WANT TO BELIEVE.
- IT'S OBVIOUSLY
ONE OF NARAKU'S TRAPS.
- YOU'RE WRONG.
I TRUST KOHAKU.
- THAT'S WHAT NARAKU WANTS.
- WHAT CHOICE DO I HAVE
EXCEPT TO TRUST
MY YOUNGER BROTHER?
- THAT'S WHEN KAGURA SHOWS UP
TO TAKE BACK THE SHARD,
BRINGING AN ARMY OF DEMONS
WITH HER.
IF THE SHARD IS REMOVED,
KOHAKU WILL DIE.
INUYASHA AND MIROKU
BEGIN FIGHTING OFF THE DEMONS
IN ORDER TO DISTRACT THEM.
MEANWHILE, KOHAKU AND I
ESCAPE INTO THE FOREST.
- I WANT TO REMEMBER HER
AND EVERYTHING ELSE.
STILL, WHY DO I FEEL THIS WAY?
IT'S LIKE I'M SCARED.
THERE'S SOMETHING
I DON'T WANT TO REMEMBER.
- KILL HER.
KILL KAGOME.
- WHAT A SHAME.
THEY ARE ALL OUT OF ARROWS.
- HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
KOHAKU?
- HIRAIKOTSU.
DON'T WORRY, KOHAKU.
I'LL NEVER LET NARAKU
TAKE YOU AWAY FROM ME AGAIN.
[KAGOME SCREAMS]
KAGOME.
KILALA.
- INUYASHA,
WE MUST KEEP KAGURA
AND HER DEMONS DISTRACTED
AS LONG AS WE CAN.
- SURE. I'LL DO WHAT I CAN.
KAGURA.
YOU NEED TO BRING A WHOLE ARMY
JUST TO CAPTURE ONE PUNY KID?
FINE BY ME.
- HMM.
THEY'RE FALLING
STRAIGHT INTO NARAKU'S TRAP.
NOW YOU MUST FOLLOW THROUGH,
KOHAKU.
MY, ISN'T THIS
JUST SO CONVENIENT?
MIGHT AS WELL SLAUGHTER YOU ALL
WHILE WE'RE AT IT.
DON'T YOU WORRY, THOUGH.
I SHALL PERSONALLY
TAKE YOUR HEAD, INUYASHA.
DANCE OF BLADES.
KOHAKU, PLEASE.
WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM?
WHY DID HE CHANGE
ALL OF A SUDDEN?
- KOHAKU, KILL KAGOME.
KILL HER.
- KOHAKU.
- KILL HER.
KILL HER.
- NO, KOHAKU.
- KAGOME. KOHAKU.
- SANGO.
- KOHAKU...
I KNEW IT.
YOU'RE STILL...
ARE YOU OK?
- I'M ALL RIGHT.
IT'S NOT THAT SERIOUS.
- KOHAKU.
KILALA, YOU STAY HERE
WITH KAGOME.
YOU MUST BE IN A LOT OF PAIN.
- SANGO, I'M OK.
- I'M SORRY.
- POOR SANGO.
WAIT A MINUTE.
I HOPE SHE'S NOT PLANNING TO...
- THERE'S TOO MANY.
- DANCE OF BLADES.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
WHY DON'T YOU
DRAW YOUR SWORD, INUYASHA?
- IT'D BE A WASTE
USING THE TETSUSAIGA
TO KILL THE LIKES OF YOU.
- IRON REAPER SOUL STEALER.
- HE MUST BE USING HIS CLAWS
BECAUSE HE'S STILL
NOT STRONG ENOUGH
TO CONTROL HIS TETSUSAIGA.
WHAT A BRILLIANT IDEA.
- FOOL.
- UH-OH.
DID I SAY THAT OUT LOUD?
- THAT'S WHY
YOU'RE NOT USING YOUR SWORD.
- I'M GOING TO SILENCE YOU
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
TETSUSAIGA.
HUH?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER,
INUYASHA?
SEEMS YOU'RE HAVING
AN AWKWARD TIME OF IT
WITH YOUR SWORD.
- DAMN.
IT'S STILL TOO HEAVY
TO WIELD EASILY.
- WE MUST KEEP
THOSE DEMONS BELIEVING
THAT KOHAKU IS HIDING
INSIDE THE HUT.
HUH?
- MIROKU.
- YOU SHOULD
PAY MORE ATTENTION.
[SHIPPO SCREAMS]
- HUH?
- A-HA.
SO THE HUT WAS EMPTY
ALL ALONG.
VERY CLEVER.
YOU FOOLED US
INTO THINKING KOHAKU
WAS INSIDE.
- YOU'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
- HMM.
- THIS FIGHT
IS FAR FROM OVER, KAGURA.
- HMM.
- WAIT A MINUTE.
DON'T BE TRICKED,
INUYASHA.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- WE THOUGHT IT WAS KOHAKU
THAT KAGURA
AND THE DEMONS WERE AFTER.
SO WHY IS IT THAT NONE OF THEM
ARE GOING AFTER HIM?
MAYBE THIS WHOLE BATTLE
WAS STAGED FROM THE BEGINNING,
AND WE WERE THE ONES
WHO WERE ENSNARED IN THEIR TRAP.
- HUH?
- WHAT IF IT WASN'T EVEN KOHAKU
THAT NARAKU IS AFTER?
- KAGOME.
SHE'S TAKEN KOHAKU
INTO THE FOREST.
I KNEW IT.
NARAKU STILL HAS KOHAKU
UNDER HIS MIND CONTROL.
- YOU'RE ONLY
REALIZING THAT NOW?
WHAT A SHAME.
YOU'RE PROBABLY TOO LATE.
- DAMN YOU.
YOU USED KOHAKU
TO GET TO KAGOME.
- CORRECT.
THAT GIRL WHO CAN USE
SACRED ARROWS,
SHE'S QUITE A NUISANCE.
- NO, MIROKU.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU'LL GET THE POISON INSECTS.
- WIND TUNNEL.
- MIROKU, DON'T DO IT.
- MIROKU.
HE'S SUCKING IN
THE POISON INSECTS.
- INUYASHA,
GO AND RESCUE SANGO AND KAGOME.
- COUNT ON IT.
THANKS, MIROKU.
DON'T DIE.
- NO, YOU DON'T.
- DON'T MOVE, KAGURA.
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS TURN,
AND I'LL SUCK YOU IN,
AS WELL.
- HUH.
I'LL PASS, THANKS.
- HUH?
SHE ESCAPED.
- MIROKU, ARE YOU DYING?
- NO TIME TO WASTE.
WE MUST HURRY AFTER INUYASHA.
- YEAH. SURE.
- DAMN THAT KID,
ACTING LIKE SOMEONE
WHO WOULDN'T EVEN HURT A FLY.
KAGOME.
- KOHAKU.
INUYASHA WARNED ME.
YOU HAVEN'T ESCAPED
NARAKU'S GRASP AFTER ALL.
YOU CAME TO HURT KAGOME
AND TO STEAL THE SHARDS
OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
WHY SHOULD I LET NARAKU
KEEP CONTROLLING YOU?
I'D RATHER...
KOHAKU, DON'T MOVE.
LET ME FREE YOU
FROM THAT DEMON.
KOHAKU,
I WON'T LET YOU DIE ALONE.
I'LL FOLLOW IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL BE RIGHT BEHIND YOU,
I PROMISE.
LET ME END IT.
- KAGOME.
- HUH?
- INUYASHA,
YOU HAVE TO GO AFTER SANGO.
SHE DIDN'T SEEM LIKE HERSELF.
- KAGOME, KOHAKU DID THIS
TO YOUR ARM, DIDN'T HE?
- IT'S NOT THAT SERIOUS.
IT COULD HAVE BEEN
A LOT WORSE.
HE COULD HAVE KILLED ME
IF HE'D WANTED TO.
HE COULD HAVE,
BUT HE DIDN'T.
- HUH?
- I DIDN'T HAVE A CHANCE
TO TELL SANGO.
SHE MIGHT BE PLANNING
TO KILL KOHAKU.
- OK.
I UNDERSTAND.
KOHAKU DIDN'T KILL KAGOME,
EVEN THOUGH HE COULD HAVE.
DOES THAT MEAN
HE DISOBEYED NARAKU'S ORDERS?
IF SO, THEN HE STILL
HAS A WILL OF HIS OWN,
EVEN IF HIS MIND
IS BEING CONTROLLED.
- KOHAKU.
- UH, EXCUSE ME.
- HUH?
- YOU'RE EMBRACING ME.
IT'S KIND OF EMBARRASSING.
- WHY ARE YOU SO SHY?
WE'RE SIBLINGS.
KOHAKU, STAY HERE.
DON'T LEAVE ME ANYMORE.
YOU'RE MY BROTHER,
THAT'S WHY.
KOHAKU, YOU'RE MY ONE
AND ONLY LITTLE BROTHER.
I'M GOING TO KILL YOU,
THEN MYSELF.
IT'S MY ONLY CHOICE.
THIS IS THE ONLY WAY
TO FREE YOU FROM NARAKU.
FORGIVE ME, KOHAKU.
- I'M GOING TO KILL YOU,
THEN MYSELF.
IT'S MY ONLY CHOICE.
THIS IS THE ONLY WAY
TO FREE YOU FROM NARAKU.
FORGIVE ME, KOHAKU.
- STOP, SANGO.
- OH, INUYASHA,
WHY DID YOU STOP ME?
- DON'T BE STUPID.
KILLING KOHAKU
WILL ONLY ACCOMPLISH ONE THING.
IT WILL MAKE NARAKU HAPPY.
HUH?
KOHAKU, COME BACK HERE.
SNAP OUT OF IT, YOU BRAT.
KAGURA.
- AS COMMANDED,
KOHAKU SHALL MURDER KAGOME.
KOHAKU IS UNABLE
TO DEFY NARAKU'S ORDERS.
- OH, YEAH?
- INUYASHA, WHY DO YOU THINK
KOHAKU HAS LOST HIS MEMORY?
- THAT'S OBVIOUS.
BECAUSE NARAKU
IS CONTROLLING HIS MIND.
- THAT'S PART OF IT,
BUT IT'S ALSO
BECAUSE KOHAKU HIMSELF
DOESN'T WISH TO REMEMBER...
SUCH AWFUL MEMORIES.
- HUH?
- THAT'S ENOUGH.
DON'T SAY ANYTHING MORE
IN FRONT OF KOHAKU.
- DAMN YOU, KAGURA.
- KOHAKU DIDN'T WANT
TO REMEMBER,
SO NARAKU GRANTED HIS WISH
AND ERASED HIS MEMORIES.
IT'S SO EASY
TO MANIPULATE SOMEONE
WHO'S A BLANK SLATE.
- KOHAKU, YOU GOTTA REMEMBER.
BRING YOUR MEMORIES BACK.
REMEMBER SANGO
AND THE DEMON SLAYERS.
- INUYASHA.
- YOU'RE GOING TO REMEMBER
EVERY LAST DETAIL.
DO IT, IF YOU WANT TO LIVE.
- STOP IT.
- THE ONLY WAY TO FREE HIM
FROM NARAKU'S CONTROL
IS TO GET HIM TO REMEMBER
EVERYTHING HE FORGOT.
NARAKU WILL EVENTUALLY
KILL HIM ANYWAY
TO TAKE THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD
IN HIS BACK.
- YOU ALWAYS SEE
THE WORST IN PEOPLE.
- COME BACK HERE.
- I'D THINK TWICE
ABOUT FORCING THIS BOY
TO REMEMBER EVERYTHING.
HIS PAST REALLY WOULD
DESTROY HIM.
LET THE POOR LAD
DIE IN BLISS,
FREED FROM ALL THOSE
TERRIBLE MEMORIES.
- KOHAKU.
DAMN.
NOT AGAIN.
- SANGO.
- NO, NOT AGAIN.
- DAMN.
YOU AND YOUR BROTHER
ARE A REAL PAIN.
- HMM?
- INUYASHA.
- HEY, SANGO,
MAYBE THIS WILL MAKE YOU
DO THINGS A LITTLE
DIFFERENTLY NEXT TIME.
NARAKU ORDERED KOHAKU
TO KILL KAGOME.
- HUH?
- BUT, YOU SEE,
KOHAKU DIDN'T CARRY OUT
HIS ORDERS...
AND THAT'S BECAUSE
HE STILL HAS A HUMAN HEART.
THAT'S WHY
WE CAN'T KILL KOHAKU.
WE HAVE TO TAKE HIM ALIVE.
GOT THAT?
- MM-HMM.
- KOHAKU, REMEMBER
THAT I SPARED YOUR LIFE.
I ALSO ERASED
YOUR TERRIBLE MEMORIES
FOR YOU...
AND YET YOU STILL FAILED
TO KILL KAGOME.
WHY IS THAT, KOHAKU?
DO YOU WISH
TO BECOME HUMAN AGAIN?
THEN DO YOU WANT
YOUR MEMORIES RETURNED?
ALL OF YOUR MEMORIES?
- NO. NO.
- HUH.
FAIR ENOUGH.
I'LL LET YOU LIVE, FOR NOW.
FORGET IT ALL.
- YES.
STILL, I CAN'T ERASE
THAT WOMAN'S FACE FROM MY MIND.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- A VILLAGE
IS ATTACKED BY LOOTERS.
GATENMARU, THE VICIOUS LEADER,
IS ACTUALLY A MOTH DEMON
DISGUISED AS A HUMAN.
INUYASHA AND MIROKU
ARE TRAPPED IN A POISON COCOON.
MEANWHILE,
SESSHOMARU SEARCHES FOR CLUES
INTO WHY INUYASHA TRANSFORMS,
AND LEARNS SOME
FRIGHTENING SECRETS
FROM A TREE DEMON.
NEXT TIME...
SEE YOU SOON.