- HUH?
UNH!
HUH?
- DIE, INUYASHA!
- INUYASHA HAD BEEN SEARCHING
FOR THE SACRED JEWEL OF 4 SOULS
TO ENABLE HIS TRANSFORMATION
INTO A FULL-FLEDGED DEMON.
BUT ALONG THE WAY,
AN EVIL CREATURE NAMED NARAKU
HAD COME BETWEEN
KIKYO AND INUYASHA,
SETTING THEM UP FOR BETRAYAL
AND A GRUDGE THAT WOULD
BURN INTO ETERNITY.
- AAH! AAH!
AAH...AH.
WHY DID YOU BETRAY ME,
INUYASHA?
- HUH?
- IF WE KEEP LOOKING FOR
THESE JEWEL FRAGMENTS,
WE'RE SURE TO RUN INTO NARAKU
OURSELVES SOONER OR LATER.
- I WILL HUNT DOWN KIKYO'S
KILLER AND AVENGE HER DEATH!
ARRGH!
[HORSES NEIGHING]
[MEN LAUGHING AND TALKING]
- WE'RE RICH!
- RESPECTABLE HAUL,
WOULDN'T YOU SAY, CHIEF?
LOOK AT THOSE BALES OF RICE.
[LAUGHING]
- WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
THAT TINY VILLAGE
WOULD HAVE SUCH
A LARGE STOREHOUSE?
- LET'S HURRY OUT OF THIS AREA
INSTEAD OF SETTING CAMP
FOR THE NIGHT.
- HUH?
- THEY SAY WHEN THE SUN SETS,
THE MONSTERS
COME OUT AROUND HERE.
- WHAT KIND OF OUTLAWS ARE YOU,
RUNNING FROM LITTLE GOBLINS?
- HEY, CHIEF, LOOK UP AHEAD.
- HUH?
THAT'S NO DEMON.
IT'S ONLY A HUMAN.
- A HUMAN WITH ARMOR
AND WEAPONS, NO DOUBT.
- HA! KILL HIM
AND STRIP HIS WEAPONS.
[MEN SHOUTING]
HA!
HUH?!
AAAAH!
OHH...
[LAUGHING]
- WELL, ONCE AGAIN,
YOU MADE QUICK WORK OF THEM.
VERY IMPRESSIVE, MASTER.
I MUST SAY, SLAYING
THAT BLUE DEMON EARLIER
AND PLUNDERING HIS ARM
WAS A SPLENDID IDEA!
- OPEN YOUR EYES, FOOL.
- AAH!
OH, OH!
- THIS ARM HAS ALREADY
BEEN RENDERED USELESS.
- OH, DEAR.
THAT DIDN'T LAST VERY LONG.
OHH! AAH!
- GO FIND ME A MORE
SUITABLE DEMON,
AND BRING ME BACK HIS ARM.
KNOW THAT IF YOU DON'T,
I WILL HAVE TO KILL YOU.
[PANTING]
- AAH! RELEASE ME AT ONCE!
OOH!
AIEE!
[SIGHS]
MOTHER WAS RIGHT.
I SHOULD HAVE BEEN A FERRY MAN.
THIS IS ENTIRELY
INUYASHA'S FAULT
FOR SEVERING
LORD SESSHOMARU'S ARM!
[GROWLING]
- NOW!
AAAH!
UNH!
- IT IS NOT THE SWORD
THAT SEVERED HIS ARM
WHICH I DIRECT
MY HATRED TOWARD.
IT IS TOWARD THE BEAST
THAT WIELDED IT--INUYASHA!
BY ALL RIGHTS, THE TETSUSAIGA
BELONGS TO LORD SESSHOMARU,
AND WE SHALL TAKE IT BACK
FROM INUYASHA WITHOUT FAIL!
[WIND WHISTLING]
- EVEN IF I AM PROVIDED
WITH ANOTHER ARM,
IT SHALL ALSO BE USELESS
AFTER A SHORT PERIOD.
- A VEXING PROBLEM, ISN'T IT?
- AAH!
[WHIMPERING]
- IF I AM NOT MISTAKEN, YOU ARE
THE ELDER BROTHER OF INUYASHA,
LORD SESSHOMARU, ARE YOU NOT?
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
SHOULD I KNOW YOU?
- I AM SOMEONE
WHO, LIKE YOURSELF,
DESPISES INUYASHA.
FORGIVE ME,
BUT I HAPPENED TO OVERHEAR
YOUR CONVERSATION JUST NOW.
PERHAPS I CAN BE OF ASSISTANCE.
MIGHT I SUGGEST THAT
YOU EMPLOY THIS ARM?
- HAVE YOU LOST YOUR SENSES?
CLEARLY THAT IS
THE ARM OF A HUMAN!
- YES, CLEARLY.
THIS ARM BELONGED TO A MORTAL,
BUT EMBEDDED IN IT IS A SHARD
OF THE SACRED SHIKON JEWEL.
- THE SHIKON JEWEL?
- SHOULD YOU CHOOSE
TO EMPLOY THIS ARM,
THE JEWEL SHARD WILL ENABLE YOU
TO WIELD THE TETSUSAIGA,
INUYASHA'S FABLED SWORD.
THE SWORD IS KNOWN TO WORK
FOR THE BENEFIT OF MAN.
AT PRESENT,
A DEMON SUCH AS YOURSELF
WOULD BE UNABLE TO EVEN
TOUCH THE TETSUSAIGA.
- YOU MENTIONED SOMETHING ABOUT
YOUR DESPISING INUYASHA.
TELL ME, DO YOU INTEND TO USE ME
TO EXACT YOUR REVENGE?
- YES.
- HOW DARE YOU EXPLOIT
MY MASTER IN SUCH A MANNER?!
- HMM. SOUNDS INTERESTING.
I SHALL ACCEPT THE ARM FROM YOU.
- MASTER, PLEASE RECONSIDER!
- OH, AND ONE OTHER THING...
- HUH?
- TAKE THIS HIVE.
YOU SHALL BE ABLE TO MAKE
GOOD USE OF IT, WITH CERTAINTY.
- I SHOULD KNOW THE NAME OF
THE ONE I MAKE A PACT WITH.
- MY APOLOGIES.
CALL ME NARAKU.
- VERY WELL, NARAKU.
YOU HAVE YOURSELF A DEAL.
[SEA GULLS CRYING]
- AH, THIS IS SO MUCH BETTER
THAN SLEEPING IN THE FOREST!
WE'LL HAVE A HOT MEAL,
A NICE BATH,
AND CLIMB UNDER
OUR NICE, CRISP SHEETS
AND HAVE A GOOD REST
FOR A CHANGE.
- WELL, EXCUSE ME FOR MAKING YOU
SLEEP IN THE WILDS ALL THE TIME!
- TOUCHY, TOUCHY.
WHAT'S WITH YOU THESE DAYS?
- I IMAGINE HE'S PUT OUT BECAUSE
COMING HERE WAS MIROKU'S IDEA.
WITH FOOD LIKE THIS,
WHO CARES WHOSE IDEA IT WAS?
- RIGHT!
[GROANS]
- THERE.
THAT SHOULD SUFFICE.
WITH THE LAST SEAL IN PLACE,
THE OMINOUS BLACK CLOUDS
THAT HOVER OVER YOUR TAVERN
SHOULD DISAPPEAR FOR GOOD.
- I AM FOREVER
IN YOUR DEBT, GOOD MONK.
GOODNESS ME, WHEN YOU
APPEARED ON MY DOORSTEP
CLAIMING THAT AN EVIL
CLOUD HUNG OVERHEAD,
WHY, I ALMOST JUMPED
OUT OF MY SKIN IN FEAR.
BUT NOW, THANKS TO YOUR
EXORCISM, I CAN SLEEP EASY.
- IT IS ALL IN A DAY'S WORK
FOR A SIMPLE MONK.
- AHH.
I CAN'T EAT ANOTHER BITE.
- THAT WAS THE BEST MEAL
I'VE HAD IN AGES.
HEY!
HOW'D THE EXORCISM GO?
- UNEVENTFUL.
NOW I'M READY
FOR SOME RELAXATION.
- HOLD UP THERE, MIROKU.
THERE'S SOMETHING I HAVEN'T
BEEN ABLE TO FIGURE OUT
ABOUT YOUR POWERS.
- YES?
- WHENEVER WE'RE LOOKING
FOR A PLACE TO BED DOWN,
YOU SUDDENLY DETECT
AN OMINOUS CLOUD HANGING OVER
WHATEVER SEEMS TO BE
THE FINEST TAVERN IN THE AREA.
HOW IS THAT?
- OH.
YOU NOTICED THAT, DID YOU?
THEY SAY A FALSEHOOD IS
SOMETIMES THE EXPEDIENT PATH.
- HUH?
- YOU MEAN, THERE NEVER
WAS ANY BLACK CLOUD?
- WHAT, YOU'RE JUST
FIGURING THAT OUT NOW?
[SIPS]
- JEEZ! YOU'RE SHIFTIER
THAN I THOUGHT!
- PARTAKE IN MY SHARE
OF THE SPOILS,
AND YOUR OPINION OF ME
WILL SOFTEN.
- SWEET DUMPLINGS--
MY FAVORITE!
- YOU'RE JUST AS BAD AS HE IS!
- CALM DOWN, INUYASHA.
[RUMBLING]
HUH?
- HUH?
- WHAT IS THAT? AAH!
- I DON'T LIKE
THE SOUND OF THIS!
- WHATEVER IT IS, IT'S BIG.
- YES. LET'S RUN.
- HMM? WHAT?! NO WAY!
YOU CAN'T JUST EAT AND RUN!
- IF THE DEMON IS TRULY BIG,
THEN WE ARE NO MATCH FOR IT.
IT'S IRRATIONAL,
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE,
IT'S AGAINST MY RELIGION.
- YOU OUGHT TO BE ARRESTED.
- I'M SENSING A JEWEL
FRAGMENT NEARBY...
AND IT'S APPROACHING US
VERY QUICKLY!
- OH, WELL, THAT'S A CHANGE.
WE'VE NEVER HAD THEM
BRING US THE JEWELS BEFORE.
- I SUPPOSE IF THERE'S
A JEWEL FRAGMENT INVOLVED,
I COULD MAKE
A LITTLE EFFORT.
- HUH? WAIT!
THIS ONE'S MINE!
- WH-WHAT'S MAKING THAT SOUND?
- IT SOUNDS LIKE A THUNDERSTORM.
- OHH!
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[VILLAGERS SCREAMING]
- HMM?
- OVER THERE!
- THAT'S SESSHOMARU!
- AAH!
- AS USUAL, YOU ARE SLOW
TO TAKE ACTION, LITTLE BROTHER.
[COUGHING]
- SESSHOMARU, TO WHAT HONOR
DO WE OWE THIS VISIT?
- SPARE ME
THE FEIGNED INNOCENCE.
I'M HERE FOR
THE TETSUSAIGA, OF COURSE.
- STILL HAVEN'T GIVEN UP
ON IT YET, HUH?
- THEY KNOW ONE ANOTHER?
- HE'S INUYASHA'S BROTHER.
- REMARKABLE.
- BUT HE ISN'T
A HALF-DEMON LIKE INUYASHA.
HE'S THE REAL THING.
SO HE'S STILL
AFTER THE TETSUSAIGA.
LAST TIME, HE COULDN'T MAKE
THE SWORD WORK FOR HIM.
IN FACT, HE COULDN'T
EVEN LIFT IT.
WAIT!
WHY WOULD THAT HAVE CHANGED?
- DRAW YOUR SWORD, INUYASHA,
OR WILL YOU SURRENDER IT NOW,
WITHOUT THE NEED FOR A BATTLE?
- NO CHANCE.
THIS TIME, I'LL TAKE OFF MUCH
MORE THAN JUST ONE OF YOUR ARMS!
UNH!
YAAH!
- SUCH A PITY.
I SEE YOU HAVE YET TO UNLEASH
THE FULL POWER
OF THE TETSUSAIGA.
- OH, YEAH?
LET'S SEE ABOUT THAT!
UNH!
[GRUNTING]
[ALL GASP]
- SUCH PITIFUL
SWORDSMANSHIP.
THE LITTLE MAN IS HAVING
TROUBLE HOLDING HIS SWORD.
- AAH!
- THE FLESH IS BURNING
FROM HIS WRIST!
- IT'S HIS POISONOUS NAILS!
- YOUR WRIST OR THE SWORD--
WHICH WILL BE FIRST TO DROP?
[GRUNTING]
- WELL, IT AIN'T
GONNA BE THE SWORD.
UNH!
UNH, UNH, YAAH!
- HE CAN'T OVERPOWER HIM.
- I'LL SPLIT YOU IN HALF,
YOU SAD EXCUSE FOR A DEMON!
- YOU SHOULD HAVE SURRENDERED.
- UNH.
OH, NO!
IMPOSSIBLE!
- BUT HE SHOULDN'T BE ABLE
TO TOUCH THE SWORD!
- UNH!
BUT SESSHOMARU IS A DEMON.
WHY IS HE ABLE TO TAKE HOLD
OF THE TETSUSAIGA?
- I'M THE TETSUSAIGA'S
RIGHTFUL OWNER.
STAND BACK AS I
DEMONSTRATE ITS TRUE POWER.
JAKEN.
- YES, MY LORD!
I SHALL SUMMON ALL THE DEMONS
DOWN FROM THE MOUNTAIN.
[RUMBLING]
GO FORTH!
[CRASH]
- OHH!
[GASPS]
[MOANING]
- WITNESS THIS AND LEARN
FROM A MASTER, INUYASHA.
WITH ONE STROKE, I SHALL
SLAUGHTER 100 DEMONS.
[DEMONS SCREAMING AND MOANING]
- NO!
THAT CAN'T BE!
- OH!
- THE MOUNTAIN!
- HE'S SLAYED THE DEMONS,
AND HE ALSO SPLIT THE MOUNTAIN.
- NOW DO YOU SEE?
THIS SWORD, FORGED OF OUR OWN
FATHER'S FANG, REIGNS SUPREME.
UNFORTUNATELY,
THE TETSUSAIGA'S NOT CAPABLE
OF CHOOSING ITS OWNER.
BUT PERHAPS NOW YOU,
A MERE HALF-BREED,
REALIZE THAT YOU CAN
NEVER MASTER IT.
- DAMN HIM!
- INUYASHA!
- HOLD IT, KAGOME!
STOP RIGHT THERE!
I SHALL GO.
BOTH OF YOU MAKE SURE
TO STAY BEHIND ME.
- YOU'RE GOING TO USE YOUR HAND?
- YOUR BLOOD SHALL
STAIN THIS SWORD--
TRULY A FITTING END
FOR YOU, IS IT NOT?
- NEVER!
I'LL NEVER LET HIM KEEP
THE TETSUSAIGA!
- I'M AFRAID I CAN LISTEN
TO THIS NO LONGER.
I MUST PUT AN END TO
THIS FOOLISH SIBLING RIVALRY.
- HEY, BUTT OUT!
- THAT MONK...
- I CAN HANDLE THIS!
- NOT ON YOUR OWN, YOU CAN'T.
- BACK OFF, CREEP!
I WANT TO STAND IN THE FRONT!
- DON'T BE SUCH A STUBBORN MULE!
- VERY FUNNY, COMING FROM YOU.
- NARAKU SPOKE
OF A CERTAIN MONK.
COULD THIS BE THE SAME
YOUNG MAN BEFORE US?
- JOURNEYING WITH INUYASHA
IS A YOUNG MONK.
HE MAY PROVE TO BE
EVEN MORE TROUBLESOME
THAN INUYASHA HIMSELF.
- HA! HE LOOKS
NO MORE TROUBLESOME THAN
ANY OTHER MERE MORTAL.
HMPH!
- AAH!
- MY LORD, ALLOW ME
TO FINISH THE MONK OFF!
NO SENSE IN WASTING YOUR ENERGY
ON SUCH A FEEBLE OPPONENT.
- AS YOU WISH.
I WILL OBSERVE.
- ONWARD!
CRUSH THEM ALL!
- MOVE BACK!
WIND TUNNEL!
- NO! STOP THIS!
[WHIMPERING]
- YOU SHOW 'EM, MIROKU!
- MIROKU, YOU'RE THE BEST!
OH, YEAH.
YOU WERE GOOD, TOO.
- GEE, THANKS.
I CAN TELL IT WAS
FROM THE HEART.
- I SUPPOSE THIS IS
AS GOOD A TIME AS ANY.
- THIS IS THE HIVE
OF THE SAIMYOSHO,
THE INSECTS OF HELL.
IT SHALL PROVE EXTREMELY USEFUL
IN PLUGGING THE HOLE
IN THE MONK'S RIGHT HAND.
- HUH. WE SHALL SEE
IF NARAKU IS CORRECT.
[INSECTS BUZZING]
- UNH!
GIANT INSECTS!
- HUH?
- WHAT ARE THOSE THINGS?
WAIT.
THEY'RE NOT BEING SUCKED IN.
THEY'RE FLYING AT HIM!
- WHAT ARE THESE?!
UNH!
[GRUNTING]
INUYASHA,
YOU'LL HAVE TO TAKE OVER.
- MIROKU!
- WHAT'D THEY DO TO YOU?
- AAAH-HA!
- IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
- MIROKU, ARE YOU GOING
TO BE ALL RIGHT?
- THE INSECTS HAVE POISONED ME
WITH THEIR VENOM.
- OH, NO!
- FOX FIRE!
- CAREFUL, SHIPPO!
- DON'T WORRY.
I CAN HANDLE THEM.
OH! AAH!
- SHIPPO!
- LISTEN, MIROKU,
DON'T YOU MOVE.
I'LL LOOK FOR AN ANTIDOTE.
INUYASHA, WATCH MIROKU!
- COME ON, MIROKU!
HOW ABOUT A LITTLE HELP HERE?
- UNH.
SORRY, INUYASHA.
THE VENOM'S GOTTEN TO ME.
HOW COULD INSECTS HAVE BLOCKED
THE USE OF MY HAND?
- BLADES OF BLOOD!
YOU OWE ME BIG TIME
FOR THIS ONE, MIROKU.
WAIT.
HE SAID SOMETHING
ABOUT VENOM.
IS HE IN SERIOUS TROUBLE?
- AAH!
WE'VE GOT COMPANY COMING!
- HE HAS NO HOPE.
- NOW WHAT DO I DO?
WE'RE TRAPPED.
ONE STRIKE WITH THE TETSUSAIGA,
AND WE'LL ALL BE DONE IN.
- THIS IS THE END FOR YOU.
DIE.
THIS IS THE END FOR YOU.
- UNH!
[GROWLING]
[CHUCKLING]
- YOUR STUPIDITY
KNOWS NO BOUNDS.
RUN AND HIDE WHILE YOU CAN.
THAT, AND ONLY THAT,
IS THE ONLY CHOICE LEFT TO YOU.
THEN AGAIN, PERHAPS YOU SHOULD
STAND UP AND FACE YOUR DEATH.
AT LEAST YOU WOULD DIE
WITH HONOR.
- BLAH, BLAH, BLAH.
THE GUY STARTS SWINGING
A BIG NEW SWORD AROUND,
AND SUDDENLY
HE'S LOOKING FOR A SOAPBOX
TO STAND ON
AND PREACH TO THE WORLD.
HA HA HA HA!
LET ME GIVE YOU
A PIECE OF ADVICE,
NOW THAT I HAVE
YOUR ATTENTION.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO KILL SOMEONE,
MAKE SURE YOU DO IT RIGHT
THE FIRST TIME,
BECAUSE IF YOU ONLY MAIM THEM
WITH THE FIRST ATTACK,
THEY HAVE A NASTY WAY OF COMING
BACK TO MAKE YOU REGRET IT...
LIKE THIS!
AAAH!
UNH!
- SILENCE!
I HAVE HEARD ENOUGH!
- AAAH!
[GRUNTING]
HE'S HOLDING OFF
THE TETSUSAIGA...
WITH THE TETSUSAIGA SHEATH!
[GRUNTING]
[LAUGHING]
- LORD SESSHOMARU
NEARLY KILLED ME,
HIS SERVANT,
WITH HIS OWN BLOW!
HIS BLATANT DISREGARD
FOR ALLY OR FOE
WHEN HE SETS HIS MIND
ON KILLING SOMEONE
IS MUCH MORE TERRIFYING
THAN HIS AWESOME POWER.
OH!
MY FUTURE MAY NOT BE
IN GOOD HANDS.
OH...
- UNH!
[COUGHING]
- YOU--YOU'RE STILL ALIVE!
- IMP, PERHAPS YOU CAN
EXPLAIN SOMETHING.
- HOW IS IT THAT WE HAVE NEVER
MET, YET UNLESS I'M MISTAKEN,
YOU TWO BROUGHT ALONG
THOSE INSECTS SPECIFICALLY
TO OBSTRUCT MY WIND TUNNEL?
- UH, UH...WE DID?
OH, YES.
- LOOK OUT!
- RARRGH!
- AAH! UNH!
- YOU MISERABLE...
[CACKLING]
- A WEAK MONK
AND A PUNY FOX CHILD.
I AM POWERFUL ENOUGH
TO TAKE YOU BOTH OUT AT ONCE!
[GROANS]
[GRUNTING]
- OH, PLEASE--TRYING
TO RESIST MY TETSUSAIGA
WITH A SWORD SHEATH?
- YEAH, BUT THIS IS
NO ORDINARY SHEATH.
YOU'LL CHANGE YOUR MIND
SOON ENOUGH...
WHEN I USE IT TO CRACK OPEN
THAT HEAD OF YOURS.
- WAAH!
- IS THAT ALL YOU GOT?
COME ON!
- HOW ABOUT THIS?!
- YOU FOOL!
- UNH! I DON'T GET IT.
THAT ONE ALWAYS WORKS.
- SAVE YOURSELF, SHIPPO.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
- I'M STAYING.
[CACKLING]
- AAH!
- WHOA!
- THAT WILL KILL ME?
LET'S SEE YOU PROVE IT.
- UNH!
- ONE STRIKE.
ONE MORE STRIKE,
AND IT'S OVER.
[SNARLING]
- HUH?
THE TETSUSAIGA'S
TRANSFORMED BACK!
HUH?
- SESSHOMARU!
- HUH?
- DROP THE SWORD, OR THE NEXT
ARROW'S GOING IN YOUR HEART.
- KAGOME!
- INUYASHA, GET OUT OF THERE.
MOVE IT!
- THAT YOUNG WOMAN'S ARROW
CANCELED TETSUSAIGA'S
TRANSFORMATION?
- IT MUST BE TRUE.
KAGOME REALLY IS
THE REINCARNATION
OF THE PRIESTESS!
- HUH?
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- MIROKU'S WIND TUNNEL
IS UNUSABLE,
AND THE TETSUSAIGA
HAS BEEN STOLEN.
AND WORST OF ALL,
THE EVIL SESSHOMARU
HAS INUYASHA BACKED
INTO A CORNER.
A JEWEL WAS EMBEDDED
IN ME BEFORE,
SO MAYBE I REALLY CAN SUMMON
THE MAGICAL POWERS
OF KIKYO THE PRIESTESS
TO HELP US GET OUT OF THIS MESS.
FINALLY, WE'RE ALL
WORKING TOGETHER.
BUT WHOA!
WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO INUYASHA NOW?
NEXT TIME, "GO HOME
TO YOUR OWN TIME, KAGOME!"
SEE YOU SOON!