[THUNDER RUMBLES]
>> HUH?
HMM.
MUST HAVE IMAGINED IT.
>> YOU SHOULD BE SO LUCKY.
>> HUH?
HMM?
>> [CHUCKLES]
>> WHO ARE YOU?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> BE QUIET.
IT'LL BE OVER BEFORE YOU KNOW
IT.
>> HUH?
>> DANCE OF BLADES.
[GRUNTS]
>> [SCREAMS]
>> [LAUGHS]
>> "ENTEI, THE DEMON HORSE
UNLEASHED."
>> OH!
I'M STILL HUNGRY.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU JUST ATE A BUNCH OF FISH.
>> YEAH, BUT I DIDN'T HAVE ANY
RICE WITH IT.
>> OH, LET ME GET THIS STRAIGHT.
>> NOW, NOW.
KAGOME, I'LL HELP YOU OUT IF
YOU'RE STILL HUNGRY.
>> DO YOU HAVE SOMETHING TO EAT?
>> NO.
NOT A CRUMB WITH ME, I'M AFRAID.
BUT LOOK OVER THERE.
>> HUH?
>> A VILLAGE!
>> HOW ABOUT THAT.
YEAH!
MIROKU, I'M COUNTING ON YOU TO
DO YOUR THING.
>> LEAVE IT TO ME.
>> I CAN TASTE IT NOW.
>> WOW!
A REAL MEAL!
>> HUH?
HEY, ISN'T THERE SOMETHING KIND
OF STRANGE ABOUT THAT VILLAGE?
>> LOOK AGAIN.
>> HUH?
>> HMM?
>> THE HEAD PRIEST?
>> YES.
HE WAS KILLED, I'M AFRAID.
>> NOT AGAIN.
>> ANOTHER CASE OF SPIRITUAL
MONKS AND PRIESTS BEING SLAIN
MYSTERIOUSLY.
IT'S TROUBLING.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHO'S BEHIND
THESE MURDERS, BUT ONE THING'S
CERTAIN: THEY'VE BEGUN TO HAPPEN
OFTEN ENOUGH THAT WE HAVE TO
TAKE THEM SERIOUSLY.
>> AFTER THIS ATTACK, THE DEMON
WHICH WAS SEALED IN THE SHRINE
WAS SET FROM AND IS NOW WREAKING
HAVOC EVERYWHERE.
>> A DEMON?
>> SO THAT'S WHY THE VILLAGE IS
IN SHAMBLES.
>> HMM.
HMM?
>> HUH?
>> [SNIFFING]
>> IS ANYTHING WRONG AROUND
HERE, INUYASHA?
ARE YOU SENSING SOMETHING?
>> YEAH.
OVER THAT WAY.
I CAN SMELL HIM.
NOTHING BUT SMALL-FRY DEMONS,
BUT THEY'RE HERE.
>> THEY'RE TRYING TO HIDE
THEMSELVES.
[RUMBLING]
>> GET READY.
>> STAY ON YOUR TOES, EVERYONE.
>> [ROARING]
>> INUYASHA!
>> LEAVE HIM TO ME.
ONE STRIKE, AND THEY'LL BE DEAD.
WIND SCAR!
HA.
>> THANK YOU FOR FEEDING US!
MMM, MMM, MMM!
DELICIOUS.
>> THAT REMINDS ME.
I MEANT TO ASK IF THERE HAVE
BEEN ANY SIMILAR INCIDENTS IN
THIS NEIGHBORHOOD LATELY.
>> YES.
THERE HAVE BEEN A GREAT MANY
RUMORS ABOUT THEM RECENTLY.
THERE'S BEEN A STRING OF MONKS
AND PRIESTS SLAIN IN RECENT
TIMES.
>> WHO COULD BE DOING IT?
>> GET OVER IT.
>> YES.
GOOD QUESTION.
>> WHY DO YOU ALWAYS PICK ON ME?
>> I NEED WAY MORE FOOD...
>> IF YOU BELIEVE THE RUMORS,
IT'S A WOMAN THAT CARRIES AN
INFANT WITH HER?
>> HUH?
>> AN INFANT?
YOU DON'T THINK IT'S...
THAT BABY?
>> YOU GOT IT, SANGO.
THE WOMAN MUST BE KAGURA.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> WHAT COULD THEY POSSIBLY BE
SCHEMING THIS TIME, AND WHY
WOULD THEY NEED HUMANS?
>> FORGET THE GUESSING GAMES.
WHO CARES?
IF NARAKU'S INVOLVED, THAT'S ALL
WE NEED TO KNOW.
WE CAN'T IGNORE IT.
RIGHT?
>> DEFINITELY.
I SEE YOUR POINT.
>> WHAT CAN WE DO?
WE DON'T EVEN KNOW WHERE KAGURA
IS.
>> WE'LL KNOW THE ANSWER TO THAT
SOON ENOUGH.
>> HUH?
>> SIR, COULD YOU TELL US WHO IS
THE MOST SPIRITUAL PRIEST OR
MONK IN THIS AREA?
>> HMM.
YOU MEAN SOMEONE WHO'S STILL
ALIVE?
>> OF COURSE THEY GOTTA
BE ALIVE.
>> LET ME SEE, NOW.
A MONK OR PRIEST WHO IS HIGHLY
SPIRITUAL AND STILL ALIVE FROM
THE AREA.
THAT WOULD HAVE TO BE MONK
SHINSEN OF MONGON TEMPLE.
>> MONK SHINSEN?
YOU MEAN THE MONK SHINSEN?
>> HUH?
YOU'VE HEARD OF HIM?
>> YES, OF COURSE.
HE'S PRACTICALLY A LEGEND.
IT'S SAID THAT NO ONE PUTS A
DEMON UNDER SEAL MORE SKILLFULLY
THAN HIM.
>> HUH?
I'M A DEMON SLAYER, AND EVEN
I'VE HEARD OF HIM.
THAT MAKES HIM A REALLY FAMOUS
MONK.
>> AMONG HIS FEATS IS HIS
SUBJUGATION OF THE DEMON
RENGOKUKI.
AND THEN THERE'S THE FAMOUS
STORY OF HOW HE PUT ENTEI THE
DEMON HORSE UNDER SEAL.
>> HUH.
>> HUH?
>> IS SOMETHING THE MATTER,
MASTER SHINSEN?
YOU LOOK A LITTLE TROUBLED.
>> NEVER MIND.
IT'S NOTHING.
I THOUGHT I HEARD THE SOUND OF
ENTEI OUTSIDE THE TEMPLE JUST
NOW.
>> WHO IS ENTEI?
>> OH...
THE DEMON HORSE THAT I
SEALED IN THE MOUNTAIN BEHIND
THIS TEMPLE.
AS HIS NAME ENTEI, OR FIRE
EMPEROR, IMPLIES, HE IS A DEMON
HORSE WITH HOOVES OF FLAME.
HE IS ABLE TO RUN 1,000 LEAGUES
IN A DAY.
HE IS SWIFT BEYOND IMAGINATION.
>> A DEMON?
>> YES.
ACCORDING TO LEGEND, ABOUT 100
YEARS AGO A SWIFT HORSE DIED IN
A FIRE.
ITS VENGEFUL SPIRIT WAS
RESURRECTED.
AND THEN THERE'S ANOTHER LEGEND
ABOUT ENTEI BEING BORN FROM A
VOLCANIC EXPLOSION.
>> ANOTHER LEGEND?
SO YOU'RE NOT REALLY SURE ABOUT
THIS?
>> WELL, I SUPPOSE YOU COULD SAY
THAT.
BUT THOSE AREN'T THE ONLY RUMORS
ABOUT THE DEMON HORSE.
>> HUH?
>> THERE'S ONE EVEN MORE FAMOUS
LEGEND ABOUT ENTEI.
>> IF A PERSON CAN MOUNT ENTEI,
HE'LL CONQUER THE WORLD?
>> YES.
I'VE HEARD THAT AS WELL.
I DON'T KNOW WHO STARTED IT, BUT
THAT RUMOR HAS SPREAD FAR AND
WIDE.
NATURALLY, IT'S NOTHING MORE
THAN SUPERSTITION.
STILL, HUMANS AND DEMONS FOUGHT
COUNTLESS BATTLES TO TRY TO
CAPTURE ENTEI.
THE LAST ONE LEFT STANDING WAS
RENGOKUKI, AND IT WAS HE WHOM
ENTEI ALLOWED TO MOUNT HIM.
>> HMM.
HMM?
>> MANY VILLAGES WERE VICTIMIZED
BY RENGOKUKI'S ATTACK.
>> [SCREAMING]
>> THEY WANTED THE DEMON SLAIN.
THE SOONER THE BETTER.
SO THE VILLAGERS PLEADED WITH
MONK SHINSEN FOR HELP.
>> MY BATTLE WITH RENGOKUKI WAS
INTENSE.
IT LAST 3 DAYS AND NIGHTS.
AND I NEEDED ANOTHER 3 DAYS AND
NIGHTS TO SEAL ENTEI.
[SCREAMING]
>> [GROWLING]
>> FINALLY I WAS ABLE TO DEFEAT
BOTH THE DEMONS.
I SEALED THEM IN TWO SEPARATE
LOCATIONS.
>> AND THAT'S WHAT'S IN THE
SHRINE?
>> YES.
THIS ALL HAPPENED MANY YEARS
AGO, MIND YOU.
>> I'LL SAY THIS THOUGH.
MASTER SHINSEN WAS ABLE TO PUT
UNDER SEAL TWO FRIGHTENING
DEMONS.
HE IS INDEED A REMARKABLE MONK,
MY FRIENDS.
>> YEAH.
HE MUST BE INCREDIBLE,
ESPECIALLY IF HE'S STRONG ENOUGH
TO SEAL AWAY THOSE DEMONS.
IT'S NO WONDER THAT KAGURA WOULD
GO AFTER HIM, THEN.
>> ALL RIGHT, THEN.
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE GET GOING?
WE DON'T HAVE TIME TO SIT HERE
YAKKING.
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
>> [SIGHS]
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER?
GET GOING.
>> I KNOW, I KNOW.
HONESTLY...
YOU SURE KNOW HOW TO
ORDER PEOPLE AROUND.
>> HUH?
>> WHAT IS IT, MASTER SHINSEN?
IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG?
>> DO NOT SENSE ANYTHING.
>> HUH?
>> AN EVIL AURA IS OUTSIDE
RAPIDLY APPROACHING THE TEMPLE.
YOU TWO HIDE YOURSELVES.
GO QUICKLY.
>> YES, MASTER.
>> WHO GOES THERE?
>> HMM.
IT SEEMS YOU'RE STRONGER THAN
THE OTHERS BEFORE YOU.
>> YOU SHOW YOURSELF, DEMON!
[SCREAMING]
>> HA.
YOU THINK PUTTING UP A LITTLE
BARRIER WILL SAVE YOU FROM ME?
>> HUH?
YOU MUST BE THE ONES WHO HAVE
BEEN SLAYING INNOCENT MONKS AND
SHRINE KEEPERS.
I HEARD THE DEMON WAS A FEMALE
WITH AN INFANT.
THERE'S SOMETHING ABOUT THAT
INFANT.
IT COULD VERY WELL BE MORE EVIL
THAN THE WOMAN.
>> [LAUGHS]
A PRIEST WITH HIS POWER
SHOULD BE ABLE TO SEE THE BORDER
BETWEEN THIS LIFE AND THE NEXT.
>> [GASPS]
THE INFANT CAN SPEAK!
>> STAY BACK, YOU TWO.
>> OVER HERE, MONK.
LET'S SEE IF YOU CAN COUNTER
THIS.
DANCE OF BLADES.
>> WHAT'S THIS?
>> NOT BAD, OLD MAN.
TRY TO COUNTER THIS.
DANCE OF THE DRAGON.
>> LOOK OUT, MASTER SHINSEN!
>> TAKE THIS!
>> IT'S USELESS!
WHAT THE--
[YELLING]
[SCREAMING]
OOF!
>> OH, NO.
MASTER.
>> I'M GOING TO LOOK INTO YOUR
SOUL, OLD MAN.
>> THERE.
DID IT WORK?
I FEEL SO OLD ALL OF A SUDDEN.
>> MASTER SHINSEN!
>> RIGHT.
THIS CAN'T BE GOOD.
>> THE SMELL OF BLOOD.
>> YEAH.
AND IT'S STILL FRESH.
THERE'S ALSO THE SMELL OF
INCENSE.
IT HAS TO BE COMING FROM THE
TEMPLE.
>> [WEEPING]
OH, NO.
IT'S ANOTHER DEMON.
>> REST ASSURED WE MEAN YOU NO
HARM.
>> HUH?
>> OVER THERE!
>> KAGURA MUST HAVE BEEN HERE.
>> YEAH.
I CAN STILL SMELL HER SCENT IN
HERE.
I'M GUESSING A WOMAN WITH AN
INFANT DID THIS TO YOUR MASTER.
IS THAT WHAT HAPPENED HERE
TONIGHT?
>> YES.
THAT'S CORRECT.
>> MASTER SHINSEN FOUGHT WITH
GREAT SKILL AGAINST THEM.
HE DID HIS BEST TO PROTECT US.
HE WASN'T ENTIRELY WITHOUT
SUCCESS.
AT LEAST HE MANAGED TO DESTROY
THE INFANT.
>> HUH?
THE BABY'S DEAD?
>> YOU SURE?
>> YES.
ABSOLUTELY SURE.
>> MASTER SHINSEN'S POWER TORE
THE BABY IN HALF.
>> WELL, WHAT DO YOU THINK OF
ALL THIS, MIROKU?
>> THAT CHILD WAS AN
INCARNATION.
NARAKU CREATED IT INSIDE
MOUNT HAKUREI.
AND THEN WHEN MOUNT HAKUREI WAS
DESTROYED, HE WENT TO A LOT OF
TROUBLE TO LET HIM ESCAPE.
>> SO THE BABY WAS SOMEHOW VITAL
TO NARAKU?
IS THAT WHAT IT MEANS?
>> YES.
MOST LIKELY.
>> YEAH.
THIS SEEMS TOO EASY.
>> WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON?
>> SAIMYOSHO?
WHERE ARE THEY LEADING US?
KANA.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
DID NARAKU SEND YOU?
OH, WELL.
TOO BAD, SO SAD, I GUESS.
SO, I SUPPOSE YOU'VE COME HERE
IN NARAKU'S PLACE TO LECTURE ME?
HEY, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
WHAT ABOUT THIS?
>> KEEP THAT ONE.
YOU CAN PROTECT IT.
>> HUH?
>> IT'S HIS FATE.
THIS WAS ALL MEANT TO HAPPEN.
>> WHAT'S THIS TALK ABOUT THE
BORDER BETWEEN THIS WORLD AND
THE NEXT?
WHAT'S IT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
>> I HEARD THE INFANT SPEAK OF
THIS BORDER.
IT WAS RIGHT BEFORE THEY KILLED
MASTER SHINSEN.
>> HE SAID HE WAS GOING TO LOOK
INTO MY MASTER'S SOUL.
>> WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
>> AT FIRST I THOUGHT I KNEW
WHY KAGURA AND THE INFANT WENT
AROUND KILLING MONKS AND
PRIESTS.
I THOUGHT THAT IT WAS THEIR
PURPOSE TO UNSEAL AND FREE THE
DEMONS.
IT SEEMS THAT WASN'T THEIR ONLY
OBJECTIVE.
>> THE BORDER BETWEEN THIS WORLD
AND THE NEXT?
WHAT'S THERE?
[RUMBLING]
>> LISTEN TO THAT NOISE!
>> YOU DON'T THINK THE DEMON
COULD HAVE SOMEHOW BROKEN THE
SEAL?
>> A DEMON'S SEALED HERE?
>> LET'S GO!
>> WHOA!
>> THE MOUNTAIN OUT BACK?
>> YES.
IT TOOK EVERYTHING IN HIS POWER
FOR MASTER SHINSEN TO SEAL ENTEI
THE DEMON HORSE THERE.
>> DID YOU SAY ENTEI?
>> THE LEGENDARY DEMON HORSE
THAT SOME SAY ALLOWED RENGOKUKI
TO BE HIS RIDER?
>> YES.
THAT'S RIGHT.
>> IS THAT IT?
>> HUH?
>> I DON'T LIKE THE LOOK OF THIS.
>> [GRUNTS]
>> IS THAT IT?
>> ENTEI.
>> ALL RIGHT, YOU DAMN BEAST!
AAH!
EVERYONE, RUN!
YOU'RE NOT HURT OR ANYTHING, ARE
YOU, KAGOME?
>> NO.
>> MIROKU, ARE YOU GUYS ALL
RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT US.
YOU FOCUS ON THAT THING--
THAT DEMON HORSE.
>> OH, I'M FOCUSING, ALL RIGHT.
HE'S GONNA GET MY PERSONAL
THANKS FOR THAT ATTACK.
GET READY FOR MY WIND SCAR!
>> HE DODGED IT!
>> THAT THING'S FAST!
>> HE'S COMING, MIROKU.
>> KIRARA!
>> HIRAIKOTS!
HE DISAPPEARED.
WHERE IS HE?
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING, SANGO?
HE'S RIGHT ABOVE YOU!
>> [GASPS]
[SCREAMS]
>> SANGO.
>> SANGO!
>> ALL RIGHT.
THAT DOES IT.
I'LL HAVE TO USE MY WIND TUNNEL.
>> WHAT NOW?
>> A MIASMA.
DAMN.
HE'S SPREADING IT AROUND.
YOU'RE WELCOME'S WEARING THIN!
CRAP!
>> ARE YOU HURT ANYWHERE, SANGO?
>> NO.
NEVER MIND ME.
WE HAVE TO STOP THAT DEMON
HORSE.
>> NO, HE'S GOING TOO FAST.
I CAN'T GET A GOOD AIM ON HIM.
>> WE'VE GOTTA STOP HIM FROM
RACING AROUND SO MUCH.
HUH?
>> HE STOPPED MOVING.
>> AND THAT'LL BE HIS LAST
MISTAKE.
IT'S OVER, HORSE!
YOU'RE GOING BACK TO BEING A
LEGEND!
>> WAIT!
DON'T DO IT!
>> WHAT DID YOU STOP ME NOW FOR?
>> SOMETHING'S WRONG.
I'M SURE OF IT.
>> WHAT IS THAT THING?
>> HUH?!
>> HUH?
RUN!
GET OUT OF HERE FAST!
>> [SCREAMING]
>> [GRUNTING]
THAT WAS A CLOSE CALL, HUH,
KAGOME?
>> MM-HMM.
>> HEY, IS EVERYONE SAFE OVER
THERE?
>> YES.
MORE OR LESS, ANYWAY.
>> THOUGHT I WAS A GONER THAT
TIME.
>> [GROWLS]
HE'S GONE.
>> I'M GUESSING HE'S GONNA TRY
TO MEET UP WITH HIS FORMER DEMON
MASTER.
>> LET'S GO AFTER HIM, INUYASHA.
>> YEAH.
>> JUST MY LUCK.
WHAT THE HELL DO I DO WITH THIS
ONE?
IT'S NOT EVEN BREATHING.
MAYBE IT IS ALIVE.
SO, ARE YOU BACK FROM THE DEAD?
[HEARTBEAT]
HE'S DEFINITELY ALIVE.
HE'S...
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
♪ I GET, I GET, I GET
GET A FEELING
I GET, I GET, I GET,
GET A DREAMING ♪
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
♪ COME MY WAY ♪
♪ COME CLOSE TO ME ♪
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
♪ I'LL BE WITH YOU
I'LL BE WITH YOU ♪
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
♪ SO COME MY WAY
COME MY WAY ♪
>> YOU REMOVED THE DEMON'S SEAL?
>> ENTEI HAS CHOSEN AN EVIL
CHILD AS HIS NEW MASTER.
>> MY NAME IS HAKUDOSHI,
BUT YOU PROBABLY FIGURED
THAT OUT.
I'M NARAKU'S INCARNATION.
>> WHAT IS THIS BORDER BETWEEN
THIS WORLD AND THE NEXT?
WHAT'S THERE?
>> WHAT I SAW WAS A LAND OF A
WHITE MIST.
WILL YOU JOIN IN THE SEARCH FOR
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS?
>> NEXT TIME, UNTAMED ENTEI AND
HORRIBLE HAKUDOSHI.
>> COME ON.
YOU'RE GETTING AWAY ALL THE GOOD
STUFF.