- GATHERING SHARDS OF
THE SACRED JEWEL ALONG THE WAY,
WE CONTINUE OUR JOURNEY TO
BATTLE OUR ARCH ENEMY NARAKU.
INUYASHA IS SO DENSE,
HE HASN'T NOTICED
THAT MIROKU THE MONK
AND SANGO THE DEMON SLAYER
SEEM TO HAVE FALLEN
FOR EACH OTHER.
NEITHER OF THEM ARE WILLING
TO ADMIT IT, THOUGH,
SO THEIR RELATIONSHIP
IS GOING NOWHERE FAST.
[THUNDER]
- A DEMON IS COMING!
- HUH?
- WHAT?
- [GROWLING]
- [SCREAMING]
- FIRE!
- IT'S THE ONLY CHOICE WE HAVE.
- MY LORD, THERE MUST
BE OTHER OPTIONS.
- STOP WASTING MY VALUABLE TIME.
FIND HER AND LEAVE
NO STONE UNTURNED.
- MMM!
- [HUMMING]
- [SNEEZES]
LOUSY WEATHER.
- WHY DON'T YOU USE AN UMBRELLA
TO COVER YOUR HEAD?
- HATS AND THOSE UMBRELLA
THINGS OF YOURS
ARE ONLY FOR WOMEN
AND CHILDREN.
- YOUR PRIDE IS GONNA
GET YOU A NASTY COLD.
- I'M NOT A WEAKLING
LIKE SOME PEOPLE.
- YOU JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- UNDERSTAND WHAT?
- WELL, UMBRELLAS CAN REALLY
COME IN HANDY, YOU KNOW.
- SO, YOU'RE GONNA EXPLAIN?
- OH, YOU KNOW IT.
HUH?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- SOMETHING'S COMING.
I CAN FEEL IT.
- ME, TOO.
HUMANS.
- YEP, AND LOTS OF THEM.
- WOULD YOU BE SANGO
THE DEMON SLAYER
AND HER TRAVEL PARTY?
- HUH?
- YES, THIS IS SANGO HERE.
- I AM THE VASSAL ASARTI,
REPRESENTING THE TAKETA CLAN.
WE HAVE COME TO
SPEAK WITH SANGO.
- HUH?
- I HAVE BEEN ASKED TO REQUEST
THAT YOU DESTROY A DEMON
THAT PLAGUES OUR CASTLE NIGHTLY.
WE WILL NOT QUESTION
YOUR METHODS,
AND IF NECESSARY,
WE WILL EVACUATE THE CASTLE.
CONSIDER THIS
AN ADVANCE PAYMENT.
AFTER THE DEMON IS DESTROYED,
YOU WILL RECEIVE
THE OTHER HALF OF THE SUM.
I BELIEVE THIS OFFER IS FAIR.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- BUT THAT'S FAR TOO MUCH MONEY.
- YES.
IT'S 20 TIMES WHAT
SHE NORMALLY GETS PAID.
- THEN YOU WILL ACCEPT?
- THE OFFER IS TOO GENEROUS.
SORRY, I MUST DECLINE.
- YOU CANNOT REFUSE!
IT'S BEEN FAR TOO LONG, SANGO.
- UH...
DO I KNOW YOU?
- LOOK CLOSER, SANGO.
DOESN'T HE SEEM FAMILIAR?
- HE SURE SEEMS TO KNOW YOU.
- YEAH.
- WELL, I CAN'T BLAME HER
FOR NOT REMEMBERING.
IT WAS AN AWFULLY LONG TIME AGO.
COME, LET'S RETIRE
TO THE CASTLE,
WHERE WE CAN TALK IN LEISURE
AND BECOME REACQUAINTED
WITH ONE ANOTHER.
- UM...
- HMM.
- YES! THIS IS IT!
WOW!
THIS PLACE IS INCREDIBLE.
- WHAT A FINE CASTLE!
- PLEASE ALLOW ME
TO INTRODUCE MYSELF.
I AM KURANOSUKAI TAKETA,
LORD OF THIS CASTLE.
- HE'S A LORD?
- NO WONDER HE'S SO FORMAL.
- WAIT A MINUTE.
NOW I REMEMBER.
THAT SNOTTY-NOSED LITTLE--
I MEAN, THAT YOUNG LORD.
- I'M GLAD YOU FINALLY
REMEMBER ME.
YES.
IT'S BEEN 6 LONG YEARS ALREADY.
MY CASTLE HAD BEEN
PLAGUED BY A DEMON,
AND WE HAD HIRED YOU
AND THE OTHER SLAYERS.
- [GROWLING]
- [SHOUTING]
- YOU FOUGHT
A MAGNIFICENT BATTLE.
YOU SHONE LIKE A SINGLE
WHITE LILY ON THE BATTLEFIELD.
YOU WERE ABSOLUTELY
AWE-INSPIRING.
- I WAS?
- BUT ENOUGH OF THE PAST.
I WILL GET TO THE POINT.
SANGO, SLAY THE DEMON
FOR US AT ONCE,
THEN BECOME MY WIFE.
- HUH? WHAT'S ALL THE RUSH?
- I KNEW RIGHT FROM
THE VERY MOMENT I SAW YOU.
YOU'RE THE WOMAN
WHO WILL BE MY WIFE.
SANGO, IT IS ONLY YOU.
- UH...ONLY ME?
- I HOPE YOU'LL
ACCEPT MY PROPOSAL.
SERVANTS, PREPARE ROOMS
FOR OUR HONORED GUESTS!
- YES, SIR.
- HMM.
- HOW COME SHE GETS
THE ROYAL TREATMENT?
HUH?
- SO, SHE GOT MORE FOOD THAN US.
THE LORD'S TRYING TO WOO HER,
SO YOU CAN'T BLAME HIM
FOR TREATING HER BETTER.
- WHAT'LL I DO?
HOW WILL I TURN HIM DOWN?
WAIT.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING, MIROKU?
- WOULD YOU CONSIDER
BEARING MY CHILDREN?
- [GASP]
- [GROANS]
- SURELY YOU JEST WITH ME,
MY ITINERANT MONK.
- NOT AT ALL.
I ASSURE YOU,
I'M ENTIRELY SERIOUS.
[SMACK]
YOW!
- HUH?
- HMPH!
- WHAT AN IDIOT.
- THE NERVE OF HIM,
FLIRTING LIKE THAT!
[SIGHS]
- [GRUNTS]
- HUH?
- [GASPS]
- GOOD GRIEF.
NOW, THAT HARDLY CALLED
FOR SUCH BRUTALITY.
- MIROKU, YOU CAN'T REALLY
BLAME HER FOR BEING JEALOUS
AFTER THE WAY YOU CAME
ONTO THAT OTHER WOMAN.
- NO WONDER SANGO WAS SO ANGRY.
- WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
IT'S NOT LIKE SHE'S NEVER
SEEN HIM AT IT BEFORE.
HE FLIRTS WITH PRACTICALLY
ANYTHING THAT MOVES.
- THAT'S TYPICAL.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND ANYTHING.
- LIKE WHAT, FOR INSTANCE?
- LIKE SANGO WANTS MIROKU
TO STOP HER FROM ACCEPTING.
- ACCEPTING WHAT?
- HUH?
HE GIVES "DENSE"
A WHOLE NEW MEANING.
THIS MIGHT BE A PERFECT CHANCE.
I'M SURE MIROKU'S ALREADY
CONCERNED ABOUT SANGO.
MAYBE ALL HE NEEDS IS
A LITTLE PUSH FROM ME.
[RINGING]
- CONGRATULATIONS!
YOU'RE MARRIED!
- YAY!
- [CHEERING]
- [LAUGHTER]
- IT'S PERFECT.
I GOT IT ALL FIGURED OUT.
- WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO HER?
- IT'S ANYBODY'S GUESS.
- THIS PLAN'S FAIL-PROOF.
NOW TO PUT IT INTO ACTION!
COME ON, MIROKU.
WE'VE GOT THINGS TO DO.
- KAGOME, WHAT'S GOING ON?
- JUST HURRY!
- I'M COMING!
- HUH?
- I'M GONNA HAVE TO
BE STRONG FOR THIS.
- YEAH.
- NOW, WHAT'S ALL
THE PANIC ABOUT, KAGOME?
- ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
WE'VE GOT TO DO SOMETHING,
OR SANGO MIGHT ACCEPT
LORD TAKETA'S PROPOSAL
AND WIND UP MARRIED.
- AND THAT'S A PROBLEM,
I TAKE IT?
- OF COURSE IT'S A PROBLEM!
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
LET IT HAPPEN, ARE YOU?
- IT'S A DECISION THAT SANGO
HAS TO MAKE HERSELF.
AND AS FAR AS I CAN TELL,
IT'S NONE OF OUR BUSINESS.
- HMM?
I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
ANY WOMAN'S GOOD ENOUGH FOR YOU.
YOU HAVE NO FORTUNE,
NO HOME, AND NO STATUS.
YOU'RE JUST A FLIRTATIOUS
ITINERANT MONK.
THE CLAN LORD,
ON THE OTHER HAND,
IS YOUNG, HANDSOME,
AND RICH.
HE'S HARD-WORKING AND DEDICATED,
AND WITH THAT KIND OF DEVOTION,
HE'S UNLIKELY TO STRAY
TO OTHER WOMEN.
HE IS ONE CATCH THAT
NO GIRL WOULD PASS UP.
THERE'S NO QUESTION WHO'S
THE MOST ELIGIBLE BACHELOR.
WHY SO QUIET?
OH, I BET YOU'RE NERVOUS NOW.
- IS THAT ABOUT ALL YOU
WANTED TO SAY TO ME?
- HUH?
- IF SO, THEN I'LL BE ON MY WAY,
BECAUSE THERE IS SOMETHING
THAT I WOULD LIKE
TO GO AND CHECK ON.
- HUH?
MIROKU!
- [CHOMPING]
- HMM.
- [GRUNTING]
- BUSTED!
I KNEW YOU WERE JEALOUS OF HIM!
QUIT HIDING YOUR FEELINGS
AND ADMIT THAT YOU'RE
IN LOVE WITH HER!
[LAUGHING]
- I WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN
HALF AS SURPRISED
IF SHE HADN'T LEAPED OUT
OF THE BUSHES AT ME.
- [SIGH]
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
I DON'T WANT TO HURT HIM.
- HOW CAN I PROVE
MY FEELINGS TO HER?
- [CHOMPING]
- SANGO.
- YES?
WHAT IS IT, MY LORD?
- DON'T CALL ME LORD.
PLEASE CALL ME KURANOSUKAI.
YOU CAN EVEN CALL ME
RUNNY-NOSE IF YOU'D LIKE.
HA HA HA!
JUST JOKING, OF COURSE.
- LISTEN, WE NEED TO TALK.
- SANGO...
- HUH?
- WITH THE STATE OF THE WORLD,
THERE ARE FEW PEOPLE
I CAN TRUST.
EVIL DEMONS ABOUND IN
THE MOUNTAINS AND RIVERS,
AND MORTALS RESORT
TO TRICKERY AND BETRAYAL.
SOME CALL THIS A HELL ON EARTH,
BUT I'M NOT SATISFIED TO ACCEPT
THINGS THE WAY THEY ARE.
I SWORE THAT THE WOMAN
I CHOSE TO SPEND MY LIFE WITH
WOULD BE SOMEONE I LOVED
WITH ALL MY HEART AND SOUL.
- BUT WHY DID YOU CHOOSE ME?
- I MAY BE THE LORD OF THE CLAN,
BUT I AM ALSO AN EXCELLENT
JUDGE OF CHARACTER.
SANGO, I LOVE YOU.
I TRULY LOVE YOU.
- I'M FLATTERED.
I'M HAPPY TO HEAR HOW YOU FEEL.
- HUH?
[GASP]
MIROKU!
- WOULD YOU PLEASE
BE MY WIFE, SANGO?
- NO.
SORRY, I CAN'T ACCEPT.
- BUT WHY EVER NOT?
- THERE IS SOMETHING I MUST DO
BEFORE I CAN POSSIBLY
CONSIDER MARRIAGE.
I'M CERTAIN IT WILL BE VERY
DIFFICULT TO ACCOMPLISH,
PERHAPS EVEN IMPOSSIBLE.
BUT I MUST TRY.
I MUST CARRY OUT THIS DEED,
OR ELSE I WON'T BE ABLE
TO GO FORWARD IN LIFE.
AND THAT'S WHY I MUST MOVE ON
AND CONTINUE MY JOURNEY.
PLEASE, YOU MUST FIND SOMEONE
MORE SUITABLE AS YOUR WIFE.
- NO ONE IS MORE
SUITABLE THAN YOU.
I WAITED 6 YEARS.
IT MATTERS NOT HOW MANY
MORE I WAIT FOR YOUR RETURN.
- HUH?
- SANGO, I UNDERSTAND PERFECTLY
HOW YOU FEEL RIGHT NOW,
AND SO I WILL WAIT FOREVER.
- NO, I DIDN'T MEAN--
- PLEASE COME TO ME ANYTIME
YOU REQUIRE MY ASSISTANCE.
I PROMISE I WILL DO
EVERYTHING IN MY POWER
AS A LORD TO HELP YOU.
[LAUGHING]
- NO, WAIT!
- WAIT, MIROKU!
WHY ARE YOU GOING TO LET HER GO?
AREN'T YOU GONNA
TRY AND STOP HER?
- IF SANGO'S HAPPINESS
IS OUR PRIMARY CONCERN,
THEN SHOULDN'T WE ALLOW HER
TO MAKE HER OWN DECISIONS?
- HUH?
- HER DESTINY WAS
SHATTERED BY NARAKU,
AND NOW SHE MUST
FIGHT TO SURVIVE.
SUDDENLY, SHE HAS A CHANCE
TO MARRY AND SETTLE DOWN.
WHICH LIFESTYLE DO YOU THINK
WOULD BRING HER MORE HAPPINESS?
THE ANSWER IS OBVIOUS.
- NO, WAIT!
- IT MIGHT NOT BE
CLEAR TO YOU NOW,
BUT ONE DAY,
YOU'LL UNDERSTAND.
- DON'T SANGO'S FEELINGS COME
INTO THE EQUATION HERE, MIROKU?!
[ECHOING]
- [SNORING]
[WOLF HOWLS]
- HMM?
- HUH?
[CHUCKLES]
- UH...
- I WISH YOU HAPPINESS.
- [GASPS]
- THE DEMON HAS COME!
- HUH?
- [MUTTERING]
- [GROWLING]
- AAH!
- WHAT TOOK YOU SO LONG?!
[GRUNTING]
- INUYASHA!
- IT'S ABOUT TIME.
DON'T MATTER.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF THAT DEMON
WITH ONE STRIKE OF MY SWORD.
- STAY OUT OF THIS, INUYASHA,
AND LET ME HANDLE IT.
- WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
I CAN HANDLE THAT
LITTLE DEMON ON MY OWN.
- SLAYING THAT THING IS MY JOB.
BESIDES, I WOULDN'T MIND BLOWING
OFF A LITTLE STEAM RIGHT NOW.
- UH...OK.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
DID YOU SAY SOMETHING TO HER?
- NO, NOTHING IN PARTICULAR.
- AARRGGH!
- [GRUNTING]
- [SCREAMING]
- BOY, I'VE NEVER SEEN SANGO
LOOK SO FIERCE IN BATTLE.
- I DON'T THINK THERE'S
A PERSON IN THIS WHOLE WORLD
WHO'D BE ABLE TO
DEFEAT SANGO RIGHT NOW.
- [GRUNTING]
- DON'T COME CRYING TO ME.
- UH...
THIS'LL FINISH YOU OFF!
[SCREAMING]
- [GURGLING]
- SHE DID IT!
WAY TO GO!
- HMPH.
- AH!
[GROWLING]
- MIROKU?
[GASPS]
- HE MISCALCULATED.
SANGO, WHEN I WAS
WATCHING YOU FIGHT,
I REALIZED THAT
THIS DEMON IS ACTUALLY
A GHOSTLY SPIRIT
SEEKING VENGEANCE.
IT CANNOT BE DESTROYED
IN THE USUAL WAY.
I'LL EXORCISE THIS DEMON!
- [SCREAMING]
[CREAKING]
- BEAR ORNAMENTS?
- IS THAT WHY
THE BEAR DEMON WAS SO VENGEFUL?
- NO.
IT'S NOT THAT SIMPLE.
- OH!
- TAKE A LOOK OVER THERE,
IF YOU WILL.
- HMM?
- IT'S A BEAR PELT.
- BUT THAT'S THE SAME DEMON
WE SLAYED 6 YEARS AGO.
WE TOLD YOU WAY BACK
THEN TO OFFER YOUR PRAYERS
AND THEN BURY THE THING.
- PLEASE ALLOW ME TO EXPLAIN.
WE WERE FOLLOWING
YOUR INSTRUCTIONS
AND WERE ABOUT
TO BURY THE DEMON.
SUDDENLY, THE LATE
MASTER STOPPED US
AND GAVE US NEW ORDERS.
WE WERE INSTRUCTED TO
MAKE WOODEN CARVINGS
OF THE BEAR DEMON
AND MARKET THESE TOKENS
AS OUR REGIONAL
KEEPSAKES IN AN EFFORT
TO RESTORE THE CLAN'S FINANCES.
THE WOODEN CARVINGS
WERE SOON FOLLOWED
BY THE BIG BEAR BEAN JAM CAKES,
THE BIG BEAR TOWELS,
AND THE BIG BEAR WOODEN COINS.
- DON'T TELL ME.
THEY DIDN'T SELL.
- NOT A ONE.
- KURANOSUKAI.
- NEVER MIND.
DON'T SAY ANOTHER WORD.
I THINK BY NOW I HAVE
AN EXCELLENT UNDERSTANDING
OF HOW YOU FEEL.
- HUH?
- GO ON.
YOUR FRIENDS ARE
WAITING FOR YOU.
- YES.
- SANGO, DO NOT THINK
THAT I HAVE GIVEN UP ON YOU.
- MIROKU, WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR UMBRELLA HAT?
- I'VE GOT IT.
BUT THE STRAP IS BROKEN,
I'M AFRAID.
- HMM.
- [CHUCKLES]
- HUH?
THANK YOU.
- MM-HMM.
HOW IS YOUR WOUND?
- FINE.
- UM, MIROKU?
- I'M GLAD.
- HUH?
- IT TURNS OUT WE'LL BE ABLE TO
CONTINUE OUR JOURNEY TOGETHER.
- SO WHAT ARE THEY
ALL CHUMMY ABOUT?
- I TOLD YOU UMBRELLAS
WERE CONVENIENT.
IT'S BROUGHT THEM TOGETHER,
AND LOOK HOW HAPPY THEY ARE.
- HUH?
- AWW!
- AH!
- HMM!
- [CHUCKLING]
- [GROWLING]
[LAUGHS]
- [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- HEY, DO YOU KNOW JANKEN?
- SURE.
THAT LITTLE IMP THAT'S ALWAYS
HANGING AROUND SESSHOMARU.
- NO, THAT'S JAKEN.
I'M TALKING ABOUT JANKEN,
THE GAME.
ROCK, PAPER, SCISSORS--
LIKE THIS.
1, 2, 3.
I WIN!
- THIS IS THE WEIRDEST
DAY I'VE EVER HAD.
- ROCK, PAPER, SCISSORS.
I WIN AGAIN!
- LOOK, IT'S JAKEN!
ARE THEY AFTER THE TETSUSAIGA?
NEXT TIME, "JAKEN'S PLAN
TO STEAL THE TETSUSAIGA."
- IT'S NOT JAKEN.
IT'S JANKEN--
ROCK, PAPER, SCISSORS.
- OH, BROTHER.