>> HERE WE COME.
IT'S THE START OF "INUYASHA."
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL THE
SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY NARAKU WITH
MY TETSUSAIGA.
>> IN OUR SEARCH FOR NARAKU, WE
HEAD TOWARD THE SACRED LAND OF
MOUNT HAKUREI, BUT BLOCKING OUR
WAY IS BANKOTSU, THE LEADER OF
THE BAND OF SEVEN, WHO APPEARS
BEFORE US.
>> IT'S UP TO ALL OF US.
>> TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FEUDAL FAIRY TALE.
>> INUYASHA!
[WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> HMM.
LET'S SEE.
[SIGHS]
THAT'S NO GOOD.
WAIT.
I'VE GOT IT.
"PREPARE TO DIE."
HMM.
NO, NO, NO.
DAMN IT!
>> BANKOTSU, SIR, I HAVE BROUGHT
YOU YOUR FRIENDS.
>> HEY, BANKOTSU!
>> YO!
HA HA HA!
>> SO, BIG BROTHER, WE ARE ALL
BACK TOGETHER AT LAST.
>> NOT ALL.
>> YOU SEE, THE THING IS--
>> BIG BROTHER, THE TRUTH IS
KYUKOTSU AND MUKOTSU WERE--
>> THEY WERE KILLED.
COULDN'T BE HELPED.
>> YOU KNEW ALREADY?
>> NOW RENKOTSU, YOU'RE THE
SMART ONE, SO YOU CAN WRITE.
>> SURE, BUT WRITE WHAT?
>> LET'S SEE.
"THE TIME HAS COME TO SETTLE OLD
SCORES.
OUR VENGEANCE WILL KNOW NO
BOUNDS, SO PREPARE TO DIE"...
OR SOMETHING TO THAT EFFECT.
>> DO WE GET TO KILL PEOPLE?
>> YEAH.
REMEMBER THAT CASTLE?
>> WHY?
SHOULD WE?
>> YES.
THE INHABITANTS OF THAT CASTLE
ARE THE DECEITFUL BASTARDS WHO
CHOPPED OUR HEADS OFF.
>> THAT LAST BATTLE WAS A LOT OF
FUN, WASN'T IT?
>> I LIKE IT WHEN THEY BEG FOR
MERCY.
>> GRR.
>> MAYBE THIS NEXT JOB WILL BE
JUST AS ENJOYABLE.
>> MAYBE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, BIG BROTHER?
>> WILL IT BE FUN?
>> YES, I RATHER THINK IT WILL
BE.
LOOK THERE.
THE CASTLE.
>> HMM.
>> SO, WHO IS THIS GUY?
>> HE'S THE GENERAL OF THE
SAMURAI OF THIS CASTLE.
>> YOU'RE KIDDING.
ISN'T THE LORD HIMSELF GOING TO
APPEAR?
>> MY LORD WANTS YOU TO ATTACK A
CERTAIN VILLAGE IN THE EASTERN
LANDS.
>> AS AN ADVANCE TEAM?
>> IF THE BAND OF SEVEN IS AS
GOOD AS THE RUMORS SAY, IT
SHOULD BE NO PROBLEM.
>> IF YOU MEET OUR PRICE.
>> MY LORD HAS INSTRUCTED ME TO
PAY WHATEVER YOU DEMAND.
>> THEN WE ACCEPT.
>> I'M GLAD THAT THEY HAVEN'T
BEEN WIPED OUT BY SOME OTHER
LORD OVER THE YEARS.
>> YES, OTHERWISE MY COMPANION
MIGHT NOT STILL BE THERE.
>> YOU MEAN, THEY STILL HAVE IT?
>> YEAH, AND NOW I'LL SHOW THEM
HOW IT'S USED.
>> BIG BROTHER, WILL THIS DO?
>> LET'S SEE.
>> KOHAKU!
TAKE THIS LETTER TO THE CASTLE
FOR ME.
GIVE IT TO THE LORD HIMSELF.
>> WHY ME?
>> YOU ARE A NINJA, AREN'T YOU?
>> NO, SIR, I'M NOT A NINJA.
>> WELL, THEN, WHAT ARE YOU?
>> I--
I'LL TAKE IT.
>> YOU TAKE CARE NOW, KOHAKU.
[GRUNTS]
>> HERE YOU GO.
YOU WANTED TO EAT IT, DIDN'T
YOU?
>> SORRY.
MY MISTAKE.
>> BIG BROTHER, SHOULDN'T WE BE
GETTING READY?
>> WHY DO YOU THINK I SENT THAT
LETTER?
BECAUSE I WANT TO TAKE MY TIME
AND LET THEM SQUIRM WITH FEAR.
I'LL LET THEM LOOK AFTER MY
COMPANION FOR JUST A LITTLE
LONGER.
>> IT'S EXACTLY AS LADY KIKYO
SAID IT WAS.
>> IT'S TRUE.
SHE WAS RIGHT.
MOUNT HAKUREI IS SO SERENE.
WHAT'S THE MATTER, KILALA?
KILALA?
>> SOMETHING'S WRONG WITH
SHIPPO, TOO.
>> MIROKU, WHAT DOES THIS MEAN?
>> THEY'VE BEEN EXPOSED TO THE
AURA OF THE MOUNTAIN.
LADY KIKYO TOLD US IT AFFECTS
FULL DEMONS LIKE SHIPPO AND
KILALA.
NO DOUBT INUYASHA FEELS IT, TOO.
>> INUYASHA?
>> THERE'S SOME KIND OF BARRIER
HERE.
>> YES, AND IT IS PROBABLY
INTENDED TO PROTECT THIS SACRED
PLACE.
I BELIEVE THE BARRIER IS
POWERFUL ENOUGH TO INSTANTLY
PURIFY ANY EVIL, DEMON OR
OTHERWISE.
STRANGE THAT I SHOULD FEEL IT,
TOO, A MONK UNTAINTED BY ANY
TRACE OF EVIL.
>> YEAH, BUT WE'RE FINE, AREN'T
WE?
>> YEP.
>> WHY DON'T WE JUST SEE WHO'S
UNTAINTED?
>> WAIT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
NO, PLEASE, DON'T DO THIS.
DON'T, PLEASE!
PLEASE, DON'T!
AAH!
>> LOOKS LIKE SOMEBODY'S NOT AS
PURE AS THEY THOUGHT, WOULDN'T
YOU AGREE?
>> HEY, WAIT, I JUST HAD AN
IDEA.
PERHAPS NARAKU IS TAKING
ADVANTAGE OF THIS BARRIER AND
HE'S USING IT TO PREVENT HIMSELF
FROM BEING DETECTED.
>> NO WAY.
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
NARAKU IS PURE EVIL.
HE TAKES ONE STEP ON THE
MOUNTAIN AND HE'D BE PURIFIED
IMMEDIATELY.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
THERE'S NO WAY NARAKU COULD
SURVIVE ON MOUNT HAKUREI.
>> THE BARRIER AROUND MOUNT
HAKUREI IS AMAZING, ISN'T IT?
>> YOU SAID IT.
>> SO, INUYASHA, TELL ME, WHAT
DO WE DO NOW?
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN, WHAT DO WE
DO?
>> WE KNOW NARAKU'S NOT HERE, SO
WHERE DO WE LOOK FOR HIM?
>> THE BAND OF SEVEN.
WE'LL LOOK FOR THEM.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT'S A GOOD IDEA.
WE KNOW NARAKU IS CONNECTED TO
THEM SOMEHOW.
>> ONCE WE FIND THEM, WE'LL
CAPTURE THEM, AND THEN WE'LL
MAKE THEM TELL US WHERE NARAKU
IS.
>> WELL, THEN, LET'S LEAVE THIS
PLACE QUICKLY.
SHIPPO AND KILALA SEEM TO BE IN
PAIN.
>> DO YOU THINK THAT'S TRUE?
>> HE'S THE ONLY ONE IN PAIN
AROUND HERE.
>> JUST HOW IMPURE DO YOU THINK
HE IS?
>> HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
DON'T YOU KNOW THAT IF YOUNG
FOLK LIKE YOU WANDER AROUND
HERE, THE MEN FROM THE CASTLE
WILL CAPTURE YOU?
ALL THE ABLE-BODIED PEOPLE IN
THIS AREA HAVE BEEN FORCIBLY
TAKEN TO THE CASTLE, AND THERE'S
NO EXCEPTION FOR TRAVELERS.
>> FOR WHAT REASON?
IS THERE A BIG BATTLE COMING UP?
>> NO, BUT IT SEEMS THAT A
WARNING NOTE WAS SENT TO THE
LORD OF THE CASTLE.
>> A WARNING NOTE, YOU SAY?
>> IT SAID THAT THE CASTLE
TREASURE WOULD BE TAKEN.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY CASTLE
TREASURE?
>> WELL, NO ONE REALLY KNOWS FOR
SURE, BUT NEVER MIND THAT.
YOU'D ALL BETTER HIDE OUT
SOMEWHERE.
>> OH, NO!
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> THE GENERAL FROM THE CASTLE.
>> YOU THERE, IDENTIFY
YOURSELVES.
>> ACTUALLY, WE'RE JUST HARMLESS
TRAVELERS.
>> DON'T TAKE ME FOR A FOOL.
I AM AMAZED THAT DEMONS WOULD
DARE TO WANDER WITHIN OUR
BORDERS IN BROAD DAYLIGHT.
>> YOU GOT A PROBLEM WITH ME OR
SOMETHING?
>> WHAT THE HELL DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
>> YOU'RE AN IMPERTINENT ONE,
BUT THERE WON'T BE A SECOND
CHANCE.
LEAVE THIS AREA IMMEDIATELY.
>> OH, YEAH?
>> WAIT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> I COULD TAKE HIM DOWN NO
PROBLEM.
>> DO YOU KNOW ABOUT THE BAND OF
SEVEN?
>> THE BAND OF SEVEN!
>> PLEASE, GOOD SIR, WHAT
INFORMATION CAN YOU TELL US
ABOUT THE BAND OF SEVEN?
>> THE BAND OF SEVEN WERE
MERCENARIES WHO WREAKED HAVOC ON
THESE LANDS SOME TIME AGO.
>> TELL ME SOMETHING I DON'T
KNOW.
>> THE WARRIOR WE JUST MET WAS
THE ONE RESPONSIBLE FOR
EXECUTING THE BAND OF SEVEN.
>> THAT GUY?
>> THAT MAN IS A DEVIL.
>> WHAT WILL WE DO NOW?
DO YOU THINK PERHAPS WE SHOULD
GO AND TALK TO HIM?
>> DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT IT.
IF YOU GO ANYWHERE NEAR THE
CASTLE NOW, YOU'RE ALL DONE FOR.
>> INUYASHA.
>> LOOK, THERE IT IS.
>> IT MAKES ME SICK.
>> YOU GOT THAT RIGHT.
>> I STILL REMEMBER, LIKE IT WAS
YESTERDAY.
>> TAKE THAT!
[LAUGHING]
[CHUCKLING]
>> THAT WAS EASY.
>> IT WAS OVER MUCH TOO QUICKLY.
>> YES, NO KIDDING.
>> THESE PATHETIC LORDS AND
THEIR WARRIORS ARE NO MATCH FOR
THE BAND OF SEVEN.
>> TELL ME, BIG BROTHER, DON'T
YOU THINK IT IS ABOUT TIME WE
FOUND A CASTLE OF OUR OWN TO BE
LORDS AND MASTERS OF?
THINK OF IT.
YOU COULD EVEN BECOME SHOGUN.
>> I THINK IT WOULD BE TOO MUCH
TROUBLE.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
DO YOU WISH TO BE THE LORD OF A
CASTLE, OR EVEN SHOGUN?
>> NO.
BIG BROTHER, YOU'D BE FAR BETTER
SUITED THAN I.
>> HEY, I'LL EVEN HELP YOU IF
YOU WANT ME TO.
MY OWN AMBITION IS SIMPLY TO
KILL AS MANY PEOPLE AS HUMANLY
POSSIBLE.
NOW THAT EXCITES ME.
>> YEAH, WHAT A TURN ON.
>> DON'T WORRY.
THERE ARE PLENTY OF VICTIMS FOR
EACH OF US...
AND THEN SOME.
>> HAVEN'T THEY LEARNED THEIR
LESSON YET?
>> YES.
TIME FOR MORE KILLING.
>> OK, LET'S GET TO WORK.
[MEN CHEERING]
HEY, I THOUGHT WE WERE SUPPOSED
TO BE THE ADVANCE TEAM!
>> THE BAND OF SEVEN HAS BECOME
TOO NOTORIOUS.
>> SO YOU CHANGED YOUR MIND
ABOUT PAYING US?
>> YOU ARE TOO BLOODTHIRSTY.
WHETHER YOU ACT AS FRIEND OR FOE
TO THEM, THE LORDS OF THE LAND
HAVE DECIDED THAT THE BAND OF
SEVEN HAS BECOME TOO STRONG.
>> OH, NO.
>> BROTHER BANKOTSU!
>> IF THAT IS SO, DO YOU REALLY
THINK YOU CAN DEFEAT US NOW?
>> THERE IS NOWHERE YOU CAN RUN.
THE LORDS OF THE REGION HAVE
UNITED TO SEE THAT YOU ARE
DESTROYED.
>> WHAT NOW?
>> RUN!
>> YOU ARE TOO DANGEROUS TO
ALLOW TO EXIST, EVEN IN THIS AGE
OF WARS.
>> HA!
BEFORE I WAS KILLED, I MYSELF
HAD KILLED 999 MEN.
IT'S TIME TO FINALLY EVEN THINGS
UP.
OK, THIS IS IT, MEN.
DON'T FAIL.
>> COME ON, I'D NEVER LOSE IN A
REAL BATTLE.
>> WELL, YOU BETTER NOT.
>> I WONDER WHEN WE'LL BE ABLE
TO RETURN TO OUR VILLAGE.
>> YEAH, I WANT TO GO HOME.
>> HEY!
YOU TWO GET BACK TO YOUR POSTS
IMMEDIATELY.
>> YES, SIR.
>> MY LORD, REINFORCEMENTS WILL
ARRIVE SOON.
WE'VE CONSCRIPTED THE VILLAGERS,
AND NOW I CAN ASSURE YOU THAT
THE CASTLE IS COMPLETELY SECURE.
>> I THINK YOU'RE OVERREACTING.
>> HEY, YOU!
HOLD IT!
WHO ARE YOU?
>> BUT, MY LORD, LISTEN!
GREAT ATROCITIES THOUGHT TO BE
THE WORK OF THE RESURRECTED BAND
OF SEVEN HAVE BEEN REPORTED IN
VARIOUS REGIONS.
AND WHAT OF BANRYU, OUR CLAN'S
MOST TREASURED POSSESSION?
>> HEY, I'M HERE TO TAKE BACK MY
COMPANION.
>> IT'S HIM!
>> TAKE HIM!
>> REST EASY.
THE HALBERD BANRYU IS TESTAMENT
THAT WE DESTROYED BANKOTSU, THE
LEADER OF THE BAND OF SEVEN.
WERE HE TO RETURN, WE WOULD
MERELY KILL HIM AGAIN.
[EXPLOSIONS]
>> WHAT'S THAT?
MEN, HOLD YOUR GROUND!
DO NOT ALLOW THEM TO ENTER THE
CASTLE GROUNDS!
DON'T--
DON'T PANIC.
>> TAKE THAT!
>> LORD, THEY'RE COMING.
>> JUST STAY CALM.
THEY'LL NEVER MAKE IT THIS FAR.
>> OH, THERE YOU ARE.
DID YOU GET MY LETTER?
>> IT'S YOU.
>> BUT WHAT ABOUT MY GUARDS?
>> OH, YOUR GUARDS.
I THINK THEY'RE A LITTLE HUNG UP
RIGHT NOW.
>> BUT HOW DID--
>> OK, THEN.
>> WAIT!
JUST LISTEN.
YOU'VE COME HERE TO RECLAIM THE
GREAT HALBERD, HAVE YOU NOT?
>> HEY, IT'S MY BANRYU.
>> IT'S YOURS.
TAKE IT.
>> THAT HUGE HALBERD REQUIRED 3
STRONG MEN TO CARRY IT HERE, AND
YET HE CAN PICK IT UP WITH ONE
HAND.
>> HEY, LOOK.
IT'S SO SHINY.
YOU POLISHED IT, HUH?
>> YES.
LOOK, I DON'T CARE IF YOU ARE A
SPECTER.
WILL YOU SERVE ME?
>> BUT, MY LORD...
>> BE MY NEW GENERAL, AND
TOGETHER WE SHALL CONQUER THIS
LAND.
>> HEY, COME ON, NOW.
ARE YOU SURE YOU READ MY LETTER?
>> WHAT LETTER?
>> "NO BOUNDS."
>> NO BOUNDS?
>> "OUR VENGEANCE WILL KNOW NO
BOUNDS"--
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
1,000.
>> THE FUN'S OVER FOR NOW, I
GUESS.
>> YEAH.
OOH.
IT JUST GOT FUN AGAIN.
>> I GUESS IT'S TIME FOR THE
NEXT ROUND.
>> YOU TWO, STEP ASIDE.
>> OH, YOU GOT YOUR COMPANION
BACK.
>> YEP, AND IT'S TIME TO TEST IT
OUT.
>> THE CASTLE!
>> HIM AGAIN.
HALT.
>> HEY, THERE.
IT'S BEEN AWHILE.
>> DAMN YOU.
WHAT DID YOU DO WITH OUR LORD?
>> 1,000.
>> WHAT?
>> OUR HEADS WERE CHOPPED OFF,
IF YOU'LL RECALL, SO I RETURNED
THE FAVOR.
>> A CURSE ON YOU.
>> ARE YOU READY TO FOLLOW YOUR
LORD?
>> KILL THEM!
>> I FEEL EVEN BETTER THAN WHEN
I WAS ALIVE.
>> I SENSE A JEWEL SHARD!
>> NOT ONLY THAT, I SMELL
GUNPOWDER AND LOTS OF BLOOD.
THERE'S NO MISTAKE.
THE BAND OF SEVEN ARE UP AHEAD.
>> NOT A SINGLE PERSON LEFT
ALIVE?
THAT'S RATHER INCONVENIENT.
YOU WEREN'T REALLY THINKING,
WERE YOU, JUKOTSU?
YOU COULD HAVE AT LEAST KEPT A
WOMAN OR TWO ALIVE TO POUR OUR
DRINKS.
>> HOW COULD I THINK OF LITTLE
THINGS LIKE THAT, BIG BROTHER?
I'VE GOT MUCH MORE IMPORTANT
THINGS TO WORRY ABOUT, LIKE WHEN
AM I GOING TO SEE MY BELOVED
INUYASHA AGAIN?
>> YOU MUSTN'T WORRY, JUKOTSU.
INUYASHA HAS A KEEN SENSE OF
SMELL.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
ALL WE NEED TO DO IS SIT
PATIENTLY AND INUYASHA WILL
FOLLOW THE SCENT OF BLOOD RIGHT
TO US.
>> YOU THINK SO?
WELL, I GUESS WE JUST WAIT,
THEN.
>> BIG BROTHER, ARE YOU NOT
WORRIED ABOUT NARAKU?
>> WHAT ABOUT HIM?
>> WHY DO YOU THINK HE BROUGHT
US BACK FROM THE DEAD?
>> TO HELP HIM GET RID OF HIS
ENEMIES, SUCH AS THE ONES NAMED
INUYASHA AND KOUGA, THAT'S WHY.
>> BIG BROTHER, YOU'RE THE ONLY
ONE OF THE BAND OF SEVEN WHO'S
MET NARAKU.
DO YOU THINK YOU COULD TELL US A
LITTLE BIT MORE ABOUT WHAT HE'S
ACTUALLY LIKE?
>> LISTEN, RENKOTSU.
WE'VE BEEN RESURRECTED AND WE
CAN WREAK HAVOC JUST LIKE THE
GOOD OLD DAYS.
ISN'T THAT GOOD ENOUGH FOR YOU?
>> YES.
BIG BROTHER IS DETERMINED NOT TO
TELL ME ANYTHING MORE THAN HE
ALREADY HAS.
WHY?
>> INUYASHA, I REALLY HOPE YOU
GET HERE SOON.
>> SOME KIND OF WHIRLWIND.
>> I ASSUME YOU ARE THE BAND OF
SEVEN.
>> OH, HEY THERE, KOUGA.
>> WELL, WELL, WELL.
SO THE WOLF GETS HERE BEFORE THE
DOG, I SEE.
>> QUIT ACTING SO SMUG.
I KNOW FOR A FACT YOU'RE IN
CAHOOTS WITH NARAKU.
SO TELL ME WHERE HE IS.
>> GEE, IT SEEMS THAT THIS
NARAKU CHARACTER HAS MADE
ENEMIES OF A LOT OF PEOPLE.
>> TELL ME WHERE HE IS!
>> IT REALLY MAKES ME WONDER, DO
YOU THINK HE CAN BE TRUSTED?
>> WHY ARE YOU ASKING ME?
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE WHO'S MET
HIM, BANKOTSU.
>> IF YOU REFUSE TO TELL ME,
I'LL KILL YOU!
>> RIGHT, I NEARLY FORGOT.
WE STILL HAVE A MATCH TO FINISH.
>> NICE TRY.
I ALREADY KNOW ABOUT THAT
SNAKEBITE SWORD OF YOURS, AND IT
AIN'T GOING TO WORK!
>> DAMN.
HE AVOIDED THE SHOT.
>> HEY, YOU'RE A QUICK ONE,
AREN'T YOU?
I THINK IT MUST BE BECAUSE OF
THE SHIKON JEWEL SHARDS IN YOUR
LEGS.
>> WHAT DID YOU--
>> THAT REMINDS ME.
NARAKU ASKED ME IF I WOULD TAKE
THOSE FOR HIM.
>> THIS GUY...
>> I DON'T GET IT.
THERE'S SOMETHING DIFFERENT
ABOUT THIS ONE.
>> HEY, EVERYONE, DON'T LET HIM
GET AWAY!
>> QUIT JUMPING AROUND!
>> MOVE, YOU WIMPY WOLF!
>> WELL, WELL.
FOUND YOU.
[WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> I'M GOING TO AVENGE THE
DEATHS OF MUKOTSU AND KYUKOTSU.
>> SO YOU'RE THE LEADER OF THE
BAND OF SEVEN.
>> BE CAREFUL, INUYASHA.
BANKOTSU HAS 3 SACRED JEWEL
SHARDS IN HIS NECK.
>> IF YOU WANT TO KNOW WHERE
NARAKU'S HIDEOUT IS, ASK MY
BANRYU.
>> WHILE THE BAND OF SEVEN
ATTACK US, NARAKU MAKES HIS
APPEARANCE.
>> SESSHOMARU?
SHOULD I KILL HIM, TOO?
>> NEXT ON "INUYASHA," THE BIG
CLASH: BANRYU VERSUS THE WIND
SCAR.
>> "SMELL OF WATER AND FLOWERS?"
WHAT DO THEY MEAN?