>> IT ALL STARTED WITH
THE SACRED TREE.
>> FIGHTING AND SEARCHING
FOR OUR DREAMS.
>> A STRONG BOND FORMS
BETWEEN US.
>> A NEW HOPE,
A BRIGHT FUTURE BEGINS NOW.
>> A BATTLE TO THE DEATH
IN THE NETHERWORLD.
NARAKU HAS SEALED OFF THE PATH
BACK HOME.
AND JUST WHEN IT LOOKS LIKE
WE'LL NEVER MAKE IT
OUT OF HERE ALIVE,
SESSHOMARU SHOWS UP.
>> THE FINAL JEWEL SHARD
GUIDES US.
>> ON THE OTHER SIDE OF
THE WELL, A NEW DAY AWAITS.
>> FEUDAL FAIRY TALE.
"INUYASHA."
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> UH--UH!
[GRUNTING]
>> HEH HEH HEH HEH.
FINALLY, I HAVE IT IN
MY GRASP--THE LAST SHARD
OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> THE LAST SHARD?
UH!
AAH--UH!
>> DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND,
INUYASHA?
IT'S ALL OVER.
HMM?
>> HUH?
WHAT WAS THAT?
>> SESSHOMARU.
>> SESSHOMARU?
>> UH!
[GRUNTING]
>> OH!
>> VERMIN.
>> DAMN IT.
>> YOUNG ONE.
DO YOU STILL HAVE
THE STRENGTH TO FIGHT?
>> HUH?
>> HUH!
>> HAH, YOU'RE STRONGER
THAN INUYASHA.
I'LL SAY THAT MUCH FOR YOU.
>> INCREDIBLE!
EVEN THE FORCE OF
LORD SESSHOMARU'S SWORD WAS
NOT ABLE TO BREAK THROUGH
NARAKU'S BARRIER.
HUH?
>> UNLESS SOMETHING IS DONE,
THE IMPURE SHARD WILL
BE ASSIMILATED INTO
THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> HAH!
YEAH, THAT MUCH WE FIGURED OUT
ON OUR OWN.
>> SLAY ME BEFORE THAT HAPPENS.
>> HUH?
>> YOU MUST SLAY ME IN ORDER TO
BREAK THROUGH NARAKU'S BARRIER.
>> MASTER HOSENKI!
DOES THAT MEAN YOU WILL PASS ON
YOUR DEMONIC POWERS TO
INUYASHA'S TETSUSAIGA?
>> THAT'S RIGHT!
TETSUSAIGA GAINS AN ADDITIONAL
DEMONIC POWER EACH TIME IT SLAYS
A STRONG DEMON.
[GROWLS]
>> THE BLADE IS TURNING RED!
>> STILL.
>> WHAT ABOUT YOU, THOUGH?
WHAT'LL HAPPEN IF I CUT
YOU DOWN?
>> DO YOU HAVE THE LUXURY TO
BE WORRYING ABOUT THE OTHERS?
BESIDES...
>> AH!
LOOK AT HOSENKI'S HEAD!
>> IT'S BEING COVERED
BY ADAMANT.
>> IF YOU ARE NOT WORTHY OF
POSSESSING THE SHARD,
YOU WILL BE UNABLE TO SLAY ME.
INSTEAD, YOU WILL PAY WITH YOUR
LIFE--HERE AND NOW.
>> OH!
>> DO YOU HAVE THE RESOLVE
TO DO IT?
>> WELL, THAT MAKES ME FEEL A
LITTLE BETTER ABOUT DOING THIS.
>> WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
>> HE'S PREPARED TO DIE TRYING?
>> GET OUT OF THE WAY, YOU GUYS.
>> INUYASHA!
>> HERE I COME!
[GROWLS]
UH!
AAH!
[GRUNTING]
>> INUYASHA!
>> HE'S BEEN CUT BY
ADAMANT SHARDS!
>> I DIDN'T EVEN MAKE A CRACK.
>> [LAUGHING]
SESSHOMARU, DO YOU WISH TO
DESTROY ME THAT BADLY?
IN THAT CASE, YOUR WISH SHALL
BE GRANTED.
>> AAH!
NARAKU'S OUT!
HE'S OUTSIDE THE BARRIER!
[HISSES]
LOOK OUT, LORD SESSHOMARU!
[GROWLS]
>> AAH--UH!
AAH!
>> INUYASHA!
>> [GROWLS]
>> THERE ISN'T A SCRATCH ON HIM!
>> MAYBE SOMEONE SHOULD HELP.
>> WHAT'S WRONG, INUYASHA?
YOU TOLD ME YOU HAD THE RESOLVE.
>> SHUT UP, HOSENKI.
I'LL LET YOU KNOW IF
I NEED REMINDING.
I AIN'T QUITTING TILL THIS
IS DONE.
UH!
>> HEH HEH HEH HEH.
>> AAH!
NO, LORD SESSHOMARU!
UH-OH.
>> [YELLS]
UH!
>> OK.
FINE BY ME.
>> NO, INUYASHA!
STOP ALREADY!
>> DON'T DO IT!
>> YOUR BODY CAN'T TAKE
MUCH MORE OF THIS!
>> SHUT UP, WOULD YA?
I SAID I WAS READY TO DO THIS,
SO LEAVE ME ALONE!
>> YES, BUT--
>> STAND BACK AND WATCH.
>> INUYASHA!
>> [SIGHS]
UH--
>> AAH!
>> HUH?
>> [WHIMPERS]
>> GET BACK!
IT'S A MIASMA!
>> KAGOME!
>> YEAH!
>> AH--AH!
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> HAH, YOU'RE NOT DELUDED
ENOUGH TO THINK THIS PATHETIC
MIASMA WOULD HAVE ANY EFFECT
ON ME.
>> HA HA.
NO MATTER IF IT DOESN'T.
>> [WHIMPERS]
>> GET BACK, YOU GUYS!
I'LL PURIFY THE MIASMA, UH!
>> I CAN BREATHE AGAIN.
THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
>> WHAT NOW, SESSHOMARU?
THE MIASMA WILL INCREASE
EVERY TIME YOU CUT MY BODY,
AND EVERYONE IN THIS AREA
WILL PERISH...
WITHOUT FAIL.
>> UH!
>> AAH!
LORD SESSHOMARU!
>> IT'S ALL RIGHT NOW.
AS LONG AS WE HAVE KAGOME'S
ARROWS, I AIN'T AFRAID OF
ANY MIASMA.
>> I'M OUT OF ARROWS, ACTUALLY.
[SCREAMING]
>> THE ARROW I JUST USED WAS
MY LAST ONE.
>> WAIT--LOOK!
THERE'S ANOTHER ONE RIGHT IN
YOUR QUIVER!
>> THAT ONE'S...NO GOOD.
KIKYO'S ARROW IS REJECTING ME.
>> NARAKU.
>> HMM?
>> IS THAT ALL YOU HAVE
TO SAY TO ME?
YOU SEEM TO THINK THAT
I WOULD HOLD BACK MY SWORD
FOR THE SAKE OF HUMANS.
>> I'M NOT NEARLY SO
SENTIMENTAL.
>> HUH?
>> OH, I KNEW IT!
>> THE MIASMA IS COMING!
>> BACK UP OUT OF THE WAY,
YOU GUYS.
I'LL GET RID OF THE MIASMA.
>> INUYASHA!
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER, BOY?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE GOING
TO SLAY ME AND STRENGTHEN
YOUR SWORD.
>> HAH!
SHUT UP!
I'LL GET BACK TO YOU LATER.
>> AH!
INUYASHA, HAS SEEING YOUR
COMRADES IN DANGER MADE YOU
FORGET ABOUT YOUR RESOLVE?
FOOL.
>> HA HA HA HA.
SO IT DOESN'T MATTER TO YOU
IF EVERYONE DIES?
WELL, YOU'RE SHOWING YOUR TRUE
COLORS AS A FULL-BLOODED DEMON,
SESSHOMARU.
YOUR HEART IS UNLIKE THE OTHERS.
>> MY HEART HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH THIS.
NARAKU, YOU WILL BE DEFEATED
TODAY BY MY OWN HAND.
NOTHING ELSE MATTERS.
>> [GROWLS]
>> ARE THE LIVES OF YOUR
COMRADES MORE IMPORTANT THAN
STRENGTHENING YOUR SWORD?
IS THAT BECAUSE YOU ARE
A MERE HALF-DEMON?
>> I AM WHAT I AM,
AND I'LL DO THINGS
THE WAY I WANT TO.
>> INUYASHA, EVEN IF YOU
OBTAINED MY DEMONIC POWERS,
WOULD YOU BE ABLE TO CONTROL
THEM?
>> SHUT UP!
MAYBE I DON'T WANT 'EM
AFTER ALL!
YOU CAN KEEP YOUR GREAT
DEMONIC POWERS.
I'LL PASS!
>> INUYASHA!
>> I'M GONNA FOCUS ON WHAT
HAS TO BE DONE RIGHT NOW.
NOTHING ELSE MATTERS TO ME!
WIND SCAR!
HUH?
WHAT THE--
>> EVEN IF HE DOES USE
THE WIND SCAR TO DISSIPATE
THE MIASMA...
IMPOSSIBLE!
THESE ARE HOSENKI'S SPEARS
OF ADAMANT!
>> LOOK!
NARAKU'S BARRIER HAS BEEN
SHATTERED!
>> THE TETSUSAIGA.
>> IT'S TRANSFORMED!
>> THINGS WOULD HAVE ENDED
DIFFERENTLY IF YOU HAD BEEN
MOTIVATED BY GREED, DESIRING
ONLY TO STRENGTHEN YOUR SWORD.
THAT SHOWER OF ADAMANT SPLINTERS
WOULD HAVE TAKEN YOUR LIFE.
>> HUH?
>> NOW HOSENKI'S
SPLITTING APART!
>> INUYASHA, PRESERVE YOUR
SPIRIT OF A HALF-DEMON
AND INHERENT MY POWER--
THE ADAMANT BARRAGE.
>> NARAKU, YOU WON'T ESCAPE!
ADAMANT BARRAGE!
>> HE DID IT!
>> THAT'S REALLY GOTTA HURT!
>> CURSE YOU--UH!
>> I SEE YOU NO LONGER HAVE
THE STRENGTH TO PUT UP
A BARRIER.
IT LOOKS LIKE THAT ARROGANCE
OF YOURS WILL TURN OUT TO BE
YOUR DOWNFALL.
AND NOW I SHALL DELIVER
THE FINISHING BLOW.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> DID HE DO IT?
>> NO, NOT YET.
>> HUH?
>> HE'S DISAPPEARING.
>> KIKYO'S ARROW.
>> OH, NO!
>> NARAKU IS GETTING AWAY!
>> THERE'S A JEWEL SHARD AMONG
THE PIECES OF HIS FLESH.
DOES THIS MEAN I SHOULD USE
IT NOW?
I CAN SHOOT THIS ARROW.
I HAVE TO DO IT.
THIS IS IT.
THIS 1 ARROW CAN FINISH NARAKU.
NO--IT CAN PUT AN END
TO EVERYTHING!
UH!
GO!
>> OH!
>> A SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
>> WHAT ABOUT NARAKU?
>> HE'S GONE.
>> KIKYO'S ARROW WENT AFTER
NARAKU, AND IT DISAPPEARED
AS WELL.
>> IF NARAKU WERE TO DIE
AT THIS BORDER TO THE AFTERLIFE,
NOW THAT WOULD BE SOMETHING
TO CELEBRATE.
I GUESS THAT WOULD BE WISHING
FOR TOO MUCH.
IT'S A BARRIER.
KOHAKU, TELL ME,
WHAT'S GOING ON WITH HAKUDOSHI?
RIGHT, I GUESS THERE'S NO POINT
IN ASKING YOU.
>> KAGURA, WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN
ALL THIS TIME?
>> YOU'RE AWAKE, ARE YOU?
>> ANSWER ME.
>> I WAS TAKING A BREATHER.
IT'S TIRING BEING WITH YOU
EVERY SINGLE MINUTE OF THE DAY.
>> HUH?
>> NARAKU!
>> [WHIMPERS]
>> EVEN AFTER ALL THIS,
NARAKU STILL WON'T DIE.
>> THIS ARROW.
KAGOME WAS THE ONE WHO SHOT IT,
BUT ITS SPIRITUAL POWER BELONGS
TO KIKYO.
HAKUDOSHI'S BARRIER CONNECTED
ME TO THIS WORLD.
IF I'D BEEN SHOT A MOMENT
SOONER, I WOULD NOT HAVE BEEN
ABLE TO RETURN.
HA HA HA HA.
I GUESS I HAVEN'T RUN OUT
OF LUCK JUST YET.
>> HOSENKI, I'M GOING TO TAKE
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
>> DO AS YOU PLEASE.
INUYASHA, I WAS UNABLE TO
PROTECT THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
I DIDN'T THINK THAT ANYTHING
EVIL WOULD COME THIS FAR IN
ITS PURSUIT.
I WAS NOT ABLE TO PUT AN END
TO THE FIGHTING OVER
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
>> IT WON'T END YET,
NOT UNTIL THE SACRED JEWEL
IS GONE FOR GOOD.
I HAVE NO IDEA HOW TO RID THE
WORLD OF THE JEWEL OF 4 SOULS.
THE ONLY THING I CAN DO IS
FIGHT EVIL DEMONS LIKE NARAKU
WHO PURSUE IT.
SO UNTIL NARAKU'S DEAD,
UNTIL THERE'S NO ONE LEFT
WHO COVETS THE JEWEL,
I'LL KEEP FIGHTING THEM.
>> MMM.
INSTEAD OF PROTECTING
THE SHARD,
INSTEAD OF RUNNING AWAY,
YOU CHOOSE TO FIGHT?
THEN RETURN TO YOUR WORLD.
IF YOU LINGER,
THE GATE WILL CLOSE.
>> CLOSE?
MASTER INUYASHA, YOU MUST
GO AFTER LORD SESSHOMARU!
HURRY!
>> DID YOU HEAR THAT?
>> YEAH.
I'M COMING.
>> NOW GET OUT OF HERE,
HALF-DEMON.
>> RIGHT.
LET'S GO, PEOPLE!
>> YEAH!
>> I WON'T LET GO!
LORD SESSHOMARU, PLEASE WAIT!
LORD SESSHOMARU!
>> PIPE DOWN AND QUIT MAKING
SUCH A FUSS.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER, SANGO?
YOU SEEM SORT OF BLUE.
>> MIROKU, YOU HEARD INUYASHA.
THAT UNTIL THE SACRED JEWEL
DISAPPEARS,
THE FIGHTING OVER IT WON'T END.
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
>> YOU'RE THINKING ABOUT
YOUR LITTLE BROTHER KOHAKU.
>> KOHAKU'S LIFE IS LINKED TO
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD EMBEDDED
IN HIS BACK.
WHEN THE SACRED JEWEL IS GONE,
KOHAKU'S LIFE WILL GO WITH IT.
>> NARAKU IS ALIVE,
BUT HIS BARRIER WAS DESTROYED,
AND HIS BODY WAS TORN TO SHREDS.
WHERE IS IT?
WHERE IS HIS HEART?
>> IS SOMETHING THE MATTER,
INUYASHA?
>> NAH.
IT'S NOTHING, REALLY.
>> [MUSIC]
>> HAKUDOSHI CAUSES
THE DEMON RATS TO GO ON
A RAMPAGE WHILE KOHAKU WATCHES.
>> THE RATS WILL SCATTER
AND RAVAGE THE HUMAN VILLAGES.
SOON THEY'LL DEVOUR
THIS ENTIRE LAND.
>> BUT THE RATS SOON BEGIN
TO CONGREGATE!
>> MAYOSE, A SPELL THAT LURES
THEM TOGETHER AND DESTROYS THEM.
THERE'S ONLY 1 PERSON WHOSE
SPIRITUAL POWER IS STRONG ENOUGH
TO CAST SUCH A SPELL.
>> NEXT TIME,
STAMPEDE OF THE COUNTLESS
DEMON RATS.
>> KIKYO'S JUST AHEAD OF
THE RAT STAMPEDE?