>> IT ALL STARTED WITH THE
SACRED TREE...
>> FIGHTING AND SEARCHING FOR
OUR DREAMS.
>> A STRONG BOND FORMS BETWEEN
US!
>> A NEW HOPE, A BRIGHT FUTURE
BEGINS NOW.
>> THE BIRD MASTER, PRINCESS
ABI, BETRAYS NARAKU AND ENGAGES
US IN A FIERCE 3-WAY BATTLE.
AND NOW THAT KIKYO HAS
HEALED, HER REUNION WITH
INUYASHA DRAWS NEAR.
>> THE FINAL JEWEL SHARD GUIDES
US.
>> ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE
WELL, A NEW DAY AWAITS.
>> FEUDAL FAIRY TALE: INUYASHA!
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
[GRUNTS, SNIFFS]
>> THE SCENT OF THOSE BIRDS.
THAT MEANS WE MUST BE CLOSE TO
THE NEST.
HUH?
THEY'RE KIKYO'S SHIKIGAMI.
>> LADY KIKYO AWAITS.
>> SHE WAITS FOR YOU.
>> HEY, STOP!
WAIT UP!
>> WHAT ARE THOSE LIGHTS?
>> KIKYO!
[GRUNTING]
HUH?
HEY, THOSE ARE...
SOUL COLLECTORS.
IT'S KIKYO.
>> INUYASHA.
>> HOW ARE YOU FEELING, KIKYO?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT NOW?
>> I'M SURE YOU HEARD WHAT
HAPPENED.
NARAKU'S MIASMA WAS CONSUMING MY
BODY UNTIL IT WAS PURIFIED BY
KAGOME.
>> YEAH, I HEARD.
KIKYO, SHE LOOKS LIKE SHE'S
STILL IN PAIN.
SHE'S NOT COMPLETELY HEALED YET.
>> INUYASHA, YOU MUST HAVE
NOTICED THIS YOURSELF.
THE BARRIER AROUND THE NEST HAS
VANISHED.
>> I GET IT.
NO WONDER I COULD SMELL THOSE
BIRD DEMONS.
>> INUYASHA, WHAT DO YOU THINK
NARAKU'S TRYING TO ACCOMPLISH?
>> HE'S TRYING TO GET TO THE
BORDER BETWEEN THIS WORLD AND
THE AFTERLIFE IN ORDER TO GET
THE LAST SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
>> SO THAT'S WHY HE USED THE
BIRDS TO GATHER HUMAN BLOOD.
IF THAT'S THE CASE, THE PATH TO
THE NETHERWORLD WILL SOON OPEN
AND NARAKU WILL GET THE JEWEL.
>> INUYASHA DID?
>> YES.
I SAW HIM FOLLOWING AFTER 2
YOUNG CHILDREN.
>> 2 YOUNG CHILDREN?
THOSE 2!
INUYASHA WENT TO SEE KIKYO!
>> INUYASHA, YOU AND YOUR
FRIENDS INTEND TO GO THE BORDER
BETWEEN THIS WORLD AND THE NEXT.
>> YEAH, OF COURSE WE'RE GOING
THERE.
WE'RE NOT GONNA LET SOMEONE LIKE
NARAKU GET HIS HANDS ON THE LAST
SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
>> LISTEN, DO NOT TAKE KAGOME
WITH YOU.
>> HUH?
WHY SHOULDN'T I TAKE HER?
>> NARAKU REMOVED THE BARRIER
AROUND THE NEST FOR A REASON: TO
LURE YOU AND ALL YOUR FRIENDS
INTO HIS TRAP.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> NARAKU'S AFTER KAGOME'S EYES.
>> HUH?
YOU MEAN HER POWER TO SEE THE
JEWEL SHARDS.
RIGHT.
>> I'M ALMOST CERTAIN THAT
NARAKU WANTS TO LURE YOU TO THE
BORDER BETWEEN THE 2 WORLDS AND
THEN USE KAGOME TO LOCATE THE
LAST SHARD.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> I WILL DEAL WITH NARAKU.
>> WHAT?
KIKYO, WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
BE CAREFUL.
YOU'RE NOT FULLY HEALED YET.
YOU CAN'T GO IN YOUR CONDITION.
>> I KNOW I CAN DO THIS.
MY SPIRITUAL POWERS HAVEN'T
WEAKENED.
>> DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
NARAKU WILL KILL YOU FOR
CERTAIN.
YOU KNOW BETTER THAN THAT.
NARAKU WANTS YOU DEAD.
THAT HASN'T CHANGED.
LISTEN, KIKYO, I MESSED UP BIG
TIME.
WHEN YOU WERE ATTACKED AT MOUNT
HAKURE, I WASN'T ABLE TO PROTECT
YOU.
I REFUSE TO GIVE NARAKU A SECOND
CHANCE TO TAKE YOUR LIFE.
I NEVER WANT TO GO THROUGH THAT
AGAIN.
>> I'LL ONLY BE A BURDEN TO YOU.
IS THAT WHAT YOU MEAN?
>> COME ON, KIKYO.
I'M BEGGING YOU.
PLEASE JUST STAY HERE AND WAIT
FOR ME.
PLEASE, KIKYO!
>> THE ARROWS.
TAKE THIS WITH YOU.
PLEASE, GIVE THIS ARROW TO
KAGOME.
ONLY KAGOME HERSELF CAN
DETERMINE WHETHER OR NOT SHE
WILL BE ABLE TO USE IT.
[THUNDERING]
>> MIROKU, LOOK AT THE SKY.
DOESN'T IT SEEM STRANGE TO YOU?
>> YES.
KEEP ON WATCHING.
>> THEY'RE DEMONS.
>> THEY'RE NARAKU'S DEMONS...
AND THEY'RE HEADING SOMEWHERE
WITH A PURPOSE.
>> OH, GREAT.
THE ONE TIME WE NEED INUYASHA
AROUND.
I WONDER WHERE HE WENT ANYWAY.
>> HE'S BEEN OUT ALL NIGHT, AND
HE'S STILL NOT BACK.
>> YOU KNOW THOSE SHIKIGAMI THAT
INUYASHA WENT AFTER?
>> I KNOW.
I'M PRETTY SURE THEY WERE
KIKYO'S.
OH, BROTHER.
TALK ABOUT TERRIBLE TIMING.
>> THIS CAN'T BE A GOOD THING.
>> NOPE.
>> WE'VE GOT A PROBLEM ON OUR
HANDS.
>> HMM?
[THUNDERING]
[SIGH]
>> LOOK AT KAGOME.
SHE SEEMS SO INTENSE.
>> HMM.
I'VE GOT TO KEEP IT TOGETHER FOR
EVERYONE.
>> SO I WAS RIGHT AFTER ALL.
HE WANTED TO SEE HER ALONE.
STILL, HE DIDN'T HAVE TO SNEAK
OFF TO HER LIKE THAT.
HMM?
>> HEY, KAGOME.
>> YEAH?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> IT'S INUYASHA.
>> UH-OH.
HERE COMES THE FIGHT.
>> I REALLY HOPE HE DOESN'T GO
AND SAY SOMETHING STUPID TO HER.
>> I WENT TO SEE KIKYO LAST
NIGHT.
>> HUH?
>> HE CAME RIGHT OUT AND
ADMITTED IT!
>> AS IF SHE DIDN'T KNOW
ALREADY.
>> WHAT AN IDIOT.
>> SO, WHAT ABOUT IT?
>> SHE TOLD ME TO GIVE THIS TO
YOU.
>> AN ARROW?
HEY, THIS IS KIKYO'S.
>> IT'S BEEN RUBBED WITH DIRT
FROM ONIGUMO'S CAVE.
SHE SAID IT SHOULD WORK ON
NARAKU.
>> OK, AND...?
>> AND WHAT?
>> COME ON, INUYASHA.
KAGOME WANTS TO KNOW WHAT
HAPPENED BETWEEN YOU AND KIKYO.
STOP PLAYING GAMES.
>> I'M NOT PLAYING GAMES WITH
ANYONE.
REALLY!
ALL I DID WAS SEE HER.
I JUST...
I JUST WANTED TO SEE FOR MYSELF
THAT SHE WAS ALIVE.
THAT'S ALL THERE IS TO TELL.
>> IS THAT REALLY ALL?
>> ARE YOU UPSET, KAGOME?
>> NOT REALLY.
I TRUST YOU, INUYASHA.
>> THANKS, KAGOME.
>> AND THAT'S WHY...
>> THAT'S WHY WHAT?
>> I WANT YOU TO TELL ME
HONESTLY WHAT HAPPENED.
>> SHE DOESN'T BELIEVE ME AND
SHE'S ANGRY.
>> IT'S UP TO ME TO KEEP THINGS
TOGETHER.
[THUNDERING]
>> ARE THOSE NARAKU'S DEMONS
LAUNCHED, SESSHOMARU?
>> IT'S VERY FAINT, BUT I SMELL
IT MIXED IN WITH THE SCENT OF
THE BIRD DEMONS.
I SMELL NARAKU'S EVIL AURA.
LET'S GO.
>> YES, MY LORD.
I WILL FOLLOW YOU ANYWHERE.
OH, WAIT!
WAIT FOR ME, LORD SESSHOMARU.
>> NARAKU REMOVED THE BARRIER
AROUND THE BIRD DEMON'S NEST?
>> YEAH, HE DID.
AND NOW IT REEKS WITH THE SMELL
OF BIRDS.
>> IT'S KAGOME'S EYES THAT
NARAKU IS AFTER.
>> LOOK, KAGOME, WHEN WE GET TO
THE NETHERWORLD, YOU MAY FACE
MORE DANGER.
EVEN MORE THAN THE REST OF US.
>> WHAT'S THE POINT OF TELLING
ME THAT NOW?
WITHOUT ME, YOU CAN'T EVEN FIND
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
AM I RIGHT?
>> NARAKU REMOVED THE BARRIER
FROM THE NEST TO LURE YOU INTO
HIS TRAP.
>> EVEN IF THIS IS ONE OF
NARAKU'S TRAPS, I WON'T LET IT
GO HIS WAY.
DON'T WORRY, KAGOME.
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE BESIDE YOU.
I'LL DO WHATEVER IT TAKES TO
PROTECT YOU FROM NARAKU.
>> THANKS.
I KNOW YOU WILL, INUYASHA.
>> HUH?
THAT SCENT.
IT DEFINITELY BELONGS TO NARAKU.
>> AND HE'S CLOSE.
I SENSE A SACRED JEWEL SHARD
NEARBY.
>> DAMN THAT NARAKU.
HE'S AT THE DEMON BIRD'S NEST.
>> WHY, NARAKU.
I NEVER THOUGHT YOU'D COME
LOOKING FOR A FIGHT.
HAVE YOU COME TO PAY ME BACK FOR
DESTROYING YOUR CASTLE?
>> PRINCESS ABI, I UNDERSTAND
YOUR BIRDS SUCKED OUT EVERY LAST
DROP OF HUMAN BLOOD AT THE
CASTLE.
>> THEY CERTAINLY DID.
AND NOW MY MOTHER HAS BEEN
COMPLETELY CURED.
>> IS THAT SO?
>> NARAKU, MY MOTHER IS
INTRIGUED.
SHE SAYS SHE WANTS TO MEET YOU.
[LAUGHING]
[BIRDS CRYING, THUNDER]
>> IT IS FINALLY OPENING, THE
PATH TO THE BORDER BETWEEN THIS
WORLD AND THE NEXT.
>> HA HA, NARAKU.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
SCHEMING USING US LIKE THIS.
UNFORTUNATELY FOR YOU, THOUGH,
WE NO LONGER NEED YOU.
[CACKLING]
NARAKU, IT SEEMS YOU CHOSE THE
WRONG PEOPLE TO MANIPULATE.
DIE!
>> AH, THAT WAS EASY.
>> YOUR AIM LEAVES MUCH TO BE
DESIRED.
>> HUH?
>> DON'T UNDERESTIMATE ME,
NARAKU.
YOUR ATTACKS MIGHT DESTROY SOME,
BUT THEY WON'T WORK ON US!
>> THIS WILL FINISH YOU OFF!
[LOW LAUGH]
>> SMALLER FLAMES LIKE THAT
WON'T BRING DOWN MY BARRIER.
>> NO?
I'LL DEVOUR BOTH YOU AND YOUR
BARRIER!
>> NARAKU, IS THAT THE EXTENT OF
YOUR STRENGTH?
>> ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
>> NARAKU'S ALREADY AT THE BIRD
DEMON'S NEST?
>> I'M POSITIVE.
IT'S DEFINITELY HIS STENCH.
>> NARAKU REMOVED THE BARRIER
AROUND THE NEST AND DIDN'T SEND
KAGRO OR HAKUDOSHI, BUT WENT
HIMSELF.
>> SOMETHING'S HAPPENING.
WAIT A MINUTE.
THE PATH TO THE BORDER OF THE
AFTERLIFE MUST BE ABOUT TO OPEN.
>> I'M NOT SURE, BUT IT
DEFINITELY LOOKS THAT WAY.
>> WHO CARES WHAT NARAKU IS
SCHEMING?
WHAT DOES IT MATTER?
AS LONG AS WE DEFEAT HIM, IT'LL
BE ALL OVER.
>> MASTER!
>> MYOGA, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
HERE?
>> INUYASHA, IS IT TRUE THAT
NARAKU IS AT PRINCESS ABI'S
NEST?
>> YEAH.
I'M POSITIVE.
>> THIS NOT GOOD.
TEKKEI WILL BE THERE.
>> WHO THE HELL IS THAT?
>> MYOGA, TELL US.
WHO IS THIS TEKKEI?
>> TEKKEI BELONGS TO A GROUP OF
BIRDS THAT LIVE IN HELL.
IN OTHER WORDS, SHE'S A DEMON
CONNECTED TO THE NETHERWORLD!
>> WE COULDN'T HAVE ASKED FOR
MORE.
>> TEKKEI IS A BRUTALLY FIERCE
DEMON, SO YOU MUST BE EXTREMELY
CAREFUL AROUND HER.
REMEMBER, YOU HAVE BEEN WARNED.
AND WITH THAT, I'M OUT.
>> OH, NO YOU DON'T.
NOW TELL ME HOW TO GET TO THE
OTHER SIDE, MYOGA.
WELL, I'M WAITING.
>> INUYASHA, LOOK AT THAT.
>> IT'S ENORMOUS!
WHAT IS THAT HUGE BIRD?
>> IS THAT HER?
>> IT MUST BE.
[THUNDERING]
>> INUYASHA, HAVE YOU ALL COME
TO DIE HERE AS WELL?
>> PRINCESS ABI.
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO NARAKU.
>> HA HA.
SORRY YOU MISSED HIM.
HE'S ALREADY DEAD.
>> WHAT?
>> DEAD?
YOU KILLED NARAKU?
[LAUGHING]
>> YES, INDEED.
HE'S IN MY BELLY.
>> UH, IS THAT ANOTHER WAY OF
SAYING YOU ATE HIM?
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
>> DON'T TAKE THIS THE WRONG
WAY, BUT I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT
NARAKU WOULD HAVE BEEN BEATEN SO
EASILY.
>> STAY WHERE YOU ARE AND I WILL
EAT YOU UP AS WELL.
>> NOT HAPPENING!
>> HMM.
>> CUBE HIM!
[SCREECHING]
>> THERE AREN'T ANY SHIMYOSHO,
SO I DON'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT
USING MY WIND TUNNEL.
>> I DON'T THINK SO!
[GRUNTING]
>> WELL STAR!
>> IT'S USELESS.
>> WHAT?
>> DIE, INUYASHA.
[GRUNTING]
[LAUGHING]
>> A HALF-DEMON THINKS HE CAN
DEFY ME AND MY DAUGHTER?
HA HA.
OOH.
OH, WHAT'S THIS?
OH.
WHAT THE...?
[GRUNTING]
>> MOTHER?
DAMN YOU, NARAKU.
>> YOU BASTARD!
>> HA HA HA.
WHAT TOOK YOU SO LONG, INUYASHA?
>> NARAKU, HOW DARE YOU!
>> PRINCESS ABI, YOU DID A FINE
JOB INDEED.
>> I'LL TEAR YOU APART!
WHAT?
>> IT'S HER TRIDENT.
>> HAD YOU FORGOTTEN?
THAT TRIDENT WAS ORIGINALLY PART
OF MY BODY.
>> UGH!
>> YOU HAVE PERFORMED VERY WELL
FOR ME, PRINCESS ABI.
>> OH, DAMN YOU!
>> THIS IS YOUR REWARD.
YOU SHALL NOT SUFFER WHEN I KILL
YOU.
[SCREAMING]
>> HOW HORRIBLE.
>> HE TAKES EVERY ADVANTAGE OF
THEM THEN DOES THIS.
>> DAMMIT!
I KNEW YOU WERE EVIL, NARAKU,
BUT THIS IS DESPICABLE!
>> COME NOW.
WEREN'T YOU PLANNING TO DESTROY
PRINCESS ABI AS WELL?
THE WAY I SEE IT, YOU SHOULD BE
GRATEFUL.
[SNARLING]
THANKS TO ME, THE PATH TO THE
BORDER IS OPEN.
YOU ARE ALL NOW ABLE TO TRAVEL
TO THE BORDER OF THE AFTERLIFE.
[LAUGHING]
[MUSIC]
>> WE CHASED NARAKU DOWN A RIVER
OF BLOOD AND FIND OURSELVES AT
THE BORDER BETWEEN THIS WORLD
AND THE AFTERLIFE.
>> THEN SUDDENLY WE'RE ATTACKED
BY A SPEAR OF LIGHT.
>> DAMMIT!
THOSE SPEARS CAME FROM MY OLD
MAN'S GRAVE.
>> GRAVE ROBBERS WHO SEEK THE
SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
>> LET'S GO.
COULD IT BE HOUSENKI?
>> THE SHARD CHOSE TO COME WITH
ME.
>> NEXT TIME: THE DEMON
PROTECTOR OF THE SACRED JEWEL
SHARD.
>> I WON'T LET ANYONE TAKE IT
FROM ME.