>> IT ALL STARTED WITH THE
SACRED TREE.
>> FIGHTING AND SEARCHING FOR
OUR DREAMS.
>> A STRONG BOND FORMED BETWEEN
US.
>> A NEW HOPE, A BRIGHT FUTURE
BEGINS NOW.
>> SANGO HAS NO IDEA THAT
KOHAKU'S MEMORY HAS BEEN
RESTORED.
ONLY KIRARA KNOWS HOW THE TWO
FEEL.
THEN AT THE DEMON PLAYER'S
VILLAGE, A MIRACLE OCCURRED.
>> THE FINAL JEWEL SHARD GUIDES
US...
>> ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE
WELL, A NEW DAY AWAITS.
...FAIRY TALE.
"INUYASHA"!
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> SANGO'S YOUNGER BROTHER
KOHAKU WAS CAUGHT IN NORAKU'S
DESPICABLE TRAP AND MUST BEAR
A HEAVY BURDEN.
AFTER ALL THIS TIME, KOHAKU WAS
STILL BEING MANIPULATED BY HIM.
SANGO FEELS AN ENORMOUS GUILT
THAT SHE'S RESPONSIBLE, AND WE
WANT TO DO SOMETHING FOR HER.
IF ONLY THINGS WERE THAT SIMPLE.
I WONDER WHAT KIRARA THINKS OF
KOHAKU.
>> IT'S JUST RIGHT.
>> MMM, MMM, MMM!
>> STILL NO SIGN OF KIRARA.
I WONDER WHERE SHE IS.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GETTING ALL
WORKED UP FOR?
YOU SHOULD KNOW BETTER THAN
THAT.
KIRARA CAN MANAGE ON HER OWN.
>> BUT SHE SURE HAS BEEN TAKING
OFF ON HER OWN A LOT THESE DAYS.
>> WE'RE NOT TOO FAR FROM
SANGO'S BIRTHPLACE, SO KIRARA IS
PROBABLY VERY NOSTALGIC ABOUT
THE AREA.
>> HMM...
>> HUH?
>> HEY, KOHAKU.
YOU WON'T FIND ... AROUND HERE.
TRUST ME.
TRY SOMEPLACE ELSE.
>> YES, I UNDERSTAND.
[SIGHS]
JUST KEEP YOURSELF BUSY ENOUGH
THAT NORAKU SPARES YOUR LIFE,
AND I'LL DO THE SAME.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
>> HMM...
[GIGGLING]
>> UHH!
AHH...
>> YEAHHH!
>> AAH!
UHH!
[GIGGLING]
>> THERE IT IS!
IT'S COMING YOUR WAY, KOHAKU!
>> JUST LEAVE IT TO ME.
HMM...
GOTCHA!
WHOA!
>> HA HA HA!
>> LOOK, IT'S STARTED RAINING.
>> [AH-CHOO!]
>> YOU'LL CATCH A COLD.
>> IT'S OK, SISTER.
>> STOP SQUIRMING.
THERE.
[RAARRRHH!]
>> AAH!
UHH!
[GROWLING]
[SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
SISTER.
>> FIND SOME COVER, KOHAKU.
[GROWLING]
[SIGHS]
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> UH-HUH.
>> AAH!
>> BE BRAVE.
IT WON'T LAST.
THERE YOU GO.
>> THANKS FOR HELPING ME OUT,
SANGO.
>> NO PROBLEM.
>> UHH!
HEY, SANGO!
HANG ON JUST A MINUTE.
>> HMM...
[PURRING]
>> SISTER!
>> KOHAKU, ARE YOU OK?
>> HERE.
>> YOU GOT THESE FOR ME?
>> UH-HUH.
>> THEY'RE GORGEOUS.
THANK YOU.
[GROWLING]
>> OW!
KIKOMA, THAT'S WAY TOO HOT!
>> OH, SORRY!
>> KIRARA.
>> SANGO!
>> SANGO, PLEASE, COME OVER AND
HAVE TEA WITH US.
>> GET OVER IT, SANGO.
STANDING THERE ALL FIDGETY WON'T
BRING HER BACK ANY FASTER.
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT KIRARA.
SHE'S THE MOST RELIABLE ONE
AROUND HERE.
>> SHE'S BEEN GONE TOO LONG.
I'M GOING TO LOOK FOR HER.
>> HUH?
[GROWLING]
>> LET'S DO IT, KIRARA.
[BREATHING HARD]
>> HMM?
WELL, IF IT ISN'T THE DEMON
SLAYER.
I'M SURPRISED TO SEE YOU ALONE.
>> KAGRA.
>> HERE, KIRARA, HAVE ONE.
IT'S SURE NICE TO SEE YOU.
IT'S BEEN A WHILE.
HOW'S MY SISTER?
IS SHE OK?
[MEOW]
I SEE.
YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT ME, AREN'T
YOU?
HMM, I APPRECIATE IT.
I CAN'T COME BACK, THOUGH.
I'VE GOT SOMETHING TO DO BEFORE
I GO BACK TO SANGO.
>> HEY, DEMON SLAYER, DON'T
SUPPOSE YOU HAVE ANY IDEA WHERE
WE MIGHT FIND KIKIYA.
>> IS KOHAKU WITH YOU?
>> HMM...
>> WELL, IS HE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> WHERE IS HE?
>> SEARCH FOR YOURSELF, IF
YOU'RE THAT WORRIED ABOUT HIM.
HOLD IT.
WHAT ARE YOU PLANNING ON DOING
IF YOU MANAGE TO FIND HIM?
>> NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS, KAGRA.
>> EVEN IF YOU MANAGE TO FIND
HIM, HE'S BOUND TO NORAKU UNTIL
THE DAY HE DIES.
>> I TOLD YOU, IT HAS NOTHING TO
DO WITH YOU!
>> KOHAKU...
>> SO MANY PEOPLE HAVE DIED...
AND BECAUSE OF ME.
THAT'S WHY THE LEAST I CAN DO IS
TRY TO AVENGE THEIR DEATHS.
NORAKU, I'LL GET HIM.
I PROMISE.
I MAY NOT MAKE IT OUT OF THIS
ALIVE.
BESIDES, I DON'T EVEN KNOW IF I
DESERVE TO LIVE AFTER WHAT I'VE
DONE.
[CREAK]
>> WELCOME HOME, EVERYONE!
>> HEY!
>> HERE WE GO!
♪ DEMON SLAYERS
ARE THE BRAVEST ♪
[CONTINUES SINGING INDISTINCTLY]
[LAUGHING]
♪ ...ONE MORE TIME
HERE WE GO AGAIN ♪
>> HUH?
I'M SORRY, KIRARA.
HUH?
YOU'RE HURT.
[MEOW]
I'VE GOT SOMETHING HERE.
STAY STILL.
[PURRS]
ALL RIGHT, ALL DONE.
>> KO...
KOHAKU.
>> HEY, KIRARA, COME WITH ME.
I'LL SHOW YOU A SECRET PLACE OF
MINE THAT NOBODY ELSE KNOWS
ABOUT.
>> THEY HAVEN'T BEEN DEAD FOR
VERY LONG.
HE'S NEAR.
>> WHAT DO YOU PLAN ON DOING IF
YOU FIND HIM?
>> UHH!
>> NO!
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENED, KOHAKU
IS STILL MY BROTHER.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
ISN'T THIS PLACE GREAT?
THIS SPOT HASN'T CHANGED A BIT.
I WISH SANGO COULD SEE IT.
I THINK SHE'D LOVE IT HERE.
[BREATHING HARD]
>> KOHAKU! KOHAKU!
>> IT WAS NICE SEEING YOU,
KIRARA.
SAY HELLO TO MY SISTER FOR ME.
[MEOW]
GOOD-BYE, THEN, KIRARA.
[SNIFFS]
>> KOHAKU!
[VOICE ECHOING]
>> SISTER?
I JUST...
UHH! UHH!
SANGO.
KIRARA!
KIRARA, ARE YOU TRYING TO GET ME
TO FOLLOW YOU?
KIRARA, WHAT DID YOU WANT TO
SHOW ME?
BEAUTIFUL.
A GARDEN OF LILIES.
[MEOW]
YOU'RE INJURED.
AND THERE'S MEDICINE ON IT.
KOHAKU.
[LAUGHING]
>> SANGO, WAIT UP.
>> KIRARA, YOU WERE WITH HIM.
KOHAKU!
[CRYING]
[MUSIC]
>> SHIPPO FALLS UNDER THE SPELL
OF A PARASITE CHRYSALIS.
>> WE'VE GOT TO STOP THIS.
HE'S BECOME A NASTY PRANKSTER.
>> I SHOWED HIM, DIDN'T I?
>> THE VILLAGERS ARE FURIOUS.
WE'VE GOT TO HURRY AND FIND THEM
BEFORE THEY SLAY HIM.
>> GET REAL.
LIKE YOUR FOXFIRE'S GONNA DO ME
ANY HARM.
>> I GOT A LITTLE SOMETHING UP
MY SLEEVE.
NEXT TIME, "POSSESSED BY A
PARASITE: SHIPPO OUR WORST
ENEMY."
>> WHY DO YOU KEEP USING YOUR
FOX MAGIC ON ME?