[SCREAMING]
- TSUBAKI IS A PRIESTESS
ON THE DARK SIDE WHO
SPECIALIZES IN CURSES.
SHE DESIRES ETERNAL YOUTH
AND AGREES TO WORK HER
MALEVOLENT SKILLS FOR NARAKU
IN EXCHANGE FOR
THE SACRED JEWEL.
USING HER SHIKIGAMI,
A DEMON SERPENT,
SHE PLACES A CURSE ON ME
AND TAKES CONTROL OF MY BODY.
[GASP]
THE SHARDS ARE GOING INSIDE ME!
- KAGOME!
HUH?
- GET...AWAY.
- WHAT DO I DO?
- HEH HEH HEH!
SUFFER, INUYASHA.
- RUN AWAY.
GET OUT OF HERE.
- HEH HEH HEH!
VERY AMUSING.
HOW DOES IT FEEL, INUYASHA,
TO ONCE AGAIN
HAVE THE WOMAN YOU LOVE
POINT AN ARROW AT YOU?
- INUYASHA!
- UNH!
K-KIKYO...
HOW COULD--I THOUGHT--
[GROANING]
- YOU CAN RE-EXPERIENCE
THAT EXACT MOMENT 50 YEARS AGO
WHEN KIKYO SHOT AND KILLED YOU,
ONLY THIS TIME, YOU WILL DIE
AT KAGOME'S HANDS.
RELISH THE PAIN, INUYASHA.
IT WON'T LAST NEARLY
LONG ENOUGH.
- THE BARRIER HERE IS SO STRONG.
- MEANING THE DARK
PRIESTESS MUST BE INSIDE.
LOOKS LIKE WE FINALLY FOUND HER.
MIROKU, ARE WE ABLE
TO BREAK THE BARRIER?
- HMM.
[MUTTERING]
KIRARA, TAKE US DOWN.
- AAH!
- I HATE TO ADMIT IT,
BUT IT'S TOO STRONG FOR ME.
- MIROKU, LOOK DOWN THERE.
- HUH?
- I FEEL IT.
THIS DEMONIC AURA
IS SATED WITH EVIL.
- KIKYO!
- WHY IS SHE HERE?
- THOSE ARE INUYASHA'S FRIENDS.
WHAT COULD BE HAPPENING
BEYOND THIS BARRIER?
- YOU SEE THAT?
SHE WALKED RIGHT IN!
[GROANING]
- HEH HEH HEH!
CHOOSE, INUYASHA.
WILL YOU BE SLAIN BY KAGOME, OR
WILL YOU FLEE AND SAVE YOURSELF?
IF YOU RUN, KAGOME WILL
PERISH UNDER THE CURSE
OF THE DARK PRIESTESS.
- RUN AWAY.
GO NOW.
- KAGOME, DON'T BE STUPID.
AS IF I'D RUN AND LEAVE YOU!
- KILL INUYASHA.
- UNH!
- AAH!
- INUYASHA SEEMS TO HAVE CHOSEN
DEATH AT THE HANDS OF THE WOMAN.
- HEH HEH HEH!
- NARAKU, YOU ARE TRULY EVIL--
TO FORCE KIKYO'S REINCARNATION
TO KILL THE MAN
SHE LOVES...ONCE AGAIN.
HUH?
HMM? KIKYO?
- WHO ARE YOU?
- IT SEEMS KIKYO HAS
MADE HER APPEARANCE.
- KIKYO HAS?
DO NOT UNDERESTIMATE
THE POWER OF THAT PRIESTESS.
ARE YOU SURE WE CAN TRUST HER?
- LET HER CONTINUE.
WE CAN TAKE CARE OF HER AFTER
WE SEE WHAT SHE HAS PLANNED.
[GROANING]
- HUH?
KAGOME?
AH! KAGOME!
- INU...YASHA.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- MM-HMM.
THE VOICE IN MY HEAD IS GONE.
IT STOPPED.
- KAGOME.
- I CAN SENSE IT.
TAKE ME THERE.
I CAN SENSE THE SACRED JEWEL.
[GASPS]
- HUH? KAGOME!
- KAGOME! LIE DOWN!
YOU'RE TOO SICK TO WALK!
- THE VOICE HAS STOPPED.
THIS IS MY ONLY CHANCE.
- YOU'RE GOING
TO LOOK FOR THE JEWEL?
THE DARK PRIESTESS
IS DANGEROUS.
THE CURSE ISN'T LIFTED YET.
- I'LL PROTECT KAGOME.
DON'T WORRY.
- INUYASHA!
- I HOPE THAT
SHE'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
SHE'S STILL IN A LOT OF PAIN.
- KAGOME IS A STRONG GIRL.
SHE WILL BE FINE.
INUYASHA WILL SEE TO IT.
LET US GO INSIDE AND WAIT FOR
THEM ALL TO RETURN SAFELY.
- TAKE GOOD CARE
OF YOURSELF, KAGOME.
- IT'S TAKING ALL OF KAGOME'S
WILL TO ENDURE HER PAIN.
INUYASHA, YOU MUSTN'T
LET HER PERISH.
YOU MUST FIND A WAY TO BREAK
THE CURSE AND SAVE HER.
- INUYASHA, I'M SO SORRY.
- YOU DIDN'T SHOOT THAT ARROW.
DON'T EVEN THINK THAT WAY.
- THE ENEMY IS SO CLOSE
YET OUT OF OUR REACH.
- THE DARK PRIESTESS'
CURSE IS WORKING ITS
EVIL EVEN AS WE SPEAK.
- KAGOME WON'T BE ABLE
TO ENDURE IT FOR MUCH LONGER.
- BREAKING THROUGH THIS BARRIER
MIGHT BE NEXT TO IMPOSSIBLE.
- WELL, IT'S BETTER THAN
DOING NOTHING, MIROKU.
COME ON. LET'S GO.
- RIGHT.
- KIRARA!
- WHAT IS THIS?
THIS GIRL KAGOME--
SHE IS YOUR REINCARNATION,
IS SHE NOT, KIKYO?
- TSUBAKI, I SEE THAT YOU
HAVE PUT A CURSE ON KAGOME.
YOUR POWERS WILL BE
USELESS ON THE GIRL.
- HMMPH!
DON'T UNDERESTIMATE ME.
KIKYO, I HAVE CHANGED
SINCE YOU LAST DEFEATED ME.
- SO I SEE.
ONE GLANCE TELLS ME
THE ENTIRE ACCOUNT.
TSUBAKI, I KNOW THAT
YOU SOLD YOUR SOUL TO A DEMON
IN EXCHANGE FOR YOUTH.
- CLEVER GIRL.
FOR YOUTH AND BEAUTY, THOUGH.
AHH, THIS YOUTH AND BEAUTY.
SOMEDAY I SHALL LOSE IT.
IS THIS THE FATE OF ALL MORTALS?
NO.
IF I CAN TAKE POSSESSION
OF THE SACRED JEWEL
THAT KIKYO GUARDS,
THEN MY BEAUTY
SHALL BE ETERNAL.
- ME, BECOME A HUMAN?
- IT'S POSSIBLE.
IT'S TRUE THAT
YOU'RE HALF-DEMON,
BUT YOU ARE ALSO HALF-HUMAN.
IF THE SACRED JEWEL
OF THE 4 SOULS FELL INTO
THE HANDS OF A DEMON,
THEIR POWERS WOULD
UNDOUBTEDLY INCREASE.
HOWEVER, IF IT WERE USED
TO TURN YOU INTO A HUMAN,
IT WOULD BE PURIFIED.
THE JEWEL OF THE 4 SOULS
WOULD PROBABLY CEASE TO EXIST.
- AND THEN WHAT?
WHAT WOULD HAPPEN TO YOU?
- MY DUTY IS
TO PROTECT THE JEWEL.
WITHOUT IT, I COULD LIVE
THE LIFE OF AN ORDINARY WOMAN.
[GASP]
- I CAN DEFEAT KIKYO NOW,
WHILE SHE IS INFATUATED
WITH THE HALF-DEMON.
ARISE, MY SHIKIGAMI.
KILL KIKYO AND STEAL
THE SACRED JEWEL FOR ME.
GO!
[GROWLING]
[SCREAMING]
THAT DAY 50 YEARS AGO,
YOU INFLICTED ME WITH
MY OWN CURSE, KIKYO.
MY FACE!
MY BEAUTIFUL FACE!
AAH!
- HMM.
I WASN'T ABLE TO STEAL
THE SACRED JEWEL FROM YOU,
BUT I COLLABORATED WITH A DEMON
AND HENCE GAINED
ETERNAL YOUTH AND BEAUTY,
NOT TO MENTION
MY OWN DEMON POWER.
- HOW FOOLISH.
- YOU'RE ONE TO TALK.
TELL ME, HOW IS IT THAT
YOU APPEAR BEFORE ME,
LOOKING EXACTLY
AS YOU DID 50 YEARS AGO?
[GASP]
KIKYO, YOU--
YOU'RE DEAD.
THAT BODY THAT YOU'RE INHABITING
IS NEITHER MORTAL
NOR THAT OF A DEMON.
IT'S A COUNTERFEIT.
KIKYO, YOU WALK ONLY BY
THE GRACE OF BORROWED SPIRITS,
YET YOU DARE TO LECTURE ME?
- I MERELY CAME HERE
TO ASCERTAIN THE CAUSE
OF THE DEMON AURA.
I CARE NOT WHAT HAPPENS
TO YOU, TSUBAKI.
THEY'RE COMING CLOSER.
- OH!
WHAT?
- INUYASHA,
WHY DIDN'T YOU RUN AWAY?
- LOOK, I ALREADY TOLD YOU,
I WOULD NEVER LEAVE YOU, KAGOME.
- ONE WRONG MOVE,
AND IT WOULD HAVE ENDED UP
LIKE THE TIME WITH KIKYO.
- WELL, THAT'S A CHANCE
I HAD TO TAKE.
I WASN'T GONNA RUN AWAY.
I'M STAYING WITH YOU,
SO YOU BETTER GET USED TO IT.
UNH!
- HUH? INUYASHA! KAGOME!
- THE DARK PRIESTESS.
SHE'S INSIDE THAT BARRIER.
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- THE JEWEL'S BEING PURIFIED.
- WHO'S DOING THIS?
IS IT YOUR REINCARNATION,
THIS KAGOME?
- I ALREADY TOLD YOU, TSUBAKI.
A CURSE BY THE LIKES OF YOU
WILL HAVE NO EFFECT ON KAGOME.
- HOW DARE YOU?
THIS IS YOUR FAULT,
FOR YOUR UNWANTED APPEARANCE!
- THIS BARRIER'S COMING DOWN!
THIS BARRIER'S COMING DOWN!
- HUH?
KAGOME BROKE THROUGH IT.
- MY BARRIER.
[GASP]
THAT'S HIM! INUYASHA!
OH, NO.
KAGOME MISSED HIM.
- HMM.
[GASP]
- KIKYO, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- SILENCE!
WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?
SPEAK THE TRUTH.
YOU ATTEMPTED TO HAVE
KAGOME SLAY INUYASHA.
- WHAT AILS YOU?
SOME UNPLEASANT
MEMORIES, PERHAPS?
YOU ARE CORRECT.
I DROVE KAGOME
TO SHOOT THE ARROW.
IRONIC?
IT WAS THE SAME WAY THAT YOU
KILLED INUYASHA YEARS AGO.
- TSUBAKI, DO AS YOU PLEASE
WITH KAGOME.
I HAVE NO INTENTION
OF INTERFERING.
BUT IF YOU SHOULD EVER
DO ANY HARM TO INUYASHA,
I WILL PERSONALLY
SEE TO YOUR DEMISE.
[PANTING]
- YOU WENCH!
HOW DARE YOU PRESUME
I WOULD FEAR YOU?!
- BE WARNED.
HEED MY WORDS.
IT IS NO IDLE THREAT.
[PANTING]
- INUYASHA!
- KAGOME!
- GOOD TIMING.
- IT'S INSIDE.
I'M SURE THAT
THE SACRED JEWEL IS INSIDE.
SO IS THE DARK PRIESTESS,
THE WOMAN THAT CURSED ME
WITH HER SPELL.
[WIND WHISTLES]
- ARE YOU THE DARK PRIESTESS?
- I AM KNOWN AS TSUBAKI.
ARE YOU INUYASHA,
KIKYO'S LOVER?
- HEY, TSUBAKI,
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE WITH KIKYO?
I KNOW SHE WAS IN THERE.
- KIKYO?
- DON'T DENY IT.
I SAW HER AS WELL.
I SAW HER COMING HERE.
- HMM. THAT KIKYO.
INUYASHA, SHE CAME TO ASK ME
TO SPARE YOUR LIFE.
- HUH?
- KIKYO STILL HAS FEELINGS
FOR INUYASHA.
- SHE CAN'T FACE DEATH,
BECAUSE SHE LOVES YOU,
SO SHE BORROWS
THE SPIRITS OF THE DEAD.
- MIROKU, SANGO,
WATCH OVER KAGOME.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, KAGOME?
- YES.
- WHAT'S THE DEAL?
YOU SEEM TO KNOW AN AWFUL
LOT ABOUT ALL OF US.
AND YOU USED A FOUL CURSE
TO POSSESS KAGOME
AND MAKE HER TRY AND KILL ME.
I BET YOU'VE MADE
A PACT WITH NARAKU.
- HA! AND WHAT OF IT?
- WELL, I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT OF IT.
YOU'RE GOING DOWN!
TETSUSAI--
- DRAW YOUR SWORD,
AND KAGOME WILL DIE!
- HUH?
- PATHETIC FOOL.
MY CURSE HAS NOT
YET BEEN BROKEN.
AS LONG AS I HOLD
THE SACRED JEWEL IN MY HAND,
KAGOME'S LIFE BELONGS TO ME.
- WHY, THAT--
[GROANING]
KAGOME!
- THE EVIL HAS RETURNED.
THE POOR GIRL.
NOT EVEN SHE CAN THWART
THE JEWEL'S POWERS.
HOW LUDICROUS.
THE JEWEL PURIFIED,
AND MY BARRIER WAS BROKEN
NOT BY KAGOME'S STRENGTH
BUT BECAUSE KIKYO INTERFERED
AND DISTRACTED MY
CONCENTRATION ON THE CURSE.
- A CURSE BY THE LIKES OF YOU
WILL HAVE NO EFFECT ON KAGOME.
- KIKYO CERTAINLY THINKS HIGHLY
OF KAGOME'S ABILITIES.
- YOU DIRTY, CONNIVING WITCH.
- I WILL DO ANYTHING IN ORDER TO
POSSESS THE WHOLE SACRED JEWEL.
INUYASHA,
YOU'LL BE FIRST TO PERISH.
[GASP]
- LOOK AT THAT!
- AH!
- THAT PRIESTESS--SHE HARBORS
DEMONS INSIDE HER BODY!
- UNH!
HUH?
[GROWLING]
[GRUNTING]
- DON'T DRAW YOUR SWORD,
INUYASHA,
OR I SHALL CURSE
KAGOME TO DEATH.
HA HA HA!
FIGHT YOUR PATHETIC BATTLE AND
DIE AT THE HANDS OF MY DEMON.
[GROWLING]
- I CAN'T TAKE THIS ANYMORE.
I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING
ABOUT THIS CURSE.
- THE DARK PRIESTESS
HAS RENDERED INUYASHA
VIRTUALLY HELPLESS.
- BUT WHAT CAN WE DO ABOUT IT?
- WASTE THAT DEMON, INUYASHA!
- KAGOME?
- HA HA!
KILL HIM, MY PRECIOUS DEMON!
[ROARING]
[GRUNTING]
- IRON REAPER, SOUL STEALER!
- OH, INUYASHA.
- HA HA HA!
WITHOUT YOUR SWORD,
YOU ARE HELPLESS.
NOW YOU SHALL BECOME FODDER
FOR MY DEMON, INUYASHA.
HA HA HA!
- WHY, YOU...
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING
ABOUT THIS CURSE.
- WHO ARE YOU?
- HUH? WHAT HAPPENED?
WHY AM I BACK IN THE PRESENT?
WHERE ARE SANGO AND MIROKU?
- ARE YOU...ME?
- I'M...
- HEED MY WARNING, OR YOU WILL
END UP SLAYING INUYASHA AGAIN.
- NEXT TIME, "TSUBAKI'S
UNRELENTING EVIL SPELL."
I'M KAGOME.
KAGOME!