- [GROWLING]
[SCREAMING]
FILTHY VERMIN!
- [SCREAMING]
- I DON'T REMEMBER A THING
FROM WHEN I WAS TRANSFORMED.
- THE TETSUSAIGA SUPPRESSES THE
DEMON NATURE IN YOU, INUYASHA.
- YOUR PRECIOUS TETSUSAIGA IS
NOTHING MORE THAN
A DART RIGHT NOW.
- DURING A PREVIOUS BATTLE,
THE TETSUSAIGA WAS BROKEN,
AWAKENING INUYASHA'S
DEMON BLOOD.
ONCE IT'S INITIALLY ROUSED,
THE DEMON NATURE
WILL CONTINUE TO SURFACE
BY TRANSFORMING ITS HOST
IN ORDER TO PROTECT ITSELF.
THAT'S WHY HE CAN'T EVER
LET GO OF THE TETSUSAIGA.
OTHERWISE, WHEN HIS LIFE
IS ON THE LINE,
HIS DEMONIC NATURE
WILL TAKE OVER.
- THE NEXT TIME I TRANSFORM,
I MAY EVEN COME AFTER YOU
WITH THESE CLAWS, KAGOME.
HEY, YOU THERE, TOTOSAI?
- HMM?
- WE NEED TO TALK.
- AH, YES.
I EXPECTED YOU WOULD COME.
- HMM.
- WHERE COULD INUYASHA
HAVE GOTTEN TO, ANYWAY?
- YOU'RE THINKING MAYBE WE
SHOULD LEAVE HIM ALONE, KAGOME?
- MM.
- IF YOU ASK ME, INUYASHA WANTS
TO MAKE THE TETSUSAIGA
LIGHTER IN WEIGHT.
COULD IT BE THAT HE'S
JUST OFF TRAINING SOMEWHERE?
- THINK SO?
SOUNDS LIKE
WAY TOO MUCH HARD WORK
FOR THE INUYASHA
I KNOW AND LOVE.
- NOW, NOW.
IN ANY CASE,
WE'LL JUST HAVE TO SEARCH
EVERY SINGLE PLACE
THAT WE CAN THINK OF.
- HMM.
I HAVEN'T TOLD THE OTHERS,
BUT INUYASHA IS
REALLY TORMENTED.
IT'D BE BETTER TO LEAVE HIM
ALONE FOR A WHILE
TO SORT THINGS OUT ON HIS OWN.
BUT I CAN'T STAND THE THOUGHT
OF WAITING IT OUT.
I'M SO WORRIED.
- I'M VERY DISAPPOINTED
IN YOU, INUYASHA.
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE
YOU STILL HAVE TROUBLE
WIELDING THE TETSUSAIGA.
- THAT'S WHY I'M ASKING YOU
TO MAKE MY SWORD LIGHTER,
OLD MAN.
THERE MUST BE SOME WAY.
- THEN WHY DON'T YOU
FIGURE IT OUT?
- I'M IN A HURRY, OK?
AND BESIDES, I DON'T WANT
TO TRANSFORM ANYMORE.
- UH...
- I COULDN'T MASTER
THE TETSUSAIGA,
SO I WAS TRAPPED
BY THAT PETTY DEMON.
I TOTALLY LOST CONTROL
OF MYSELF.
I DON'T WANT TO GO
THROUGH THAT AGAIN.
IT WAS TERRIFYING.
- HMM.
[CLICK]
[GRUNTS]
- OW!
[SLURPING]
- AHH.
MASTER INUYASHA,
NICE TO TASTE YOU AGAIN.
[GRUNTING]
AND HERE I WAS
WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
- SO THIS IS WHERE
YOU'VE BEEN HIDING OUT, IS IT?
THANKS A LOT
FOR KEEPING ME IN THE DARK
ABOUT THE SWORD, MYOGA.
- HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- DON'T ACT INNOCENT!
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO TOLD HER
ABOUT THE TETSUSAIGA.
KAGOME SAID THAT MY SWORD IS
WHAT KEEPS MY DEMON NATURE
IN CHECK.
- HMM.
WELL, THAT FIGURES.
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN BETTER
THAN TO TRUST HER TO SECRECY.
- HUH.
YEAH, WELL, KNOWING THE TRUTH
WON'T HELP ME
KEEP HOLD OF MY SWORD.
[CRYING]
- UHH.
- I HAVE TO MASTER
THE TETSUSAIGA, OR ELSE.
THAT'S THE ONLY WAY.
- HMM.
I SEE YOU'VE PUT QUITE A GOOD
DEAL OF THOUGHT INTO THIS.
YOU'VE HAD
ENOUGH TRANSFORMATIONS.
- YEAH.
- WELL, THAT LEAVES
BUT ONE CHOICE.
- HUH?
- INUYASHA, YOU MUST
KILL RYUKOTSUSEI.
- RYUKOTSUSEI?
- WHO?
- HMM?
- YOU DIDN'T SAY
RYUKOTSUSEI, DID YOU?
- HE IS THE DEMON
YOUR FATHER BATTLED
AND SEALED INTO A DORMANT SLEEP.
INUYASHA, WHY DO YOU THINK
THIS NEW TETSUSAIGA IS SO HEAVY?
IT IS BECAUSE YOUR FANG
HAS NOT YET REACHED
THE POWER OF YOUR FATHER'S.
- IN OTHER WORDS, IF I DESTROY
THE DEMON MY FATHER FOUGHT,
THEN I'LL SURPASS
THE OLD MAN IN STRENGTH?
- NOW, LISTEN, MASTER INUYASHA.
BY DESTROY, ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS PIERCE THE DEMON'S HEART
SINCE HIS POWERS
STILL LIE DORMANT.
- WHAT?
I DON'T HAVE TO FIGHT HIM?
[BUZZING]
- OF COURSE NOT.
IT TOOK EVERY OUNCE OF STRENGTH
FOR YOUR FATHER TO PUT
THIS DEMON UNDER SEAL.
HE WASN'T ABLE TO LEVY
A FINISHING BLOW.
- SO NOW I'M THE ONE
WHO GETS STUCK
SLAYING HIM LIKE A COWARD.
- IF YOU KEEP COMPLAINING,
I WILL NOT SHOW YOU THE WAY.
OH!
- JUST WHO DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE TALKING TO, MYOGA?
- OH, I JUST--
[GRUNTING]
[BUZZING]
- HMM.
VERY INTERESTING, KANNA.
I'VE DISPATCHED YOU, KAGURA,
GOSHINKI, JUROMARU,
AND KAGEROMARU,
AND NOT A SINGLE ONE OF YOU
WERE ABLE TO PUT AN END
TO INUYASHA.
HMM.
LET'S GIVE THIS RYUKOTSUSEI
A TRY, SHALL WE?
[LAUGHS EVILLY]
- UHH. UHH.
[GRUNTING]
- HOW MUCH FURTHER
IS IT, MYOGA?
- NOT MUCH.
WE'LL BE ABLE TO SEE IT SOON.
KEEP MOVING.
- UHH.
I SHOULD SQUASH YOU.
UHH.
- TOTOSAI.
- HMM?
WHAT ARE YOU YOUNGSTERS
DOING HERE?
- WE'RE LOOKING FOR INUYASHA.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHERE HE IS?
- INUYASHA?
HMM.
LET ME SEE.
INUYASHA, YOU SAY.
- HE'S HAVING TROUBLE
WIELDING THE TETSUSAIGA,
SO WE THOUGHT HE MIGHT HAVE
COME TO SEE YOU FOR HELP.
- LET ME SEE.
WHAT TO DO?
- YOU KNOW, DON'T YOU?
WHERE IS HE?
TELL ME!
[SCREAMING]
- OOH!
[CRASH]
- SORRY ABOUT THAT.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- INUYASHA HAS GONE
TO THE VALLEY OF RYUKOTSUSEI.
- THE VALLEY OF RYUKOTSUSEI?
- HUH?
- UHH.
UHH.
- LOOK, MASTER INUYASHA,
OVER THERE.
- OH.
SO THAT'S RYUKOTSUSEI.
- CORRECT.
AND LOOK WHERE YOUR FATHER'S
CLAW HAS PIERCED HIM,
RENDERING HIS POWERS DORMANT--
RIGHT ABOVE HIS HEART.
- HUH?
[LAUGHING]
- NARAKU.
- BUT, MASTER TOTOSAI,
IF THERE WAS SUCH A SIMPLE WAY
TO MASTER THE TETSUSAIGA,
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL HIM EARLIER?
[CHEWING]
- THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN TOO EASY.
HE WON'T LEARN IF I HAND HIM
ALL THE ANSWERS, NOW, WILL HE?
HUH?
- I THINK THAT INUYASHA
HAS ALREADY SUFFERED ENOUGH.
- POOR THING.
- HE AGONIZED
OVER WHAT HE'D DONE.
THAT'S WHY HE CAME TO SEE YOU.
- THAT'S TRUE.
- EVEN THOUGH THEY WERE BANDITS,
THE FACT REMAINS THAT THEY WERE
STILL HUMAN BEINGS
THAT HE KILLED.
[SCOFFS]
- THAT'S WHY I TOLD HIM
WHAT HE NEEDED TO DO.
IF HE'D FELT NOTHING
AFTER KILLING THOSE HUMANS,
HE'D HAVE NO RIGHT
TO WIELD THE TETSUSAIGA.
- NARAKU, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
[GASPS]
- THAT CLAW SEALS HIS POWERS.
[SHUDDERING]
[LAUGHS]
- RYUKOTSUSEI, OVER YONDER
STANDS THE SON OF THE DEMON
WHO HURLED YOU INTO DORMANCY.
DO WITH HIM AS YOU PLEASE.
OH...
[GRUNTING]
[GROWLS]
- THIS IS TERRIBLE!
WE MUST FLEE, MASTER INUYASHA!
- WHAT?
YOU MUST BE OUT OF YOUR MIND.
THIS WAY IS MUCH BETTER THAN
SLAYING A DEFENSELESS DEMON
LIKE I WAS SOME KIND
OF PATHETIC COWARD.
IF I'M GONNA MAKE
THE TETSUSAIGA LIGHTER,
THEN I WANT TO FACE HIM
HEAD TO HEAD.
I'M GONNA TAKE YOU OUT.
- LITTLE MAN, YOU THINK THAT
YOU CAN DESTROY ME?
[LAUGHS]
HOW VERY ENTERTAINING.
THIS SHALL PROVE AMUSING.
- AMUSING?
UHH!
UHH.
UHH. UHHH!
- NO!
IT'S HOPELESS!
[WHIMPERING]
- AHHH!
UHH.
- SUCH AN EASY MARK.
- UHH.
[CHUCKLES]
[LAUGHING]
- HMM?
- AHH.
THAT DEMON IS REMARKABLE.
IT SHOULD BE EASY FOR HIM
TO OVERCOME INUYASHA.
I SHALL ENJOY THIS PERFORMANCE.
- A MERE DEMON PUPPET.
HARDLY A WARRIOR.
- SO HE WAS GOING AFTER NARAKU
FROM THE START.
- LITTLE MAN,
I HOPE YOU'LL PROVIDE ME
MORE AMUSEMENT THAN HE COULD.
- HA.
MORE THAN HAPPY TO OBLIGE YOU.
- THIS LOOKS LIKE
A NEW DEVELOPMENT.
- IT'S A DEMON AURA.
- AAH...MAYBE SOMETHING BAD
HAS HAPPENED.
- TOTOSAI, DOES THAT MEAN
HE'S IN TROUBLE?
- OH, THAT FOOL.
HE HAS AWAKENED RYUKOTSUSEI.
- I'VE NEVER FELT
SUCH AN OMINOUS AURA.
- THEN THIS DEMON
INUYASHA'S GONE TO FIGHT
MUST BE FORMIDABLE.
[GASPS]
- KAGOME.
- I THINK WE SHOULD ALL
GO AND HELP HIM.
- HEY, WAIT FOR ME!
- OH, DEAR.
WHAT A MISERABLE DAY.
- COME AT ME, LITTLE MAN.
DON'T DENY ME
SOME ENTERTAINMENT.
- HUH, I'M THE ONE
WHO'S GONNA BE ENTERTAINED.
THE SCAR LEFT
BY MY FATHER'S CLAW.
IF I CAN PIERCE HIM THERE,
THE TETSUSAIGA
WILL BECOME LIGHTER.
[SCREAMING]
YAAA!
HEH.
HUH?
[GRUNTING]
THE TETSUSAIGA COULDN'T
CUT THROUGH HIS THICK SKIN.
- SEE?
IT'S USELESS, NO MATTER
HOW HARD YOU TRY.
MY BODY IS MIGHTIER THAN ARMOR.
[GASPS]
- UHH!
UHH!
UHH.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- M-MASTER INUYASHA,
WE DON'T STAND A CHANCE!
- SAVE IT.
THIS BATTLE IS
JUST GETTING STARTED.
- I ALREADY TOLD YOU
IT TOOK EVERYTHING
IN YOUR FATHER'S POWER
TO RENDER HIM DORMANT.
MORE IMPORTANTLY, THE WOUND
INFLICTED UPON YOUR FATHER
DURING THE BATTLE
WAS ULTIMATELY WHAT KILLED HIM.
- HUH?
UH.
- SO HE PERISHED, DID HE?
AND YOU ARE THAT WRETCH'S SON?
DON'T TELL ME
YOU CAME TO AVENGE HIM
WITH THAT
RIDICULOUS LITTLE SWORD.
- HUH, UNFORTUNATELY,
I DON'T EVEN REMEMBER
WHAT MY OLD MAN LOOKED LIKE.
AS IF I WOULD EVEN CARE ABOUT
AVENGING HIS DEATH.
- WHAT?!
HOW DARE YOU SAY THAT?
YOU'VE BEEN SAVED
COUNTLESS TIMES
BY THE VERY SWORD THAT
YOUR FATHER PASSED DOWN TO YOU.
- STOP INTERFERING.
- TRAITOROUS SON.
I'LL HAVE NOTHING
TO DO WITH YOU.
[SOBBING]
- RIGHT.
I KNOW YOU'RE JUST RUNNING AWAY.
HUH?
UHH!
UHH.
DAMN!
MY FANGS USED TO REPAIR
MY BROKEN TETSUSAIGA,
AND THE REASON IT'S SO HEAVY
IS BECAUSE I'M NOT
AS STRONG AS MY FATHER WAS.
I KNOW.
I MUST SOMEHOW
DESTROY RYUKOTSUSEI
AND SURPASS MY FATHER IN POWER.
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
- WHAT AN OMINOUS AURA.
- THIS ISN'T A GOOD SIGN.
- HOW COULD RYUKOTSUSEI
HAVE BEEN BROUGHT
OUT OF DORMANCY?
- AS IF I'D KNOW.
I MUST SAY THAT IT POSES
QUITE THE PROBLEM, THOUGH.
[SIGHS]
- IF RYUKOTSUSEI
RISES UP ONCE MORE,
THE PLAINS OF MUSOSHI WILL BE
RAZED TO A FIELD OF ASHES.
- OH, IS HE REALLY
THAT FRIGHTENING A DEMON?
- YES.
- HOW CAN WE POSSIBLY
HOPE TO STOP HIM, THEN?
- THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY TO STOP
THE REAWAKENED RYUKOTSUSEI.
HE MUST USE THE BAKURUYUHA,
OR BACKLASH WAVE.
- BACKLASH WAVE?
WHAT'S THAT?
- A POWERFUL ULTIMATE TECHNIQUE
OF THE TETSUSAIGA.
- YOU MEAN IT'S EVEN STRONGER
THAN THE WINDSCAR?
- THE WINDSCAR IS
A MERE TRICK FOR NOVICES.
- IT IS?
BUT INUYASHA CAN'T EVEN
HOLD UP THE TETSUSAIGA,
LET ALONE USE THE WINDSCAR.
HE CAN'T MASTER A NEW TECHNIQUE.
- I SUPPOSE YOU'RE RIGHT.
[SQUEAKING]
- HMM?
[GRUNTING]
MYOGA, HAVE YOU RUN OUT
ON INUYASHA YET AGAIN?
KAGOME!
[SHUDDERS]
- INUYASHA.
I HOPE YOU'RE OK.
[GRUNTING]
- PITIFUL.
THIS IS MORE TEDIOUS
THAN I EXPECTED.
DESTROYING YOU DOES NOTHING
TO RELIEVE THE ANGER I FEEL
TOWARDS YOUR FATHER!
- UHH.
UHH.
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
- DO YOU NOT UNDERSTAND
THAT YOU CANNOT SLAY ME
WITH SUCH AN INFERIOR SWORD?
[GRUNTING]
[GASPS]
- TETSUSAIGA!
- INUYASHA, YOU MUSTN'T
PART WITH THE TETSUSAIGA.
WHEN YOUR LIFE IS IN DANGER,
YOUR DEMON NATURE
WILL TAKE CONTROL OF YOU.
- UHH.
[GRUNTING]
TETSUSAIGA.
- I SEE THEM!
OVER THERE!
[GASPS]
- HOW PATHETIC.
CRUSHED ALREADY.
HMM?
[HEARTBEAT]
WHAT IS HAPPENING?
- INUYASHA.
- HMM?
- OH, NO!
INUYASHA ISN'T
HOLDING TETSUSAIGA!
[HEARTBEAT]
- INUYASHA!
[GROWLING]
- KAGOME.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- INUYASHA TRANSFORMS
INTO A DEMON.
IF WE STICK AROUND,
HE MIGHT EVEN COME
AFTER US, TOO.
TOTOSAI WANTS US TO LEAVE,
BUT I WON'T ABANDON INUYASHA.
NOT NOW,
WHEN HE'S TRYING SO HARD
TO DISCOVER HIS TRUE POWER.
WAIT.
THE TETSUSAIGA
IS STARTING TO PULSATE.
NEXT TIME...
SEE YOU SOON.