>> WHAT THE HECK ARE
THOSE THINGS?
>> SHIPPO, KIRARA, GET DOWN!
WHAT THE...
DAMN IT.
>> GRRR!
QUIT JUMPING AROUND SO MUCH.
YOU DON'T WANT YOUR FRIENDS
TO DIE ALONE, NOW, DO YOU?
>> YOU ARE AWAKE.
I'M SO GLAD.
NOW JUST RELAX AND RECUPERATE.
>> A SACRED JEWEL SHARD?
THEN THIS MAN IS ONE OF THE BAND
OF 7?
>> WHAT DO I DO?
I KNOW I CAN'T USE
THE WIND SCAR.
SO WHAT CAN I...
I GOT AN IDEA.
>> YOU SHOULD HAVE STAYED DOWN.
IT'S USELESS.
>> UP HERE, CREEP!
>> HUH?
WIND SCAR!
>> [SCREAMING]
KAGOME...
HANG IN THERE, KAGOME.
I KNOW THIS SMELL.
IT'S THE SMELL OF DEAD BODIES
AND GRAVEYARD DIRT.
DOES THAT MEAN ONE OF THE BAND
OF 7 IS JUST UP AHEAD?
NO, IT'S DIFFERENT.
I'M VERY CLOSE.
>> HMM?
TELL ME, ARE YOU INUYASHA
BY ANY CHANCE?
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU
TO ARRIVE.
>> WAITING FOR ME?
HUH?
GOOD, SHE'S ALL RIGHT.
>> I TAKE IT THAT YOU'RE BEING
PURSUED.
>> WHO ARE YOU?
>> AS YOU CAN SEE, I AM THE HEAD
MONK OF THIS TOWN.
LATELY THERE HAS BEEN TALK IN
THE VILLAGE NEARBY THAT THE
SPIRITS OF THE BAND OF 7 WHO
WERE AMBUSHED AND PUT TO DEATH
OVER 10 YEARS AGO HAVE SOMEHOW
BEEN RESURRECTED, BRINGING GREAT
CALAMITY TO THIS REGION.
>> SO HE KNOWS OF THEM.
>> THE DEAD THAT YOU SAW ME
BURYING WHEN YOU FIRST ARRIVED
WERE BURNED TO DEATH BY THESE
RESURRECTED SPIRITS.
>> AND YET YOU SOMEHOW SURVIVED
THE ATTACK?
>> I WAS FILLED WITH SUCH FEAR
THAT I HID LIKE A COWARD BEHIND
A STATUE OF BUDDHA.
I UNDERSTAND THAT YOU ARE BEING
PURSUED BY THESE 7 EVIL SPIRITS.
>> LOOK, I'M NOT BEING PURSUED.
I'M THE ONE DOING THE PURSUING.
SO GET IT STRAIGHT.
>> I MEANT YOU NO OFFENSE.
BUT PLEASE ANSWER ME THIS.
WHY HAS THE BAND OF 7
BEEN RESURRECTED?
>> WHY DO YOU WANT TO KNOW THAT?
>> AS YOU KNOW, I SERVE BUDDHA,
BUT I WAS HELPLESS TO STOP
THE SLAUGHTER OF MY BRETHREN.
AND SO I WISH TO MAKE AMENDS.
IF I'M ABLE, I WISH TO PUT AT
PEACE THE SOULS OF THE DEAD.
>> THE SMELL.
JUST FORGET ABOUT IT.
THIS IS NO BUSINESS FOR A MONK
LIKE YOU.
I DEFINITELY SMELL A LIVING
PERSON.
THE OTHER SMELL MUST BE FROM
THE PEOPLE HE BURIED OUTSIDE.
>> WHAT IS THAT?
TAKE ME DOWN LOWER, BIRD.
YEP, I'D RECOGNIZE THAT SWAMP
OF DEVASTATION ANYWHERE.
THAT'S THE AFTER EFFECT OF
MASTER INUYASHA'S WIND SCAR.
OOH, I GUESS MASTER INUYASHA
DIDN'T COME NORTH SIMPLY TO
ENJOY THE DELIGHTFUL HOT SPRINGS
AND MOUNTAIN SCENERY.
AAH!
WHAT THE HECK IS THAT THING?
FLY HIGHER!
[SCREAMING]
FLY AWAY!
GET GOING, YOU STUPID CROW!
>> KOGA, PLEASE!
WAIT FOR US!
>> WHEN IT'S FOR KAGOME,
HE ALWAYS RUNS SO MUCH FASTER.
>> WHERE IS INUYASHA'S SCENT?
WAIT.
IT'S THE SMELL
OF GRAVEYARD DIRT.
>> SOMEONE NAMED NARAKU
CALLED FORTH THE DEAD SOULS.
TELL ME, WHO IS THIS NARAKU?
>> HE'S SORT OF LIKE A DEMON.
>> HOW DO YOU MEAN "SORT OF?"
>> NARAKU IS NOT A COMPLETE
DEMON.
RIGHT NOW, I WOULD IMAGINE
HE'S HIDING HIMSELF SOMEWHERE.
HE'S UNDERGOING ANOTHER
TRANSFORMATION AND INCREASING
HIS POWER.
AND HE'S USING THE BAND OF 7
AS A DECOY TO BUY TIME.
HUH?
>> [GRUNTS]
>> THAT SOUNDED A LOT
LIKE GINKOTSU.
HOW IN THE HECK COULD HE STILL
BE ALIVE?
LISTEN, MONK, IF YOU WANT
TO STAY ALIVE, STAY HIDDEN.
>> DAMN, GINKOTSU.
HE SHOULD HAVE WAITED LONGER
BEFORE COMING.
I'VE LEARNED ONE IMPORTANT
THING, THOUGH.
NARAKU CANNOT BE TRUSTED.
>> YOU CAN ALL DIE NOW.
>> INUYASHA!
>> GINKOTSU!
THIS TIME I'M GONNA TAKE YOU
DOWN.
>> GRRR!
>> THOSE METAL THREADS AGAIN.
>> I GOTCHA.
>> IF YOU THINK THESE THINGS
CAN HOLD ME DOWN...
THEN THINK AGAIN!
HUH.
YOU HAD IT COMING TO YOU.
I SMELL SMOKE.
KAGOME.
HUH?
>> [LAUGHS]
I AM RENKOTSU OF THE BAND OF 7.
>> WHY, YOU...
LIAR.
BUT I DON'T GET IT.
HE SMELLS LIKE AN ORDINARY
HUMAN.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER, INUYASHA?
I DARE SAY YOU LOOK JUST
A LITTLE CONFUSED.
YOUR NOSE IS EXTREMELY
SENSITIVE.
AM I RIGHT?
I HONESTLY THOUGHT YOU WERE ON
TO ME EARLIER.
BUT THEN I SUSPECT THAT I DIDN'T
EMANATE THE SCENT OF DEAD BODIES
OR GRAVEYARD DIRT.
AM I CORRECT, INUYASHA?
>> DAMN IT.
I GET IT.
IT'S THIS PLACE.
>> IT SEEMS THAT TAKING OVER
THIS TEMPLE WAS A WISE MOVE.
IT'S SURROUNDED BY GRAVEYARD
DIRT, OF COURSE.
SO YOU WOULDN'T REALIZE
THE SCENT CAME FROM ME.
I WORE THE CLOTHING THAT THE
REAL MONK KINDLY LEFT BEHIND.
YOUR SENSE OF SMELL IS SO SHARP
THAT YOU CAUGHT HIS SCENT RIGHT
AWAY, AND IT IRONICALLY HELPED
PUT YOUR SUSPICIONS ASIDE.
>> WHY, YOU...
YOU KILLED THE MONKS
OF THE TEMPLE?
>> AND I HAD JUST FINISHED
BURYING THEM WHEN YOU FIRST
ARRIVED.
>> I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
HOW COULD I BE SO BLIND?
>> HELLO, WHAT'S THAT SMOKE?
AAH!
[GRUNTING]
WHAT?
OH, NO!
IT'S KAGOME.
WAKE UP!
WAKE UP, SHIPPO!
IT'S ME, MYOGA!
SHIPPO!
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO ME?
THE LAST THING I REMEMBER WAS
THE MONK BRINGING IN THAT
INCENSE, AND THEN I GOT REAL
SLEEPY.
AAH!
MIROKU, WAKE UP!
SANGO!
KAGOME!
OH, NO!
THEY'RE NOT WAKING UP!
THE POISON HASN'T GONE AWAY!
>> AAH!
POISONOUS GAS!
>> YOU CANNOT ESCAPE FROM
JAKOTSU'S POISON.
>> KAGOME, PLEASE HANG IN THERE.
>> HA HA HA HA!
SO, KAGOME, YOU'RE THE ONE WHO
HAS THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS,
CORRECT?
>> KAGOME!
KAGOME!
>> PLEASE, SHIPPO, RUN AWAY.
>> NO, I WON'T!
I GAVE THEM AN ANTIDOTE FOR
THE POISON, BUT IT DIDN'T WORK.
FIRST THINGS FIRST.
I GOTTA PUT OUT THIS FIRE.
COME ON, THERE'S GOT TO BE
SOMETHING USEFUL IN HERE.
OOH, AHA!
MAYBE THE WIND FROM MY SMASHING
TOP WILL HELP.
GO MAGIC SMASHING TOP!
OH, NO!
IT'S MAKING IT WORSE!
>> [SQUEAKS]
>> KIRARA!
>> DAMN IT.
YOU SET THE TEMPLE ON FIRE.
>> [LAUGHS]
THE FLAMES ONLY HASTEN
THE INEVITABLE.
YOUR FRIENDS WERE ALREADY
HALF-DEAD FROM THE POISON
ANYWAY.
>> GET OUT OF MY WAY!
>> WHAT THE...
>> GOING SOMEWHERE?
>> [INUYASHA SHOUTS]
>> IT LOOKS AS IF YOU'RE IN A
BIT OF A PREDICAMENT.
>> YOU...
YOU BASTARD.
>> I KEEP CATCHING A SCENT OF
DEAD BODIES AND GRAVEYARD DIRT.
>> HI THERE.
YOU MUST BE KOGA OF THE WOLF
DEMON TRIBE.
>> GOODNESS, AND I THOUGHT I'D
SEEN EVERYTHING.
>> HI, YOURSELF.
I FIGURED YOU MUST BE A PAL
KYOKOTSU.
I'D KNOW THAT SMELL ANYWHERE.
TELL ME, HAVE YOU COME HERE
LOOKING FOR REVENGE?
>> HMM...
THE OUTFIT I KIND OF LIKE,
AND A LITTLE USE OF FUR IS
DEFINITELY WORKING FOR ME,
BUT I HATE TO TELL YOU
YOU'RE JUST NOT DOING IT FOR ME.
>> HUH?
WHAT ON EARTH IS THIS FOOL
TALKING ABOUT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> ENOUGH CHIT-CHAT.
LET'S GET DOWN TO BUSINESS!
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
UP TO, BUDDY, BUT I'M TAKING
YOU DOWN!
WHAT'S WITH THAT SWORD?
IT MOVES LIKE A SNAKE.
>> LOOK, I'M IN A RUSH,
SO QUIT RESISTING.
HURRY UP AND DIE SO I CAN WATCH
INUYASHA'S DEATH, OK?
>> HUH?
HEY, WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
WHAT WAS THAT YOU WERE JUST
SAYING ABOUT INUYASHA'S DEATH?
>> WHAT IS YOUR RELATIONSHIP
WITH INUYASHA?
>> I DON'T CARE WHAT HAPPENS TO
THAT MUTT, BUT THERE'S A GIRL
CALLED KAGOME TRAVELING
WITH HIM.
SHE'D BETTER NOT BE
IN ANY DANGER.
>> OH, COME ON.
WHO CARES ABOUT WOMEN?
SHE'S PROBABLY LONG DEAD BY NOW.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN "DEAD?"
>> KIRARA!
KIRARA, PLEASE SNAP OUT OF IT!
IT'S GOT TO BE THAT WOUND.
I'LL TRY AND MOVE THE POST
OFF OF YOU.
MY FRIENDS LIVES ARE IN DANGER,
AND I CAN'T DO ANYTHING AT ALL
TO HELP THEM!
IT'S USELESS.
HUH?
COME ON, PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER,
SHIPPO, AND BE A MAN.
I'VE GOT TO KEEP IT TOGETHER.
I'LL DO MY VERY BEST TO PROTECT
THEM UNTIL INUYASHA COMES.
BUT I--BUT I DON'T HAVE
THE STRENGTH TO DRAG THEM ALL
OUTSIDE.
OH, WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
COME ON, USE YOUR HEAD, SHIPPO.
THERE'S GOT TO BE A WAY.
AAH!
>> KAGOME.
HANG IN THERE.
I'M COMING.
>> HA HA HA!
GIVE UP, INUYASHA.
IT'S ALL OVER FOR YOUR FRIENDS.
THEY'LL EITHER DIE
FROM THE FLAMES OR FROM
JAKOTSU'S POISON.
EITHER WAY, THERE'S NO SAVING
THEM.
>> WHY DON'T YOU SHUT UP?
AAH!
>> I'VE GOT TO KEEP IT TOGETHER.
I'VE GOT TO KEEP IT TOGETHER.
>> GINKOTSU.
>> YES!
I HAVE ANOTHER IDEA.
I'LL RUN YOU THROUGH.
>> GO AHEAD AND TRY IT.
>> HA HA HA HA!
>> AAH!
>> YES!
CAN'T DO MUCH WITHOUT
YOUR SWORD, CAN YOU?
>> I'LL SHOW YOU WHAT I CAN DO.
IRON WEAVER SOUL STEALER!
>> WHAT?
>> OH, NO, YOU DON'T.
>> OK, THAT'S IT.
I'VE WASTED ENOUGH TIME ON YOU,
YOU FREAK!
NOW TRY THIS.
WIND SCAR!
>> [SCREAMING]
>> THE TEMPLE.
MIROKU, SANGO, KAGOME!
OUT OF MY WAY.
>> HMM...
SO BOTHERING TO KILL ME
WASN'T WORTH HIS TIME.
I'M INSULTED.
STILL, I DID MANAGE TO FIND OUT
A LITTLE MORE ABOUT NARAKU, AND
I HAVE THE SHIKON JEWEL SHARDS.
WELL, ALL THINGS CONSIDERED,
THAT'S NOT TOO BAD
FOR A DAY'S WORK.
>> KAGOME!
KAGOME!
>> AAH!
>> WHOA, THAT WAS SCARY.
IT'S THE FIRST TIME ANYONE HAS
SIDESTEPPED MY ATTACK LIKE THAT.
I DO BELIEVE THIS GUY
IS BECOMING A BOTHER.
HEY, WAIT!
>> SORRY, I DON'T HAVE TIME TO
FOOL AROUND WITH YOU RIGHT NOW.
I'VE GOT TO RUN.
BUT THE NEXT TIME WE MEET,
I'LL SHOW YOU WHAT SCARY
IS ALL ABOUT.
>> HEY, KOGA, WAIT UP!
>> KOGA HAS NO QUALMS ABOUT
RETREATING, DOES HE?
>> KAGOME!
>> [KIRARA SQUEAKS]
>> KIRARA?
KIRARA.
KIRARA?
HUH?
SHIPPO!
>> INUYASHA.
>> I'M GLAD TO SEE YOU'RE ALIVE.
>> I KNEW.
I KNEW.
I KNEW I HAD TO BE STRONG.
I TRIED MY VERY BEST.
>> I KNOW.
YOU WERE VERY BRAVE.
YOU PROTECTED EVERYONE FROM
THE HEAT WITH YOUR FOX FIRE.
HUH?
>> I KNOW, BUT...
BUT...
EVEN THOUGH I TRIED
TO SAVE THEM...
[CRYING]
THEY ALL STOPPED BREATHING,
INUYASHA!
>> [WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> THEY ALL STOPPED BREATHING!
>> WHY ARE YOU CURSING YOURSELF,
INUYASHA?
AFTER ALL, YOU ARE ONLY A
HALF-DEMON.
>> SESSHOMARU.
>> YOU CAN BARELY TAKE CARE
OF YOURSELF.
AND YET YOU WIELD THE
TETSUSAIGA, WHICH WAS FORGED IN
ORDER TO PROTECT OTHERS.
>> NEXT ON "INUYASHA,"
INUYASHA SHEDS TEARS FOR
THE FIRST TIME.
>> YOUR FRIENDS NEVER STOOD
A CHANCE.
>> THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING.
COME ON.
OPEN YOUR EYES, KAGOME.