[LOW SINGING]
>> THE TOMB OF THE 7 IS WHERE
THE BODIES OF THE 7 MERCENARIES
KNOWN AS THE BAND OF 7 WERE
BURIED.
RECENTLY, THIS ACCURSED MONUMENT
SPLIT INTO TWO.
>> BUT THAT IS NOT ALL,
PRIESTESS.
THE BONES OF THE 7 MERCENARIES
BURIED HERE ALL INEXPLICABLY
DISAPPEARED.
>> AND WE'RE WORRIED THAT IT'S
SOME KIND OF CURSE AND THEY HAVE
RETURNED.
>> ♪ PURE HAS BECOME IMPURE... ♪
>> YES, I UNDERSTAND.
I SHALL PURIFY THE SITE.
>> OH, THAT WOULD BE SUCH A
SERVICE TO US, PRIESTESS.
>> HOW CAN WE EVER THANK YOU?
>> OH, WHAT A GREAT RELIEF.
>> USELESS, BUT IT'LL PUT THEIR
MINDS AT EASE.
I DON'T DETECT ANY SIGN OF EVIL
HERE ANYMORE.
IN FACT, THE AIR IS UNUSUALLY
CLEAN AND CLEAR.
IS THIS BECAUSE OF MOUNT
HAKUREI?
MOUNT HAKUREI, THE SPIRITUAL
MOUNTAIN THAT PURGED THE SINS OF
ALL EVIL-DOERS.
>> I HEARD OF A SPECIAL PLACE
WHERE EVEN VILLAINS LIKE ME CAN
FIND SALVATION.
TAKE THIS LOCK OF HAIR AND BURY
IT SO I MIGHT BE SAVED.
>> PLEASE, FORGIVE ME, KANSUKE,
BUT I WILL NOT BE ABLE TO
FULFILL YOUR WISH.
TO LIVE IS TO DIE.
TO DIE IS TO LIVE.
>> KAGOME!
>> UHH...
INUYASHA.
>> I'M GLAD TO SEE YOU'RE ALIVE.
>> I KNEW!
I KNEW!
>> I KNOW.
YOU WERE VERY BRAVE.
YOU PROTECTED EVERYONE FROM THE
HEAT WITH YOUR FOX FIRE.
>> THEY ALL STOPPED BREATHING,
INUYASHA!
[CRYING]
[SOBBING]
>> KAGOME!
THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING.
COME ON, KAGOME, OPEN YOUR EYES.
SAY SOMETHING, KAGOME!
>> MASTER INUYASHA, PLEASE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> YOU WERE HERE TOO, MYOGA?
>> BOTH YOU AND SHIPPO WILL END
UP BURNING TO DEATH UNLESS YOU
GET OUT OF HERE NOW.
WE'VE GOT TO GET EVERYBODY TO
SOMEPLACE SAFER.
>> ARGH!
DAMN!
[SOBBING]
I SHOULD'VE KNOWN RENKOTSU
WOULD PULL SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
IF ONLY I HAD DEFEATED
GINKOTSU SOONER.
[SOBBING]
DON'T CRY, SHIPPO.
YOU DID EVERYTHING YOU COULD.
>> BUT IT WASN'T ENOUGH, AND IF
THEY ALL DIE, I'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO FORGIVE MYSELF!
IT'S MY FAULT!
IF ONLY I HADN'T BROUGHT THEM TO
THIS TEMPLE!
>> JUST QUIT IT!
YOU'RE NOT TO BLAME FOR
ANYTHING.
IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
>> YOU'RE JUST SAYING THAT!
IT'S ALL MY FAULT, AND YOU KNOW
IT!
>> HEY, ENOUGH ALREADY.
CRYING ISN'T GONNA SOLVE
ANYTHING.
WE'VE GOT TO GET THESE 3 AWAY
FROM HERE IN TO AN OPEN AREA.
>> HUH?
[GROANING]
IT'S OK, SHIPPO.
I'LL DO IT.
>> HUH?
INUYASHA?
>> KAGOME, PLEASE BE ALIVE.
[PANTING]
>> PLEASE WAIT, KOGA.
>> WHAT'S THE BIG HURRY?
DO YOU EVEN KNOW WHERE KAGOME
IS?
>> 'COURSE I DO.
SHE'S VERY CLOSE.
SHE'S CLOSE, ALL RIGHT, BUT WHAT
IF THAT MUTT COULDN'T PROTECT
KAGOME?
[PANTING]
>> OH...
>> I SEE.
APPARENTLY, THAT GIRL DIED.
WHAT IS THIS?
WHY DO I SHED THESE TEARS?
I DO NOT FEEL ANY SADNESS.
[CRYING]
>> HEY, SHIPPO, LET ME ASK YOU
AGAIN.
>> HUH?
>> ARE YOU POSITIVE THAT THE 3
OF THEM SWALLOWED THE ANTIDOTE?
>> UH...THEY DID.
I'M SURE OF IT.
IT WAS A SPECIAL ANTIDOTE THAT
GINENGI GAVE ME.
DOESN'T MATTER.
IT DIDN'T HAVE ANY EFFECT.
>> HMMM.
HUH?
HEY, SHIPPO, DO YOU KNOW WHERE
MASTER INUYASHA WENT?
>> UH-UH.
>> OH, NO.
I SURE HOPE HE ISN'T DOING
ANYTHING RASH!
>> ARGH!
COME ON OUT, YOU FILTHY
BASTARDS!
I'M RIGHT HERE WAITING FOR YOU,
SO IF YOU WANT TO FIGHT, THEN
COME ON OUT.
JAKOTSU, RENKOTSU, AND WHOEVER
ELSE I HAVEN'T KILLED YET.
I AM GONNA FINISH OFF EVERY LAST
ONE OF YOU.
DAMMIT!
I SAID QUIT HIDING AND COME OUT
AND FIGHT!
[GROANING]
DAMN.
>> SO, RENKOTSU, IS INUYASHA
STILL ALIVE?
>> YES.
REST ASSURED.
>> OH, I'M SO GLAD.
I WAS THINKING ABOUT THAT TASTY
LITTLE MORSEL INUYASHA THE WHOLE
TIME I WAS FIGHTING KOGA.
TO BE PERFECTLY HONEST WITH YOU,
IT WAS A LITTLE DISTRACTING.
>> SO, YOU LET KOGA GET AWAY,
DID YOU?
SHAME ON YOU, JAKOTSU.
>> SORRY.
COULDN'T BE HELPED.
THE GUY RAN SUPER FAST.
YOU SHOULD'VE SEEN HIM.
>> EXCELLENT.
THIS IS JUST RIGHT.
[GROANING]
JUST WAIT, GINKOTSU.
YOU'RE ABOUT TO BE REWARDED.
OH, YES, AND I SHALL SEE TO IT
THAT YOU ARE MUCH, MUCH
STRONGER.
[YAWNING]
>> THIS IS ALL SO TEDIOUS.
I WONDER WHAT INUYASHA'S DOING.
>> DAMN.
I REALLY MESSED UP.
IF ONLY I HAD REALIZED SOONER
JUST WHO RENKOTSU WAS.
DAMN.
DAMN!
>> WHY ARE YOU CURSING YOURSELF,
INUYASHA?
>> HUH?
GET LOST.
I'M IN NO MOOD TO TALK TO YOU.
>> SO, ONLY NOW YOU REALIZE HOW
WEAK YOU ARE.
>> SHUT UP!
>> AFTER ALL, YOU ARE ONLY A
HALF-DEMON.
YOU CAN BARELY TAKE CARE OF
YOURSELF AND YET YOU WIELD THE
TETSUSAIGA WHICH WAS FORGED IN A
WAR TO PROTECT OTHERS.
YOUR FRIENDS NEVER STOOD A
CHANCE.
[GROANING]
>> THEN MAYBE I SHOULD KILL YOU,
SESSHOMARU, AND TAKE YOUR
TENSEIGA.
THEN I COULD RESURRECT KAGOME
AND THE OTHER TWO.
>> HMM, AS IF YOU COULD EVER
MASTERMIND TENSEIGA.
[GROANING]
>> WELL, WE WON'T KNOW UNLESS I
TRY!
HE'S GONE.
OR MAYBE HE WAS NEVER THERE.
AM I STARTING TO SEE THINGS NOW?
>> HELLO?
HE'S NOT HERE.
>> LOOK, HERE COMES LORD
SESSHOMARU NOW.
>> LORD SESSHOMARU, WHERE HAVE
YOU BEEN?
>> I FOUND HIM.
>> HUH?
>> UH...FOUND WHO?
>> THAT LITTLE TROUBLEMAKER.
>> LITTLE TROUBLEMAKER?
LITTLE TROUBLEMAKER...
OH, YOU MEAN THE BOY THAT WAS
WITH NARAKU!
>> YOU MEAN KOHAKU?
>> OH...
OH, WAIT!
PLEASE WAIT, LORD SESSHOMARU!
>> IS LORD SESSHOMARU GOING TO
KILL KOHAKU?
[SNIFFLING]
>> INUYASHA?
>> SHIPPO, PLEASE DON'T CRY
ANYMORE.
MEN NEVER SHOW THEIR TEARS NO
MATTER WHAT.
[SNIFFLING]
>> OK, I'LL TRY.
>> KAGOME, FORGIVE ME.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
IF I HADN'T FAILED YOU, YOU'D...
YOU'D STILL BE RIGHT HERE NOW.
>> INUYASHA, I CAN'T...
I CAN'T BREATHE.
>> KAGOME?
[GROANING]
I'M KIND OF DIZZY.
>> BUT YOU WERE--
>> THAT'S TO BE EXPECTED.
I SUCKED OUT A WAD OF BLOOD WITH
THE POISON.
[SUCKING]
WOW, I GOTTA TELL YOU,
EVEN FOR ME, THIS POISON PACKS
QUITE A WALLOP.
>> ARE YOU TELLING ME THAT--
THAT YOU...
>> WELL, WELL.
SO, YOU'LL BARE MY CHILD THEN?
>> I SHOULD'VE LET THIS ONE DIE.
>> MIROKU?
>> HUH?
WAS IT JUST A DREAM?
HOW DISAPPOINTING.
>> I SHOULD'VE KNOWN YOU WERE
DREAMING ABOUT WOMEN.
SANGO, HEY, ARE YOU OK?
[GROANING]
>> UH-HUH.
>> THAT MEANS THAT EVERYONE'S
STILL ALIVE.
I'M SO GLAD.
>> I WAS ONLY ABLE TO REVIVE YOU
BECAUSE THE POISON HAD NOT
COMPLETELY GONE THROUGH YOUR
BODIES.
HAD I BEEN ANY LATER, IT
WOULD'VE BEEN TOO LATE.
>> WELL, I GOTTA HAND IT TO YOU,
MYOGA, I GUESS YOU CAN BE USEFUL
EVERY ONCE IN AWHILE.
>> WHY, YOU INSOLENT LITTLE
WHIPPERSNAPPER!
HOW DARE YOU SPEAK TO ME LIKE
THAT!
>> I'M SORRY, INUYASHA, FOR
MAKING YOU WORRY.
>> STOP IT.
DON'T APOLOGIZE.
>> INUYASHA?
>> HUH?
HEY, WHAT GIVES, INUYASHA?
I THOUGHT MEN NEVER SHOW THEIR
TEARS NO MATTER WHAT!
>> SHUT UP!
>> OOH!
>> DON'T BE SILLY, SHIPPO.
I HAVE SERVED MASTER INUYASHA
FOR MANY, MANY YEARS, AND I HAVE
NEVER ONCE SEEN HIM SHED TEARS.
>> WELL, THEN WHAT DO YOU CALL
THESE BABIES?
>> LET ME TAKE A CLOSER LOOK.
WHY SHOULD I CRY?
EVERYONE'S ALIVE NOW, AREN'T
THEY?
>> INUYASHA, THANK YOU.
>> PURE HAS BECOME IMPURE.
IMPURE HAS NOW BECOME PURE.
GOOD HAS NOW BECOME EVIL.
EVIL HAS BECOME GOOD.
FOR ONE TO LIVE IS TO DIE.
FOR ONE TO DIE IS TO LIVE.
PERHAPS IT IS THE POWER OF
MOUNT HAKUREI TO PURGE, BUT IN
THE SURROUNDING AREAS, THERE'S
ABSOLUTELY NO MIASNU.
IT IS ALMOST TOO PURE.
IT MUST BE PAINFUL FOR YOU TO BE
HERE AS WELL AS FOR I.
IS IT IMPOSSIBLE FOR ME TO GET
ANY CLOSER TO MOUNT HAKUREI?
I SENSE THE PRESENCE OF A JEWEL
SHARD.
HMM?
>> THIS WILL DO.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> COME AGAIN IN 3 DAYS AND I'LL
APPLY MORE OINTMENT.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH, DOCTOR.
>> THAT MAN...
[PHONE RINGING]
HE HAS A JEWEL SHARD IN HIS
NECK.
>> TAKE CARE.
>> YOU TAKE CARE, TOO, CHIYO.
HUH?
OH, MY.
SUCH A BEAUTIFUL PRIESTESS.
>> WHO IS THAT MAN?
>> OH, THAT MAN'S NAME IS DOCTOR
SUIKOTSU.
>> A DOCTOR?
>> CHIYO, DO WE HAVE A VISITOR?
>> HELLO, THERE.
YOU ARE KNOWN AS SUIKOTSU?
>> YES, AND YOU ARE...?
>> MY NAME IS KIKYO.
[CHILDREN LAUGHING, CHATTERING]
WHETHER HE BE A DEMON OR A
HUMAN, IF ONE WITH A WICKED
HEART IMPLANT THE JEWEL SHARD IN
HIS BODY, THE SHARD WILL BECOME
COMPLETELY DEFILED.
HOWEVER, THIS MAN'S SHARD IS NOT
TARNISHED AT ALL.
THE CURIOUS THING IS THIS MAN
HAS ALREADY DIED.
>> I'M SORRY, INUYASHA.
I LET THE JEWEL SHARDS GET
STOLEN.
>> YEAH, I KNOW, BUT DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT TOO MUCH, KAGOME.
WE CAN ALWAYS GET IT BACK LATER.
BUT HERE.
DRINK THIS.
MIROKU, SANGO, YOU, TOO.
>> HUH?
>> YEAH, BUT WHAT IS IT?
>> JUST DRINK IT.
COME ON.
IT'S MY SPECIAL POTION.
I SUCKED OUT A LARGE AMOUNT OF
BLOOD FROM YOU 3 ALONG WITH THE
POISON.
NOW, IF YOU DRINK THIS POTION,
IT'LL INCREASE YOUR BODY'S BLOOD
CONTENT AND MAKE YOU HEALTHY.
>> MAYBE SO IF IT DOESN'T KILL
US FIRST.
>> JUST GRIN AND BEAR IT, SANGO,
BECAUSE THE LONGER WE TAKE TO
RECOVER, THE LONGER WE'RE
VULNERABLE TO OUR ENEMIES.
>> HE'S RIGHT.
WE HAVE TO GET BETTER AS SOON AS
POSSIBLE.
>> HEY, MYOGA, LOOK!
I BROUGHT YOU SOME MORE
INGREDIENTS.
>> EXCELLENT.
GOOD JOB, SHIPPO.
>> HUH?
>> I COMBINED THE BLOOD OF THIS
POISONOUS SNAKE WITH THESE RARE
FUNGI INSIDE MY BODY,
REGURGITATED IT ALL, AND VOILA,
MY SPECIAL POTION.
WATCH AND LEARN.
[SUCKING]
NOW JUST MIX THINGS AROUND A
LITTLE.
>> AND HERE YOU GO.
>> THANK YOU.
>> SO, WHO'S FIRST?
>> NO THANKS.
>> I THINK I'M STARTING TO FEEL
MORE SICK.
>> THERE'S SOME SECRETS BETTER
LEFT UNKNOWN.
>> HUH?
>> KAGOME!
>> OH, HI, KOGA.
>> ARE YOU OK?
I CAME AS FAST AS I COULD.
>> KOGA.
>> HUH?
>> WHY YOU...
>> OH, HEY THERE.
YOU'RE STILL ALIVE, TOO?
>> I'LL KILL YOU!
>> HEY!
>> HOW DARE YOU!
>> SO, KOGA, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
HERE?
>> WELL, I WAS PURSUING NARAKU
WHEN A STRANGE WARRIOR WIELDING
A SNAKE-LIKE SWORD APPEARED.
>> THAT SOUNDS A LOT LIKE...
>> GINKOTSU.
>> THIS RATHER ODD FELLOW
PROCEEDED TO TELL ME THAT YOU
WERE DEAD.
>> HOW THOUGHTFUL!
YOU WERE WORRIED ABOUT ME.
>> LET GO OF HER HANDS RIGHT
NOW, KOGA, OR I'LL RIP YOUR
ARMS OFF.
>> YOU ARE DESPICABLE, INUYASHA.
KAGOME'S HANDS FEEL MUCH COLDER
THAN THEY USUALLY DO, AND HER
BEAUTIFUL CHEEKS, WHICH ARE
USUALLY SO ROSY, ARE PALE LIKE A
FISH'S BELLY.
I CAN TELL YOU PUT KAGOME'S LIFE
IN TERRIBLE DANGER.
WELL, I WOULD NEVER LET ANYTHING
LIKE THAT HAPPEN TO HER!
>> YOU...WHY YOU...
>> HAH!
>> MASTER INUYASHA.
>> THAT'S IT.
TIME TO TEACH THIS GUY A LESSON
HE'LL NEVER FORGET.
>> YEAH. YEAH!
>> I WON'T DO IT.
I WON'T...EVER LET ANYTHING LIKE
THAT HAPPEN TO KAGOME AGAIN, SO
YOU CAN JUST GET LOST!
>> INUYASHA.
[GROANS]
>> THESE CHILDREN LOST THEIR
PARENTS TO FAMINE AND DISEASE,
AND SO EVER SINCE, I'VE TAKEN
CARE OF THEM.
THEY'RE SLEEPING SO SOUNDLY.
[PHONE RINGING]
HUH?
WHAT IS IT?
>> UH...NOTHING.
>> HELP!
DOCTOR SUIKOTSU!
PLEASE, DOCTOR, WE NEED YOUR
HELP.
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM?
>> HE FELL AND BADLY INJURED HIS
LEG WITH A SICKLE.
>> IT HURTS!
IT HURTS SO BAD!
>> DOCTOR SUIKOTSU?
>> HUH?
>> IS THERE ANYTHING I CAN DO
TO HELP YOU?
>> UM, THANK YOU, LADY KIKYO.
I'D APPRECIATE THAT.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU LOOK SO PALE.
>> IT'S NOTHING.
I'M JUST NOT FEELING WELL.
[GROANING]
WHAT A RELIEF.
THE WOUND AS NOT AS DEEP AS I'D
FEARED.
>> IT HURTS!
IT HURTS!
>> DOCTOR SUIKOTSU, YOU SEEM
TIRED.
SHALL I TAKE OVER?
>> OH, THANK YOU.
PLEASE DO.
>> DOCTOR SUIKOTSU?
>> HUH?
>> THE TWO MEN JUST LEFT.
>> I'M SO EMBARRASSED.
>> DON'T BE.
>> DOCTOR SUIKOTSU DOESN'T LIKE
THE SIGHT OF BLOOD MUCH.
>> AND I CALL MYSELF A
PHYSICIAN.
THE MOMENT I SEE BLOOD, MY WHOLE
BODY STARTS TO SHAKE
UNCONTROLLABLY.
>> HAVE YOU BEEN A DOCTOR IN
THIS VILLAGE YOUR WHOLE LIFE?
>> NO, I WAS BORN IN THE EASTERN
REGION.
FOR A LONG TIME, I TRAVELED FROM
VILLAGE TO VILLAGE LOOKING AFTER
THE SICK AND INFIRMED.
FINALLY, I ENDED UP HERE.
IT'S POOR, BUT BECAUSE IT'S DEEP
IN THE COLD NORTH, THE WAR
HASN'T REACHED US.
IT'S PEACEFUL.
HUH?
[GROANING]
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER?
DOCTOR SUIKOTSU?
>> MY HANDS.
>> HUH?
>> MY--MY HANDS!
BLOOD.
I MUST WASH MY HANDS.
I MUST WASH.
>> BUT THERE'S NO BLOOD ON YOUR
HANDS, DOCTOR.
>> DOCTOR SUIKOTSU GETS LIKE
THAT SOMETIMES.
WHEN IT'S BAD, HE'LL KEEP
WASHING FOR A WHOLE HOUR OR
MORE.
>> THE BLOOD.
THE BLOOD.
IT WON'T COME OFF.
I CAN'T WASH THIS BLOOD FROM MY
HANDS.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> ANOTHER DEAD PERSON APPEARS
FOR THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD IN
HIS POSESSION.
>> YOU BELONG IN THE BAND OF 7.
>> I AM A PHYSICIAN.
YOU ARE MISTAKING ME FOR SOMEONE
ELSE.
>> QUIT LYING AND SHOW YOUR TRUE
SELF!
>> CHIYO, UTA, RUN AWAY!
>> HUH?
HE LET THE CHILDREN GO.
ISN'T HE WITH THE BAND OF 7?
>> NEXT ON "INUYASHA," THE
SECRET OF THE PURE LIGHT.
THE MAN WITH TWO HEARTS NOW
AWAKENS!