[BIRDS CAWING]
- SHOW YOURSELF, TSUBAKI!
- JUST AS I FEARED,
IT IS THE SAME WOMAN AFTER ALL.
- WHO ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- THE PRIESTESS WHO WAS PASSED
OVER FOR MY SISTER KIKYO.
- SISTER,
WHO IS THAT PRIESTESS?
- HER NAME IS TSUBAKI.
- I NEVER IMAGINED SHE WOULD
TURN TO THE DARK SIDE.
- WHO THE HECK CARES
WHAT HAPPENED IN THE PAST?
I WANT TO KNOW WHERE SHE IS NOW!
WHAT'S THE MATTER, KAGOME?
- DEEP INSIDE,
I SENSE THE SACRED JEWEL.
- ALL RIGHT!
- WAIT. THIS AREA
COULD BE DANGEROUS.
- HUH?
- WHAT DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT THIS PLACE, KAEDE?
- LEGEND TELLS OF AN OGRE THAT
WAS SEALED AWAY IN THIS REGION.
- AN OGRE?
[PANTING]
- OVER THERE!
[GROWLING]
- HMPH. FIGURES THEY'D BE HERE.
GET OUT OF MY WAY!
HYAH!
- HIRAIKOTSU!
- HMM?
[GROANING]
- YOU'VE FINALLY COME TO.
- AAH! YOU AGAIN!
- CALM DOWN.
I HAVE NO INTENTION
OF HARMING YOU.
I JUST...
- JUST WHAT?
- I JUST WANT TO ASK
IF YOU WILL BEAR MY CHILDREN.
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
- HOW ABOUT YOU?
WOULD YOU BE WILLING
TO HAVE MY CHILDREN?
- HMM?
- NOT VERY CHOOSY, ARE YOU?
- THERE'S ENOUGH OF ME
TO GO AROUND.
- HI. YOU'RE BOTH FINALLY AWAKE.
- HMM?
THERE'S THE LITTLE DEMON!
- KEEP YOUR DISTANCE!
- HUH?
- YOU'RE MISTAKEN.
SHIPPO IS THE ONE WHO HAS TAKEN
CARE OF YOU ALL THIS TIME.
- HUH? THIS DEMON HAS?
- I WAS ORDERED
BY KAGOME AND THE OTHERS
NOT TO TOUCH YOU TWO,
AND SO THAT LEFT SHIPPO TO TAKE
CARE OF THE BOTH OF YOU LADIES.
- MAYBE I SHOULDN'T
HAVE BOTHERED!
- YOU MEAN HE'S NOT A BAD DEMON?
- I HAVE NEVER HURT A HUMAN.
- ARE YOU CERTAIN?
- HMM.
- IT'S COMPLETELY UNDERSTANDABLE
THAT PRIESTESSES
SUCH AS YOURSELVES
WOULD CONSIDER ALL DEMONS BAD.
[GIRLS LAUGHING]
- HMM? WHAT'S WRONG?
UH...UH...
- SO CUTE!
- ADORABLE!
- I LOVE HIS TAIL!
- AND THESE EARS!
- MIROKU!
[GIRLS LAUGHING]
- THAT'S THE PRICE
YOU'LL HAVE TO PAY
IN ORDER TO PROVE
YOU'RE NOT A BAD DEMON.
[SIGHS]
LUCKY YOU.
- TELL US,
WHY DO YOU HUNT DOWN TSUBAKI?
- YES. ISN'T THAT INUYASHA
FELLOW A REALLY BAD DEMON?
- LISTEN, TSUBAKI CURSED KAGOME
TO SEND HER TO HER DEATH.
- IMPOSSIBLE!
- SHE WOULDN'T!
- NOW, I DON'T KNOW WHAT
TSUBAKI TOLD BOTH OF YOU,
BUT SHE'S A DARK PRIESTESS,
AND SHE CURSES INNOCENT PEOPLE.
- HMM?
- HAH! THAT WAS
HARDLY WORTH THE EFFORT.
- INDEED. THOSE SHIKIGAMI
WERE NOT STRONG AT ALL.
- DOES THAT MEAN TSUBAKI'S POWER
IS BEGINNING TO WEAKEN?
- BUT WHY, THOUGH?
SHE HAS THE SACRED JEWEL.
- SHE PROBABLY DOESN'T KNOW
HOW TO USE IT PROPERLY.
LET'S KEEP MOVING. COME ON.
THIS IS IT?
- YEAH.
- WHAT IS THIS TOWER?
- THE PLACE WHERE YOU'LL DIE.
- HUH?
[CREAKING]
- KAGURA, YOU AGAIN.
- I KNEW IT.
NARAKU AND TSUBAKI
HAVE BOTH JOINED FORCES.
- NARAKU'S WITH HER, HUH?
THAT'S ALL THE BETTER.
I'LL KILL ALL THREE OF YOU
WHILE I'M HERE.
- HA! DON'T BE SO HASTY.
I'M NOT THE ONE YOU SHOULD
BE BATTLING, INUYASHA.
I MERELY CAME HERE TODAY
TO WITNESS YOUR TRAGIC DEATHS.
[GROWLING]
- HUH.
THIS'LL BE EASY.
IT'S PROBABLY JUST
ANOTHER DEMON PUPPET.
HYAH!
- INUYASHA!
- UNH!
HUH. HE'S A LITTLE STRONGER
THAN I FIGURED.
TRY AND STOP THIS!
HYAH!
- DANCE OF BLADES!
[ROARING]
- AAH!
- YOU'RE HARDLY AN OBSERVER.
HIRAIKOTSU!
- JUST STAVING OFF BOREDOM.
DANCE OF BLADES!
- AAH!
UNH.
- INUYASHA!
[GROWLING]
- UNH! UHH!
- DANCE OF THE DRAGON!
- AAH! UNH!
- DANCE OF BLADES!
- NO, YOU DON'T!
[GASP]
UHH! UNH!
[GROWLING]
- TIME FOR MY WIND SCAR!
HYAH!
[GARBLED SCREAM]
- AND YOU'RE GOING DOWN NEXT.
- MMM.
- STOP!
- TSUBAKI SHOULD BE
YOUR NEXT VICTIM.
- DAMN.
- INUYASHA,
I SENSE THE SACRED JEWEL.
- HMM.
- THERE WAS A BARRIER HERE
TO KEEP SOMETHING SEALED WITHIN,
BUT THE SEAL HAS BEEN BROKEN.
- YOU MEAN LIKE
THOSE PAPER SHIKIGAMI?
- YES, BUT A SEAL THIS STRONG
WOULD NEVER BE NEEDED
FOR THOSE SPIRITS.
- WE'LL FIND OUR ANSWERS INSIDE.
COME ON!
- TSUBAKI TRULY IS
A DARK PRIESTESS?
- IT'S ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE
TO BELIEVE.
- YOU STUDIED UNDER
THE SAME MASTER AS TSUBAKI,
SO I DON'T BLAME YOU
FOR BEING SO SKEPTICAL.
NOW, WHY DON'T YOU COME
AND SEE FOR YOURSELVES
WHAT TSUBAKI IS TRULY LIKE?
- HUH?
- WE'D BETTER HURRY.
HANG ON TIGHT, LADIES.
- GLAD SOMEONE'S
HAVING A GOOD TIME.
- KIRARA, LET'S GO!
[SNARL]
- UNH!
OPEN, OGRE GATES.
COME FORTH, GOLDEN GOD.
[CRACKING]
- HOW DARE YOU SEAL ME WITHIN?
YOU SHALL PAY WITH YOUR LIFE!
- HA HA!
I WILL GIVE YOU POWER.
I HOLD THE ULTIMATE POWER
OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
[GROWL]
- SURELY YOU DESIRE THIS POWER,
DON'T YOU?
- GIVE IT TO ME.
GIVE IT TO ME!
[GROWLING]
[LAUGHING]
- OGRE, WHAT GREAT POWER.
HA HA HA! INCREDIBLE POWER!
HA HA HA!
- WE FOUND YOU, TSUBAKI.
- YOU AGAIN.
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU.
- GIVE US THE SACRED JEWEL BACK!
- IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE AFTER?
THIS IS TRULY INCREDIBLE.
- LOOK, THE SACRED JEWEL
IS IN TSUBAKI'S RIGHT EYE.
- IN HER EYE?
- I NEVER IMAGINED
IT WOULD BE THIS POWERFUL.
IF ONLY THE SACRED JEWEL
HAD COME INTO MY POSSESSION
50 YEARS AGO.
- 50 YEARS AGO?
TSUBAKI, WHAT HAPPENED
BETWEEN YOU AND MY SISTER KIKYO?
- KIKYO? YOU KNOW OF HER?
[GROWLING]
- AAH!
- IT'S ALL KIKYO'S FAULT!
KIKYO, THAT COLD
AND HEARTLESS PRIESTESS.
- NOBODY IS GOING
TO SMEAR HER NAME!
- SILENCE!
- INUYASHA!
- UNH!
UHH!
- INUYASHA!
- SO WHAT'S NEXT
AFTER THOSE DEMONS?
WHAT ARE YOU HIDING
IN THAT EYE OF YOURS?
- HA HA! I'M OVERFLOWING
WITH DEMONIC POWER!
IT'S COURSING THROUGH MY VEINS!
- DEMONIC POWER?
[LAUGHING]
- WHAT HAPPENED TO THE TOWER?
- IMPOSSIBLE.
THE FORBIDDEN TOWER GATES
MUST NEVER BE OPENED.
- YOU SAY IT'S FORBIDDEN?
- WHO COULD HAVE DONE THIS?
[RUMBLING]
- WHAT WAS THAT?
- LOOK THERE!
INUYASHA!
[PANTING]
[GROWLING]
- BEHOLD THE POWER
OF THE SACRED JEWEL!
WITNESS THE TRUE MIGHT
OF THE OGRE!
[ALL GASP]
- HA HA HA!
WHAT'S WRONG?
HAS MY POWER LEFT
ALL OF YOU SPEECHLESS?
- THE SEAL HAS BEEN BROKEN.
- OH, NO! THAT'S TSUBAKI!
SHE WOULDN'T DARE
HAVE BROKEN THE SEAL.
- WITH THIS POWER,
I SHALL HAVE ETERNAL LIFE!
- GET BACK NOW!
- RIGHT!
- THIS POWER IS UNPARALLELED!
- INUYASHA!
- UNH!
YOU'RE THROUGH!
HYAH!
AAH!
DAMN! UHH!
- SHE'S STRONG ENOUGH
TO STOP THE TETSUSAIGA!
- SURRENDER! IT'S USELESS!
[INUYASHA GROWLING]
- DON'T BE SO SURE ABOUT THAT.
HAVE A TASTE OF MY WIND SCAR!
NO WAY!
MY WIND SCAR DIDN'T KILL HER.
- YOU FOOL!
AAH!
- UNH!
- INUYASHA! NO!
- I'LL GET HER!
WIND TUNNEL!
- MY TURN!
[SCREAMS]
- HA HA HA!
YOU MAY BE KIKYO'S
REINCARNATION,
BUT YOU ARE VIRTUALLY POWERLESS.
[GASP]
- KIKYO WAS A FOOLISH PRIESTESS
WHO SQUANDERED THE POWER
OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
- WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
- I, TSUBAKI,
AM THE PERFECT MATCH
FOR THE SACRED JEWEL.
- WHAT IS THAT, KIKYO?
- THE SACRED JEWEL.
I HAVE BEEN ENTRUSTED WITH
THE DUTY OF KEEPING IT PURE.
- HA HA HA!
50 YEARS HAVE PASSED,
AND AT LAST THE POWER
OF THE SACRED JEWEL IS MINE.
- NOT FOR LONG!
UNH!
YOU WON'T GET YOUR WAY, TSUBAKI!
AAH!
UHH! UNH!
- HIRAIKOTSU!
- COME FOR ME.
THE SACRED JEWEL CAN
TAKE ON ALL OF YOU...AND MORE!
HA HA HA!
THERE ARE COUNTLESS DEMONS THAT
DESIRE THE POWER OF THIS JEWEL.
I WILL DEVOUR THEM ALL,
AND I WILL HAVE BOTH
THEIR STRENGTH AND ETERNAL LIFE.
- SHE INTENDS TO USE
THE SACRED JEWEL
TO CONSUME DEMONS
AND GAIN THEIR POWER.
- NOT IF I CAN HELP IT.
UHH!
- HALF-DEMON,
YOU WILL SOON BE MINE.
- I DOUBT IT.
- HA HA HA!
INUYASHA, AREN'T YOU THE ONE
THAT MADE KIKYO LOSE HER WAY
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
- WHY, YOU...
- I SHALL DEVOUR WHOLE
THE HALF-DEMON THAT
KIKYO COULD NOT HAVE.
[STRAINING]
COME AND SURRENDER YOUR HEART
TO THE SACRED JEWEL!
[LAUGHING]
- THAT THING IS POWERFUL.
- NOW EXPLAIN YOURSELF,
HALF-DEMON!
WHY DO YOU NOT GIVE YOURSELF
TO THE POWER?
- BECAUSE YOU TARNISHED
THE SACRED JEWEL, TSUBAKI!
KIKYO NEVER DID THAT!
- HOW DARE YOU?!
- AAH!
- INUYASHA!
- I SACRIFICED EVERYTHING
IN ORDER TO POSSESS
THE SACRED JEWEL.
- WAIT! TSUBAKI, STOP!
- NO, MASTER!
I CAN NEVER ACCEPT THIS!
WHY DID YOU ENTRUST
THE SACRED JEWEL TO
KIKYO AND NOT TO ME?
- WELL...
- WHY COULDN'T YOU
CHOOSE ME INSTEAD?
- TSUBAKI!
- I REFUSE TO TAKE
SECOND PLACE TO KIKYO.
- KNOW THE WRATH OF MY POWER!
- AAH!
- THIS IS TROUBLE!
AAH!
- AAH!
- INUYASHA!
- HYAH!
- PATHETIC FOOL!
- THAT DEMONIC AURA
IS THE ONLY THING
KEEPING YOU ALIVE.
HYAH!
TIME FOR MY BACKLASH WAVE!
[SCREAMING]
- THE OGRE!
- THE OGRE IS DISAPPEARING!
- NO! BUT WHY?
UNH!
- I'M NOT FINISHED.
I STILL POSSESS
THE SACRED JEWEL.
UHH.
AH!
[BUZZING]
- MY SACRED JEWEL!
- YOU WON'T GET AWAY! UNH!
[CHUCKLES]
[ALL GASP]
- GIVE THAT BACK TO US!
- SO LONG.
[GROANING]
CURSE YOU. CURSE YOU ALL.
[GASP]
MY YOUTH IS EVAPORATING!
MY YOUTH, MY BEAUTY...
- SHE AGED SO SUDDENLY.
- TSUBAKI HAS LOST
HER ORIGINAL DEMONIC POWERS,
AS WELL AS THOSE OF THE JEWEL.
NOW SHE IS RETURNING
TO HER ORIGINAL FORM.
- UH...EXACTLY WHERE
DID I GO WRONG?
DID I UNDERESTIMATE
THAT HALF-DEMON
OR PERHAPS KAGOME?
OR WAS IT BECAUSE
I MADE A PACT WITH NARAKU?
WHERE DID I GO WRONG?
- TSUBAKI!
- I WILL NOT TAKE
SECOND PLACE TO KIKYO!
I'M THE ONE WHO SHOULD HAVE
THE SACRED JEWEL, NOT KIKYO!
I, TSUBAKI...
AM THE GREATEST PRIESTESS!
- THAT'S THE END
OF THE DARK PRIESTESS.
- POOR TSUBAKI.
- SORRY FOR THE TROUBLE.
- THERE'S NO NEED TO APOLOGIZE.
IT WASN'T YOUR FAULT.
- TAKE CARE, SHIPPO.
- YOU, TOO.
- IT TURNS OUT THAT WE HAVE
ONCE AGAIN FALLEN VICTIM
TO NARAKU'S EVIL TRICKS.
- YEAH, WHO DID?
- TSUBAKI...
AND THE REST OF US, AS WELL.
- HMPH!
- AND NARAKU'S THE ONE
WHO POSSESSES
THE SACRED JEWEL ONCE AGAIN.
- I'LL GET IT BACK FROM HIM.
- YEAH. I'M SURE
YOU'RE RIGHT, INUYASHA.
- OH, BOY, I'M SO TIRED.
- WELL, SHALL WE GO BACK, THEN?
- HMM?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, INUYASHA?
- FORGET IT. PROBABLY NOTHING.
GUESS I IMAGINED IT.
- TSUBAKI WAS ENTIRELY OBSESSED
WITH THE SACRED JEWEL,
SO SHE WAS DOOMED TO FAILURE.
OBSESSED...
JUST AS I AM OBSESSED.
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
TURNER ENTERTAINMENT GROUP
CAPTIONED BY THE NATIONAL
CAPTIONING INSTITUTE
--www.ncicap.org--
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, MYOGA?
YOU USUALLY TRY TO AVOID US,
BUT TODAY YOU'VE ACTUALLY
HUNTED US DOWN.
NOW WHAT'S GOING ON?
MIROKU IS ATTACKING SANGO!
AND EVEN INUYASHA
IS ACTING STRANGE.
DOES THIS HAVE ANYTHING TO DO
WITH THE CURSE
OF THE GIANT CENTIPEDE?
NEXT TIME...
"FAREWELL, DAYS OF MY YOUTH."
WHOSE YOUTH ARE
WE TALKING ABOUT ANYWAY?