- UNH.
I'M HOME, GRANDPA!
MIND RUNNING A BATH FOR ME?
I'D BETTER HURRY,
OR I'LL BE LATE
FOR SCHOOL AGAIN.
- SHINGLES? IS THAT SERIOUS?
- THAT SOUNDS LIKE HOJO.
- IT'S A NASTY FORM OF HERPES,
UH, FROM A CHICKEN POX VIRUS.
- THAT DOES SOUND NASTY.
LAST WEEK, SHE HAD RHEUMATISM.
HERE, THIS MIGHT HELP.
- OH, YOUR MOM'S GOING TO GO
BROKE GIVING ALL THIS AWAY.
THANK YOU.
I'LL THINK OF YOU
WHEN I PUT THIS ON MY--
I MEAN,
KAGOME'S SWOLLEN ANKLES.
- IT IS HOJO!
AND GRAMPS IS TELLING HIM
ANOTHER BOGUS STORY!
- HEE HEE HEE!
- SO, HOW'S MY RHEUMATISM?
- KAGOME, YOU SHOULDN'T BE
OUT HERE IN YOUR CONDITION!
NOW, GET BACK INTO BED AND PUT
YOUR FEET UP ON SOME PILLOWS
BEFORE THE SWELLING
GETS TOO BAD!
- I DON'T HAVE ANY SWELLING!
AND IF YOU'D QUIT TELLING
ALL THESE STORIES,
I MIGHT BE ABLE TO GO TO SCHOOL
FOR A CHANGE!
- WELL, SOMEBODY GOT UP ON
THE WRONG SIDE OF THE BED!
- NOBODY EXCEPT MY FAMILY
KNOWS OF MY EXCURSIONS
THROUGH THE HIDDEN WELL
INTO THE FEUDAL ERA.
EVEN IF I TOLD
SOME OF MY FRIENDS,
I DOUBT THAT ANYONE WOULD
BELIEVE ME.
CAN YOU BLAME ME
FOR KEEPING IT TO MYSELF?
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- THERE YOU GO.
- [SIGHS]
- KAGOME,
I HEAR YOU HAVE TO TAKE
THE MAKE-UP COURSE
FOR MATH, TOO.
- YEAH, I FOUND OUT LAST WEEK.
- I DON'T GET IT.
YOU'VE ALWAYS HAD
TOP MARKS
IN THE MATH CLASS
UP UNTIL NOW.
WONDER IF HOJO
WILL KEEP COMING AROUND
IF HE FINDS OUT
ABOUT YOUR GRADES?
- SO, WHAT DID YOUR NEW
BOYFRIEND BRING YOU THIS TIME?
MAYBE SOME ARTHRITIS CREAM?
- HE'S NOT MY BOYFRIEND!
AND IT WASN'T FOR ARTHRITIS!
THEY WERE EXPENSIVE PLASTERS
TO TREAT MY RHEUMATISM!
- BUT I THOUGHT RHEUMATISM WAS
A KIND OF ARTHRITIS.
- UH...UH, YEAH.
I'M SO CAUGHT UP
IN GRANDPA'S TALES,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S WHAT!
HOW AM I EVER GONNA MAKE IT
INTO HIGH SCHOOL
WITH ALL THESE CLASSES I MISS?
- HEY, LOOK!
THEY'VE GOT FIREWORKS!
- HA! COOL!
- REMEMBER WHEN WE USED TO DO
THAT WHEN WE WERE KIDS?
- HUH?
- OH, MY GOD!
- OH, NO!
- JOHNNY, COME BACK HERE!
- GET AWAY FROM THAT!
DON'T TOUCH ANYTHING!
BE CAREFUL!
- HEH HEH HEH!
THAT'LL KEEP THEM BUSY!
LITTLE BRATS!
- NO! STOP! HEY!
HOLD IT RIGHT THERE!
WHAT'D YOU SCARE
ALL THOSE KIDS FOR?
THAT WASN'T VERY NICE!
- WAIT A SECOND.
YOU MEAN YOU CAN SEE ME?
- WHAT'S WITH THIS GIRL?
SHE DOESN'T EVEN HAVE
ANY SHOES ON.
AND WHY IS SHE WEARING A DOWN
JACKET WHEN IT'S ALMOST SUMMER?
LOOK, YOU OWE THOSE KIDS
AN APOLOGY.
I'LL COME WITH YOU
TO MAKE IT EASIER.
- MIND YOUR OWN BUSINESS!
UNH!
- AAH!
OH! UNH!
- I DON'T WANT TO TALK
TO YOU ANYMORE!
LEAVE ME ALONE!
- OH!
[SIGHS]
- WHAT'D YOU RUN OFF FOR,
KAGOME?
- HOW COME YOU WERE
TALKING TO YOURSELF?
- UH...
SHE VANISHED!
AM I LOSING IT?
NO, THAT GIRL WAS REAL.
I FELT HER HAND!
[BUZZING]
- HOW MUCH LONGER
IS THIS GONNA TAKE, ANYWAY?
- AHH, BE PATIENT, MY LORD.
IF YOU TRY TO TAKE THE SHEATH
FROM THE STEEL WASPS NOW,
YOU'LL BE STUNG TO DEATH.
THE SHEATH OF YOUR SWORD
WAS BADLY CRACKED
DURING YOUR LAST BATTLE.
LET THE STEEL WASPS
DO THEIR JOB
AND REPAIR IT
WITH THEIR SPECIAL WAX.
- WOO!
HEY, HOW ABOUT A BITE?
AHH!
- [GRUNTING]
HEY! I WAS ONLY TRYING TO LIVEN
THINGS UP AROUND HERE!
WHERE'S KAGOME, ANYWAYS?
I'M GETTING TIRED OF
HANGING AROUND WITH YOU.
- FUNNY YOU SHOULD
MENTION THAT.
- IT'S NOT FAIR!
WHY DO I HAVE TO BE
ALONE WITH YOU?
- HUH!
- UM, DON'T I DESERVE
TO BE COUNTED, HMM?
- [GIGGLING]
- WHAT'S THAT?
- IT'S A DEMON!
- WHY ARE YOU SCARED?
YOU'RE A DEMON, TOO, REMEMBER?
- THAT'S NO ORDINARY DEMON.
IT'S THE SOUL PIPER.
WHEN A CHILD DIES,
THE SOUL PIPER STAYS
AND PLAYS WITH THAT CHILD
UNTIL THE SOUL IS READY
TO REST IN PEACE.
AS LONG AS THE EYES
OF THE MONSTER REMAIN CLOSED,
THERE'S NOTHING
TO BE AFRAID OF.
BUT WHEN THE SOUL PIPER'S
EYES OPEN,
IT BECOMES A FEARFUL DEMON.
- [GIGGLING]
- COME ON, MOM!
IT'S SATURDAY!
WHY DO I HAVE TO TAKE YOU TO SEE
YOUR FRIEND IN THE HOSPITAL?
IT'S NOT FAIR.
- I CAN'T HELP IT.
MOM'S BUSY, AND I'M NOT
ALLOWED TO TAKE THE TRAIN
BY MYSELF, REMEMBER?
- YEAH, YEAH.
BUT I DON'T WANT TO STAY THERE
ALL DAY, OK?
- UH, HEY, SIS?
- UH-HUH?
- DO YOU THINK EVIL GHOSTS
REALLY EXIST?
- HUH?
- OH, SOTA!
IT'S SO NICE OF YOU TO VISIT.
- HOW'S SATORU?
WILL HE BE GETTING OUT SOON?
- I'M AFRAID HE'LL BE IN HERE
FOR A WHILE YET.
HE STILL HASN'T WOKEN UP
SINCE THE ACCIDENT.
- WELL, MAYBE THESE
WILL HELP.
- GET-WELL CRANES.
HOW VERY THOUGHTFUL
OF YOU, SOTA.
- HER HANDS ARE BURNED.
- HMM? OH, THESE.
THEY WERE BURNED IN THE FIRE.
- I DIDN'T MEAN TO STARE!
- FORTUNATELY,
HE WASN'T BURNED,
BUT HE'S BEEN IN A COMA
FOR HALF A YEAR--
SINCE THE FIRE.
- AAH!
OH!
HUH?
THAT'S THE SAME GIRL I SAW
IN THE PARK!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- NOT AGAIN!
- HUH?
- WHY DOES THIS KEEP HAPPENING?
- WHO IS THAT GIRL?
WHAT DOES SHE WANT?
I'VE GOT TO GET
TO THE BOTTOM OF THIS!
[FLUTE PLAYING]
- ONE OF THESE DAYS,
I'M GONNA FINISH OFF
MY STUPID BROTHER FOR GOOD!
- WHY WERE YOU ASKING
ABOUT EVIL GHOSTS
BEFORE WE GOT
TO THE HOSPITAL?
- SOME PEOPLE IN OUR CLASS
THINK THERE'S AN EVIL GHOST
AFTER SATORU.
HE'S BEEN IN A COMA
FOR 6 MONTHS NOW, RIGHT?
EVERYONE FROM THE CLASS
USED TO COME
AND VISIT HIM
ALL THE TIME,
BUT THEN ALL KINDS OF
WEIRD THINGS STARTED HAPPENING
WHEN THEY CAME TO SEE HIM.
LIKE, THEY WERE
PUSHED DOWN STAIRS,
ALMOST HIT BY CARS,
AND OTHER STUFF.
EVERYONE'S SCARED
TO VISIT HIM NOW.
HIS SISTER MAYU DIED
IN THE FIRE, YOU KNOW?
SOME GUYS
IN THE CLASS THINK
MAYBE SHE'S DOING
ALL THE CREEPY STUFF.
- AND THAT'S
WHERE THEIR APARTMENT WAS?
- YEAH. THEY KEPT TRYING
TO CLEAN IT UP
AND REBUILD IT AFTER THE FIRE,
BUT EVERY TIME SOMEONE GOT NEAR,
THERE WAS ANOTHER ACCIDENT.
- LOOK OUT!
- AAH!
- UNH!
SEE? I TOLD YOU THERE WAS
AN EVIL GHOST AROUND!
AAH! OOH!
- SOTA!
HELP!
HUH?
NO! GET OFF OF THERE!
OH!
HUH?
- DUH! I'M DEAD!
DON'T YOU GET IT?
- YOU'RE MAYU,
SATORU'S SISTER!
WHY ARE YOU BEING SO MEAN?
YOU DON'T REALLY WANT
TO HURT PEOPLE, DO YOU?
- I DON'T CARE ABOUT ANYONE,
ESPECIALLY NOT MY MOMMY.
MOMMY COULDN'T STAND ME.
SHE DIDN'T EVEN CARE
THAT I DIED!
SHE LEFT ME IN THE FIRE.
SHE ONLY SAVED
MY LITTLE BROTHER.
- I'M SURE
YOU'RE WRONG ABOUT THAT.
I'VE TALKED TO
YOUR MOTHER, MAYU.
I'M SURE SHE LOVED YOU
AS MUCH AS YOUR BROTHER.
- WHAT DO YOU KNOW?!
YOU'D BETTER STAY OUT OF MY WAY,
OR I'LL HAVE TO KILL YOU, TOO!
- OH!
AAH!
UNH...
HUH?
- [WHISTLING]
- HUH?
WHAT IS THAT THING?
"WHEN THE EYES OPEN WIDE..."
IT'S GONE!
WHAT WAS IT TRYING TO
TELL ME?
YOU'VE HEARD OF IT, THEN?
SO THAT DEMON IS KNOWN AS
THE SOUL PIPER?
- YES. IT SOUNDS LIKE WE'RE
TALKING ABOUT THE SAME THING.
THE SOUL PIPER CONSOLES
THE CHILDREN
UNTIL THEY CAN ACCEPT
THEIR DEATHS.
IT ENTERTAINS THE CHILDREN
WITH ITS FLUTE
UNTIL THEY CAN FIND PEACE.
- WOW!
- AHH!
- WHAT IF THEY CAN'T FIND PEACE?
WHAT IF THEY HAVE SOMETHING
HOLDING THEM BACK,
LIKE JEALOUSY OR HATRED?
- THEN THE CHILDREN BECOME
EVIL SPIRITS.
- YOU'RE NOT SERIOUS!
- YOU'VE HEARD OF POLTERGEISTS,
FULL OF RAGE AND HATRED.
WHEN THE SOUL PIPER SENSES
THE CHILD'S RAGE, ITS EYES OPEN,
AND THE SOUL PIPER HURLS
THE CHILD INTO THE DEPTHS
OF HELL.
- MOST OF THE TIME,
THE SOUL PIPER'S EYES
ARE CLOSED,
BUT LOOK OUT
WHEN THEY OPEN!
- THEY WERE OPENING!
I'VE GOT TO DO SOMETHING
TO SAVE MAYU!
- LET IT BE, KAGOME.
- HUH?
- GHOSTS AND SPIRITS
AREN'T LIKE MONSTERS.
WE CAN'T JUST TAKE OUT
OUR SWORDS
AND START ORDERING THEM AROUND.
GHOSTS ARE DIFFERENT
AND MUCH MORE DANGEROUS.
- I DON'T CARE IF THEY ARE!
I COME FROM A LONG LINE
OF PRIESTS.
I WON'T SIT BY
AND WATCH SOMEONE SUFFER!
- HEH!
WELL, YOU CAN COUNT ME OUT.
THERE'S NOTHING YOU CAN DO
TO HELP THE GIRL AT THIS POINT.
HUH?
- YOU SHOULDN'T
TALK TO YOURSELF.
PEOPLE WILL WONDER.
- GRR!
- I CAN'T LET HER CARRY ON
LIKE THIS!
POOR MAYU!
SHE'S ALREADY SUFFERED SO MUCH!
- MOMMY, I CAN'T WAIT TO TRY ON
MY NEW KIMONO!
I'LL WEAR IT TO THE FESTIVAL
AND CATCH LOTS OF GOLDFISH
FRIENDS FOR MY NEW TANK!
ARE YOU ALMOST FINISHED,
MOM?
- ALMOST.
BUT THE FESTIVAL'S
STILL A LONG WAY OFF.
- YEAH, I KNOW,
BUT I WANT TO TRY IT!
- YES, HONEY.
HEE HEE HEE!
- THIS TIME,
WHEN MOM LEAVES THE HOSPITAL,
I'M GONNA MAKE SURE THAT SATORU
HAS AN ACCIDENT.
- [FLUTE PLAYING]
- HUH?
- WHAT'S SHE DOING?
- SURE, THANK YOU.
OH, GOOD NIGHT, MRS. AKAIDA.
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
WE'LL CALL IF THERE'S ANY NEWS.
- THANKS.
GOOD NIGHT.
- HAVE A GOOD NIGHT'S REST.
- MRS. AKAIDA!
- HELLO!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
VISITING HOURS ARE OVER, DEAR.
- I KNOW, BUT I NEED
TO TALK TO YOU.
IT'S ABOUT MAYU!
[SIREN IN DISTANCE]
- AROUND THE BACK.
WE'RE ALL READY FOR YOU!
- IT SEEMS LIKE JUST YESTERDAY.
- I HATE YOU, MOMMY!
WHY DIDN'T YOU COME TO
THE SCHOOL'S OPEN HOUSE?
- I'M SORRY, MAYU,
BUT YOUR BROTHER'S BEEN
SICK IN BED ALL DAY.
- IT'S ALWAYS ABOUT
STUPID SATORU!
- HUH? THAT'S NOT TRUE!
- I CAN'T STAND YOU OR SATORU!
- MAYU!
DON'T RUN OUT ON ME!
[DOOR SHUTS]
IT SEEMED WE WERE ALWAYS HAVING
ARGUMENTS LIKE THAT.
I THOUGHT
I HEARD THE DOOR SLAM,
AND I ASSUMED THAT SHE'D RUN OFF
TO THE NEIGHBORS' APARTMENT,
AS SHE USUALLY DID.
I WAS MISTAKEN.
[NO AUDIO]
HOW COULD I HAVE KNOWN THAT MAYU
WAS STILL INSIDE?
- WE GOT A BODY IN HERE!
POOR THING.
LOOKS LIKE JUST A KID.
- IF I HAD KNOWN,
I WOULD HAVE GONE BACK IN.
BUT I WAS SO SURE
THAT SHE WASN'T THERE!
- SO MAYU'S MOM DIDN'T
EVEN KNOW
SHE WAS STILL IN THE APARTMENT
DURING THE FIRE!
[GLASS SHATTERING]
[BOTH GASP]
- THAT'S SATORU'S ROOM!
- IT'S MAYU!
MAYU, NO!
STOP DOING THIS!
LET'S TALK!
THIS IS ALL A MISUNDERSTANDING!
- OH! MAYU!
BUT YOU--
- STAY OUT!
- AAH! UNH!
UNH!
- DON'T BLAME YOUR MOM!
TRY AND THINK BACK!
YOUR MOM DIDN'T
ABANDON YOU IN THE FIRE.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
SHE DIDN'T THINK YOU WERE
AT HOME WHEN THE FIRE HAPPENED!
REMEMBER?
- OOH! IT'S NICE
AND WARM IN HERE.
- OHH, HI THERE, MAYU.
MOM SAID YOU'RE NOT
SUPPOSED TO HANG STUFF
OVER THE STOVE WHEN IT'S ON,
REMEMBER?
- YOU GOING TO SNITCH ON ME?
I'M GONNA PLAY A TRICK ON MOMMY.
DON'T TELL HER I'M IN HERE,
OR I'LL BE MAD!
I'M GONNA MAKE HER
WORRY ABOUT ME!
I LEFT MY SCARF
OVER THE STOVE.
IT MUST HAVE FALLEN
AND CAUGHT FIRE!
IT WAS MY FAULT
OUR APARTMENT BURNED DOWN.
MOMMY DIDN'T KNOW I WAS HOME.
- MAYU...
- I FORGOT THAT.
BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER,
BECAUSE I STILL HATE HER!
- AAH!
UGH...
- SATORU!
OH!
THE POOR BOY!
- CAN'T YOU HANDLE ANYTHING
ON YOUR OWN?
- OH! HMM?
INUYASHA!
YOU CAME TO HELP ME!
- GOOD THING I DID, TOO,
OR THIS KID WOULD BE IN TROUBLE.
GIVE UP ON THE GIRL.
IT'S TOO LATE FOR HER.
EVEN IF YOU DO MAKE HER REALIZE
WHAT HAPPENED AND MAKE HER STOP,
I GUARANTEE YOU SHE'S NOT GOING
ANYWHERE NEAR HEAVEN.
- LOOK! ITS EYES!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
LET ME GO!
I WANT TO STAY HERE!
- I'M MAKING THIS UP
AS I GO,
BECAUSE LIKE I TOLD YOU,
I'M NO EXPERT IN SPIRITS
AND GHOSTS.
- I KNOW, BUT WE'VE GOT TO DO
WHATEVER WE CAN TO STOP MAYU
FROM GOING TO HELL!
- WE'VE GOT TO FIND
THE GIRL'S APARTMENT.
ACCORDING TO MYOGA,
THE SOUL PIPER DRAGS
THE TORMENTED SOUL
TO ITS PLACE OF DEATH,
THEN HURLS IT
INTO THE PITS OF HELL.
UNH!
THAT MUST BE IT.
LET'S JUST HOPE
WE'RE NOT TOO LATE.
UNH!
- THIS IS GOOD.
LET ME HANDLE IT FROM HERE.
- LIKE YOU HANDLED THE KID
BACK AT THE HOSPITAL?
I DON'T THINK SO.
I'M GOING WITH YOU.
I CAN RELATE TO WHOEVER
FIRST SAID,
"THERE'S NOTHING SCARIER
THAN AN IGNORAMUS."
HUH?
SHE DISAPPEARED!
RIGHT--THIS IS THE
DIMENSION WHERE HUMANS
ARE DRAGGED INTO HELL!
I'M HALF-DEMON, SO I CAN'T
MAKE IT PAST THIS BARRIER!
OH, DAMN. KAGOME CANNOT
HANDLE THIS ON HER OWN!
- WHERE AM I?
WHY IS IT SO DARK IN HERE?
[CHAINS RATTLING]
THE LIGHT'S ON.
HUH?
[SCREAMING]
- HUH?
- YOU'RE AWAKE.
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
- HUH?
WHERE AM I?
WHAT HAPPENED?
- SATORU HAS WOKEN UP.
- HUH?
SATORU!
- UNH...
M-MOMMY?
- OH...OH...
- MMM.
MOMMY...
MAYU...SHE'S HIDING FROM YOU
IN THE CLOSET.
- HUH?
- HURRY AND GET HER, MOMMY.
- I'M AT MY HOUSE.
THIS IS HOW I DIED.
NOBODY SAVED ME
BECAUSE THEY DIDN'T
KNOW I WAS HERE.
- MAYU!
MAYU, WHERE ARE YOU?
- IS THAT YOU, MOMMY?
- WHERE ARE YOU?
ANSWER ME!
THERE YOU ARE!
COME ON, MAYU.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE!
- HOW MANY TIMES
DO I HAVE TO TELL YOU?
I'M DEAD, YOU STUPID IDIOT!
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
WHY DON'T YOU--AAH!
AAH!
- [BOTH SCREAMING]
- [WHINING]
- MAYU!
- [BOTH GRUNTING]
- DON'T LET GO!
- [WHIMPERING]
- YOU HAVE TO GO HOME!
GO HOME AND MAKE UP
WITH YOUR MOTHER!
YOUR MOTHER LOVES YOU NOW,
AND SHE ALWAYS DID LOVE YOU!
DON'T YOU WANT TO MAKE UP
WITH HER BEFORE YOU SAY
GOOD-BYE FOR GOOD?
- ISN'T MOMMY MAD AT ME?
- HUH?
- ARE YOU SURE
MOMMY'S NOT MAD?
- SHE'S NOT MAD, REALLY.
SHE JUST LOVES YOU
AND MISSES YOU, THAT'S ALL.
- [WHIMPERING]
- MAYU, YOU KNOW YOUR MOM
BETTER THAN ANYONE.
SHE'D NEVER BE MAD AT YOU.
- MOMMY!
I MISS YOU, MOMMY!
I WANT TO SAY SORRY TO YOU!
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED
TO MAKE UP WITH YOU!
I'M SORRY, MOMMY!
- MAYU?
- MOMMY?
- HUH?
MAYU?
- I'M SORRY, MOMMY.
WILL YOU FORGIVE ME?
- YES.
- HMM.
BYE, MOMMY.
I HAVE TO GO NOW.
- [SIGHS]
- I HOPE MAYU'S ALL RIGHT NOW.
- WHAT WERE YOU THINKING,
GOING IN THERE ALL ALONE?
THAT GIRL COULD HAVE EASILY
PULLED YOU INTO HELL, KAGOME,
AND I WOULDN'T HAVE
BEEN ABLE TO SAVE YOU.
- IT WAS WORTH THE RISK.
ONE WEEK LATER, SATORU CAME HOME
FROM THE HOSPITAL.
- KAGOME?
- HUH?
IT'S YOU!
- I WANTED TO SEE YOU
ONE LAST TIME BEFORE I LEFT.
- I LOVE YOUR SUMMER KIMONO.
YOU LOOK ADORABLE!
- THANKS!
MY MOMMY MADE IT JUST FOR ME.
I'D BETTER BE GOING NOW.
BYE!
[FLUTE PLAYING]
- MAYU, I DON'T THINK YOU WERE
EVER AN EVIL SPIRIT.
YOU WERE JUST
AN ORDINARY LITTLE GIRL
WHO LOVED HER MOM
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
- [LAUGHING]
- [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- INUYASHA IS HALF-DEMON
AND HALF-HUMAN,
AND HIS GOAL IS
TO GATHER THE SHARDS
OF THE SACRED
SHIKON JEWEL
SO HE CAN BECOME
A FULL-FLEDGED DEMON.
DURING OUR SEARCH
FOR THE JEWEL FRAGMENTS,
WE COME TO THE RESCUE OF A GIRL
WHO TAKES US TO AN OLD TEMPLE.
THERE, THE SPIDER LORD
LURKS IN THE SHADOWS.
INUYASHA'S DARK SECRET
IS ABOUT TO BE REVEALED
ON THIS MOONLESS NIGHT.
NEXT TIME,
"THE MYSTERY OF THE NEW MOON
AND THE BLACK-HAIRED INUYASHA."
SEE YOU SOON!