[GASP]
- THAT'S RIGHT!
KAGOME WAS ABDUCTED BY
THE PANTHER TRIBE,
AND IT'S UP TO US TO SAVE HER!
KOUGA AND SESSHOMARU
SHOWED UP
AND ARE ALSO FIGHTING
THE PANTHER TRIBE.
- YOU'LL HAVE TO COME TO OUR
CASTLE IF YOU WANT HER BACK...
IF YOU CAN, THAT IS.
WE'LL BE WAITING FOR YOU,
INUYASHA.
- [GRUNTING]
- SESSHOMARU.
- AAH!
MIROKU!
SANGO!
- SO, YOU'RE ALIVE, SHIPPO.
- HI, MYOGA.
WHERE IS EVERYONE?
- PROBABLY DEEP WITHIN
THE PANTHERS' CASTLE.
- HURRY UP AND MOVE OUT OF
THE WAY, OR YOU'LL REGRET IT.
- JUST TRY AND GET PAST US.
- HMPH!
YOU'RE ON!
- HEH HEH HEH!
- YAAH!
WHAT?
- [LAUGHING]
- WHAT IS THIS?
DAMN IT!
- GET OUT OF THE WAY!
- NO CHANCE!
- DIE!
[SCREAMING]
- THEY GOT ROYOKAN!
- WHAT IS THAT?
IS IT LIGHTNING?
- NOT TOO BAD, LITTLE MAN.
HA HA HA!
- HE DOESN'T MOVE QUICKLY,
BUT HIS LIGHTNING IS DEADLY.
- FIREBALL!
HYAH!
AAH!
[PANTING]
TAURON!
- WHAT A SURPRISE.
I THOUGHT YOU WOULD BE WEAKER
THAN YOU WERE BEFORE.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
- YOU'RE SHORT AN ARM.
WHO COULD HAVE DONE SUCH A THING
TO THE MIGHTY SESSHOMARU?
[CHUCKLES]
AT LAST, THE CELEBRATIONS
ARE ABOUT TO BEGIN.
WE'LL BE WAITING FOR YOU.
[CHUCKLES]
- WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
NOT HOLDING BACK
ON MY ACCOUNT, ARE YOU?
COME AND GET ME!
- HIS LIGHTNING BOLTS ARE FAST,
BUT THAT'S ALL
HE'S GOT GOING FOR HIM.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE DEAD!
- TOO SLOW!
- OH, NO, I'M NOT!
YOU ARE!
[GROANING]
- HAD ENOUGH?
- RETREAT, PANTHER TRIBE.
[GRUNTING]
- HA HA! SERVES YOU RIGHT.
HOW'S THE BIG GUY
DOING BACK THERE?
- HE'S BREATHING.
- I DON'T THINK HE'S FAINTED.
MORE LIKE HE'S ASLEEP.
- THEN LEAVE HIM.
LET'S GO.
I KNOW KAGOME IS IN THERE.
[LAUGHING]
- I CAN'T TELL
WHICH ONE OF THEM IS REAL.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING, INUYASHA?!
- SHUT UP!
- LET ME HANDLE THIS!
NOW, BEHOLD AS I DISPEL
THE ILLUSIONS!
- IS THAT THE REAL ONE?
- MM-HMM.
- OH, NOT BAD FOR A LITTLE IMP.
- YOUR TRICKS CAN'T FOOL ME.
DON'T UNDERESTIMATE MY POWER.
- HMPH! NOW THAT I KNOW
WHO I'M DEALING WITH...
AARRGGH!
- HA HA HA!
LET'S CONTINUE THIS
AT THE CASTLE.
- DAMN HER
AND HER STUPID TRICKS.
- THE TIME IS NOW UPON US,
MASTER.
THE MOON IS ALMOST
DIRECTLY OVERHEAD.
IN MOMENTS, THE DOGS
WE DESPISE WILL BE SLAUGHTERED,
AND THE PANTHER TRIBE WILL REIGN
OVER THIS LAND.
- A BARRIER.
- SOON OUR MASTER
WILL BE RESURRECTED.
SESSHOMARU, PREPARE TO DIE.
[GROWLING]
[GASP]
- OUR MASTER HAS AWAKENED.
- GIVE ME BLOOD, FLESH...
AND SOUL.
- WHAT'S THIS?
- IT'S THE PANTHER TRIBE.
- WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- KAGOME!
- KOUGA!
- [GRUNTING]
- DAMN IT! A BARRIER!
- HA HA HA!
AS IF FOOLS LIKE YOU COULD BREAK
THE GREAT ONE'S BARRIER.
- STICK AROUND AND JOIN US
FOR DINNER.
WE'RE HAVING SACRIFICIAL LAMB.
[GROWLING]
- FIND YOURSELF ANOTHER MEAL.
- MIROKU!
[SCREAMING]
- KAGOME!
- THE TETSUSAIGA IS RED.
[GRUNTING]
- SORRY TO KEEP YOU.
- THE MUTT--HE BROKE
OUR MASTER'S BARRIER!
- HOW DARE HE?
- LORD SESSHOMARU!
LORD SESSHOMARU!
[PANTING]
I HAVE SEARCHED EVERYWHERE
FOR YOU!
INUYASHA HAS SURPRISED ME.
WHEN DID HE BECOME SO POWERFUL
AND LEARN TO WIELD
THE TETSUSAIGA LIKE THAT?
- INUYASHA!
- KAGOME, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- UH-HUH. I JUST KNEW THAT
YOU WOULD COME FOR US.
- [CHUCKLING]
HUH?
- NO NEED TO WORRY ANYMORE,
KAGOME.
- HUH?
- HANDS OFF HER, KOUGA!
- GIVE ME BLOOD!
- INUYASHA!
- REST ASSURED, KAGOME.
IT'S GONNA BE EASY TO GET
YOU OUT OF HERE.
- I'M NOT LEAVING
THE OTHERS BEHIND!
- HE'S ATTACKING OUR MASTER!
- INUYASHA, THE SACRED JEWEL
SHARDS ARE IN HIS THROAT.
- HMPH! GOTCHA.
I'LL GET THEM BACK.
- OK.
ALL RIGHT, PEOPLE.
STICK TOGETHER AND RUN FOR IT!
COME ON, THIS WAY!
[SCREAMING]
- STOP THEM!
DON'T LET THEM ESCAPE!
[MURMURING]
- THERE'S NO WAY OUT!
- WE'RE DOOMED!
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
AREN'T WE SUPPOSED
TO BE YOUR LIVE SACRIFICE?
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE NOT
SUPPOSED TO KILL US.
NOW, MOVE.
- WOULD YOU LOOK AT HER GO?
- THAT'S OUR GAL!
- ALL RIGHT.
DON'T JUST STAND THERE.
CLEAR THE WAY FOR HER.
[SHOUTING]
- [GROANING]
- ARE YOU OK?
MIROKU?
- HUH?
- UP HERE, MIROKU!
- SANGO!
- HELP HAS ARRIVED.
- THEN LET'S GET GOING.
- RIGHT.
HYAH!
- HURRY, PEOPLE!
THIS IS OUR CHANCE!
- THIS WAY!
- DIE!
- MASTER!
- GIVE ME BLOOD...AND A SOUL!
- WE WILL.
PLEASE WAIT A LITTLE LONGER.
MASTER, I PROMISE THAT I WILL
BRING YOU THE HEAD
OF THE DOG GENERAL'S SON
ON A PLATTER.
- HUH! I DON'T CARE WHO
THIS MASTER OF YOURS IS.
YOU'RE NOT USING HUMAN FLESH
AND BLOOD TO RESURRECT HIM.
- WE WILL, AND YOU SHALL BE
OUR FIRST SACRIFICE.
- YOU MIGHT NOT FEEL THAT WAY
AFTER YOU'VE FELT HOW SHARP
MY BLADE IS.
- AHH!
ANOTHER GLORIOUS BATTLE,
MY LORD, AND A VICTORY FOR YOU.
- THERE WAS NO VICTORY.
THEY FLED FROM BATTLE,
THAT'S ALL.
I CANNOT USE THIS SWORD.
THE TENSAIGA IS
A SWORD OF HEALING.
I CANNOT KILL MY ENEMIES
WITH THIS.
I NEED THE OTHER SWORD
THAT FATHER LEFT BEHIND...
THE TETSUSAIGA.
- [GRUNTING]
- WIND SCAR!
- I NEED IT, AND YET I DO NOT
HAVE THE POWER TO WIELD IT.
- [LAUGHING]
- YOU'RE THROUGH!
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
CAN'T YOU USE YOUR SWORD
LIKE THIS?
[CHUCKLING]
-[GASP]
- [SCREAMING]
- [GROANING]
- I TOLD YOU NOT TO INTERRUPT.
- STAY THERE WHERE YOU ARE.
THESE PANTHER DEMONS
BELONG TO ME.
- NOT THIS TIME.
YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO'LL HAVE TO BACK DOWN.
- ENOUGH!
- NO CHANCE!
OUT OF MY WAY!
- AHH!
WHY CAN'T THEY JOIN FORCES
INSTEAD OF FIGHTING EACH OTHER?
- BACK DOWN!
- I DON'T NEED ANY HELP
FROM YOU.
- OH, YEAH?
- ARE THEY BOTH
OUT OF THEIR MINDS?
- IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE
THEY'RE BROTHERS.
- YEAH. WHAT IN THE WORLD
ARE THEY THINKING?
- THE DOG GENERAL'S SONS
ARE FIGHTING EACH OTHER,
WHICH MEANS THAT WE MUST
STAY UNITED.
WE'LL COMBINE OUR POWERS
AND STRIKE THEM ALL AT ONCE.
- ALL RIGHT!
- OH, YEAH!
- RIGHT!
- [GROWLS]
GIVE ME LIFE!
- YES, MASTER.
PLEASE BE PATIENT.
WE SHALL OFFER YOU THEIR SOULS
IN BUT A MOMENT.
- GIVE ME YOUR SOUL!
- AAAH!
- KAURON!
- [SCREAMING]
- HOW COULD HE?
- HMM?
- HE DEVOURED HIS OWN KIN
SO THAT HE COULD REVIVE HIMSELF.
- YOU TWO,
SONS OF THE DOG GENERAL...
YOU'RE NEXT.
- SHONRON, KAURON, SHURON...
IT CAN'T BE.
[SOBBING]
- DOGS! YOU WILL NOW FEEL
THE FULL EXTENT OF MY WRATH!
- TIME TO WAKE UP FROM
YOUR PIPE DREAMS.
MAYBE MY SWORD CAN HELP YOU.
OUT OF MY WAY!
WIND SCAR!
DEAD ON.
- [CHUCKLING]
NO SUCH LUCK.
- YOU'VE GOT THE STRENGTH
TO FIGHT MY OLD MAN,
I'LL GIVE YOU THAT MUCH.
HA! YOU WON'T GET PAST ME,
THOUGH.
- DON'T BE SO SURE, INUYASHA.
HE'S BECOME MORE POWERFUL
THAN RIUKOTSAY.
HE HAS THE POWER OF
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS NOW.
- [GRUNTING]
- IT'S THE HUGE PANTHER DEMON!
- LOOK! THE PANTHER KING'S
COME BACK TO LIFE!
- I THOUGHT HE NEEDED
A LIVE SACRIFICE.
- MAYBE HE HAD
SOME FRESH DOG MEAT.
- DON'T SAY THINGS LIKE THAT!
- PERISH.
- LORD SESSHOMARU!
- [CHUCKLING]
YOU SHALL BE MY NEXT VICTIM.
- AARRGGH!
[GRUNTING]
- LORD SESSHOMARU!
MY LORD, WHAT IS IT?
- [GROANING]
CURSE HIM.
HUH? THE TENSAIGA.
YOU WISH TO BE DRAWN?
- AAH!
- FATHER, WHY DID YOU
LEAVE ME THE TENSAIGA?
I STILL DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- [CHUCKLING]
- HUH?
- HUH? WHAT WAS THAT?
- [WHIMPERING]
- YOU CAN'T HARM ME
WITH THAT USELESS SWORD.
ITS BLADE IS FAR TOO DULL.
VANQUISHED!
[GROANS]
MY POWER...
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
I'M LOSING MY POWER...
- HUH?
- I'M LOSING MY POWER.
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE TO ME?
- YOU FINISH HIM OFF
WITH THE TETSUSAIGA.
- GIVE ME MY...SOUL!
- WIND SCAR!
[SCREAMING]
[GURGLING]
- I'M TAKING THESE BACK, THANKS.
- AHH!
- [GROANING]
- HUH?
- TAURON.
- AHH...
- [GASP]
- YOU'RE ALL ALIVE!
- WHAT THE HELL
JUST HAPPENED TO US?
- YEAH. I WAS SURE THAT
THE MASTER HAD KILLED US ALL.
- SOMEONE MUST HAVE SAVED US.
- IT WAS NONE OTHER
THAN LORD SESSHOMARU!
- HUH?
- YOUR OWN MASTER TOOK
YOUR LIVES,
BUT LORD SESSHOMARU USED
HIS SWORD, THE TENSAIGA,
TO BRING YOU BACK TO LIFE.
- HE SAVED US?
- THAT MUTT?
- HOW ABOUT A SHOW OF GRATITUDE?
RIGHT, LORD SESSHOMARU?
WHERE'D HE GO?
HUH?
OH, PLEASE DON'T LEAVE ME
BEHIND AGAIN!
- [GRUNTING]
- SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WANT TO PICK UP WHERE
WE LEFT OFF?
- HMM.
NO. WE SHALL RETURN TO THE WEST.
- HUH?
- TAURON.
- THIS IS FINISHED.
THERE'S NO REASON FOR US
TO SEEK REVENGE.
YOU CAN TELL SESSHOMARU
I SAID THAT.
- WE'RE NOT EXACTLY A CLOSE-KNIT
FAMILY, IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
- HMM.
JUST TELL HIM NEXT TIME
YOU SEE HIM.
- ALL RIGHT.
- WE ARE FOREVER INDEBTED
TO YOU ALL.
- YOUR VILLAGE WILL BE SAFE NOW
BECAUSE THE PANTHER DEMONS
WON'T BE COMING BACK.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
FINALLY, WE CAN LIVE IN PEACE.
- WE SHOULD BE ON OUR WAY NOW.
- [CRYING]
I WANTED TO ASSIST
LORD SESSHOMARU SO BADLY!
- IT'S TOO LATE NOW.
WELL, THERE'S ALWAYS NEXT TIME,
I SUPPOSE.
- WITH GUYS LIKE THAT AROUND,
NO WONDER THE HUMANS ARE SCARED
ALL THE TIME.
- YEAH. THEY GIVE A BAD NAME
TO THE REST OF US DEMONS.
- YES, INDEED.
- YEAH. WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU ACTUALLY EXPECT A THANK YOU
FROM THOSE MORTALS?
- YOU AGAIN?
WHY DON'T WE FINISH OFF
THAT LITTLE SCORE OF OURS?
- SURE! THOUGHT YOU'D NEVER ASK.
- YOU SHOULD BE SO LUCKY.
- INUYASHA, SIT!
- UNH!
- JEEZ, WHAT ARE YOU
TRYING TO PROVE?
- OH, MAN!
- [HUMMING]
♪ IN THE MOUNTAINS
IN THE BREEZE ♪
♪ IN THE FOREST
IN MY DREAMS ♪
♪ LORD SESSHOMARU
WHERE ARE YOU? ♪
♪ JAKEN IS SERVING
UNDER YOU, TOO ♪
- RIN.
- LORD SESSHOMARU!
- LET'S BE OFF.
- OH, HURRY UP!
- COMING! AHH!
♪ I WILL WAIT FOR YOU
ON MY OWN ♪
♪ PLEASE RETURN TO ME
WAITING ALL ALONE ♪
[WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
♪ EVERY HEART ♪
[CONTINUES IN JAPANESE]
- I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
SANGO'S BEEN PROPOSED TO
BY A LORD!
- HOW CAN SHE FLIRT WITH HIM?
AND RIGHT IN FRONT OF ME, TOO.
- YOU'RE ONE TO TALK.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO SAY,
SANGO?
HE'S HANDSOME, SINCERE,
AND HE REALLY LOVES YOU.
HE'S THE EXACT OPPOSITE
OF MIROKU.
- NOW, NOW, LET'S NOT START
CRITICIZING PEOPLE.
- WOULD YOU MAKE UP YOUR MIND?
HERE. LET ME DECIDE FOR YOU.
NEXT TIME, "ONLY YOU, SANGO."
- EXCUSE ME, MISS.
WOULD YOU HAVE MY CHILDREN?
- HE'S HOPELESS!