>> HERE WE COME.
IT'S THE START OF INUYASHA.
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL THE
SHARDS OF THE SECRET JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY NARAKU WITH
MY TETSUSAIGA.
>> INUYASHA'S OLDER BROTHER,
SESSHOMARU, DETESTED HUMANS SO
MUCH, YET A YOUNG MORTAL GIRL
NOW ACCOMPANIES HIM.
HIS SQUIRE JAKEN IS CAUGHT
BETWEEN THEM, AND THEY'RE QUITE
THE TRIO.
>> IT'S UP TO US, MIROKU, SANGO,
SHIPPO, AND KIRARA.
>> TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FEUDAL FAIRY TALE.
>> INUYASHA!
[INTRO SONG IN JAPANESE]
>> WE'RE TRYING TO TRACK DOWN
NARAKU, WHO HAS DISAPPEARED AND
HEADED TO THE NORTHEAST.
AT THE SAME TIME, INUYASHA'S
OLDER BROTHER, SESSHOMARU, IS
ALSO LOOKING FOR NARAKU.
>> LORD SESSHOMARU, I'M
STARTING TO GET REALLY HUNGRY.
MAY I GO AND LOOK FOR SOMETHING
TO EAT?
>> QUIET.
A FOREST LIKE THIS WILL HAVE
NOTHING FOR YOU TO EAT.
YOU'LL JUST HAVE TO WAIT.
>> YES, BUT...
>> I DON'T WANT TO HEAR ANY
"BUTS" OUT OF YOU.
BE QUIET AND--UH?
>> I'LL BE VERY QUICK.
>> OH, SILLY GIRL.
YOU COME BACK HERE RIGHT NOW!
>> JAKEN.
>> UH?
>> LET HER BE.
>> OH, I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
>> I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
WHY'D YOU EAT IT ALL?
>> GET OFF MY BACK, WOULD YOU?
>> BUT THAT WAS THE LAST BAG OF
GARLIC FLAVORED CHIPS.
>> SO WHAT?
IT WAS JUST A COUPLE BAGS.
>> NEWS FLASH: THAT'S NOT THE
POINT, INUYASHA!
I WANTED TO GIVE THEM TO
JINENJI.
BESIDES, YOU NEVER EAT THESE.
>> IT'S NOT MY FAULT.
I TOOK ONE PIECE, AND I
COULDN'T STOP.
>> SO WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO
BRING HIM NOW?
>> UM, WHO'S THIS JINENJI
PERSON?
>> DON'T YOU REMEMBER?
WHEN KIRARA COLLAPSED FROM
NARAKU'S TOXIC POISON, IT WAS
JINENJI WHO GAVE US THE
ANTIDOTE.
>> OH, I REMEMBER THAT.
>> WE'RE NEAR JINENJI'S
VILLAGE, SO I THOUGHT MAYBE WE
COULD STOP BY AND PAY HIM A
LITTLE VISIT.
BUT SOMEONE ATE HIS PRESENT.
>> ARGH, QUIT GOING ON ABOUT
THAT!
>> SAY, ISN'T JINENJI A
HALF-DEMON AS WELL?
>> YES, BUT HE'S GENTLE AND A
VERY NICE PERSON...
UNLIKE INUYASHA.
>> OH, WELL, THERE'S NO PRESENT
FOR HIM SO LET'S JUST KEEP ON
GOING.
>> NO, IF THERE IS AN ANTIDOTE
TO THE POISON, WE REALLY SHOULD
STOP BY AND GET SOME FOR SAFE
KEEPING.
>> I WANT TO THANK HIM FOR
SAVING KIRARA, TOO.
>> GREAT, THEN LET'S ALL GO
VISIT HIM.
INUYASHA CAN DO AS HE PLEASES.
>> ABSOLUTELY HEARTLESS.
>> OH.
AH.
THESE ARE EDIBLE.
[SCREAMING]
AH!
>> YOU ARE ABSOLUTELY
BRILLIANT, LORD SESSHOMARU!
>> YOU'RE SO DASHING, LORD
SESSHOMARU!
>> THE SANYOSHO, NARAKU'S
POISONOUS INSECTS.
>> STAND BACK OUT OF THE WAY.
THAT NARAKU, HE LEFT BEHIND
SOME ANNOYING VERMIN.
JAKEN, THERE SHOULD BE A HIVE
LOCATED NEARBY.
>> YES, I'LL GO LOOK FOR IT!
>> JAKEN.
>> LOOK, MASTER JAKEN.
THAT'S IT, THE HIVE!
>> UH?
RIN, GET DOWN NOW!
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> FEEL THE WRATH OF THE STAFF
OF TWO HEADS!
>> PERSISTENT PESTS!
RIN, KEEP YOUR HEAD DOWN!
I MUST PROTECT RIN, OTHERWISE
WHO KNOWS WHAT LORD SESSHOMARU
WILL SAY!
>> MASTER JAKEN.
>> WHAT?
STILL HERE?
>> JAKEN.
>> YOU SAVED ME, LORD
SESSHOMARU!
>> THANK YOU, LORD SESSHOMARU!
>> AH!
>> MASTER JAKEN!
>> THEY SHOULD LEAD ME TO HIM.
>> LORD SESSHOMARU!
>> RIN, TAKE THE STINGERS OUT!
>> DID YOU GET THEM OUT?
>> I'M SORRY.
I COULDN'T GET THEM.
>> AH!
NO!
THE TOXIC POISON HAS ENTERED MY
BODY!
IF I DON'T DO SOMETHING,
I MAY DIE!
[CRYING]
>> I'M SORRY.
IT'S MY FAULT.
YOU SAVED ME.
>> DON'T BE SO FOOLISH.
I'M NOT GOING TO SACRIFICE MY
LIFE FOR YOU!
I'M DYING FOR LORD SESSHOMARU!
>> MASTER JAKEN, ISN'T THERE
SOME WAY TO GET RID OF THE
POISON?
>> IT'S MUCH TOO LATE FOR ME
NOW.
I HAVE BEEN HAPPY TRAVELING THE
LAND WITH MY LORD AND MENTOR
MASTER SESSHOMARU.
EVEN IF MY LIFE SHOULD COME TO A
TRAGIC END HERE, I CAN DIE IN
PEACE.
>> MASTER JAKEN.
>> TELL LORD SESSHOMARU THIS:
I WILL BE PRAYING FOR HIS
WELL-BEING AND SUCCESS FROM MY
RESTING PLACE IN THE
NETHERWORLD.
TELL HIM FOR ME.
>> MASTER JAKEN, PLEASE DON'T
TALK LIKE THIS!
I DON'T WANT TO SEE YOU DIE!
PLEASE, PLEASE TELL ME WHAT
TO DO.
I'LL DO WHATEVER YOU ASK!
>> YOU WILL?
>> UH-HUH.
>> THERE IS ONE SMALL GLIMMER OF
HOPE.
>> MASTER JAKEN, DON'T DIE.
>> LISTEN WELL, RIN.
TO THE EAST OF HERE IS AN HERB
FARM KNOWN AS JINENJI'S GARDEN.
GO THERE AND GET THE BERRIES OF
THE SINENSO THOUSAND-YEAR
FLOWER.
>> THE BERRIES OF THE
THOUSAND-YEAR FLOWER?
>> THAT'S CORRECT.
RIN, IF YOU TRULY WANT TO SAVE
ME, YOU MUST HURRY.
BEFORE THE SUN SETS, I MUST
SWALLOW THE BERRIES OF THE
THOUSAND-YEAR FLOWERS OR ELSE
THE TOXIC POISON WILL SPREAD
THROUGHOUT MY BODY, AND I WILL
BE DOOMED.
>> DON'T WORRY, JAKEN.
I WILL RETURN BEFORE THE SUN
SETS.
I PROMISE.
>> AH-UN, GO FASTER!
>> HMM, ARE YOU QUITE SURE THIS
IS THE RIGHT WAY, KAGOME?
>> HMM, I THINK SO, BUT I'M NOT
SURE.
IT WAS THIS WAY, WASN'T IT,
INUYASHA?
>> OH, NOW ALL OF A SUDDEN MY
OPINION IS IMPORTANT?
>> COME ON, ARE YOU STILL
SULKING ABOUT WHAT I SAID?
OK, I APOLOGIZE FOR BEING RUDE.
THERE, YOU HAPPY?
>> SHE'S JUST SAYING THAT
AS USUAL.
SHE DIDN'T EVEN MEAN IT.
>> I KNOW THAT SMELL.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER, INUYASHA?
>> THAT'S DEFINITELY THEM--
NARAKU'S POISONOUS INSECTS.
>> UH?
>> HEH, I COULDN'T ASK FOR
BETTER LUCK.
THIS PLACE COULD USE SOME PEST
CONTROL.
>> INUYASHA, WAIT A MINUTE.
>> HUH?
>> KAGOME, ARE YOU SENSING ANY
SECRET JEWEL SHARDS NEARBY?
>> MM-MM, NO, NOT ANYWHERE
NEARBY.
>> AND NO DEMON PUPPETS EITHER?
THEN PERHAPS THE POISONOUS
INSECTS ARE HEADING BACK TO
NARAKU.
>> IF WE FOLLOW THEM INSTEAD OF
KILLING THEM...
>> WE'LL FIND NARAKU.
LET'S GET GOING.
>> LOOK, THEY'RE FALLING!
>> WHAT?
>> ARE THEY DEAD?
>> I DON'T GET IT.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> SESSHOMARU.
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO THE
SANYOSHO?
DID YOU KILL THEM?
>> SANYOSHO?
YOU MEAN THOSE POISON INSECTS?
>> YOU'RE SO SHORT-SIGHTED.
>> WHAT?
>> I WAS FOLLOWING THEM TO
NARAKU, BUT NOW, I HAVE NOTHING
TO LEAD ME.
>> LET ME MAKE ONE THING CLEAR.
I DIDN'T KILL THOSE BUGS.
>> YOU HAVE AN EXCUSE FOR
EVERYTHING.
IT DOES GET SO TIRESOME.
>> HA, I DON'T HAVE TO MAKE
EXCUSES FOR YOU.
I'M TELLING THE TRUTH.
>> INUYASHA ISN'T LYING.
HE DIDN'T KILL THEM!
>> STAY OUT OF THIS, KAGOME.
HE'S SO STUBBORN.
HE NEVER UNDERSTANDS.
>> INUYASHA, I'M NOT FEELING
PARTICULARLY MAGNANIMOUS TODAY.
I WON'T GO EASY ON YOU LIKE I
HAVE IN THE PAST.
>> OH, CUT THE CRAP, AND DON'T
COME CRYING TO ME AFTERWARD.
>> COME ON, STOP IT, BOTH OF
YOU!
>> YOU'RE WASTING YOUR BREATH.
>> THOSE TWO ARE CONSTANTLY AT
ODDS WITH EACH OTHER.
>> I'LL SECOND THAT.
>> AH-UN, YOU WAIT THERE UNTIL I
GET BACK.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT--AN HERBAL
GARDEN, AND THIS IS THE PLANT I
NEED!
UH, EXCUSE ME.
>> HUH?
WHO ARE YOU?
>> A WITCH.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> I'M REALLY SORRY TO INTRUDE,
BUT I WANT TO SEE JINENJI.
>> NO CAN DO.
JINENJI ISN'T SEEING ANYONE
TODAY.
GO ON HOME.
>> YOU'RE HERE, AREN'T YOU
JINENJI?
PLEASE HEAR ME OUT.
I NEED YOU TO GIVE ME SOME
SINENSO BERRIES.
MY FRIEND HAS BEEN POISONED,
AND HE MIGHT DIE ANY MINUTE!
>> THAT'S A TERRIBLE SHAME.
NONETHELESS, I DON'T HAVE ANY
SINENSO BERRIES HERE.
GO HOME.
>> JINENJI, WHAT'S WRONG WITH
YOU?
WHY DON'T YOU COME OUT FROM
UNDER THE COVERS AND TALK TO ME?
>> YOU'RE JUST A LITTLE GIRL, SO
YOU WON'T UNDERSTAND.
JINENJI IS A HALF-DEMON.
>> HALF-DEMON?
>> FROM TIME TO TIME HIS DEMON
APPEARANCE CHANGES AND HE TAKES
ON HIS HUMAN FORM.
HE'S SUCH A COWARD.
HE DOESN'T WANT ANYONE TO SEE
HIS HUMAN SELF.
>> THEN PLEASE TELL ME WHERE I
CAN FIND THE BERRIES, JINENJI.
I'LL GO GET THEM MYSELF.
>> SINENSO BERRIES ARE USED AS
AN ANTIDOTE BY DEMONS.
ARE YOU TRYING TO SAVE A DEMON,
LITTLE GIRL?
>> MM-HMM.
>> DO YOU MEAN YOU ARE SMITTEN
WITH THIS DEMON?
>> SMITTEN?
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
>> NEVER MIND DEAR, YOU ARE SO
YOUNG, YOU COULDN'T POSSIBLY
KNOW ABOUT IT.
I WAS LIKE YOU ONCE, YOUNG AND
INNOCENT.
>> NEVER MIND THAT.
I HAVE TO TRY TO SAVE MASTER
JAKEN.
>> MOTHER.
>> HUH?
>> THIS GIRL RESEMBLES KAGOME.
>> KAGOME?
OH, YES, THAT YOUNG GIRL.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> THE SINENSO GROWS IN THE
RAVINE OF THE MOUNTAIN OUT BACK.
BUT THERE ARE LOTS OF DEMONS
AND BEASTS IN THE AREA.
A HUMAN...
WOULD NEVER MAKE IT
BACK...
ALIVE.
WHEN IT'S DARK, I'LL RETURN TO
NORMAL.
WHY DON'T YOU WAIT UNTIL THEN?
>> IT'LL BE TOO LATE.
TELL ME WHAT KIND OF PLANT IT
IS.
I'LL GO GET IT MYSELF.
>> YOU ARE SO SIMILAR TO KAGOME.
>> RIN, LORD SESSHOMARU.
[CRYING]
NO, I DON'T WANT TO DIE ALONE.
>> AH-UN, THERE'S THE RAVINE!
THAT MUST BE THE PLACE.
>> TIME FOR MY WEAPON!
>> WHAT?
>> I WIN THIS TIME.
ARE YOU PREPARED TO DIE,
INUYASHA?
>> I DON'T CARE ABOUT MY LIFE.
KILL ME AND GET IT OVER WITH.
>> INDEED.
>> WAIT!
DO YOU WANT TO KNOW WHERE TO
FIND NARAKU?
THEN HEAD FOR THE OX TIGER.
SOMEONE SENSED NARAKU'S PRESENCE
HEADING THAT WAY.
>> KAGOME, SHUT UP!
>> IN THE DIRECTION OF THE OX
TIGER?
THAT'S ALL I NEED TO KNOW, THANK
YOU.
YOU WERE FORTUNATE THIS TIME,
INUYASHA.
>> WAIT, SESSHOMARU!
WHY ARE YOU AFTER NARAKU?
>> I HAVE A SCORE TO SETTLE.
>> [WHIMPERING]
AH!
HUH?
THANK YOU, AH-UN.
SINENSO BERRIES OF THE
THOUSAND-YEAR FLOWER.
[GASP]
THERE IT IS, THAT HAS TO BE IT.
AH!
SORRY, AH-UN.
KEEP THEM AT BAY.
I'M GOING TO GET THE BERRIES.
AH!
I'M SCARED!
LORD SESSHOMARU!
MY MOTHER AND FATHER ARE BOTH
DEAD.
I DON'T WANT ANYONE ELSE TO DIE.
I DON'T WANT TO SEE ANYONE ELSE
DIE.
MASTER JAKEN, PLEASE DON'T DIE.
I DON'T WANT ANYONE ELSE TO DIE.
AH!
LORD SESSHOMARU!
>> THE POISON IS SPREADING.
THE SUN IS SETTING ON ME.
RIN DIDN'T MAKE IT BACK IN TIME
WITH THE ANTIDOTE.
MY VISION IS BECOMING BLURRY.
AM I SEEING THINGS?
IT'S YOU!
LORD SESSHOMARU!
AH, THE ANTIDOTE!
HMM, NOT BAD.
>> MASTER JAKEN,
DON'T DIE ON ME.
>> WHAT?
A LITTLE GIRL CAME BY?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
I WAS WORRIED ABOUT WHETHER OR
NOT SHE WAS ABLE TO GET THE
SINENSO BERRIES SHE NEEDED.
>> SOMETHING TELLS ME SHE DID
OK.
SHE REMINDED ME SO MUCH OF
KAGOME HERE.
>> SHE WAS LIKE KAGOME?
>> SHE WAS, AND I'M QUITE
CERTAIN SHE'S MUCH STRONGER
THAN EVEN I AM.
LIKE KAGOME, SHE WARMED MY
HEART.
SHE WAS LIKE THE CHILD OF THE
SUN.
SHE HAS A VERY KIND HEART, THAT
MUCH I'M SURE OF.
>> STOP JINENJI, YOU'RE
EMBARRASSING ME.
>> LET ME CORRECT YOU THERE,
JINENJI, BECAUSE I THINK YOU'VE
GOT SOMETHING ALL WRONG.
>> HUH?
>> KAGOME'S HEART IS A LOT
SMALLER THAN YOU MIGHT THINK.
>> INUYASHA.
>> HUH?
>> SIT!
>> WHAT'D I TELL YOU, JINENJI?
WOULD A KIND-HEARTED PERSON DO
THAT?
>> SIT, SIT, SIT, SIT, SIT, SIT!
>> SO STUPID.
>> I'LL SAY.
>> YEAH.
>> OH, YOU'RE AWAKE.
>> MASTER JAKEN, YOU'RE ALL
BETTER NOW.
EITHER THAT, OR MAYBE I DIED
WHEN I FELL OFF THE CLIFF.
>> YOU SILLY FOOL.
LORD SESSHOMARU BROUGHT YOU BACK
HERE.
YOU DIDN'T DIE.
>> DO YOU MEAN HE SAVED ME?
>> THAT'S RIGHT, AND YOU'D
BETTER STOP CAUSING HIM SO MUCH
TROUBLE, YOUNG LADY.
>> I KNOW, I'M SORRY.
MASTER JAKEN, I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE
WELL AGAIN.
I WAS SO WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
>> STOP, RIN, GET AWAY, SHOO!
>> I WON'T!
>> TO THE NORTHEAST IS HE?
>> LORD SESSHOMARU.
>> WE'RE GOING.
>> HA-HA.
>> HEE-HEE, WE'RE ALL TOGETHER
AGAIN, MY LORD.
ISN'T IT WONDERFUL?
[LAUGHING]
>> [JAPANESE SONG]
>> WHAT'LL I DO?
KIRARA IS GONE.
>> MAYBE SHE WENT FOR A WALK.
IT DIDN'T SEEM LIKE ANYTHING
WAS BOTHERING HER.
>> SHE'S NEVER DISAPPEARED LIKE
THIS BEFORE, THOUGH.
MAYBE SHE'S LOST.
OH, I'M GETTING SO WORRIED.
WAIT, COULD THAT HAVE MADE HER
RUN AWAY?
>> NEXT TIME...
KIRARA COME HOME!
>> KIRARA, DON'T LEAVE ME LIKE
THIS.