>> HERE WE COME.
IT'S THE START OF "INUYASHA."
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL THE
SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY NARAKU WITH
MY TETSAIGA.
>> SANGO'S VILLAGE OF DEMON
SLAYERS WAS ATTACKED, AND HER
YOUNGER BROTHER KOHAKU FELL INTO
NARAKU'S HANDS.
BUT SANGO HAS A CUTE, DEPENDABLE
FRIEND, KILALA, WHO'S ALWAYS BY
HER SIDE.
>> IT'S UP TO ALL OF US.
>> TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FEUDAL FAIRY TALE, "INUYASHA."
[WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> MY FRIEND KILALA IS A FELINE
NEKOMATA DEMON WITH TWO TAILS.
WHEN SHE BATTLES, SHE GROWS IN
SIZE AND EVEN FLIES THROUGH THE
AIR.
MOST OF THE TIME, THOUGH, SHE'S
JUST A LOVABLE LITTLE CAT.
SHE'S VERY GOOD-NATURED AND
PUTS
UP WITH OTHER PEOPLE'S STUBBORN
WAYS.
YOU SHOULD TEACH THEM A LESSON
ONCE IN A WHILE, KILALA.
>> KILALA!
KILALA?
HI.
YOU HAVEN'T SEEN KILALA AROUND,
HAVE YOU?
>> NOPE. NOT ME.
>> NO.
>> SOMETHING HAPPENED TO KILALA?
>> I HAVEN'T SEEN HER SINCE I
WOKE UP.
SHE WAS ALREADY GONE.
>> MAYBE SHE WENT FOR A WALK.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
SHE WOULD NEVER GO OFF WITHOUT
TELLING ME.
>> IS IT POSSIBLE SHE COULD HAVE
RUN AWAY?
>> MAYBE SHE'S JUST IN HEAT.
>> OR AT THAT REBELLIOUS STAGE.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GUYS SAYING?
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
REASSURING
HER, NOT MAKING HER WORRY.
>> KILALA SEEMED HER USUAL SELF
WHEN WE WENT TO SLEEP LAST
NIGHT.
>> SHE'S ONLY BEEN GONE FOR A
WHILE.
THAT AIN'T NO REASON FOR
EVERYONE TO START GETTING ALL
PANICKY.
>> INUYASHA!
>> I'M JUST SAYING, YOU CAN'T
GO
AROUND WORRYING ABOUT EVERY
LITTLE THING THAT GOES WRONG.
GIVE HER SOME SPACE.
SHE'LL COME BACK BEFORE YOU
KNOW IT.
>> I SURE HOPE YOU'RE RIGHT
ABOUT THAT.
>> COME ON.
STOP WORRYING.
KILALA CAN TAKE CARE OF HERSELF,
UNLIKE A CERTAIN OTHER KID I
KNOW, AND I DON'T HAVE TO NAME
NAMES.
>> OH, I HEAR YOU BIG-TIME.
WHAT CERTAIN OTHER KID?
>> A SHORT CARROT-TOP WHO'S
ALWAYS IN MY FACE, AND HE'S
ABOUT TO HAVE A LITTLE ACCIDENT!
>> AAH!
>> WHY DON'T YOU COME AND JOIN
ME, LADIES?
THE FISH IS GRILLED TO
PERFECTION.
>> I DON'T BELIEVE THAT GUY.
>> WHO SAID KILALA WOULD BE
RIGHT BACK?
>> HUH?
>> SHE'S BEEN MISSING A WHOLE
DAY NOW.
>> GET OFF MY BACK!
YOU'RE ACTING LIKE IT'S MY
FAULT!
>> IT IS YOUR FAULT!
IF IT WEREN'T FOR YOU, WE WOULD
HAVE BEEN SEARCHING FOR HER
ALREADY, DOOFUS!
>> UH!
WHAT DID YOU SAY, YOU LITTLE
CREEP?
GET OFF OF ME!
>> THAT'S IT.
I'M GOING TO TRY AND FIND
KILALA.
>> WAIT.
YOU'RE NEVER GOING TO FIND HER
WITHOUT SOME KIND OF A LEAD.
>> NOW INUYASHA DECIDES TO COME
TO THE RESCUE.
>> HUH?
AND YOU'RE SHOWING ME THIS
BECAUSE...
>> IT'S KILALA'S FOOD DISH.
THIS IS WHAT SHE EATS HER CAT
FOOD OUT OF.
>> GREAT, BUT WHAT AM I SUPPOSED
TO DO WITH IT?
>> WELL, I FIGURED YOU MIGHT
WANT TO TAKE A SNIFF OF IT.
>> LIKE I DON'T ALREADY KNOW
KILALA'S SCENT?
>> YOU CAN DO IT, INUYASHA.
WELL? DID YOU GET ANYTHING?
>> NOT REALLY.
THE SCENT ENDS RIGHT HERE.
>> SO WE'RE 3 STEPS CLOSER TO
FINDING HER.
>> I THINK WE'D BETTER SPLIT UP
AND KEEP SEARCHING.
>> IT'S A WASTE OF TIME.
HER SCENT ENDED, SO THAT MEANS
SHE MUST HAVE TAKEN OFF AND
FLOWN SOMEWHERE.
BESIDES, I'M NOT PICKING UP ANY
OF HER SCENT AROUND HERE.
>> SO WHAT?
KEEP LOOKING.
WE CAN'T JUST CARRY ON WITHOUT
HER.
>> YEAH, I FIGURED THAT MUCH.
>> WELL, THEN.
>> YO, SANGO, ARE YOU SURE THERE
ISN'T SOMETHING YOU'RE NOT
TELLING US?
>> HMM?
>> LIKE MAYBE YOU TWO HAD A
FIGHT AND SHE TOOK OFF TO STAY
WITH A FRIEND FOR A WHILE.
COME ON, THERE MUST BE
SOMETHING.
>> I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE GETTING
AT, BUT--
>> ANYTHING AT ALL WOULD HELP.
DID SHE LOSE HER APPETITE
LATELY?
OR PERHAPS SHE STARTED GETTING A
BIT MOODY.
OR MAYBE THERE'S A LARGE PATCH
OF CATNIP GROWING NEAR HERE.
>> NO, NO, BUT MAYBE IT'S MY
FAULT.
>> HUH?
>> IT'S JUST THAT EVERY TIME I
GO INTO BATTLE, I DRAG HER
ALONG WITH ME.
WHEN WE NEED TO TRAVEL A
DISTANCE, WE TAKE HER FOR
GRANTED AND RIDE ON HER BACK.
I MAKE HER GO ON ERRANDS AND
DON'T EVEN THINK TO REWARD HER.
SHE LOVES FISH, AND YET I ALMOST
NEVER TREAT HER TO SOME.
>> SANGO, DON'T PIN THE BLAME
ON
YOURSELF.
>> KILALA'S NOT THE TYPE TO RUN
AWAY OVER THOSE THINGS.
>> I GOT IT!
>> YOU GOT WHAT?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> I THINK I KNOW WHY KILALA
DISAPPEARED.
>> HMM?
>> IT CAME TO ME RIGHT AFTER
INUYASHA GAVE ME A NOOGIE.
I GAVE IT SOME SERIOUS THOUGHT,
AND THE ANSWER CAME TO ME.
>> SO, TELL US WHY KILALA TOOK
OFF.
>> IT'S OBVIOUS.
>> HMM?
>> YOU PEOPLE DROVE POOR KILALA
AWAY!
>> STOP BEATING AROUND THE BUSH
AND TELL US YOUR LITTLE THEORY.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN, SHIPPO?
I HAVEN'T BEEN TOO BAD.
>> ARE YOU POSITIVE ABOUT THAT?
>> HMM?
>> PUT YOUR HAND ON YOUR HEART
AND TAKE A GOOD LOOK DEEP INTO
YOUR SOULS.
CAN YOU HONESTLY SAY THAT NOT
ONE OF YOU HAS EVER DONE
ANYTHING MEAN TO KILALA?
>> YEAH.
I AIN'T DONE NOTHIN'.
>> I CAN'T THINK OF ANYTHING I
POSSIBLY DID TO HURT HER.
>> I WAS AFRAID IT WOULD COME TO
THIS.
I'LL HAVE TO REMIND YOU OF EACH
RANDOM ACT OF CRUELTY, WHICH
ULTIMATELY LED HER TO RUN AWAY.
FIRST, YOU, INUYASHA.
>> HUH?
>> YOU USED TO SECRETLY PRACTICE
THE WIND SCAR ON KILALA WHEN YOU
WERE TRYING TO MASTER THE
BACKLASH WAVE TECHNIQUE.
>> I PRACTICED THE WIND SCAR ON
KILALA?
HMM.
>> WIND SCAR!
OH, NO!
>> [MOANS]
>> [PANTING]
KILALA, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
NO!
YOUR FUR!
BALD SPOTS.
DON'T WORRY.
IT'LL GROW BACK.
AH!
THAT'LL ALL GROW BACK, TOO.
HA HA HA!
LET'S SEE HOW DINNER'S COMING
ALONG.
>> I SAW YOU, INUYASHA.
>> IS THAT THE TRUTH?
>> COME TO THINK OF IT, SHE DID
HAVE SOME BALD SPOTS--QUITE A
FEW.
>> YOU THOUGHT NO ONE WAS
WATCHING, BUT I WITNESSED THE
WHOLE THING.
YOU KNOW WHY KILALA RAN AWAY?
BECAUSE OF YOU, INUYASHA!
YOU ARE TO BLAME!
>> UGH!
>> WELL, I HAD NO IDEA.
>> SO INUYASHA WAS RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE BALD SPOTS, AND THAT'S
WHY SHE RAN AWAY.
>> SHE'S JUST MISSING!
YOU CAN'T MAKE IT SOUND LIKE I
DROVE HER AWAY JUST BECAUSE
SOME FUR WENT FLYING.
BESIDES, THOSE SPOTS GAVE HER
CHARACTER, AND SHE'S PROBABLY
FORGOTTEN ALL ABOUT IT BY NOW.
>> SO YOU THINK SHE LEFT FOR
ANOTHER REASON?
>> MAYBE I CAN HELP YOU THERE.
>> HUH?
>> MIROKU, DON'T TELL ME
YOU'VE FORGOTTEN.
[LAUGHTER]
>> OOH.
WHAT LUCK.
PRETTY VILLAGE GIRLS.
HUH?
I THINK IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO
HELP ME OUT, KILALA.
KILALA, GO TO THEM.
>> OH, WHAT AN ADORABLE LITTLE
CAT THIS IS.
>> WHY, HELLO.
>> [MEOWS]
>> HER NAME IS KILALA, AND SHE
MAKES A FINE TRAVEL COMPANION,
WOULDN'T YOU SAY?
>> SHE'S SO CUTE.
>> CUTE, BUT SHE'S NO
COMPARISON
TO YOU LADIES.
>> HA HA HA!
YOU FLATTER US, MONK.
>> THAT'S ONLY THE BEGINNING.
>> SUCH A MANLY MONK IS INDEED
RARE AROUND THESE PARTS.
>> YOU MUST SPEND THE NIGHT IN
OUR VILLAGE, DEAR BOY.
>> COME TO MY HOUSE.
>> NO, MINE.
[ALL TALKING AT ONCE]
>> ONLY KILALA CAN GET ME OUT OF
THIS ONE.
KILALA!
>> [HISSES]
>> [SCREAMING]
>> EVIL SPIRIT, BEGONE!
>> I SAW THE WHOLE THING,
MIROKU.
>> THAT'S DISGUSTING.
>> MIROKU, YOU'RE EVEN WORSE
THAN I AM.
>> HA HA.
IT WASN'T AS BAD AS IT SOUNDED.
>> HOW COULD YOU DO SUCH A
THING?
KILALA'S OUR FRIEND, NOT SOME
KIND OF SLAVE.
YOU SHOULDN'T GO TAKING
ADVANTAGE OF HER, MIROKU.
BETTER REMEMBER THAT.
>> HUH.
THOSE IN GLASS HUTS SHOULDN'T
CAST STONES, KAGOME.
>> HA HA.
MMM.
>> MMM.
>> [SLURPING]
>> WHAT'LL I DO?
>> WHAT'S WITH YOU, KAGOME?
IS SOMETHING THE MATTER?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
>> DON'T TELL ME--ANOTHER TEST.
>> WHAT WAS THAT?
NO, I DON'T HAVE A TEST.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
OH!
I KNOW!
>> THIS FEELS GREAT.
>> PLEASE HELP ME, KILALA.
JUST DO ME THIS ONE LITTLE
FAVOR.
PRETTY PLEASE?
IF YOU DO, I'LL GIVE YOU A
WHOLE
BUNCH OF FLOUNDER AND
TUNA-FLAVORED CAT TREATS, OK?
>> [MEOW]
>> I SAW THAT, KAGOME.
YOU MIND TELLING US WHY YOU WENT
BACK HOME THAT TIME?
>> WELL, ACTUALLY...
I KNOW IT'S A LOT TO ASK, BUT I
NEED YOU TO WAIT HERE FOR ME.
I'LL COME BACK AS SOON AS I
CAN.
STAY THERE.
I WON'T BE LONG, OK?
>> OH, I SUPPOSE WE SHOULD START
WITHOUT HER.
>> NO SENSE IN WAITING ANY
LONGER.
>> HUH?
>> GRANDPA!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, OLD GUY.
>> KAGOME, YOU'RE HOME!
>> I WAS HOPING YOU'D MAKE IT
BACK IN TIME.
>> INUYASHA DIDN'T COME BACK
WITH YOU THIS TIME, HUH?
>> NOPE. HERE.
I BROUGHT THIS PRESENT BACK FOR
YOU, GRAMPS.
>> WELL, ISN'T THIS
MAGNIFICENT?
>> THIS TIME IT'S THE REAL
McCOY, UNLIKE THAT FAKE WATER
IMP HAND YOU GAVE ME BEFORE.
>> YOU CAN STAY FOR A FEW DAYS
THIS TIME?
>> WELL, I--
>> IT IS A SPECIAL
OCCASION, SO AT LEAST STAY HERE
AND HAVE DINNER WITH US.
>> I'M WITH THAT.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
TODAY IS SPECIAL--A SPECIAL
OCCASION.
A SPECIAL OCCASION.
ON TOP OF WHICH, I FORGOT TO
BRING KILALA'S TREATS.
>> EVEN YOU, KAGOME.
>> IT WASN'T AS BAD AS IT
SOUNDED.
>> WELL, I HOPE YOU'VE ALL
LEARNED YOUR LESSON TODAY AND
YOU'LL PROMISE NEVER TO BE MEAN
TO AN INNOCENT DEMON AGAIN,
ESPECIALLY YOU, INUYASHA.
>> HUH?
>> IF YOU GIVE ME ONE MORE
NOOGIE, NO MORE KAGOME SNACKS!
NOT A FOR A WHOLE WEEK!
>> SINCE WHEN ARE YOU CALLING
THE SHOTS?
>> WAIT, SANGO.
>> KAGOME.
>> SANGO, WE DID DO THOSE
THINGS, BUT NOT MALICIOUSLY.
>> I'M SORRY, SANGO, REALLY.
>> WE DIDN'T MEAN TO HURT
KILALA'S FEELINGS.
>> I KNOW THAT.
I'M IN NO POSITION TO
CRITICIZE.
>> DON'T BLAME YOURSELF.
>> I'M NO DIFFERENT.
I TURN OVER AND ALMOST SMOTHER
HER IN MY SLEEP, AND WHEN I'M
IN A BAD MOOD, I WAKE HER UP AT
NIGHT SO I CAN THINK.
>> YEAH, I KNOW, BUT THAT'S
NOTHING TO BEAT YOURSELF UP
OVER.
I'D MAKE HER TRANSFORM JUST SO
SHE COULD LIGHT THE CAMPFIRE.
AND WHO KNOWS HOW MANY TIMES A
DAY I GRABBED HER PAWS?
I PINCHED HER NOSE WHILE SHE WAS
ASLEEP.
I DRESSED HER UP JUST FOR KICKS.
>> YOU'RE NOT DOING YOURSELF
ANY
FAVORS.
>> WHAT WE DID TO KILALA WAS
TAME IN COMPARISON.
>> SHE'S EVIL.
[RUMBLING]
>> OH!
>> AAH!
[BOOM]
>> HA HA HA!
SUCH A FOOLISH HUMAN.
HOW COULD YOU EVEN THINK YOU
COULD ESCAPE MY TERRITORY?
>> PLEASE HAVE MERCY ON ME!
>> THIS FOREST HAS LITTLE FOOD.
I WON'T LET A MEAL SLIP AWAY.
>> AAH!
>> AW, DAMN IT.
I WAS HOPING TO FIND KILALA IN
HERE, BUT IT'S ONLY SOME
ONE-EYED BABOON WANNABE AND A
MORTAL.
>> [GROWLING]
>> HEY, MISTER, YOU MIGHT WANT
TO GET OUT OF HERE.
>> AAH!
ANOTHER DEMON!
>> INGRATE.
>> HOW DARE YOU FREE MY PREY!
AAH!
>> INUYASHA!
>> A DEMON!
>> WHERE'S KILALA?
>> SHE'S NOT HERE, BUT SHE
CAN'T
BE FAR, BECAUSE I CAN SMELL HER.
>> WHO ARE YOU?
WHY ARE YOU IN MY FOREST?
>> HEY, LOOK AT THAT!
>> THE SCARF I GAVE KILALA.
>> HA HA HA!
>> THAT'S NOT ALL, EITHER.
BEHIND HIM THERE ARE BONES AND
SKULLS AND STUFF SCATTERED ALL
OVER THE PLACE.
>> OH, NO.
>> WHERE IS SHE?!
DID YOU EAT KILALA?
>> HA HA HA!
YOU FOOLS.
AS IF I'D REMEMBER THE NAMES OF
EVERY SINGLE THING I'VE EATEN.
>> DID YOU EAT OUR DEMON CAT
FRIEND?
>> NOW, NOW.
YOU WILL BE MEETING YOUR FRIEND
SOON ENOUGH.
IN MY STOMACH!
>> [SHOUTING]
>> HA HA HA!
YOU'RE ON MY LAND.
EVERYTHING IN MY FOREST ACTS AS
MY ALLY.
>> WATCH OUT!
>> HE'S TOO FAST.
>> HE USES THE TREE BRANCHES TO
PROPEL HIMSELF AND INCREASE HIS
SPEED, AND HE ATTACKS FROM A
HIGH ALTITUDE, WHICH IS AN
ADVANTAGE.
HE WASN'T JUST BOASTING.
THE FOREST IS HIS ALLY.
>> IF ONLY KILALA WERE HERE NOW
TO HELP US.
KILALA?
>> YES, AND FROM NOW ON, YOU
MUST TAKE CARE OF HER.
>> HA HA HA!
HMM.
HA HA HA!
>> [MEOW]
>> KILALA.
>> SO IT SEEMS YOU'RE MORE THAN
AN UGLY DEMON WHO'S LIGHT ON
HIS FEET.
I COULD USE A GOOD FIGHT.
>> I WANT REVENGE.
NOBODY MESSES WITH KILALA!
>> UH!
DON'T THINK YOU CAN DEFEAT ME
BY
SIMPLY TAKING DOWN A FEW TREE
BRANCHES.
AAAH!
>> [SOBBING]
>> OH, SANGO.
>> WE REALLY SHOULD HAVE
APPRECIATED KILALA INSTEAD OF
TAKING ADVANTAGE OF HER ALL THE
TIME.
>> KILALA WAS...
[CRYING]
>> HUH?
IT'S YOU!
>> KILALA!
>> YOU'RE OK AFTER ALL.
>> THANK GOODNESS.
>> KILALA?
KILALA!
>> CRAZY CAT.
SHE HAD US WORRIED FOR A WHILE.
>> SO WHERE WAS SHE?
>> MASTER INUYASHA.
[SLURPING]
>> IT'S BEEN QUITE A WHILE, MY
LORD.
>> MYOGA, IT'S YOU.
>> WHAT BRINGS YOU TO THESE
PARTS?
>> TOTOSAI ASKED ME TO BRING A
WHETSTONE FOR INUYASHA'S
TETSAIGA.
>> A WHETSTONE?
>> HOW DID YOU CARRY SUCH A
HEAVY STONE?
>> THAT WAS THE EASY PART.
I ASKED KILALA TO GIVE ME SOME
HELP.
I CAME ALL THIS WAY BACK TO GET
HER, THEN RODE KILALA BACK TO
TOTOSAI'S HUT TO PICK UP THE
STONE.
IT WAS A TOUGH COMMUTE, I MUST
SAY.
KILALA, IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME.
I NEED YOU TO DO ME A SMALL
FAVOR, MY FRIEND.
>> IT'S THE MIDDLE OF THE
NIGHT,
YOU KNOW.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> SHIPPO, TELL INUYASHA AND THE
OTHERS THAT I'M TAKING KILALA
WITH ME FOR A BIT.
TELL THEM WE'LL BE BACK IN
ABOUT
A DAY OR SO.
NOW, YOU GOT THAT?
>> WHATEVER.
>> BUT WHAT ABOUT THAT SCARF?
HOW DID IT GET INTO THE FOREST?
>> OH, THAT.
THAT'S SIMPLE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, KILALA?
PICK IT UP LATER.
WE DON'T HAVE ANY TIME TO
WASTE.
AND THAT'S IT.
>> HUH?
>> WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
>> UH, WAS THAT WHAT HAPPENED?
I MUST HAVE BEEN HALF ASLEEP.
IT'S MYOGA'S FAULT.
HE SHOULD HAVE KNOWN BETTER.
>> WELL, WELL.
HALF ASLEEP, WERE YOU?
I HOPE YOU'RE GOOD AND READY
FOR THIS, SHIPPO.
>> AAH!
KAGOME, HELP ME!
>> INUYASHA.
>> HUH?
>> DON'T BE TOO HARD ON HIM.
>> DO YOU HEAR THAT?
>> NO! MIROKU! SANGO!
>> I'M GLAD THINGS TURNED OUT
FOR YOU, SANGO.
>> IT WAS AN HONEST MISTAKE!
LET'S START OVER.
>> NOT ON YOUR LIFE.
[WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> KIKYO, IS SOMETHING WRONG?
>> LET'S HURRY AND GET OUT OF
HERE.
>> IT'S TOO LATE.
I'VE LOST MY SOUL COLLECTORS.
NOW GO ON WITHOUT ME.
THAT'S YOUR ONLY CHANCE OF
MAKING IT OUT ALIVE.
>> DON'T GIVE UP SO EASILY.
WE HAVE TO WORK TOGETHER IF
WE'RE GONNA GET OUT OF HERE.
NEXT TIME, KIKYO AND KAGOME
ALONE IN THE CAVE.
>> OH, THE WARMTH OF A LIVING
MORTAL.
IS THIS KAGOME'S STRENGTH?