KIRARA, DOES IT HURT?
[WHIMPERING]
NARAKU'S POISONS ARE STILL
IN YOUR SYSTEM.
AN HERBAL ANTIDOTE?
DOES THAT MEAN THERE'S A CURE
FOR KIRARA'S SICKNESS?
- HMM.
I HAVE HEARD RUMORS
OF AN HERB GARDEN
NOT FAR FROM HERE.
UNFORTUNATELY FOR US,
THERE'S ALSO A RUMOR
ABOUT A DEMON.
- BUT THAT'S A PERFECT JOB
FOR INUYASHA.
AFTER HE BEATS THE DEMON,
THEN WE CAN TAKE
WHATEVER WE NEED.
- HA. WELL, IF IT HELPS
KIRARA HERE,
I'M HAPPY TO DO IT.
SHE ACTUALLY HELPS IN BATTLE,
UNLIKE MYOGA.
[SPUTTERING]
- WE CAN ACTUALLY
COUNT ON KIRARA.
UNLIKE SOME PEOPLE,
WITHOUT HER STRENGTH,
WE COULD REALLY BE IN TROUBLE.
- MM-HMM.
[SPUTTERING]
- COME ON, YOU GUYS.
YOU'RE BEING UNFAIR.
MYOGA'S BEEN A BIG HELP TO US.
DON'T YOU REMEMBER
THAT TIME THAT HE--
THAT HE, UH--
UH, THAT HE, UH...
- OOH...OK! OK!
ENOUGH WITH
THE FAINT PRAISE ALREADY!
WHAT'S A FLEA GOTTA DO
TO CATCH A BREAK AROUND HERE?
YOU ACT LIKE SIZE IS EVERYTHING.
WELL, IT ISN'T!
BRAINS COUNT, TOO, YOU KNOW!
OH, COME ON, ADMIT IT!
ADMIT IT!
- SO THEY WENT TO FIND MEDICINE,
DID THEY?
INUYASHA AND THE OTHERS?
- YES, THEY DID,
AND I'VE STAYED BACK HERE
TO PROTECT AND LOOK AFTER YOU,
SO, NO MORE TALKING,
AND TRY AND GET SOME REST.
SOMETHING WRONG?
- IT MIGHT BE SAFER OUTSIDE.
- AND THAT'S WHY KAGOME SENT ME,
SO THAT I COULD PROTECT YOU
FROM BEING PROTECTED BY HIM.
- WHAT HE SAID.
[GROAN]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
- IT WOULD BE FASTER
IF I WENT BY MYSELF.
- LET'S SAY YOU COULD
GET THERE FASTER.
WHAT WOULD YOU DO
ONCE YOU GOT THERE, THOUGH?
COULD YOU TELL THE GOOD HERBS
FROM THE BAD?
I DON'T THINK SO.
AFTER ALL, KAEDE DID TEACH ME
ALL ABOUT THEM.
- YEAH. OK.
WHATEVER.
- AND IT'LL BE REALLY NICE
TO SPEND TIME TOGETHER.
DON'T YOU THINK?
AT FIRST, IT WAS JUST US
LOOKING FOR THE JEWEL,
BUT NOW WE HAVE HELP!
FIGHTING DEMONS ALL THE TIME
IS NOT EASY, YOU KNOW?
WE COULDN'T DO IT WITHOUT
OR FRIENDS, COULD WE, NOW?
HMM?
OH.
HE'S ASLEEP.
MUST BE TIRED.
I GUESS HE WOULD BE,
WITH THAT FIGHT WITH NARAKU.
HE MUST'VE REALLY WORN HIM OUT.
IF I'M QUIET, THOUGH,
HE WON'T WAKE UP.
QUIET.
- HELLO!
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
- OH, OH, OH...
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
OH, OH...
OH!
AAH!
- COME ON.
YOU'RE NOT STILL MAD
ABOUT THE BIKE, ARE YOU?
I SAID I WAS SORRY.
- LOOK, I'M NOT MAD, OK?
I'M NOT.
REALLY.
NOW WHAT?
- YOU LIKE SPENDING TIME
WITH ME, RIGHT?
- DEPENDS.
IS IT A TRICK QUESTION?
- OH, NEVER MIND.
I KNOW THE ANSWER.
- EXCUSE ME,
DID I MISS SOMETHING?
- HE ALWAYS RUINS EVERYTHING!
HMM?
UH, WHAT'S THAT?
- WHAT'S WHAT?
- THIRD ONE THIS WEEK.
- I TELL YOU, IT'S JINENJI.
- OF COURSE IT IS.
WHO ELSE WOULD IT BE
BUT THAT DEMON?
- WHAT DO WE DO?
- YEAH, WHAT?
- SO WHO'S JINENJI?
SOME KIND OF DEMON?
- WHY SHOULD WE TELL YOU?
- ANOTHER DEMON!
- HE IS, BUT HE'S NOT REALLY
A DEMON DEMON,
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
HEH.
- OHH!
- OH, WAIT!
THAT DIDN'T COME OUT RIGHT.
WE'RE JUST TRYING TO FIND A FARM
WHERE WE CAN FIND
A MEDICINAL HERB FOR OUR FRIEND.
- WHAT HERB?
- YOU MEAN JINENJI, THEN.
- JINENJI'S THE ONE
WHAT KILLED THIS POOR WOMAN.
- HUH?
- YOU WANT JINENJI.
BIG MONSTER WHO LIVES
EDGE OF THE VILLAGE
WITH HIS MOTHER.
- THEM PLANTS OF HIS
WORK SURE ENOUGH,
BUT LATELY, I--
THAT IS TO SAY, HE--
- LATELY, HE'S GOT HIMSELF
A TASTE FOR HUMAN FLESH,
IS WHAT IT IS.
[GROANING]
THAT'S HIM THERE.
BIG FELLER, AIN'T HE?
[GROANING]
- HUH. HE AIN'T SO BIG.
- DON'T GO MAKING US NO PROMISES
YOU CAN'T KEEP, NOW.
- I'M DOING IT FOR THE HERB,
NOT YOU.
KAGOME, YOU STAY HERE.
- OK.
- YOU RECKON HE'S STRONG ENOUGH?
- DON'T REALLY MATTER NOW,
DO IT?
AIN'T OUR PROBLEM NO MORE.
- IF WE'RE LUCKY,
MAYBE THEY'LL KILL EACH OTHER.
- OH, BOY.
- UHH.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
DIDN'T YOUR MOTHER EVER TELL YOU
NOT TO EAT PEOPLE
SMALLER THAN YOU?
UHH!
- HMM?
- HUH?
THAT'S WEIRD.
I HAVEN'T SEEN ANY
HUMAN BLOOD ON HIM.
[GROANING]
- OW!
- GO ON!
GET!
GET OUT OF HERE!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[THUNDER]
[ROARING]
[GROANING]
- HUH?
HEY! WAIT!
- MOM!
HELP!
- WHY, YOU!
- MOUNTAIN WITCH!
- TRYING TO TAKE OUR LAND
FOR YOURSELF AGAIN, ARE YA?
- UH...
- WELL, SO MUCH FOR THAT PLAN.
- RUN AWAY!
[SCREAMING]
- NOW I KNOW I MISSED SOMETHING.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- I DON'T KNOW WHO
PUT YOU UP TO IT,
OR WHAT YA BEEN TOLD,
BUT THIS BOY WOULD NEVER
EAT SOMEONE.
YOU GOT THAT?
WHO HE IS DON'T MATTER,
WHETHER HALF-DEMON OR NOT!
- HALF-DEMON?
[WHIMPERING]
- INUYASHA, WASN'T IT?
YOU'RE HALF-DEMON, TOO,
BUT YOU DON'T LOOK IT.
- SO YOU CAN TELL, CAN YOU?
- HALF-BREEDS ARE FUNNY
THAT WAY.
FOR EACH ONE BORN PRETTY,
LIKE YOU,
THERE'S ANOTHER BORN WHAT AIN'T.
- HE'S CUTE, ALL RIGHT,
BUT ONLY IF YOU'RE INTO DOGS.
[GROANS]
- JUST IMAGINE WHAT IT'S LIKE
FOR HIM.
BEING HALF-DEMON
SHOULDN'T MATTER,
BUT THOSE VILLAGERS, THEY--
THEY TREAT HIM LIKE HE'S
SOME KIND OF MONSTER
OR SOMETHING.
[GROANS]
- SO YOU'RE SAYING
THEY BULLY HIM?
- OH, TRYING TO KILL HIM,
MORE LIKE.
- I'M SORRY, MA.
IF I WEREN'T LIKE THIS, I...
- STOP THAT RIGHT NOW.
DON'T YOU APOLOGIZE
FOR BEING DIFFERENT.
YOUR FATHER, HE WAS DIFFERENT,
AND THAT NEVER MADE NO
NO-MIND TO ME.
I'LL NEVER FORGET
HOW I HURT MY ANKLE
AND COULDN'T WALK,
AND HOW IT WAS YOUR FATHER
WHO SAVED ME.
OH...THE MAN I SAW,
HE WAS GLOWING,
BUT I KNEW HE WEREN'T REAL.
NO MAN IS THAT PERFECT.
I LOVED HIM ANYWAY.
HIM AND HIS DEMON LIGHT.
OH...
- UH...
- WAIT.
IF YOU'RE SAYING
THE FATHER WAS THE DEMON,
THEN THE HUMAN PARENT WAS YOU?
- WHAT DID YOU THINK I WAS?
- I THOUGHT YOU WERE BABA YAGA!
UH--
- FOR YOU, FRIEND.
IT'S MEDICINE FOR THE FRIEND
YOU SAID GOT POISON IN HIM.
- UH, OK.
UM, HOW MUCH?
- NOTHING.
IT'S THE LEAST I CAN DO
TO MAKE UP FOR THE CLUBBING
I GAVE EARLIER.
NOW LEAVE,
BEFORE I GRIND YOUR BONES
AND MAKE OUR BREAD.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
- UM, UH...
INUYASHA, SHOULDN'T WE
BE STAYING?
- SHOULD WE?
- THE VILLAGERS.
THEY THINK JINENJI'S
BEEN EATING PEOPLE.
YOU KNOW THEY DO.
MAYBE HE IS DIFFERENT,
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
THAT HE'S GUILTY.
- BUT THAT'S WHAT IT DOES MEAN
WHEN YOU'RE DIFFERENT.
NOBODY TRUSTS YOU,
YOU'RE ALWAYS THE FIRST
TO BE BLAMED,
AND IT IS ALWAYS,
ALWAYS YOUR FAULT!
- GATHER EVERY SWORD,
EVERY SPEAR IN THE VILLAGE!
- THIS IS PLENTY.
EVEN HE CAN'T TAKE ALL THESE.
- TONIGHT'S GONNA BE THE NIGHT.
IT'S KILL OR BE KILLED.
- BUT IT'S NOT!
- SO IT'S YOU TWO AGAIN.
- YOU'RE NOT ATTACKING JINENJI,
ARE YOU?
- OF COURSE WE ARE!
- BUT--BUT YOU DON'T
HAVE ANY PROOF
THAT HE WAS THE ONE WHO--
- HOW CAN YOU BE SO NAIVE?
- THEY HATE US,
THE WITCH AND HER MONSTER SON.
- UH, COWARDS IS
WHAT THEY ARE.
- INTERESTING,
BECAUSE THE WAY I SEE IT,
IT'S THE OTHER WAY AROUND.
- WHAT?
- RIGHT NOW, THOUGH,
WE GOT MORE IMPORTANT BUSINESS,
LIKE CATCHING THE REAL
FLESH-EATER.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"REAL FLESH-EATER"?
YOU PLANNING ON CATCHING IT?
- INUYASHA, I'M GOING BACK.
- BACK WHERE?
- I'M GOING TO BE OVER
AT JINENJI'S FARM,
SO DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT
ATTACKING THERE, OK?
IF YOU HURT ME,
YOU'LL ALL HAVE TO DIE,
BECAUSE INUYASHA HERE
WILL HAVE TO AVENGE ME.
- I WILL?
SINCE WHEN?
- YOU'D BETTER AVENGE ME.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED
TO DO IF YOU DON'T?
- FINE.
I'LL AVENGE YOU ALREADY.
- THINK WE CAN TRUST HIM?
- WOULDN'T HOLD MY BREATH.
- THAT MURDERED WOMAN.
I COULD SMELL DEMON
ALL OVER HER.
I SMELL IT NOW.
REALLY CLOSE.
YAA!
- THEY DID, DID THEY?
- YEAH, WHICH IS WHY I TOLD THEM
I'D BE STAYING HERE,
TILL JINENJI COULD BE
PROVEN INNOCENT.
- HAVE IT YOUR WAY.
UHH.
- JUST PULL WEEDS, RIGHT?
- WELL, YEAH.
- SO MANY SCARS.
ALL FROM THE VILLAGERS, I BET.
HAVEN'T YOU EVER WANTED
TO GO SOMEPLACE ELSE?
- THIS PLACE IS BEST.
- HUH?
- MY PA LEFT ME THIS FARM.
- OH.
- I DID IT.
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN MY LIFE,
I TALKED TO A GIRL
AND SHE DIDN'T SCREAM.
[SCREAM]
- AAH!
IT'S A WORM!
THANK YOU.
[EXHALES]
- HMM.
SHE'S SCARED OF A WORM,
BUT NOT OF JINENJI?
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[LAUGHS]
- AHH.
LOOK.
DO YOU SEE THIS?
- MM-HMM.
IS THIS WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO BE HAPPY?
[SNIFFS]
- RIGHT HERE.
I'M SURE OF IT.
IT'S FRESH, LIKE JUST BURIED.
[SCREAMS]
[CRASH]
OH, MAN.
WHERE AM I?
WHERE IS THIS?
[GRUNTING]
THEY'RE EGGS, AND SOMETHING
JUST HATCHED OUT OF THEM, TOO.
THIS IS DEFINITELY THEIR NEST.
- AAH!
UH-OH, NOW THAT THEY'RE HATCHED,
THEIR PARENTS HAVE PROBABLY
TAKEN THEM OUT FOR TRAINING,
AND TRAINING FOR WHAT?
EATING HUMANS, THAT'S WHAT.
GIVING THE YOUNG
A TASTE FOR HUMAN FLESH.
KAGOME'S IN DANGER.
- MAYBE WE SHOULDN'T
- AH, DON'T TORTURE YOURSELF.
THAT HALF-DEMON'S GOT IT COMING.
- WHY SHOULD WE HAVE TO TRUST
ONE HALF-DEMON
TO KILL ANOTHER, ANYWAY?
- THIS FEELING.
I CAN'T EXPLAIN IT.
BEING WITH HER,
I FEEL SO WARM.
[SHOUTING]
- HUH?
- COME ON.
YOU THINK WE DON'T KNOW
YOU KILLED THOSE PEOPLE?
- NOBODY ASKED--
- THE VILLAGERS!
- I KNOW IT.
[WHIMPERING]
- IT'S OK.
STAY HERE.
- UH--OH--OH!
- HURT THIS OLD WITCH!
- WE LET YOU LIVE
NEAR US, TOO!
- OW!
- HEY! THAT'S ENOUGH!
- UH...
- OH, NO.
ARE YOU GONNA BE OK?
- MOVE, GIRL!
WHY ARE YOU PROTECTING THEM?
- BECAUSE THEY HAVEN'T
DONE ANYTHING, THAT'S WHY,.
WHICH YOU'D KNOW IF YOU WEREN'T
SO QUICK TO JUDGE.
AND HOW CAN YOU ALL
BE SO MEAN TO HIM, ANYWAY?
- DO YOU HEAR THAT?
SHE'S AS BAD AS THEM.
GET HER!
- ANYONE WHO LOVES HALF-DEMONS
AS MUCH AS HER MUST BE ONE!
I BET SHE'S GUILTY, TOO!
- [SHOUTING]
- OH, THE HUT!
- NO!
[WHIMPERING]
- YOU'VE GONE TOO FAR!
[SCREAMING]
- SOMEBODY HELP!
IT GOT ONE OF OUR GUYS!
[SHOUTING]
- THE YOUNG'UNS ARE
EATIN' ON HIM!
- NEXT, THEY'LL EAT US!
- DO YOU SEE?
THERE'S YOUR FLESH-EATING
MONSTER RIGHT THERE.
[SHOUTING]
- I'VE GOTTA DO SOMETHING,
AND QUICK!
[SHOUTING]
JINENJI.
YOUR MOM NEEDS
YOUR HELP OUTSIDE.
- HMM?
HUH?
OH.
- I GOT IT!
[SCREAMS]
UHH!
[ROARING]
[GROANING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
UGH!
- JINENJI!
[GASP]
- HEY!
GET AWAY!
ONLY YOU EVER TREATED ME
LIKE A REAL PERSON.
IF I LET YOU DIE HERE,
I WOULDN'T DESERVE
TO BE HALF-HUMAN.
- JINENJI.
- JINENJI!
- UHH!
- HYAH!
- SOMEBODY HELP!
AAH!
- IRON REAPER SOUL STEALER!
KAGOME!
WHERE ARE YOU?
- INUYASHA!
PLEASE HELP JINENJI!
[GROWLING]
- WHATEVER--
- DON'T YOU DO IT!
- WHAT?
- YOU MUSTN'T HELP HIM.
JINENJI HAS TO LEARN
TO FIGHT FOR HIMSELF.
- NOW?
[GROANING]
- IT HAS TO BE NOW.
- DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE LEAVING.
AND HERE THE FUN
WAS JUST GETTING STARTED.
WHO'S THE BIG COWARD NOW?
- WE ARE, OK?
JUST DON'T HURT US.
- YOU GOTTA HELP US.
WE'RE BEGGING HERE!
- OH, I GET IT.
WHOEVER'S STRONGEST IS
LEADER OF YOUR PACK, HUH?
JINENJI!
SHOW THE COWARDS!
TEACH 'EM WHO'S BOSS!
[ROARING]
[GROWLING]
[SHOUTING]
[ROARING]
[GROWLING]
[ROARING
- AMAZING!
- NO!
[MUTTERING]
- WELL, I GUESS IT'S BETTER
THEY LEARN LATE THAN NEVER.
- DON'T YOU THINK THAT'S
OVERDOING IT A BIT?
- HE'S GOTTA.
OTHERWISE, THEY'LL NEVER
RESPECT HIM.
FAT CHANCE OF TEACHING
THESE MANGY DOGS NEW TRICKS.
- I KNOW, BUT...
- WE'RE SORRY.
- WE'RE--AAH!
- PLEASE DON'T HURT US.
PLEASE.
- IT'S JUST...
- HUH?
HMM?
- LOTS OF YOU ARE HURT.
THIS WILL HELP YOU
GET BETTER FASTER.
- THERE.
YOU SEE?
- AND ALL THAT FOR NOTHING.
- AHH!
- YOU DIDN'T GET HURT,
DID YOU?
- OH, JINENJI, YOU...
- I KNOW.
- IF THAT'S HOW THINGS ARE,
THAT'S HOW THEY'LL BE.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
- YOU SURE YOU'LL BE OK?
- OH, WE'LL BE FINE.
YOU HURRY AND TAKE THAT MEDICINE
TO YOUR FRIEND, ALL RIGHT?
- MM-HMM.
SEE YOU LATER, JINENJI.
IT'S TIME FOR US TO LEAVE.
- OK.
- THANK YOU, FOR EVERYTHING.
- YOU'RE WELCOME.
- MAYBE WE SHOULD BE
THANKING THEM.
- OK, THAT'S ENOUGH OF THAT.
TOO MUCH WORK FOR TEARS.
WHAT?
- HUH.
- WE'LL HELP.
- HUH?
HAVE IT YOUR WAY.
- SO.
- YEAH?
- DID THAT KIND OF THING
HAPPEN TO YOU, TOO?
- DID WHAT HAPPEN?
- BULLYING.
WERE YOU PICKED ON?
- HA.
YEAH, RIGHT.
I DON'T ROLL OVER FOR ANYBODY.
- NO.
OF COURSE NOT.
MEANING, OF COURSE,
THAT HE WAS.
- I'M NOT ONE OR THE OTHER.
- HMM?
- NOT REALLY A DEMON,
NOT REALLY HUMAN.
I'M NOT EITHER.
THAT'S ALL.
THERE WAS NO PLACE FOR ME,
SO I HAD TO MAKE ONE FOR MYSELF.
AND THEN I REALIZED
I HAD A PLACE,
BUT I WAS THE ONLY ONE IN IT.
I DIDN'T KNOW ANY OTHER
WAY TO LIVE.
- INUYASHA, I'M JUST...
HAPPY TO HEAR IT.
- HAPPY HOW?
- WELL, IT'S JUST THAT
YOU'VE NEVER OPENED UP
AND TALKED TO ME
LIKE THAT BEFORE.
I'M GLAD YOU HAVE.
I'VE ALWAYS WONDERED
ABOUT YOUR PAST, YOU KNOW.
I TOLD MYSELF YOU WERE
ALL BARK AND NO BITE,
BUT I WASN'T SURE.
I'M HAPPY YOU CAN TALK TO ME
SERIOUSLY, IS ALL.
- AND THAT MAKES YOU HAPPY.
- UH-HUH.
SO DON'T WORRY ABOUT
SHOWING ME YOUR SOFT SIDE, OK?
- HA.
YOU MAKE IT SOUND LIKE
I'M SOME PET WHO NEEDS COMPANY.
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH THAT?
IT'S NICE NOT TO BE ALONE.
- IT'S TRUE.
I'M NOT ALONE, AM I?
SOMEHOW, WITHOUT MY
EVER NOTICING IT,
IT FELT SO NATURAL
HAVING KAGOME NEAR.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- A STRANGE MOUNTAIN
COVERED IN FOG.
YOU CAN HEAR THE SCREAMS
ALL THE WAY AT THE BOTTOM.
SOMETHING IS PULLING INUYASHA
TOWARD IT.
SOMETHING MAKING DEMONS
STICK TOGETHER LIKE MAGNETS.
IF INUYASHA KEEPS FIGHTING
LIKE THIS,
HE'LL BE A PART OF IT TOO.
KIKYO?
ARE YOU HERE TO HELP INUYASHA?
NEXT TIME...
SEE YOU SOON.