- I DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR YOU RIGHT NOW.
I HAVE TO RESCUE KAGOME,
SO GET OUT OF MY WAY!
IRON REAVER SOUL STEALER!
HUH?
[WOLVES HOWLING]
- THIS WOMAN IS OFF-LIMITS.
I'LL KILL ANYONE
WHO TRIES TO TAKE A BITE!
[GASPING]
- I'M JUST A LITTLE BIT
FREAKED OUT.
WHAT DID I DO TO DESERVE
BEING KIDNAPPED
AND TAKEN TO THE WOLF DEN AS
KOGA'S SACRED JEWEL DETECTOR?
HE'S ALREADY FOR 3 SHARDS
IN HIS ARMS AND LEGS.
AND HE'S SO FAST THAT INUYASHA
LOOKS SLOW-MO IN COMPARISON!
THE WOLF DEMON TRIBE ARE AT WAR
WITH THE BIRDS OF PARADISE,
AND THEY'RE PLANNING
TO STEAL THE JEWEL SHARD
THAT ONE OF THE BIRDS HAS.
THAT'S WHERE I COME IN,
AND I BETTER STAY USEFUL,
OR SHIPPO AND I ARE
GOING TO END UP AS LUNCH.
IF ONLY I COULD HELP SHIPPO
ESCAPE FROM THIS PLACE.
HUH?
UH, SHIPPO?
HMM?
[GASPS]
- STAND UP.
PLEASE, KAGOME.
DON'T MAKE IT LOOK
SUSPICIOUS, ALL RIGHT?
- KOGA, WHERE ARE YOU
GOING WITH THE HUMAN?
- THE WOMAN NEEDS
SOME FRESH AIR.
THIS PLACE STINKS, AND I DON'T
THINK IT'S THE WOLVES.
- WOW! GREAT ACTING!
- HEY, GINTA, HAKKAKU,
YOU TWO GO WATCH
KOGA'S BACK FOR HIM.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
GINTA AND HAKKAKU ALREADY
LEFT FOR GUARD DUTY
WITH KOGA AN HOUR AGO.
- WHAT'D YOU SAY?
THEN WHO THE HELL WAS THAT?
[SNIFFING]
- THAT HURTS! OW!
- HEY, YOU LITTLE THIEF!
TRY TO FOOL US, ARE YOU?
- SHIPPO! HURRY!
- WHOA!
- GET BACK HERE!
OH, WE'RE TRAPPED
NOW, KAGOME!
- YOU CAN EXPAND YOUR BODY
AND FLY, CAN'T YOU?
- YES, BUT I DON'T THINK
I CAN FLY WITH YOU, KAGOME.
WHOA!
- YOU'RE NOT GETTING AWAY!
- WHOA!
[GASPS]
- SHIPPO!
GO FIND INUYASHA! QUICK!
- CONNIVING WENCH!
I'LL DEVOUR YOU ALIVE!
[GASPING]
- WHO--WHO DID THAT?
- HEY! WHAT DID I SAY
ABOUT EATING HER?
I WARNED YOU.
- HUH? KOGA?
- KOGA! THE LITTLE GUY
IS FLYING!
HE'S OVER THERE.
- LET ME GO AFTER HIM, KOGA.
IT'S THE LEAST I CAN DO
AFTER LETTING HIM ESCAPE.
- I DON'T WANT TO DIE!
PLEASE!
- HUH...SHE RISKED HER LIFE
TO SAVE HER FRIEND.
SHE'S LOYAL.
[GASPS]
I'M GOING TO
MAKE YOU MY WOMAN.
- HUH?
- HEY, KOGA, I THOUGHT
YOU WERE GOING TO EAT HER
WHEN YOU WERE DONE WITH HER,
NOT MARRY HER.
- YOU DON'T WANT HER.
SHE'S A HUMAN!
- IDIOTS! THIS WOMAN CAN
SEE THE SACRED JEWEL.
THE BIRDS OF PARADISE
AREN'T THE ONLY ONES
WITH A SHARD, YOU KNOW.
WITH HER ABILITY,
WE'LL BE ABLE TO GATHER
ALL THE SACRED JEWEL
SHARDS IN THE REGION.
- THAT WOULD MAKE US
INCREDIBLY POWERFUL.
- OUR PACK WOULD BE
UNSTOPPABLE!
- THAT'S THE IDEA, YEAH.
SO, YOU SEE, SHE'S WAY
MORE VALUABLE TO US
THAN SOME FEMALE DEMON.
YOUR NAME IS KAGOME, RIGHT?
WOLVES MATE FOR LIFE,
SO YOU'RE MINE NOW.
GOT THAT?
- UH...
- I DON'T BELONG TO ANYONE!
GET YOUR HANDS OFF ME!
[SLAP]
- OH!
[GASPS]
- THAT CHICK
JUST SLAPPED KOGA!
- HONEYMOON'S OVER.
SHE'S DEAD NOW.
- HMM.
- I'M NOT SOME SLAVE
AT THE AUCTION.
YOU CAN'T PUT IN A BID
AND CLAIM ME AS YOUR PROPERTY.
BESIDES, I'M NOT AVAILABLE.
I'M ALREADY KIND OF
SEEING A GUY, SORT OF.
- YOU'RE TAKEN?
DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE WITH THAT
DOG-EARRED MUTT, INUTRASHA.
- HIS NAME ISN'T INUTRASHA,
SO DON'T INSULT HIM!
HE'S BRAVE, COURAGEOUS,
REALLY GOOD-HEARTED
WHEN HE'S NOT BEING A JERK,
AND HE'S GOT A GREAT NAME,
SO SAY IT RIGHT!
INUYASHA!
- HMM! I DON'T SEE
WHAT YOU LIKE ABOUT HIM.
- WHAT AM I SAYING?
TALK ABOUT DENIAL!
COME ON, KAGOME.
INUYASHA'S IN LOVE WITH KIKYO.
- I DON'T CARE.
NEXT TIME I SEE HIM, I'LL PUT
A SPEAR THROUGH HIS HEART
AND FEED HIM TO MY WOLVES.
[GASPS]
THEN HE WON'T BE MUCH
COMPETITION ANYMORE,
JUST A PILE OF OLD BONES.
[KIRARA ROARS]
- SANGO, ARE THEY ALLIES
OF THE WOLF DEMON TRIBE?
- I'M NOT SURE.
- MIROKU, SHOW A LITTLE EFFORT
AND GET OFF YOUR BUTT.
- INUYASHA, I THINK
YOU SHOULD LET ONE OF
THE BIRDS CAPTURE YOU.
- SAY WHAT?
- WHY, MIROKU?
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
- IF THIS AREA IS THE HUNTING
GROUND OF THESE BIRD DEMONS,
THEN THERE SHOULD BE
BONES AND SKELETONS
OF THEIR PREY SCATTERED
EVERYWHERE,
BUT I DON'T SEE ANY
SIGNS OF WOLF BONES.
- SO YOU'RE THINKING THEY'RE
IN ALLIANCE WITH THE WOLF PACK?
- THAT'S WHAT I SUSPECT,
BUT I COULD BE MISTAKEN.
- SO IF I GET CAPTURED,
I'LL GET TAKEN TO THEIR NEST,
WHICH IS LIKELY
WHERE THE WOLF DEN IS
AND THEN BE ABLE
TO SAVE KAGOME, RIGHT?
IT'S WORTH A SHOT.
HUH? WAIT A MINUTE.
MIROKU! WHY COULDN'T YOU BE
THE ONE WHO GETS CAPTURED?
IT WAS YOUR IDEA!
I'M ALWAYS DOING ALL
THE WORK, YOU LAZY BUM!
- YOU HAVE A STRONGER
CONSTITUTION.
THEREFORE, IT MAKES TACTICAL
SENSE TO SEND YOU INSTEAD OF ME.
- WE SHOULD GET GOING
IF WE'RE GOING TO FOLLOW.
- NOTHING WRONG WITH A LITTLE
DISTANCE BETWEEN US.
- MIROKU, YOU COWARD!
COME SWITCH PLACES WITH ME!
- I NEED TO FIND INUYASHA!
I WONDER WHERE HE IS.
WHOA! AAH!
INUYASHA, YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE RESCUING KAGOME!
NOW YOU'VE BEEN CAPTURED,
AND WE'VE GOT TO RESCUE YOU!
AAH!
I LET YOU OUT OF MY SIGHT,
AND LOOK WHAT HAPPENS!
OH!
- SHIPPO, IT'S YOU.
WHAT'S WRONG?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- OH, MIROKU! SANGO!
LOOK!
INUYASHA'S BEEN CAPTURED!
STRATEGY?
- YES.
WE FIGURE THE BIRD
WILL TAKE INUYASHA
RIGHT TO THE WOLF DEN,
BECAUSE THEY'RE ALLIES.
- WHO CAME UP
WITH THAT LAME IDEA?
THE BIRDS OF PARADISE
AND THE WOLF PACK
ARE BITTER ENEMIES,
AND KAGOME IS THERE
IN THE WOLF DEN.
- I SEE.
- I GUESS I SHOULD HAVE LOOKED
FURTHER OVER THE SUMMIT
FOR THEIR FEEDING GROUNDS.
THIS MOUNTAIN VALLEY
IS FILLED WITH WOLF BONES.
- INUYASHA!
THEY'RE ENEMIES!
- DAMN IT!
RIGHT NOW, I DON'T CARE
ABOUT THE WOLVES
OR THE STINKING GOOSE HEADS.
THERE'S ONLY ONE PERSON
I WANT TO KILL!
LET ME GO, BUZZARD!
[CRASH]
YOU'RE GOING TO PAY
FOR THIS, MIROKU!
BE A MAN!
GET DOWN HERE AND FIGHT!
- ARE YOU GOING TO GO
DOWN THERE AND FIGHT HIM?
- WE HAVE TO RESCUE KAGOME,
AND THAT'S OUR FIRST PRIORITY.
- HEY!
WAIT UP, YOU GUYS!
- DON'T YOU DARE
LEAVE ME HERE, MIROKU!
[SCREECHING]
- THIS IS IT!
ARE YOU READY, MEN!
- YEAH!
- THIS MOUNTAIN IS THE NESTING
PLACE FOR THE BIRDS?
- YEAH, AND ONE OF THEM
AT THE TOP POSSESSES
A SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
YOU HAVE TO FIND OUT
WHICH ONE.
- ALL RIGHT.
THERE IS A SACRED JEWEL
SHARD ON THIS MOUNTAIN.
I CAN SENSE IT.
I HAVE TO COOPERATE
IN ORDER TO STAY ALIVE.
INUYASHA, I COULD
REALLY USE YOUR HELP.
HURRY!
[GASPS]
[ROARS]
- THEY'RE ONTO US!
OK, MEN, YOU TAKE ON
THE GRUNTS YOURSELVES.
COME ON, KAGOME.
- AAH! AAH! AAH! AAH!
- AAH!
[SHOUTING]
KAGOME, CAN YOU SEE WHICH
ONE HAS THE JEWEL SHARD?
- I CAN'T CONCENTRATE ON LOOKING
WHEN YOU'RE FIGHTING!
[GASPS]
UP THERE!
IT'S RIGHT AHEAD OF US,
UP ON THAT CLIFF!
[GASPS]
AAH!
- WE'VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU.
YOU HAVE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
MY BROTHER AND I HAVE BEEN
SEEKING THEM EVERYWHERE.
- HOW CONVENIENT THAT
YOU'VE DECIDED TO MAKE
A HOME DELIVERY
AND COME TO US.
IT SAVES US THE TROUBLE
OF HUNTING YOU DOWN.
- HUH. I GOT SOMETHING
TO DELIVER, ALL RIGHT.
KAGOME, WHERE'S
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD?
- I SEE IT.
IT'S IN THE MOUTH.
- HA HA! AND YOU'LL GET
A GOOD GLIMPSE OF THE SHARD
AS WE SWALLOW
AND DEVOUR YOU!
A WOLF AND A HUMAN--
DELICIOUS!
- AAH!
[GROWLING]
- HEY!
- KOGA?
- PROTECT KAGOME.
- HUH? WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
WHAT ARE YOU PLANNING TO DO?
- I'LL BUT ITS
STUPID MOUTH WIDE OPEN.
- YOU'RE NOT GOING TO GO AFTER
THE SHARD IN ITS MOUTH
ALL ON YOUR OWN, ARE YOU?
- I'M THE ONLY ONE
STRONG ENOUGH
TO TAKE THAT TWO-HEADED
TALKING TURKEY ON.
HERE GOES NOTHING!
- DON'T WORRY, SISTER.
WE'LL GET YOU TO SAFETY.
- SISTER?
ARE YOU TALKING TO ME?
- YOU'RE KOGA'S WOMAN,
SO WE TREAT YOU LIKE
ONE OF US NOW.
- I ALREADY TOLD YOU THAT
I'M NOT HIS WOMAN, GOT THAT?
[SHOUTING]
- WATCH OUT, SIS!
AAH!
- GOT TO SAVE HIM!
- IT'S TOO LATE.
HE'LL BE TAKEN UP
TO THEIR NEST AND DEVOURED.
[GASPS]
- OH!
[GRUNTING]
HIT THE MARK!
BULL'S EYE!
[GRUNTING]
- AAH!
- YOU'RE SAFE.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- WOW!
- SHE'S ONE HELL
OF A GOOD SHOT!
- THANK YOU, SIS.
LOOK OUT! THERE'S MORE!
[SHOUTING]
- KAGOME!
AAH!
- INUYASHA.
I WAS SO SCARED!
- KAGOME!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- SANGO! MIROKU!
- KAGOME!
- SHIPPO!
- KAGOME,
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- RIGHT. WE'RE IN THE MIDDLE
OF AN ALL-OUT WAR
BETWEEN THE WOLF DEMON TRIBE
AND THE BIRDS OF PARADISE.
WE HAVE TO STOP
THOSE FLYING DEMONS.
- ALL RIGHT, THEN I'LL
TAKE CARE OF THEM.
IF YOU VALUE YOUR LIVES,
STAND BACK!
WIND TUNNEL!
[SCREECHING]
- OH!
- AMAZING!
I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE IT!
- GREAT.
IT'S THE MUTT FACE.
HE'S THE LAST THING
I NEED NOW.
I'M BUSY.
I DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR DOG TRAINING TODAY,
SO I'LL LET YOU ESCAPE.
GO HOME, PUPPY!
GET OUT OF MY FACE!
- SHUT UP!
DREAM ON, WOLF!
YOU'RE GOING TO PAY
FOR KIDNAPPING KAGOME!
- KAGOME.
- HEY, DOG BREATH,
TAKE THIS CHANCE TO RUN,
BUT KEEP YOUR HANDS
OFF MY WOMAN, GOT IT?
- HIS WOMAN?
- SHE CAN SEE THE SACRED JEWEL,
SO SHE'S PERFECT FOR ME!
- WHAT?
- IS THERE ANY TRUTH
TO WHAT HE'S SAYING, KAGOME?
- NOTHING'S GOING ON!
HE'S DELUDED!
IT'S WISHFUL THINKING!
HE'S MAKING IT UP!
- I KNEW IT!
HE'S LIVING IN A FANTASY.
YOU FLEA BAG!
- IT'S NOT A FANTASY.
I'VE CLAIMED HER AS MINE.
I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU, KAGOME!
[MOANS]
YOU'RE FAR BETTER OFF WITH ME,
AND YOU KNOW IT.
IT'S TIME TO MAKE
A CLEAN BREAK
AND GIVE UP THAT
PATHETIC MUTT FACE!
HE'S NOT GOOD ENOUGH FOR YOU.
FORGET ABOUT HIM.
I'M GOING TO KILL HIM
SOMEDAY ANYWAY.
ONCE YOU'VE BEEN WITH
A REAL WARRIOR LIKE ME,
YOU'LL NEVER GO BACK
TO SCRAPS AGAIN.
[LAUGHTER AND WHISTLING]
- HE'S PRETTY DIRECT,
ISN'T HE?
- I WISH I HAD THAT
KIND OF AUDACITY.
- NOBODY TALKS DOWN TO KAGOME
LIKE THAT WITH ME AROUND!
HOW DARE YOU HUMILIATE HER!
SHE'S NOT YOUR PROPERTY!
- STUPID MUTT.
I TOLD YOU I'M TOO BUSY.
GO PLAY FETCH
SOMEWHERE ELSE.
- THE JEWEL SHARD!
- KOGA! IT'S ABOUT
ANOTHER 50 FEET UP!
- DID SHE JUST--
DID SHE JUST HELP HIM?
- 50 FEET MORE?
BECAUSE THERE'S NOTHING
AT THE PEAK.
CHEW ON THIS!
- THANKS FOR GIVING US A HAND.
NOW WE WILL TEAR IT OFF!
- AAH! OH!
DAMN IT!
OH! THE SHARD IN MY ARM!
AAH!
[GRUNTING]
AND IT'S--IT'S COMING BACK FOR
THE JEWEL SHARDS IN MY LEGS.
OH, GREAT.
WHY ARE YOU HERE?
- SHUT UP AND
TAKE NOTES, FLEA BAG.
YOU'RE ABOUT TO WITNESS
SOME REAL POWER NOW.
- HE HAS TWO JEWEL
SHARDS LEFT, BROTHER.
- I KNOW. THINK OF THE POWER
WE'LL HAVE WHEN WE TAKE THEM!
[CACKLING]
- I DRAW ON YOUR TRUE
POWER NOW, TETSUSAIGA.
DON'T FAIL ME!
THERE'S THE WIND SCAR.
AAH!
[HOWLS]
- YOU KILLED THE GIANT BIRD
OF PARADISE WITH ONE SWING!
- YOU'VE CERTAINLY
MASTERED THE WIND SCAR.
- HUH!
YEAH, WELL...
NOW FOR THEM.
I'VE SINGLE-HANDEDLY GOTTEN
RID OF THE PIGEON FROM HELL.
NOW THERE'S JUST THIS
FLEA BAG WOLF TO DEAL WITH.
AAH!
SHE'S HUGGING HIM!
- YOU'RE NOT GOING TO BE
"DEALING WITH" ANYTHING,
YOU UNDERSTAND?
KOGA'S HURT.
THIS IS NO TIME FOR POSTURING.
- NEVER MIND.
THIS IS NOTHING.
- KOGA, DON'T GET UP.
- WHY IS SHE TAKING HIS SIDE?
I DON'T GET IT!
- TRYING TO GET ME
WHEN I'M DOWN?
BUT I'M STILL ABLE
TO WHIP YOU.
- HUH!
AGAIN WITH THE INSULTS.
YOU'RE DEAD!
- INUYASHA, SIT, BOY!
- UGH! UGH!
[GROANS]
- GET HIM OUT OF HERE
AND QUICK.
- OK, YOU'RE RIGHT.
KOGA, TAKE MY ARM.
- HEY! COME BACK!
COWARDS!
WHY'D YOU LET THEM GO?
- HE WASN'T FIT TO FIGHT.
KOGA WAS HURT.
HE WAS GOOD TO ME,
SO I RETURNED THE FAVOR.
- GOOD TO YOU?
ARE YOU NUTS?
DON'T TELL ME YOU GET OFF
ON THAT KIND OF THING!
YOU WERE KIDNAPPED
AND ALMOST KILLED!
- HE LOOKS ROUGHER THAN HE WAS.
HE, UH, PROTECTED ME
A LOT, YOU KNOW.
- YOU THINK SHE'S DEVELOPED
FEELINGS FOR HIM?
- HOW COULD SHE RESIST?
HE'S LAVISHED HER WITH
BOLD DECLARATIONS
OF LOVE AND LOYALTY.
[GROWLING]
- THIS IS STUPID!
FORGET IT!
- THOSE ARE THE TWO SHARDS
THAT THE BIRD HAD.
- THE BIRD OF PARADISE TORE
ONE OF THESE FROM KOGA'S ARM.
- WON'T HE COME AFTER US
IN SEARCH FOR IT?
- PROBABLY.
- I WONDER IF KOGA AND INUYASHA
WILL KEEP FIGHTING
OR IF THEY CAN GET OVER
THEIR DIFFERENCES.
- KAGOME.
WHY DON'T YOU TRY
TO CALM DOWN INUYASHA?
- HUH?
- HE IS VERY PROTECTIVE OF YOU,
AND THIS WHOLE EVENT UPSET HIM.
- I FEEL BAD FOR HIM,
CONSIDERING HOW THINGS ENDED UP.
- HEY...INUYASHA.
I'M SORRY I WORRIED YOU, OK?
THANK YOU FOR SAVING ME.
- I BET YOU WOULD HAVE PREFERRED
IT IF I DIDN'T SHOW UP AT ALL.
DOESN'T TAKE MUCH, DOES IT?
A FEW SWEET WORDS.
- WHAT DOESN'T TAKE MUCH?
DOES IT BUG YOU THAT
KOGA SAID HE LOVED ME?
IS THAT IT?
DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE JEALOUS.
- WHY WOULD I BE JEALOUS
OF THAT JERK?
I DON'T CARE!
- YEAH, LIKE, RIGHT!
NOT THAT IT'S ANY
OF YOUR BUSINESS,
BUT KOGA'S NOT MY TYPE, OK?
- HUH!
I WASN'T ASKING.
I DON'T CARE WHAT YOU DO.
JUST FORGET IT.
I DON'T WANT TO TALK
ABOUT IT ANYMORE,
SO JUST SPARE ME.
[SIGHS]
SO?
- HUH?
WHAT EXACTLY HAPPENED
BETWEEN YOU GUYS?
- INUYASHA.
WHAT DO YOU
TAKE ME FOR ANYWAY?
I HAVE SOME SELF-RESPECT!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'D EVEN ASK ME THAT!
- UH! YOU DON'T HAVE
TO BITE MY HEAD OFF!
I WAS JUST WONDERING!
- YOU JERK!
DON'T YOU GET ANYTHING?
- IF I'M SUCH A JERK,
THEN STOP TAGGING ALONG
AND GETTING IN THE WAY!
I'M TIRED OF WASTING
MY TIME RESCUING YOU!
- I SEE.
SANGO?
- WHAT IS IT?
- CAN I BORROW KIRARA?
- WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
- HUH. SHE MISSES HER
WOLF BOY ALREADY.
- I'M GOING BACK HOME, STUPID!
YOU HAPPY NOW?
YOU'RE SUCH A JERK!
- WHEN SHE'S ANGRY,
SHE CAN BE REALLY SCARY.
- I WASN'T SCARED.
GO BACK HOME AGAIN!
SEE IF I CARE!
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- I'VE BEEN CROSSING
BACK AND FORTH
BETWEEN THE PRESENT DAY
AND PAST FOR A WHILE NOW,
AND THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
I'VE EVER GOTTEN SO UPSET
OVER ANYTHING.
I'LL NEVER FORGIVE INUYASHA.
I'M GLAD TO BE
BACK WITH MY FAMILY,
MY LIFE AS A NINTH GRADER
IN SCHOOL,
MY FRIENDS, MY CLASSES...
THOUGH I CAN'T HELP
BUT FEEL A SENSE OF LOSS,
LIKE I'VE LEFT
SOMETHING IMPORTANT
BACK IN THE FEUDAL ERA.
NEXT ON "INUYASHA"...
SEE YOU SOON!