>> AAH!
UH, UH!
AAH!
HUH?
>> IT'S OPENING.
[GASPS]
WHAT'S THIS?
AAH!
>> IT'S THERE, BEYOND THE GATE!
>> DO YOU WISH TO PASS OR NOT?
>> WHAT, DO I LOOK LIKE I'M
AN IDIOT?
>> IN THAT CASE, WE SHALL CLOSE
THE GATE.
>> IS THAT TRUE, KAGOME?
>> MM-HMM.
I'M SURE OF IT.
WHEN I LOOKED THROUGH THE OPEN
GATE, I COULD FEEL IT.
I SENSED THE PRESENCE OF
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
>> HUH?
>> HMM.
>> I KNOW IT.
IT'S OUT THERE.
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD IS
DEFINITELY THERE.
THE QUESTION IS, WHERE?
>> TO THINK THAT THE SHARD
WAS ACTUALLY THERE.
>> LISTEN UP, MYOGA.
>> AH--WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> WHY DO I GET THIS FEELING
YOU KNEW THAT WE'D TURN TO STONE
IF WE WENT THAT WAY?
>> WOULD I HAVE FOLLOWED YOU
INTO SUCH A DANGEROUS PLACE
IF I KNEW?
>> OH, YEAH, RIGHT.
>> LOOK AT IT THIS WAY.
AT LEAST WE FOUND OUT THAT THERE
IS A SACRED JEWEL SHARD THERE,
SO IT WASN'T A TOTAL WASTE
OF TIME.
>> SHE'S RIGHT.
ALSO, HAKUDOSHI AND NARAKU ARE
LIVING BEINGS OF THIS WORLD,
SO THEY WON'T BE ABLE TO PASS
THROUGH TO THE OTHER SIDE,
EITHER.
WE'RE IN THE SAME BOAT
AS THEY ARE.
>> WELL, I GUESS WE JUST HAVE
TO FIND ANOTHER WAY.
THERE HAS TO BE ANOTHER PATH IN,
THE ONE THAT THE SACRED JEWEL
SHARD TOOK.
>> YES.
WE MUST GET THE SHARD BEFORE
NARAKU OR HAKUDOSHI CAN GET IT.
>> HA HA HA.
>> LOOK, IT'S A VILLAGE!
>> LET'S SPEND THE NIGHT THERE.
>> SOMETHING'S NOT RIGHT
AROUND HERE.
>> THERE'S NO SIGN OF ANY
PEOPLE.
>> OVER THERE.
>> HUH?
>> THEY'RE ALL DEAD.
>> MIROKU, THEY'VE ALL HAD
THE BLOOD SUCKED OUT OF THEM.
>> HEY, THERE'S A BUNCH MORE
OVER THERE.
>> WHAT COULD HAVE HAPPENED
HERE?
>> THEIR BLOOD'S BEEN DRAINED.
THINK IT COULD BE A HORDE
OF BLOODSUCKING DEMONS,
SOMETHING LIKE MYOGA?
>> [YELLING]
>> AAH!
>> YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING!
HEY, MYOGA, DO YOU KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT THIS?
GONE ALREADY.
>> HUH, THIS IS PATHETIC.
>> NO RICE OR SAKE TO STEAL.
TOTAL WASTE OF TIME.
>> MOVE OUT, MEN!
WE'RE LEAVING.
>> YES, SIR!
HUH?
WHAT ARE THEY, BIRDS?
[SQUAWKING]
>> THOSE ARE--
>> DEMONS!
RUN FOR YOUR LIVES!
>> [SCREAMING]
[SQUAWKING]
>> NO FIGHTING, NOW.
THERE'S PLENTY TO GO AROUND.
DON'T LEAVE A DROP OF BLOOD
BEHIND, MY TRUSTED SERVANTS.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
>> PRINCESS ABI,
THE BIRD MASTER.
>> YES?
WHO ARE YOU?
>> MAKE ME A PATH SO I CAN
CROSS OVER.
>> HOW DARE YOU ORDER ME AROUND
LIKE THAT!
>> IT WASN'T INTENDED
AS AN ORDER.
IT'S A TRADE.
>> HMM.
>> NOT AGAIN.
>> HOW TERRIBLE.
>> THEY'VE HAD THE BLOOD SUCKED
OUT OF THEM, TOO.
>> IT HAS TO BE SOME KIND
OF DEMON DOING THIS.
>> YEAH, SOME KIND OF CREEPY
DEMON OR MAYBE A BAND OF DEMONS
WERE WREAKING HAVOC AROUND HERE
WHILE WE WERE IN THE REALM
OF FIRE!
>> INUYASHA, WE BETTER HURRY
BEFORE ANOTHER VILLAGE IS
STRUCK DOWN.
[SQUAWKING]
>> NARAKU, YOU SAID YOUR NAME
WAS?
SO, THEN, WHAT'S IN IT FOR ME
IF I AGREE TO HELP YOU?
>> FIRST ANSWER ME THIS,
PRINCESS.
IT'S MY UNDERSTANDING THAT
YOU USE YOUR BIRDS TO COLLECT
THE BLOOD OF HUMANS.
FOR WHAT PURPOSE?
IT IS YOUR MOTHER WHO LIES
INSIDE THE CAVE.
AM I CORRECT?
IT SEEMS SHE'S ON THE VERGE
OF DEATH.
>> SHE ATE A POISONOUS DEMON AND
FELL ILL, BUT SHE IS NOT DYING.
I'M FEEDING HER HUMAN BLOOD
TO HELP DILUTE THE POISON
SHE CONSUMED.
>> IN THAT CASE, ALL YOU NEED
TO DO IS CONTINUE COLLECTING
BLOOD AND HOPE THAT YOUR MOTHER
RECOVERS QUICKLY, PRINCESS.
THAT'S ONE OPTION, OR...
IF YOU PROMISE TO ASSIST ME,
THEN I GUARANTEE TO HELP YOU
GATHER BLOOD EVEN FASTER THAN
YOU COULD EVER ACHIEVE ON YOUR
OWN.
AND I GUARANTEE YOU'LL HAVE
NO INTERRUPTIONS FROM ANYONE.
THAT IS MADE FROM MY BONES.
I SHALL LEND IT TO YOU.
>> OH.
[SQUAWKING]
[SCREECHES]
>> ABI, TELL ME WHERE I CAN FIND
YOUR MOTHER.
>> WHY SHOULD I TELL YOU
WHERE SHE IS?
>> SHE ATE OUR FATHER.
WE WON'T LET HER GET AWAY
WITH IT.
>> SHE DID EAT HIM, BUT IT SEEMS
HE WASN'T VERY TASTY.
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> THEN YOU'LL DO JUST FINE.
>> WE'LL AVENGE OUR FATHER.
>> PRINCESS ABI!
>> NOT BY YOUR HANDS!
>> BROTHER!
>> DO YOU FOOLS HONESTLY THINK
YOU CAN DEFEAT ME?
>> WE WOULDN'T HAVE MUCH OF A
CHANCE AGAINST YOU ONE ON ONE.
FEEL THE WRATH OF OUR COMBINED
POWER!
>> CURSE YOU!
>> TASTE OUR POISON AND PERISH!
>> DON'T TOY WITH ME.
>> SUCH WEAK POISON.
>> WHAT?
>> WHO ARE YOU, ABI'S ALLY?
>> YOU DO NOT SEEM TO RECOGNIZE
WHO I AM.
YOU SHALL NOW FIND OUT.
>> [SCREAMING]
>> HUH?
>> THOSE INSECTS WILL BE OF USE
TO YOU.
>> SOMEHOW I DOUBT THAT.
>> HMM.
>> ARROGANT FOOL.
>> HA HA, GO AHEAD AND USE HIM.
>> MOTHER?
>> THAT NARAKU HAS A POWERFUL
AURA, BUT HE IS STILL MERELY
A HALF-DEMON.
>> YES, I KNOW.
I HAD THOUGHT AS MUCH.
>> INDEED.
ACCEPT HIS HELP, AND AS SOON
AS HE DOES ANYTHING SUSPICIOUS,
FEED HIM TO THE BIRDS.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
FIRST WE MUST COLLECT MORE
BLOOD.
>> [GASPS]
DON'T PLAY WITH MY LIFE,
YOU BRAT!
[MOANING]
>> DOES IT HURT, KAGURA?
THAT'S BECAUSE NARAKU JUST TOOK
HOLD OF YOUR HEART FROM WHEREVER
HE IS.
TRY NOT TO FORGET, KAGURA,
NARAKU AND I ARE STILL
CONNECTED, SO NEXT TIME THINK
BEFORE YOU ACT.
BESIDES, I'D NEVER LET MYSELF
BE KILLED BY THE LIKES OF YOU.
>> HAKUDOSHI IS CERTAINLY
ANNOYING, BUT THE REAL PROBLEM
IS NARAKU.
AS LONG AS HE HAS A GRASP ON
MY HEART, I CANNOT BE THE WIND.
I'LL REMAIN CHAINED AND BOUND
TO HIM.
>> A NEIGHBORING VILLAGE WAS
ATTACKED BY DEMONS,
AND WE FEAR THAT WE MAY BE
THE NEXT VICTIMS.
>> YEAH, YOU'RE PROBABLY RIGHT.
ALL OF THE OTHER VILLAGES WE'VE
PASSED HAVE BEEN ATTACKED.
>> JUST AS WE FEARED.
>> THIS IS TERRIBLE.
>> WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
>> HOW FRIGHTENING.
>> INUYASHA, WHY DO YOU HAVE TO
GO OUT OF YOUR WAY TO SCARE
EVERYONE?
>> WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM, MIROKU?
I'M JUST TELLING THEM THE TRUTH.
>> FEAR NOT, MY GOOD PEOPLE.
MY FRIENDS AND I SHALL SLAY
THESE TERRIBLE DEMONS FOR YOU.
>> AHH.
>> WOULD YOU DO THAT FOR US?
>> OF COURSE, AND WE DON'T
REQUIRE PAYMENT FOR THIS.
WE MERELY ASK FOR LODGINGS,
FOOD, AND WOMEN.
>> WHAT WAS THAT, MONK?
>> JUST A LITTLE JOKE.
SERIOUSLY, HOW ABOUT PROVIDING
US MERELY WITH SOME WOMEN?
UH!
I SAID I WAS JOKING!
>> KEEP IT TO YOURSELF.
>> MM-HMM.
MM-HMM.
>> DO YOU HONESTLY THINK WE CAN
TRUST THESE PEOPLE?
>> WE DON'T HAVE ANYONE ELSE
TO ASK.
>> WE'VE ALREADY LOST MOST
OF THEIR TRUST, THANKS TO
MIROKU HERE.
>> YOU SAID IT, SHIPPO.
[CAWING]
>> [HUMMING]
UH, OH!
PA!
[SQUAWKING]
>> HUH?
WHAT'S OUT THERE?
>> YES.
SOMETHING'S WRONG.
STAY INSIDE.
>> YES, MONK.
[SQUAWKING]
>> WHAT ARE THOSE THINGS?
>> BIRDS?
[SQUAWKING]
[SCREECHES]
>> THESE BIRDS OR WHATEVER
THEY ARE HAVE THE STENCH
OF BLOOD ALL OVER THEM.
>> YOU THINK THEY'RE THE DEMONS
THAT ATTACKED THE VILLAGES?
>> OH, YEAH.
I'M SURE OF IT.
[SQUAWKS]
>> THAT'S LOUD!
[SQUAWKING]
>> UH...
>> WHAT'S HAPPENING?
>> HMM, HERE THEY COME.
WIND SCAR!
[SQUAWKING]
>> THERE'S MORE OF THEM COMING!
>> THEY'RE ON FIRE!
>> THEY'RE BURNING THE HOUSES
TO FORCE THE VILLAGERS OUTSIDE.
>> AAH!
>> YAH!
>> HIRAIKOTSU!
>> THEY'RE COMING BACK!
>> CURSE THEM!
WIND TUNNEL!
>> WOW, A BIRD IN THE HAND.
>> SAIMYOSHO!
>> STOP, MIROKU,
YOU'LL BE POISONED!
>> UP THERE!
>> WHO ARE YOU PEOPLE, AND WHY
DO YOU INTERFERE WITH ME?
>> SHUT UP.
ARE YOU ONE OF NARAKU'S MINIONS?
>> NARAKU?
>> YOU'VE GOT TO BE IN TIGHT
WITH HIM.
THE SAIMYOSHO BUZZING AROUND YOU
ARE PROOF!
>> I DON'T KNOW HIM,
NOR DO I KNOW WHAT YOUR
RELATIONSHIP WITH THIS NARAKU
IS, BUT YOU MADE THE MISTAKE
OF SLAUGHTERING MY BIRDS.
I'LL KILL EACH ONE OF YOU
AND DRAIN EVERY LAST DROP
OF YOUR BLOOD.
YOU WILL DIE!
>> IT'S NOT MY STYLE TO SLAY
WOMEN, BUT WITH THAT ATTITUDE,
I'LL MAKE AN EXCEPTION!
>> YOU'LL SLAY ME?
DON'T BE FOOLISH.
YOU'RE JUST ANOTHER HALF-DEMON
LIKE NARAKU.
>> WHAT?
>> HOW DARE YOU INVOLVE ME,
THE GREAT PRINCESS ABI,
IN ONE OF YOUR PETTY HALF-DEMON
QUARRELS!
>> WATCH OUT!
>> WE'LL BE KILLED.
>> GET THEM OUT OF HERE.
>> GOOD IDEA, RUN!
>> HURRY!
>> THIS WAY!
>> SUCK THEIR BLOOD AND DON'T
LET A SINGLE ONE OF THEM ESCAPE.
>> YOU'RE DEAD.
[SCREAMS]
>> DAMN YOU!
>> AAH!
>> INUYASHA!
>> CURSE YOU!
TAKE THIS!
>> WIND SCAR!
>> WHO IS THIS HALF-DEMON?
HIS DEMONIC POWER IS GREATER
THAN I THOUGHT.
HA!
>> A BARRIER!
>> SHE DEFLECTED HIS WIND SCAR.
>> THAT TRIDENT OF HIS,
IT PUT UP A BARRIER?
>> THIS TRIDENT IS MADE OF
MY BONES.
>> [GASPS]
>> I KNEW IT!
YOU ARE ONE OF NARAKU'S MINIONS.
THAT WAS ONE OF NARAKU'S
LITTLE TRICKS.
>> DID NARAKU GIVE ME THIS
TRIDENT TO FORCE ME TO FIGHT
THIS HALF-DEMON?
UH.
>> HUH?
COME BACK HERE!
>> SHE GOT AWAY.
>> DAMN!
>> [GASPS]
THE VILLAGE.
>> WE SHOULD JUST BE THANKFUL
WE'RE EVEN ALIVE.
>> IF YOU PROMISE TO HELP ME,
I WILL HELP YOU GATHER BLOOD
EVEN FASTER THAN YOU EVER COULD
ACHIEVE ON YOUR OWN.
>> HE SEEMS UNTRUSTWORTHY.
>> SHE CALLED HERSELF
PRINCESS ABI.
>> SHE SEEMS TO BE CONNECTED TO
NARAKU SOMEHOW, BUT SHE REALLY
DIDN'T SEEM LIKE ONE OF HIS
MINIONS.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT NARAKU'S LIKE.
I'M GUESSING HE'S USING THIS
PRINCESS ABI TO GET WHAT
HE WANTS.
>> FOR WHAT, THOUGH?
THAT FEMALE DEMON IS USING
HER BIRDS TO SUCK THE BLOOD OUT
OF HUMANS.
WHY WOULD NARAKU BE INTERESTED
IN HELPING HER?
WHAT COULD POSSIBLY BE IN IT
FOR HIM?
>> I DON'T KNOW, BUT SHE'S
DEFINITELY ON HIS SIDE.
>> NARAKU IS TRYING TO FIND A
WAY TO GET TO THE BORDER BETWEEN
THIS LIFE AND THE NEXT IN ORDER
TO GET THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
>> SO YOU MEAN COLLECTING
HUMAN BLOOD IS SOMEHOW RELATED
TO HIS GETTING TO THE BORDER?
>> SEEMS LIKE IT.
WHATEVER THE CONNECTION IS,
IT'S THE ONLY THING WE HAVE
TO GO ON AT THIS POINT.
>> DON'T OVEREXERT YOURSELF.
YOU WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO FIGURE
IT OUT.
AAH!
>> WHAT WAS THAT, SHIPPO?
I DIDN'T QUITE HEAR YOU.
AND I SUPPOSE YOU THINK YOU'RE
SMART ENOUGH TO FIGURE IT OUT?
>> SHIPPO, YOU WENT A LITTLE
TOO FAR THAT TIME.
>> HMM, HEAR THAT?
>> AND INUYASHA,
YOU'RE OVERDOING IT.
>> HA HA HA!
>> DON'T MAKE ME TELL YOU TO S--
[SIGHS]
>> IN ANY CASE, WE MUST FIND
A WAY TO STOP THIS PRINCESS ABI.
>> YES, BEFORE MORE INNOCENT
PEOPLE ARE KILLED.
>> SHE REEKS WITH THE STENCH
OF BLOOD.
IT SHOULD BE EASY ENOUGH FOR ME
TO FIND HER.
>> THE PATH THAT LEADS TO
THE BORDER BETWEEN THIS WORLD
AND THE NEXT...
WILL SOON OPEN.
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> ♪ I GET, I GET, I GET
GET THE FEELING
I GET, I GET, I GET
GET THE DREAMING ♪
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> ♪ COME MY WAY ♪
>> ♪ COME CLOSE TO ME ♪
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
♪ I'LL BE WITH YOU
I'LL BE WITH YOU
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
SO COME MY WAY ♪
>> ♪ COME MY WAY ♪
>> 50 YEARS AGO, KIKYO SEALED
INUYASHA TO THIS SACRED TREE.
INUYASHA, WHY IS IT THAT YOU
LOOK SO PEACEFUL IN YOUR ETERNAL
SLEEP, EVEN THOUGH YOU LOST
THE SACRED JEWEL TO MY SISTER?
>> WON'T YOU STOP THIS FIGHTING
AND BECOME A FULL-BLOODED HUMAN?
>> ME, A HUMAN?
NEXT TIME, AN INUYASHA SPECIAL:
THE TRAGIC LOVE SONG OF DESTINY.
>> THE ANSWER IS ONLY KNOWN
BY THE DEPTHS OF
THE BONE EATER'S WILL.