- INUYASHA AND KIKYO?
BUT WHY?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- HMM? KIKYO, DON'T GO!
KIKYO!
HUH?
KAGOME.
- [EXHALES]
[PANTING]
- THIS IS THE ANTIBIOTIC
TO PREVENT INFECTION,
AND THIS ONE'S AN OINTMENT
TO RELIEVE ANY PAIN.
AND LOOK AT THIS.
I BROUGHT LOTS OF GAUZE
AND BANDAGES FOR YOU. SEE?
- HMM.
- UH...
- OK, GUESS THAT'S IT.
I'M GONNA TAKE OFF.
- HUH? KAGOME...
- YOU MEAN
YOU'RE GOING BACK HOME NOW?
- WELL, I JUST CAME TO BRING YOU
SOME MEDICINE.
- IF YOU WANT MY ADVICE,
YOU SHOULD AT LEAST TRY
TO MAKE UP WITH INUYASHA.
IT REALLY WAS
A SILLY ARGUMENT.
- THAT'S WHY I FEEL SO LOUSY.
HOW COULD I HAVE
FORGOTTEN ABOUT
THAT CONVERSATION
I HAD WITH HIM?
- I DON'T CARE
HOW YOU FEEL ABOUT ME NOW,
BUT I SWEAR I WON'T LET NARAKU
HAVE YOU, EITHER.
ONLY I CAN PROTECT YOU
FROM HIM!
- [GASPS]
I FORGOT ALL ABOUT THAT ARGUMENT
WE HAD WITH EACH OTHER.
- MIROKU, KAGOME LOOKED
REALLY DEPRESSED TO ME.
- YES.
WELL, I CAN GUESS
WHY SHE'S FEELING THAT WAY.
- HMM?
- THOSE LIGHTS ARE
DISCONNECTED SOULS.
HMM?
- INUYASHA?
- UH...
- INUYASHA, KAGOME WENT
BACK TO HER HOME AGAIN.
- I SEE.
- INUYASHA, TELL ME.
YOU WENT TO SEE KIKYO, RIGHT?
- HUH?
- AND KAGOME SPOTTED
THE TWO OF YOU TOGETHER.
- UH, WELL, YEAH,
SHE SAW US.
- HOW COULD YOU SNEAK AROUND
LIKE THAT?
- HUH? HMM.
YOU MUST HAVE BEEN UP TO
SOMETHING BIZARRE
TO ACHIEVE THAT LOOK
OF ENLIGHTENMENT.
WHAT HAPPENED TO MAKE YOU SEEM
SO CALM AND SPIRITUAL?
HUH?
- HUH?
- AFTER KIKYO LEFT,
INUYASHA STARED
WITH A STRANGE LOOK IN HIS EYES.
I REALIZED HE WAS TRYING TO
TELL ME SOMETHING, BUT...
I WAS AFRAID TO LISTEN
AND RAN OFF.
INUYASHA HAD ALREADY MADE
HIS DECISION.
- INUYASHA!
- THE DEMON NARAKU
HAD DECEIVED THEM,
PITTING THEM AGAINST
ONE ANOTHER.
KIKYO HUNTED DOWN INUYASHA,
AN UNFORTUNATE DECISION
WHICH LED TO HER DEATH.
AND NOW NARAKU WAS ONCE AGAIN
AFTER KIKYO.
- I COULDN'T CARE LESS
HOW YOU FEEL ABOUT ME.
THERE'S NO WAY
NARAKU WILL HAVE YOU.
DON'T YOU KNOW I'M THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN PROTECT YOU?
- THERE'S NO ROOM FOR ME
IN HIS HEART.
WHY WOULD THERE BE?
- I'VE TRIED,
BUT I CAN'T FORGET ABOUT KIKYO,
SO I'VE DECIDED.
KAGOME, I CAN'T SEE YOU ANYMORE.
IT'D BE WRONG.
- KIKYO PROVED
SHE'S MEANT TO BE WITH INUYASHA
BY GIVING UP HER LIFE.
[SIGHS]
THAT'S MORE THAN
I COULD EVER DO.
NO, I CAN'T RETURN TO HIM.
I WON'T.
HUH?
INUYASHA WON'T COME
FOR ME ANYMORE.
BUT WHAT WILL I DO?
I BROUGHT THE SACRED JEWEL
FRAGMENTS BACK WITH ME.
I SHOULD RETURN THEM.
YES.
ONCE I GET RID OF THEM,
I CAN PUT THIS WHOLE THING
BEHIND ME.
THEN I'LL FINALLY HAVE
THE CHANCE TO GET BACK
TO MY NORMAL LIFE.
- KAGOME SURE DIDN'T
STAY THERE VERY LONG,
AND SHE HASN'T SAID A WORD TO US
SINCE SHE GOT BACK.
I KIND OF WONDER IF SOMETHING
HAPPENED TO HER.
- MMM. CAN ONLY MEAN
ONE THING.
- HER THUMB'S SORE?
- BOYFRIEND PROBLEMS.
- OH.
YOU THINK MAYBE SHE HAD
A BIG ARGUMENT WITH INUYASHA?
- AHEM. KAGOME--
- GRANDPA, I'M AFRAID MY EYES
ARE BIGGER THAN MY STOMACH.
WOULD YOU LIKE MY EGG?
- OH, WELL,
DON'T MIND IF I DO.
- MAY I BE EXCUSED?
- HEY, SIS--
- SOTA, THESE PICKLES I BOUGHT
ARE SO CRUNCHY AND DELICIOUS.
YOU SHOULD AT LEAST TRY ONE.
- UH, SURE.
- AND NO NEED TO DO
THE DISHES.
I'LL GET TO THEM LATER,
KAGOME.
- OK. THANKS.
[BUYO MEOWING]
SEE YOU LATER.
- HAVE A NICE DAY.
- AHH.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
- YEAH, MOM.
SHE'S NOT LOOKING TOO GOOD,
AND WE'RE KIND OF WORRIED.
AREN'T YOU?
- MMM!
MMM. THESE PICKLES ARE
OUT OF THIS WORLD.
- OHH...
- [SIGHS]
- KAGOME!
- HUH?
- HI. HOW ARE YOU DOING?
- THE HOSPITAL LET YOU GO?
- SO, WHAT DID
THE DOCTOR SAY
ABOUT THE STRANGE RASH YOU HAD
ALL OVER YOUR BODY?
- I GUESS WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF
FAKE ILLNESSES.
- WE'LL TALK ABOUT THAT LATER.
SO, DON'T LEAVE US IN SUSPENSE.
- HUH?
- DON'T ACT INNOCENT.
YOU KNOW WHAT WE'RE GETTING AT.
COME ON, WE TOTALLY
WANT TO HEAR ABOUT
THIS JEALOUS, RUDE,
SPOILED GUY OF YOURS.
- DID YOU TWO SPLIT UP?
- HUH?
- KAGOME--
- DO YOU THINK I SAID SOMETHING
I SHOULDN'T HAVE SAID?
- AHEM. HUH?
- [SIGHS]
HIM? OH, HE DROPPED ME
LIKE A ROCK.
- HUH?
- KAGOME DIDN'T DUMP HIM?
- THAT CAN ONLY MEAN ONE THING.
- NO WAY. DON'T TELL ME
SHE STILL LOVES HIM.
- DON'T WORRY.
NO, REALLY,
I'M TOTALLY FINE WITH IT.
- YOU'RE OVER HIM?
- MM-HMM, YOU BET.
SO LET'S NOT BRING
HIM UP AGAIN, OK?
I'M DOING JUST FINE.
- SHE DOESN'T WANT TO BE
REMINDED 'CAUSE IT HURTS.
- POOR THING.
- THAT BIG SMILE
WEIRDS ME OUT.
- INUYASHA!
HOW COULD YOU STOOP SO LOW?!
I MEAN, YOU WERE SO UPSET
BECAUSE KAGOME
GOT FRIENDLY WITH KOGA.
AND AFTER ALL THAT FUSS,
YOU ONLY WANT TO THINK ABOUT
KIKYO NOW?
- YOU NEVER HAD DEEP FEELINGS
FOR KAGOME?
- YOU ARE OBLIGED TO
GO SEE HER, INUYASHA.
- LAY OFF, OK?
I'VE DECIDED THAT I'M NEVER
GONNA SEE KAGOME AGAIN, EVER.
- GIVE IT A REST.
YOU'VE GOT A ONE-TRACK MIND.
I MEAN, GO AND BRING BACK
THE SACRED JEWEL FRAGMENTS
KAGOME TOOK WITH HER.
ONLY YOU HAVE THE POWER
TO PASS THROUGH THE WELL,
INUYASHA.
- JUST THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS?
- DON'T YOU CARE AT ALL
ABOUT KAGOME?
- IT LOOKS LIKE WE HAVEN'T
ANY SAY IN THE MATTER.
INUYASHA HAS QUITE OBVIOUSLY
CHOSEN KIKYO.
IT'D BE EVEN CRUELER
TO ASK KAGOME TO COME BACK.
- HMM.
- INUYASHA...
ARE YE REALLY SURE YE WANT TO
GO THROUGH WITH THIS?
- OH, COME ON, KAEDE.
DO I HAVE TO HEAR IT
FROM YOU, TOO?
- REMEMBER THAT THE KIKYO
YE SPEAK OF NOW
WAS CONJURED UP
FROM EARTH AND BONES.
YE WISH TO BE WITH SOMEONE
WHO'S NOT OF THIS WORLD.
- HER BODY MAY BE DIFFERENT,
BUT HER SPIRIT STILL REMAINS.
- DO YE FULLY APPRECIATE
THE IMPLICATIONS?
THE TWO OF YE CAN NEVER BE
TOGETHER IN THIS WORLD.
DEEP DOWN, WHAT THIS
RESURRECTED KIKYO WANTS
IS FOR BOTH OF YE
TO DIE TOGETHER.
- THAT'S FINE.
I AM PREPARED TO LEAP INTO HELL
WITH KIKYO IF THAT IS HER WISH.
IF THAT'S TO BE OUR DESTINY,
I'D EMBRACE IT
WITHOUT A SECOND THOUGHT.
I HAVE TO RETURN
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS.
BUT I CAN'T.
I DON'T WANT TO.
I'M AFRAID.
ONCE I GIVE THESE BACK,
I WON'T BE ABLE TO SEE
INUYASHA AGAIN.
- I'M SORRY, KAGOME.
I'VE DECIDED TO GO WITH KIKYO.
- DON'T TELL ME THAT!
IT'S JUST TOO...
HOW COULD YOU?
I WISH KIKYO WOULD DISAPPEAR
FROM OUR LIVES FOREVER!
[GASP]
NO!
HAVE I REALLY TURNED INTO
SUCH A HORRIBLE PERSON?
IT'S TRUE.
RIGHT NOW I PROBABLY HAVE
A HORRIBLE LOOK ON MY FACE.
I CAN'T LET INUYASHA
SEE ME LIKE THIS.
[GASP]
THESE SHARDS.
THE SACRED TREE.
YES, THIS TREE, OF COURSE.
THIS IS WHERE INUYASHA
WAS SEALED.
500 YEARS AGO,
THIS IS THE VERY SPOT
WHERE I FIRST MET INUYASHA.
- YOU LOOK
PRETTY DUMB THERE, KIKYO.
THE KIKYO I KNOW
WOULDN'T WASTE TIME.
WHY ARE YOU TAKING SO LONG
TO KILL IT?
JUST DO HER LIKE YOU DID ME.
HUH?
- THAT DOES IT!
KIKYO! KIKYO!
WHOEVER SHE IS, SHE'S NOT ME,
'CAUSE MY NAME IS...
INUYASHA?
INUYASHA!
[CRYING]
- KAGOME.
- WHY'D I EVER MEET HIM?
IF I KNEW IT WAS GONNA HURT
THIS MUCH,
I WISH I'D NEVER
LAID EYES ON HIM.
[SOBBING]
BUT I WANT TO SEE HIM.
I CAN'T DENY IT.
I WANT TO SEE INUYASHA
ONCE MORE.
IT'S CLEAR NOW.
I MUST BE IN LOVE WITH HIM.
BEFORE I KNEW IT,
I'D GROWN TO LOVE HIM SO MUCH.
- KAGOME?
- HUH?
OH, MOM.
MOM!
[SOBBING]
- KAGOME?
- HMM?
- WHEN YOU'RE CLOSE TO
THE SACRED TREE,
DON'T YOU FEEL
A STRANGE KIND OF POWER--
AS THOUGH YOU FEEL
TRUER TO YOURSELF,
THAT SOMEHOW ITS PRESENCE MAKES
YOUR HEART FEEL MUCH MORE PURE?
THIS IS THE SPECIAL PLACE WHERE
YOUR FATHER PROPOSED TO ME.
- HUH?
- AND, OF COURSE,
I LOVED HIM LIKE NO OTHER.
BUT THE DAY BEFORE HE ASKED ME
TO MARRY HIM,
WE HAD SOME SILLY ARGUMENT.
IT HAD MADE ME SERIOUSLY DOUBT
IF THE TWO OF US
WERE TRULY MEANT TO BE TOGETHER.
BUT THE INSTANT I WALKED
UNDER THIS TREE,
MY MIND CLEARED,
AND I ACCEPTED HIS PROPOSAL,
WHICH MEANT I WAS ABLE TO HAVE
YOU AND SOTA.
IT MIGHT SOUND FUNNY, BUT I FEEL
GRATEFUL TO THIS TREE.
[SIGHS]
I WON'T ASK YOU TO SAY
WHAT THE PROBLEM IS,
BUT I HAVE A LOT OF FAITH
IN YOU, KAGOME.
I KNOW YOU'RE A YOUNG WOMAN WHO
WILL ULTIMATELY CHOOSE THE PATH
THAT YOU BELIEVE TO BE RIGHT.
- YOU'RE THE BEST.
THANKS, MOM.
- INUYASHA!
- SHUT UP! I KNOW.
- BUT I HAVEN'T SAID A WORD.
- HUMPH. YOU'RE GONNA SAY
TO GO SEE KAGOME.
- IF YOU KNOW,
THEN WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
- BUT THAT'LL MEAN
SEEING KAGOME FACE-TO-FACE
AND FINALLY TELLING HER
GOOD-BYE.
I COULDN'T SAY IT BEFORE.
NOW I'LL HAVE TO THIS TIME.
- THE TRUTH IS,
YOU'RE NOT THE ONE WHO'S HAVING
A HARD TIME WITH THIS.
KAGOME IS.
- MIROKU'S ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
YOU'VE ALREADY MADE UP YOUR MIND
ABOUT WHO YOU WANT IN YOUR LIFE,
SO WHATEVER.
BUT I SUSPECT KAGOME
RIGHT NOW
IS SITTING AT HOME
REALLY CONFUSED.
- IF YOU'RE ANY KIND OF MAN,
YOU'LL MEET UP WITH KAGOME
AND MAKE A NICE, CLEAN BREAK.
- THAT'S FOR SURE, INSTEAD OF
PUSSYFOOTING AROUND LIKE THIS.
- JUST HOLD IT.
DO YOU WANT ME TO SPLIT UP
WITH KAGOME THAT MUCH?!
- WELL, I MEAN, DON'T YOU?
- UH, WHO SAID THAT?
Y-YOU'RE JUST
TWISTING THINGS AROUND.
LOOK, I DECIDED
I HAD TO PROTECT KIKYO.
SO YOU TELL ME,
HOW CAN I ASK KAGOME
TO COME BACK HERE?
HEY! AREN'T YOU
EVEN LISTENING?
- OH, WHAT A GUY.
IN THE GAME OF LOVE,
HE'S SURE A POOR SPORT.
- FROM NOW ON, HOW ABOUT
WE JUST CALL HIM TWO-FACED?
- GUESS IT'S ALL UP TO US.
- WHY, YOU...
- NO.
THERE'S NO WAY
I CAN ASK HER TO COME BACK.
KAGOME UNDERSTANDS THAT
PERFECTLY.
I HAVE TO GO.
I'VE GOT TO SEE HER
AND SAY GOOD-BYE FOREVER,
OR I CAN'T MOVE ON.
UHH! HUH?
KAGOME.
- I WENT BACK TO THE PRESENT
AND THOUGHT IT OVER,
WONDERING ABOUT YOU AND KIKYO
AND ABOUT ME.
- KAGOME, I'M SO...
- IT'S OK.
I UNDERSTAND HOW YOU FEEL.
AND BECAUSE OF THAT,
I CONVINCED MYSELF THAT
I COULDN'T STAY HERE WITH YOU.
- KAGOME, UNTIL I MET YOU,
I NEVER TRUSTED
A LIVING SOUL, BUT...
I WATCHED YOU SHED TEARS
FOR MY SAKE.
YOU'VE ALWAYS STAYED BY MY SIDE.
WHENEVER I'M WITH YOU,
I FEEL SO PEACEFUL
AND HAPPY, BUT I--
I'M NOT SUPPOSED TO BE
ALL AT EASE AND CHEERFUL.
KIKYO...
KIKYO CAME AFTER ME
AND LOST HER LIFE.
IT'S ONLY RIGHT THAT I REPAY HER
WITH MY OWN LIFE.
- MM-HMM.
I CAN'T COMPETE WITH KIKYO,
BECAUSE, AFTER ALL,
I'M STILL ALIVE.
[GRUNTS]
I'VE GIVEN A LOT OF THOUGHT
ABOUT KIKYO.
SHE AND I
ARE COMPLETELY DIFFERENT.
THERE'S BEEN ALL THIS TALK THAT
I'M A REINCARNATION OF HER.
EVEN IF THAT'S TRUE,
I'M STILL NOT KIKYO.
YOU SEE,
MY HEART BELONGS TO ME.
HERE'S THE THING.
I DO UNDERSTAND ONE FEELING
THAT KIKYO HAS--
SOMETHING THAT WE SHARE.
WE'RE ALIKE IN OUR DESIRE
TO BE WITH YOU AGAIN.
- HUH?
- STRANGE, YOU KNOW?
THE MOMENT IT HIT ME
THAT KIKYO AND I WERE CONNECTED
BY THIS DESIRE TO BE WITH YOU,
I FELT A LITTLE BIT BETTER.
THE DESIRE TO BE WITH YOU
GIVES US A COMMON BOND.
THAT'S HOW I WAS ABLE TO
SUMMON UP THE COURAGE
TO COME AND SEE YOU.
- KAGOME,
ALL THIS TIME,
I'VE BEEN WANTING TO
SEE YOU, TOO, BUT...
- I WANT TO BE HERE
WITH YOU, INUYASHA.
I TRIED TO FORGET YOU,
BUT I CAN'T.
- KAGOME, WHAT KIND OF ANSWER
CAN I GIVE YOU?
- INUYASHA?
- HUH?
- MAY I ASK YOU
A SIMPLE QUESTION?
INUYASHA,
WILL YOU LET ME STAY?
- SO...YOU'LL STAY WITH ME?
- MM-HMM.
I CAN NEVER BREAK THE BOND
BETWEEN INUYASHA AND KIKYO.
I UNDERSTAND THAT.
BUT THERE'S ANOTHER THING
I'VE COME TO REALIZE, INUYASHA.
MY MEETING YOU
WAS NO COINCIDENCE.
IT'S MORE THAN THAT.
DEEP DOWN, YOU MUST KNOW
THAT I WANT YOU TO LIVE.
- KAGOME...
- WELL, THEN, LET'S GO.
- HUH?
- I WANT YOU TO BE HAPPY.
I WANT YOU TO LAUGH A LOT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT EXACTLY
I'LL BE ABLE TO DO FOR YOU,
BUT I'LL ALWAYS BE
BY YOUR SIDE.
- [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- KOHAKU IS CARED FOR
BY A KIND OLD COUPLE.
WHEN A DEMON APPEARS,
IT'S GREEDY FOR THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARD ON HIS BACK.
WE ALL RUSH TO HIS RESCUE,
BUT IT GETS WORSE.
KOHAKU HAS NO MEMORY OF BEING
THE SON OF THE DEMON SLAYER.
HE DOESN'T EVEN KNOW
THAT SANGO IS HIS SISTER.
WHY? IS THIS ANOTHER TRAP
SET BY NARAKU?
NEXT TIME...
SEE YOU SOON!