- WELL, I MIGHT AS WELL GO HOME.
DID YOU HEAR WHAT I SAID,
INUYASHA?
- PUT A CORK IN IT.
JUST GET IT OVER WITH AND GO.
- EVERY TIME YOU TWO RETURN,
IT SEEMS LIKE YOU'RE IN
THE MIDDLE OF AN ARGUMENT.
- COULD YOU PLEASE TAKE CARE
OF EVERYONE ELSE, KAEDE?
- HMM!
- ARE YOU JUST GOING
TO LET HER LEAVE, INUYASHA?
- HUH! I COULDN'T CARE LESS.
- HMM.
- I SWEAR, INUYASHA,
YOU CAN BE A REAL JERK.
ONLY REASON
I STOPPED ARGUING WITH YOU
WAS BECAUSE I WAS WORRIED
THE STRAIN MIGHT MAKE
YOUR INJURIES WORSE.
- KAGOME, WAIT!
- HUH?
SHIPPO, WHAT?
- JUST BE PATIENT,
OK, KAGOME?
YOU KNOW, INUYASHA'S
ALWAYS BEEN THE JEALOUS TYPE
WHEN IT COMES TO YOU.
- KAGOME, YOU'RE MY WOMAN.
- INUYASHA'S JUST BEING...PETTY.
THAT'S THE ONLY REASON
WHY HE TOOK KOGA'S WORD
SO SERIOUSLY.
OH, AND ALSO BECAUSE
HE'S SO IN LOVE WITH YOU.
- HMM. THANKS, SHIPPO.
I NEEDED TO HEAR THAT,
BUT THE REAL REASON
I'M GOING BACK
IS TO GET SOME MORE BANDAGES
AND MEDICINE FOR US TO USE.
I'M COMING RIGHT BACK,
BUT DON'T TELL INUYASHA THAT!
- HUH?
- SOMETIMES IT'S GOOD
TO MAKE HIM WORRY A LITTLE.
- I GET IT,
BUT PLEASE COME BACK
TO US QUICKLY, KAGOME.
- MM-HMM.
HMM.
- [BIRDS CHIRPING]
- [COUGHING]
- NARAKU, I KNOW
YOU'RE OUT THERE.
- HMM. SHARP AS USUAL, KIKYO.
- HOW COULD I NOT NOTICE YOU?
AND NOT ONLY TODAY,
BUT YOU'VE COME TO SPY ON ME
QUITE OFTEN RECENTLY.
- HUH.
- YOU SEEM TO BE
QUITE INTERESTED IN ME.
[LAUGHS]
- SOMETHING AMUSE YOU?
- COME NOW,
IT'S OBVIOUS THAT THE REASON
YOU'RE SO INTERESTED IN ME,
NARAKU, IS BECAUSE...
YOU STILL HAVE ONIGUMO'S HEART
BEATING STRONGLY WITHIN YOU.
[WIND BLOWING]
- HUH. NOW HE'S GONE.
- [BIRDS CHIRPING]
- [DOOR CLOSES]
- I'M BACK!
- IT'S--IT'S KAGOME.
- HIYA, SIS.
- OH, WELCOME BACK, DARLING.
DID YOU WANT A BATH,
OR MAYBE SOMETHING TO EAT FIRST?
- [YAWN]
BATH, PLEASE.
- YOU LOOK SIMPLY EXHAUSTED.
I'LL GO RUN A NICE BATH FOR YOU.
- YOU'RE THE BEST, MOM.
- NOW, NOW.
HERE, PUT DOWN YOUR BAG.
- THAT DIDN'T SOUND LIKE
A TYPICAL CONVERSATION
BETWEEN MOTHER AND DAUGHTER.
- LOOKED MORE LIKE A CHAT
BETWEEN A HUSBAND WHO'D
BEEN ON A TRIP AND HIS WIFE.
- HMM.
- [DRIPPING]
- SO, KAGOME, HOW LONG
ARE YOU GOING TO GIFT US
WITH YOUR PRESENCE THIS TIME?
- I'M LEAVING AFTER A NAP.
OH, SOTA, DO ME A FAVOR AND GET
ME THE BANDAGES AND ANTIBIOTICS.
- HMM.
- AAH, THERE'S NOTHING LIKE
A REAL BED WITH REAL PILLOWS.
INUYASHA?
I'LL LEAVE HIM HANGING
FOR A LITTLE BIT.
- [WIND BLOWING]
- HUH.
I COULD FINISH A WOMAN LIKE THAT
OFF ANYTIME I WANT TO,
BUT MAYBE THE REASON I CAN'T
IS BECAUSE THE HEART OF ONIGUMO
STILL BEATS WITHIN ME,
AND HE COVETED KIKYO'S LOVE
ABOVE ALL THINGS IN THIS WORLD.
ONIGUMO'S HEART...
SUCH A SHALLOW,
EVIL, CRIMINAL MAN.
HE WAS UNABLE TO MOVE,
AND YET YEARNED FOR KIKYO
TO SUCH A DEGREE
THAT HE OFFERED HIS BODY
UP TO A HOST OF DEMONS,
TO BE REBORN AS MYSELF.
- IT'S THAT FOOL OF A MORTAL'S
HEART WHICH ACHES FOR KIKYO,
AND IT HAS BEGUN TO AFFECT ME.
[THUNDER AND RAIN]
- HA HA.
NONSENSE!
YOU GREATLY
UNDERESTIMATE ME, KIKYO,
FOR I, NARAKU,
AM NOTHING LIKE ONIGUMO.
NOW THAT THE SACRED JEWEL IS
NEARLY RESTORED TO ITS GLORY,
I FIND ONIGUMO'S HEART USELESS
AND RATHER UNNECESSARY.
- [BUZZING]
- [GROWLS]
- WHAT'S THAT DARK CLOUD?
- IT'S BEEN HANGING OVER
THE TEMPLE FOR SOME TIME NOW.
- IT'S SURE OMINOUS-LOOKING.
- THOSE LIGHTS ARE SOULS.
SOMETHING IS DEVOURING SOULS.
- [MOANING]
- WHAT'S THAT THING?
- I KNOW WHAT IT IS!
NARAKU'S COMING AFTER ME!
- LADY KIKYO, WHAT'S WRONG?
- I MUST BORROW YOUR HORSE.
- LADY KIKYO!
- [HOOFBEATS]
- [GROWLING]
- THAT DEMON.
DOES IT INTEND TO CONSUME
ALL OF THE SOULS IN THIS REGION?
I WON'T ALLOW IT!
- [GROWLING]
- UH.
HMM.
- [GROWLING]
[ROARS]
- UH!
NO! IT'S STRIPPING ME
OF MY OWN ACQUIRED SOULS!
- [GROWLING]
- UH!
I--I CAN'T!
- [GROWLING]
- CURSE YOU!
AAH!
[SCREAMS]
- MIROKU, HOW IS
YOUR WOUND DOING NOW?
IS IT STILL HURTING YOU?
- NO, IT'S MUCH BETTER NOW,
THANKS TO THE CARE I'VE RECEIVED
FROM YOU AND KAEDE.
NARAKU HAS MANY INCARNATIONS.
- YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT
JUROMARU AND KAGEROMARU?
- YES.
THE FOURTH INCARNATION,
JUROMARU,
IS THE YOUNGER SIBLING
OF THE TWO.
HE LIVES ONLY
FOR THE THRILL OF BATTLE,
AND SEEMS TO PAY NO HEED
TO NARAKU'S ORDERS.
FOR EVEN THOUGH HE WAS
CREATED FROM A DEATHDOM,
HE RUTHLESSLY CHOPPED
HIS MASTER'S HEAD OFF
WITHOUT HESITATION.
IT'S OBVIOUS THAT EVEN
NARAKU HAS GREAT TROUBLE
CONTROLLING HIM.
- AND THEN THERE'S KAGEROMARU,
THE OLDER SIBLING WHO LAY
DORMANT INSIDE JUROMARU.
BOTH OF THEM ARE BRUTAL
AND QUITE MYSTERIOUS.
- WE DON'T KNOW WHO OR EVEN WHAT
KIND OF ENEMY WILL ATTACK NEXT.
I ENCOURAGE YE ALL
TO BE EXTREMELY CAREFUL,
AND KEEP YOUR WITS ABOUT YE.
- MM-HMM.
SAY, INUYASHA,
AREN'T YOU GOING TO CALL KAGOME
TO MAKE SURE
SHE COMES BACK TO US?
- FORGET IT!
WE'RE GOING TO BE BETTER OFF
WITHOUT HER
HANGING AROUND ANYWAY.
- IF THAT'S THE CASE,
THEN WOULD YOU MIND
DOING US ALL A FAVOR
AND STOP THAT NERVOUS FIDGETING?
IT'S INCREDIBLY IRRITATING.
- HMM.
- YOU KNOW, I HAVE TO SAY
THAT KAGOME HAS
THE PATIENCE OF A SAINT,
PUTTING UP WITH YOU.
- I COULDN'T AGREE
WITH YOU MORE.
- BUT THE REAL REASON
I'M GOING BACK
IS TO GET SOME MORE BANDAGES
AND MEDICINE FOR US TO USE.
I'M COMING RIGHT BACK,
BUT DON'T TELL INUYASHA THAT.
- HUH?
- SOMETIMES IT'S GOOD
TO MAKE HIM WORRY A LITTLE.
- I PROMISED KAGOME
THAT I'D KEEP QUIET.
- NO MATTER HOW YOU LOOK AT IT,
KOGA'S AFFECTION IS
COMPLETELY ONE-SIDED.
- HE'S RIGHT.
THERE'S NO NEED
TO BE NERVOUS ABOUT HER.
- GRR!
LISTEN TO YOU TWO.
YOU'RE TALKING AS IF
IT WAS ALL MY FAULT
THAT SHE DECIDED
TO GET UP AND LEAVE.
WELL, I WON'T APOLOGIZE.
NOT ME.
- [ALL SIGH]
- [BIRDS CAWING]
- STUPID KAGOME.
JUST BECAUSE YOU DIDN'T
COME BACK RIGHT AWAY,
I'M THE ONE WHO GETS
ALL THE BLAME.
WHAT DID I DO
THAT WAS WRONG, ANYWAY?
OH.
KAGOME, I MUST HAVE MADE YOU
PRETTY ANGRY WITH ME THIS TIME.
I WONDER WHAT YOU'RE DOING NOW.
- [WIND BLOWING]
- HUH?
A DEMON SCENT?
WHAT THE...
A GIANT SOUL COLLECTOR?
HUH?
- [MOANING]
- KIKYO?
- INU...YASHA.
UH!
- KIKYO!
- [BUZZING]
- IT LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE INJURED.
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
NARAKU'S POISONOUS INSECTS.
IS THIS ONE OF HIS TRICKS?
- WHERE...WHERE IS IT?
- [GROWLING]
- HE MUST BE TRYING
TO GET RID OF HER.
WELL, I WON'T LET HIM.
I'D NEVER LET NARAKU HARM KIKYO.
- [GROWLING]
- [GRUNTING]
- UH!
UH!
- KIKYO, I'LL TAKE CARE
OF THAT GIANT DEMON.
YOU JUST REST EASY HERE.
ARE YOU READY, WORM?
UNH!
- [GROWLING]
- GRR!
- YOU PICKED A FIGHT
WITH THE WRONG GUY,
AND NOW I'M GOING
TO CUT YOU DOWN TO SIZE.
AAH!
- [GROWLING]
- DIE!
- [YELL]
- KIKYO COULDN'T STAY ALIVE
WITHOUT THOSE SOULS.
KIKYO!
- INU...YASHA.
WHAT ARE YOU...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- THAT'S WHAT I WAS
GOING TO ASK YOU.
WHY DID YOU COME HERE?
- THAT DEMON WAS CHASING ME.
- AND YOU LED HIM HERE KNOWING
THAT I WOULD RESCUE YOU.
- DON'T BE A FOOL, INUYASHA.
I WAS RUNNING BLINDLY
FOR MY LIFE
WHEN I HAPPENED
TO COME UPON YOU.
- HUH? KIKYO...
- [DOGS BARKING]
- [CLOCK TICKING]
- [BREATHING]
- AAH!
IT'S NIGHT ALREADY?!
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS!
WHY DIDN'T YOU WAKE ME UP,
FOR CRYING OUT LOUD?!
- WE DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WERE STILL SLEEPING.
- OVER 50 YEARS.
- WHAT'S THAT?
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING, INUYASHA?
- I WAS THINKING HOW WE REALLY
HAVEN'T CHANGED THAT MUCH
CONSIDERING 50 YEARS
HAVE PASSED.
- DON'T TALK NONSENSE.
I'VE CHANGED A LOT.
SINCE THAT TIME, LONG AGO,
WHEN I SEALED YOU
TO THIS TREE WE'RE UNDER.
- IT WAS BECAUSE
OF NARAKU'S DECEPTIONS
THAT WE HATED EACH OTHER.
SO MUCH THAT YOU TRAPPED ME
HERE FOR 50 YEARS,
AND THEN YOU DIED.
KIKYO, BE HONEST.
HAVE I CHANGED?
BEFORE I KNEW
OF NARAKU'S EXISTENCE,
THERE WAS NO DOUBT THAT
I BURNED WITH RESENTMENT
OVER WHAT YOU'D DONE TO ME,
BUT THEN YOU TOLD ME
THAT MY LIFE WAS YOURS,
AND YOURS IS MINE.
- AH!
- IT SEEMS YOU'RE
NOT SO DIFFERENT FROM
NARAKU AFTER ALL.
- YOU'RE SAYING
I'M THE SAME AS NARAKU?
- DEEP WITHIN NARAKU,
ONIGUMO'S HEART BEATS
AND STILL YEARNS FOR MY TOUCH.
- ONIGUMO'S HEART?
- HE DESIRED ME,
AND HAVING ME KILL YOU
WITH MY OWN TWO HANDS
WAS SOMETHING THAT
HE DREAMED ABOUT.
IT WAS SOMETHING THAT
THE JEALOUS HEART OF
ONIGUMO SCHEMED FOR.
- HE WAS JEALOUS OVER
SOMETHING SO RIDICULOUS?
- YES, RIDICULOUS,
BUT THAT'S WHAT MORTALS ARE.
- ONIGUMO'S HEART
REMAINS INSIDE NARAKU.
WAIT. KIKYO, DOES NARAKU HAVE
FEELINGS FOR YOU, TOO, NOW?
- HE IS RELUCTANT TO ADMIT IT,
BUT I AM CERTAIN THAT HE HAS
A LINGERING DESIRE FOR ME,
AND IN AN EFFORT
TO EASE THAT FEELING,
HE'S TRYING TO GET RID OF ME.
- GRR!
- ENOUGH TALK, INUYASHA.
THESE SOULS HAVE
FULLY REJUVENATED ME.
- KIKYO, YOU AREN'T
ACTUALLY PLANNING
TO CONFRONT NARAKU
BY YOURSELF, ARE YOU?
YOU'RE NOT STRONG ENOUGH,
AND I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT
HE MIGHT BE IN LOVE WITH YOU.
IT'S TOO MUCH TO BEAR!
- THERE!
UNH!
I AM SO LATE.
OH, WELL.
I GUESS INUYASHA'S PROBABLY
HAD ENOUGH TIME TO HIMSELF NOW.
WHAT ARE THOSE LIGHTS?
- [FOOTSTEPS ON GRASS]
- [GASP]
- INUYASHA AND KIKYO.
BUT WHY?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- I DON'T CARE HOW
YOU FEEL ABOUT ME NOW.
BUT I SWEAR I WON'T LET
NARAKU HAVE YOU, EITHER.
ONLY I CAN PROTECT YOU FROM HIM!
- [GASP]
- LET ME GO!
- I WILL SLAY NARAKU MYSELF SO
YOU WON'T HAVE TO FIGHT ANYMORE.
I WILL PROTECT YOU.
- INUYASHA...
- KIKYO.
- HUH?
KIKYO.
- ANOTHER EXAMPLE OF HOW MEN
ARE PATHETIC FOOLS.
YOU HAVE THIS BELIEF
THAT ONCE YOU EMBRACE A WOMAN,
SHE BELONGS TO YOU.
- LISTEN--
- DON'T MOVE.
I'VE LEARNED SOMETHING
FROM WATCHING YOU JUST NOW.
AS LONG AS THE HEART OF
THE WEAK AND PATHETIC ONIGUMO
BEATS WITHIN NARAKU,
THERE WILL BE
AN OPPORTUNITY FOR ME,
AND THAT WILL GIVE ME
THE CHANCE I NEED
TO TOTALLY DESTROY NARAKU.
- KIKYO.
- [WIND BLOWING]
- KIKYO, DON'T GO!
- ONCE THE THREADS
OF FATE ARE TANGLED,
THEY CANNOT BE UNDONE.
- KIKYO!
- [THUNDER]
- ENVY, A MORTAL EMOTION
LEAKING FROM THE HEART
OF THAT SIMPERING FOOL ONIGUMO.
NEVER.
AH.
- THOSE LIGHTS ARE
DISCONNECTED SOULS.
- MY SISTER KIKYO.
SHE'S SOMEWHERE NEARBY.
- HUH?
- [RUSTLING]
- KAGOME.
SO SHE WAS WATCHING.
- INUYASHA IS LOOKING
STRAIGHT AT ME.
WHY?
WHY DOESN'T HE LOOK AWAY?
WHAT IS HE THINKING?
- [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- NOW THAT INUYASHA
HAS SWORN TO PROTECT KIKYO,
I CAN'T STAY WITH HIM ANYMORE.
BUT ONLY AFTER I'VE RUN BACK
TO THE PRESENT DO I REALIZE
THAT I STILL HAVE A SHARD
OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
I KNOW FULL WELL THAT I SHOULD
RETURN IT TO THE FEUDAL ERA,
BUT I ALSO REALIZE THAT IT MEANS
THE END OF MY ADVENTURES.
TORN BY INDECISION,
I STAND IN FRONT
OF THE SACRED TREE
WHERE I FIRST MET INUYASHA.
NEXT TIME,
"BACK TO WHERE WE FIRST MET."
SEE YOU SOON!