>> YOU FELT THE PAIN OF MY TOXIC
CLAWS, AND YET YOU'RE STILL
ABLE TO RUN?
>> HA HA HA!
TAKE THIS!
>> HA HA HA HA HA!
HA HA HA HA HA!
TASTE MY POISON!
HA HA HA HA HA HA HA!
HA HA HA!
HUH?
[CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
TURNER ENTERTAINMENT GROUP]
I WAS TOO HASTY.
PLEASE, WAIT.
DON'T KILL ME!
EEE!
>> I SEE.
FIRST GINKOTSU AND NOW MUKOTSU.
>> YUP.
SO, FROM THE 7, THAT LEAVES
ONLY 4.
>> 7 MINUS 2 IS 5.
>> HUH?
WAIT.
ONE, TWO...
>> BUT, JAKOTSU, YOU SAID THAT
INUYASHA'S FRIENDS WERE EXPOSED
TO MUKOTSU'S POISON.
>> YES.
MUKOTSU'S POISON IS VERY
PERSISTENT.
BY NIGHTFALL, THEY'LL PROBABLY
ALL BE DEAD.
>> HA HA HA HA HA.
THIS GETS EVEN MORE INTERESTING.
AS IT TURNS OUT, OUR BROTHER
GINKOTSU IS HEADED THEIR WAY
AS WE SPEAK.
GINKOTSU, MORE THAN A MATCH
FOR ANY DEMON.
>> [GROWLS]
>> IT'S NOT FAIR, RENKOTSU.
I TOLD YOU BEFORE, INUYASHA
IS MINE.
>> THAT'S ENOUGH, JAKOTSU.
PLANS HAVE CHANGED SOMEWHAT.
I HAVE ANOTHER MISSION PREPARED
FOR YOU.
>> IT'S NOT FAIR, IT'S NOT FAIR,
IT'S NOT FAIR, IT'S NOT FAIR!
>> I SAID THAT'S ENOUGH,
JAKOTSU.
>> BUT, RENKOTSU, INUYASHA IS--
>> QUIT WHINING, JAKOTSU,
AND LISTEN CAREFULLY TO WHAT
I WOULD HAVE YOU DO.
>> [GROANS, SIGHS]
>> THEN, IF YOU HURRY RIGHT
BACK, YOU MAY MAKE IT IN TIME
FOR INUYASHA'S DEATH.
>> [MOANS]
>> ARE YOU IN PAIN, KAGOME?
HANG IN THERE JUST A
LITTLE LONGER.
>> DON'T YOU WORRY.
IT'S GONNA BE OK!
>> I GOT TO GET EVERYONE TO A
SAFE PLACE, RIGHT AWAY.
>> IT'S A VERY FINE DAY TODAY.
WOULDN'T YOU AGREE, MASTER?
>> YES, INDEED IT IS.
WE NEED NOT FEAR DEMONS OR
SPECTERS IN THIS WEATHER.
>> I'M NOT SURE THAT I FOLLOW
YOUR REASONING, BUT I DO NOT
DOUBT YOUR WISDOM ON THE
MATTER, MASTER.
>> NOW LET US MAKE HASTE.
WE WOULD DO WELL NOT TO TEST
THESE INDISPUTABLE TRUTHS.
>> RIGHT.
>> HUH?
>> WHAT IS THAT LIGHT?
>> [GROWLS]
>> AAH!
>> [WHIMPERING]
>> [GROWLS]
>> [SCREAMING INDISTINCTLY]
>> FAIR-WEATHER DEMON!
>> [GROWLS]
>> HE WILL DIE.
HE WON'T DIE.
HE WILL DIE.
MM.
OH, WELL.
JUST WHEN THINGS WERE
GETTING INTERESTING.
HOW CAN RENKOTSU BE SO MEAN
TO ME?
INUYASHA.
[SIGHS] OH, WELL.
I GUESS IT CAN'T BE HELPED.
I BETTER FINISH UP MY WORK HERE
BEFORE GINKOTSU KILLS INUYASHA.
I SURE HOPE INUYASHA STAYS ALIVE
UNTIL WE GET BACK.
BUT AGAINST GINKOTSU,
I DON'T KNOW.
STILL.
>> HEY, INUYASHA,
I REALLY DON'T THINK IT'S WISE
TO MOVE THEM ANY FURTHER.
IT'LL MAKE THE POISON
SPREAD FASTER.
>> YEAH, I KNOW THAT.
I ALSO KNOW THAT WE CAN'T
STOP NOW.
THE MOMENT I LEFT TO GO CHASE
AFTER JAKOTSU, THE BAND OF SEVEN
ATTACKED KAGOME, MIROKU,
AND SANGO.
>> [WHIMPERS]
>> IF THEY KNOW THAT THESE THREE
ARE INCAPACITATED, THEY'RE BOUND
TO COME THIS WAY AND ATTACK US
WHILE OUR DEFENSES ARE DOWN.
>> YEAH, BUT, INUYASHA, IF LEFT
UNTREATED, THE POISON WILL--
>> YES, I KNOW, SHIPPO.
THAT'S WHY I'M SEARCHING FOR A
SAFE PLACE TO REST.
HUH?
HMM.
>> HEY, INUYASHA, WHAT'S WRONG?
>> HMM.
>> INUYASHA?
WHAT THE HECK ARE THOSE THINGS?
>> SHIPPO, KIRARA, GET DOWN!
>> AAH!
AAH!
>> IT'S THEM.
THE BAND OF SEVEN.
>> [WHIMPERS]
>> THERE'S NO WAY I CAN
FIGHT THEM NOW.
KIRARA, FOLLOW ME.
HUH.
I BET THOSE FLYING WEAPONS
OF HIS WON'T BE MUCH USE
IN THE FOREST.
>> [GROWLS]
>> UHH. HUH?
WHAT THE!
>> [GROWLS]
>> DAMN IT.
IS HE GOING TO BLOW UP
THE WHOLE FOREST?
>> OH, WE'RE DONE FOR.
>> DON'T PANIC ON ME, SHIPPO.
THEY DON'T KNOW WHERE WE ARE.
THEY'RE FIRING RANDOMLY.
FIRST THINGS FIRST.
I HAVE TO GET THESE THREE
TO SAFETY.
>> HMM.
SO, IT'S BEGUN.
>> OH, I GUESS I BETTER
HURRY UP.
>> [BREATHING HEAVILY]
HUH?
THIS WAY.
>> HUH?
>> [GROWLS]
>> [BREATHING HEAVILY]
>> LOOK! A CAVE!
>> UHH.
DAMN.
THE POISON IS SPREADING FAST.
AT THIS RATE...
>> KAGOME.
MIROKU.
SANGO.
>> SHIPPO, STAY HERE AND
WATCH OVER THEM, AND DON'T YOU
DARE COME OUT.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO,
INUYASHA?
>> DO?
HA.
ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
UHH.
>> INUYASHA.
DON'T WORRY.
I'LL GUARD THEM WITH MY LIFE!
>> [SLURP]
>> I'LL SHOW THESE GUYS
WHO THEY'RE DEALING WITH.
UHH.
>> UHH. UHH.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I LEAVE THEM FOR JUST ONE
SECOND, AND THEY ALL RUN OFF
ON ME WITHOUT A SINGLE
PARTING WORD.
WHAT ON EARTH ARE THEY DOING
SO FAR NORTH, ANYWAY?
[GASPS]
MAYBE THEY CAME
FOR THE HOT SPRINGS.
>> [LAUGHTER]
>> ALL RIGHT!
THIS WATER FEELS TOTALLY
FANTASTIC!
>> THAT'S BECAUSE HOT SPRINGS
SUCH AS THIS IMPROVE
CIRCULATION, SOOTHE STIFF
SHOULDERS, AND HELPS CURE
ATHLETE'S FOOT.
>> [SOBBING]
I CAN'T BELIEVE THEY WOULD
LEAVE ME BEHIND WHILE THEY HAVE
SUCH A PLEASANT, RELAXING TIME!
OH!
I KNOW THIS WAS ALL YOUR IDEA,
MASTER INUYASHA.
I WILL CATCH UP TO YOU!
AAH!
HEY, WATCH IT, YOU STUPID BIRD!
>> WHERE THE HECK IS THIS GUY?
UHH.
THE SMELL OF GUNPOWDER'S
ALL OVER THIS PLACE.
HOW AM I GOING TO FIND HIM?
HUH?
I GOT YOU.
>> [GROWLS]
>> YIKES!
WHAT IS THAT THING?
>> HUH?
UHH.
DAMN.
IT WAS A TRAP TO LURE ME AWAY.
NO, KAGOME!
>> [SCREAMING INDISTINCTLY]
THIS IS BAD.
REALLY BAD!
WE'LL ALL BE BURIED ALIVE!
>> UHH.
KIRARA!
>> [GROWLS]
[GROWLS]
>> [WHIMPERS]
>> [GROWLS]
I'LL TEAR YOU ALL
INTO MINCEMEAT.
>> AAH!
>> WIND-SCAR! UHH!
UHH.
>> INUYASHA!
>> ARE YOU TWO ALL RIGHT?
>> [WHIMPERS]
YEAH, WE'RE BOTH OK.
>> HEY, YOU FREAK.
HOW DARE YOU TRICK ME LIKE THAT!
>> [GROWLS]
>> YES.
INUYASHA.
>> HEH.
YOU DON'T LOOK HUMAN,
SO WHAT ARE YOU?
>> I'M CALLED GINKOTSU.
>> GEE, I'D LOVE TO SIT DOWN
AND HEAR YOUR LIFE STORY,
BUT TIME'S A BIT SHORT
RIGHT NOW, SO I'M GOING TO PUT
AN END TO THIS.
>> YES.
SO THOUGHTLESS OF YOU TO LEAVE
YOUR FRIENDS TO SUFFER THE
EFFECTS OF MUKOTSU'S POISON,
CAUSE AT THIS RATE, THEY WON'T
LIVE PAST SUNDOWN.
>> SUNDOWN?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> BUT DON'T WORRY.
I'LL MAKE SURE YOU'RE THERE
TO GREET THEM ON THE OTHER SIDE.
>> [GRUNTING]
KIRARA, GET THE OTHERS AWAY
FROM HERE RIGHT NOW.
>> [GROWLS]
>> YES.
>> NO, YOU DON'T!
I'M THE ONE YOU'RE GONNA FIGHT!
>> INUYASHA!
>> SHIPPO, I'M COUNTING ON YOU.
[GRUNTING]
>> [GASPS]
HURRY, KIRARA.
WE GOT TO GET THEM TO SAFETY!
A SAFE PLACE.
AAH!
WHERE THE HECK AM I GONNA FIND
SOMEWHERE SAFE ENOUGH?
>> [GROWLS]
>> AAH!
OOH!
A TEMPLE!
KIRARA, TAKE US DOWN THERE!
>> UHH.
HMM.
HMM. WHOA!
UHH!
UM, EXCUSE ME.
>> HMM.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> [GROWLS]
>> UHH.
DAMN IT.
UHH.
>> YES.
QUIT JUMPING AROUND SO MUCH.
YOU DON'T WANT YOUR FRIENDS
TO DIE ALONE, NOW, DO YOU?
>> HMM.
[GRUNTING]
>> YES.
OOPS.
DOES IT HURT?
>> I'LL SHOW YOU WHAT HURT
MEANS, GINKOTSU, WHEN...
UHH.
OH.
>> KAGOME.
>> [MOANS]
SHIPPO, TELL ME.
WHERE ARE WE?
>> A TEMPLE.
THEY'VE GIVEN US SHELTER.
MIROKU AND SANGO ARE STILL
UNCONSCIOUS.
>> WHAT ABOUT INUYASHA?
>> YOU'RE AWAKE.
>> HUH?
>> I'M SO GLAD.
NOW, JUST RELAX AND RECUPERATE.
>> [GASPS]
>> HMM.
>> THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD,
AND THIS MAN IS ONE OF
THE BAND OF SEVEN?
>> MY TETSUSAIGA.
UHH.
WHAT ARE THESE METAL THREADS?
>> YE-E-E-E-ES.
I WAS WARNED TO BE CAREFUL OF
THAT SWORD OF YOURS.
>> THESE THREADS.
THEY'RE ALL OVER THE PLACE.
>> YE-E-E-E-E-ES.
>> I'M SURE OF IT.
HE HAS TO BE ONE OF THEM.
UHH.
MY BODY.
HUH?
MY VOICE IS GONE.
>> WHAT A PITY.
I UNDERSTAND YOU INHALED POISON.
YOU REALLY SHOULDN'T HAVE BEEN
MOVED SO SOON AFTER.
ALL THREE OF THEM ARE VERY WEAK.
THEY WON'T BE ABLE TO GET UP
FOR SOME TIME YET.
>> SHIPPO, PLEASE.
DON'T YOU SEE?
>> HUH?
>> [WHIMPERS]
>> HMM.
YOU SHOULD SLEEP A LITTLE MORE.
>> I HAVE TO GET AWAY
FROM THIS PLACE.
>> [MOANS]
>> [GASPS]
>> [SNORING]
>> THAT SMELL.
OH, NO!
INUYASHA, PLEASE HURRY!
>> DO NOT WORRY.
I WILL NOT LET YOU DIE
RIGHT AWAY.
AFTER ALL, IF INUYASHA SHOWS UP
AND FINDS YOU ALL DEAD,
HE'S LESS LIKELY TO BE
INTERESTED IN WHAT I HAVE TO
SAY TO HIM.
>> [GRUNTING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GRUNTING]
WHY, YOU.
OH!
[GRUNTING]
>> YE-E-ES.
>> [GRUNTING]
WHAT DO I DO?
I KNOW I CAN'T USE THE
WIND-SCAR.
SO WHAT CAN I--[GASPS]
HUH.
I GOT AN IDEA.
UHH.
>> YES.
FINALLY GETTING UP, INUYASHA?
>> YOU SHUT UP!
I'M ABOUT TO CUT YOU INTO
LITTLE BITS, SO PREPARE TO DIE.
[GROWLS]
UHH!
>> YOU SHOULD'VE STAYED DOWN.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> IT'S USELESS.
>> UHH!
UHH!
>> YES. HUH?
>> UP HERE, CREEP.
>> HUH?
>> NOW I'VE GOT LOTS OF ROOM
TO GIVE YOU A LITTLE TASTE OF
MY WIND-SCAR.
IT'S BEEN NICE KNOWING YA!
>> HUH?
>> WIND!
SCAR!
UHH!
>> [GROWLS]
>> UHH. HMM.
HUH?
I'VE GOT TO HURRY TO KAGOME
AND THE OTHERS.
KAGOME.
HANG IN THERE, KAGOME.
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> SHIPPO, THE TEMPLE IS
SURROUNDED BY FIRE!
KAGOME, THIS IS NO TIME
TO BE ASLEEP!
OH, WHY WON'T THEY WAKE UP?
>> EVERYONE'S BEEN POISONED
BY MUKOTSU.
WHY DIDN'T THE ANTIDOTE
I GAVE THEM WORK?
>> WE HAVE TO PUT THE FIRE OUT!
>> OK.
[INDISTINCT]
>> AAH!
YOU MADE THINGS WORSE!
>> NEXT TIME ON "INUYASHA,"
KAGOME, MIROKU, AND SANGO.
DESPERATE SITUATION.
>> DON'T WORRY.
I'LL PROTECT EVERYONE UNTIL
INUYASHA COMES.