- DAMN HIM TO HELL.
[CHATTER]
- HEY, WE FOUND SOME SAKE
OVER HERE, CHIEF.
- WENCH, STAND UP
AND POUR THE CHIEF A DRINK.
- YOU'VE WEAKENED CONSIDERABLY,
HALF-DEMON.
SERVES YOU RIGHT--
SIDING WITH HUMANS
AND MEDDLING IN MY AFFAIRS.
- WE'RE IN TROUBLE.
THE BARRIER
ISN'T GONNA HOLD MUCH LONGER.
- DAMN.
- ATTEND TO THE CHIEF,
YOU FOOLISH WENCH!
[GASPS]
[LAUGHS]
- ARE YOU AFRAID, WOMAN?
SUCH A LOVELY COUNTENANCE.
[SCREAMING]
- HE TRULY IS A DEMON.
- EVERY WOMAN THE CHIEF HAS HAD
ALWAYS DISAPPEARED MYSTERIOUSLY.
THIS EXPLAINS
WHAT HAPPENED TO THEM.
- CURSE HIM.
LEAVE THEM ALONE!
[GRUNTING]
- INUYASHA,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
HANG ON.
[LAUGHS]
- THE POISON HAS SPREAD
THROUGHOUT HIS BODY.
[SCREAMING]
- OBSERVE ME UNTIL YOU PERISH,
HALF-DEMON,
AS I DEVOUR THESE WOMEN
ONE BY ONE.
- IF I CAN GET THIS SWORD
TO HIM,
WE WILL ALL BE SAVED.
- HUH?
MY SWORD!
- THE TETSUSAIGA.
- YOU MUST USE THE SWORD
AND SAVE OUR WOMEN
FROM THIS TERRIBLE FATE!
- WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING?
STUPID OLD FOOL.
YOU'VE SEALED YOUR OWN FATE
THIS TIME.
- DAMN THEM.
- THAT'LL TEACH YOU
FOR TRYING TO ACT SMART,
YOU OLD GEEZER.
- GRANDPA!
- HUH?
[CRYING]
- GRAMPS.
- HUH, ANOTHER NUISANCE.
- ARE YOU OK?
- THE SWORD.
- HUH?
- GIVE THE SWORD
TO YOUR FRIEND.
- THE TETSUSAIGA?
WHERE'S INUYASHA?
WHERE?
IS HE HERE?
- AH, A DELECTABLE-LOOKING
WOMAN.
BRING HER TO ME.
- SIR.
[LAUGHING]
- WHY, YOU...
- COME QUIETLY.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT,
INUYASHA?
[GASPS]
OH, NO.
THE BARRIER'S DIMINISHING.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT WITH HER?
- WE'RE FOLLOWING
THE CHIEF'S ORDERS.
HAND THE GIRL OVER.
- NO WAY!
YOU WON'T TOUCH A HAIR
ON KAGOME'S HEAD!
- SANGO!
- YOU AIN'T GETTING AWAY.
- THERE'S TOO MANY OF THEM.
- GET HER!
- IT'S BREAKING.
THE BARRIER WON'T HOLD OUT
MUCH LONGER.
INUYASHA, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
HANG ON.
[SCREAMING]
INUYASHA?
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- WHAT'S THIS?!
- INUYASHA.
- HE RIPPED THROUGH
MY POISON COCOON.
- INUYASHA.
- OH, NO!
LOOK AT HIS FACE!
- HE'S TRANSFORMED.
- YOU AMUSE ME,
BUT THE SHOW IS OVER.
YOU ARE NO MORE
THAN A HALF-DEMON.
YOU CANNOT DEFEAT ME,
THE DEMON KATENMARU.
DIE, LITTLE MAN.
WHY DOES HE CARRY THE SCENT
OF PURE DEMON BLOOD?
I MELTED HIM!
HE WAS MERELY A HALF-DEMON.
- YOU TALKING TO ME?
- HUH?
- FILTHY VERMIN!
YOU WON'T ESCAPE.
- INUYASHA.
- LORD SESSHOMARU.
OH, LORD SESSHOMARU,
HAVE YOU GONE AWAY
AND LEFT ME ONCE AGAIN?
LORD SESSHOMARU,
WHERE ARE YOU, MASTER?
HOW COULD YOU LEAVE
WITHOUT TAKING
YOUR FAITHFUL RETAINER
ALONG WITH YOU?!
I KNOW.
IT'S ALL BECAUSE OF YOU, RIN.
CURSES!
OH, I SURE WISH
HE WOULD ABANDON THAT
HUMAN CHILD SOMEWHERE.
AH!
WAIT A MINUTE.
COULD IT BE THAT
LORD SESSHOMARU IS GONE
TO FIND INUYASHA
IN ORDER TO CONFIRM
WHAT BOKUSENO ADVISED HIM?
- HUH?
WHAT IS THIS INUYASHA LIKE,
JAKEN?
- AN EXCELLENT QUESTION, RIN.
IT'S A LONG STORY,
BUT ONE WHICH MUST BE CONVEYED.
[CLEARS THROAT]
AS YOU ARE AWARE,
INUYASHA IS LORD SESSHOMARU'S
YOUNGER BROTHER,
BUT HE HARDLY COMPARES
IN DEMON RANK
OR IN DEMON DIGNITY,
AND THAT IS BECAUSE HE IS--
HUH? HMM?
HOLD UP!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- OH, I DON'T REALLY LIKE
LONG STORIES.
LET'S GO, AH AND UN.
WE'LL FIND SOME NICE,
JUICY GRASS.
- I JUST WANTED
TO TELL THE STORY.
[SCREAMING]
- YOU WON'T GET AWAY.
- KAGOME!
- KILALA, STAY HERE
AND PROTECT THE VILLAGERS.
- INUYASHA!
- I BEG YOU TO SPARE US.
- WE WERE SIMPLY FOLLOWING
THE CHIEF'S ORDERS.
THAT'S ALL.
- HAVE MERCY ON US.
- DON'T DO IT, INUYASHA!
THEY'RE BEGGING FOR THEIR LIVES!
- IT SEEMS NOT EVEN YOU
CAN GET THROUGH TO HIM, KAGOME.
- HUH.
[LAUGHING]
- HE'S LAUGHING.
HE'S ABOUT TO SLAUGHTER THEM,
AND HE'S LAUGHING.
- KAGOME, GIVE TETSUSAIGA
TO INUYASHA,
AND HE'LL RETURN TO NORMAL.
I CAN'T STAND TO SEE
WHAT HE'S TURNED INTO NOW.
- INUYASHA,
TAKE THE TETSUSAIGA.
RETURN TO YOUR OLD SELF,
INUYASHA.
- SESSHOMARU!
- WHY IS HE HERE?
- HMM.
YOU ARE NOTHING MORE
THAN A MURDEROUS DEMON.
- UNFORTUNATELY FOR INUYASHA,
THE PURE DEMON BLOOD
OF HIS FATHER
IS TOO STRONG FOR A HALF-DEMON
SUCH AS HIMSELF.
IN ESSENCE,
THE DEMON BLOOD
WILL ATTACK THE SOUL.
HE WILL NOT BE ABLE
TO RECOGNIZE HIMSELF.
- COME AFTER ME, INUYASHA.
I WISH TO TEST YOUR STRENGTH,
TRANSFORMED AS SUCH.
- INUYASHA!
- NO! DON'T DO IT!
SESSHOMARU'S NEW SWORD
CAN SLAY AN ENEMY
WITH THE SLIGHTEST
BIT OF PRESSURE!
YOU'LL BE DESTROYED
BEFORE YOU EVEN
GET CLOSE TO HIM!
- HE FOUGHT OFF
SESSHOMARU'S SWORD.
- HUH, THAT WAS FOOLISH.
- HE'S CUT ALL OVER.
- STOP ALREADY!
INUYASHA!
- INUYASHA, YOU FEEL NO FEAR.
YOU KNOW NO PAIN.
THE DEMON BLOOD
COURSING THROUGH YOUR VEINS
HAS TAKEN OVER YOUR SOUL.
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHO YOU ARE,
AND YOU WILL CONTINUE FIGHTING
UNTIL YOU DIE.
I CAME IN YOUR PURSUIT
TO SEE IF BOKUSENO'S
WORDS WERE TRUE.
AND NOW, LITTLE BROTHER,
I UNDERSTAND.
YOU ARE NOT
A FULL-FLEDGED DEMON.
ALL YOU ARE IS A HALF-BREED.
KNOW YOUR PLACE IN THE WORLD.
A HALF-DEMON
SHOULD ACT LIKE ONE.
ON YOUR KNEES.
- INUYASHA!
INUYASHA!
PLEASE STOP.
- HE HAS FINALLY
BEEN BROUGHT DOWN.
- DON'T COME ANY NEARER.
- KAGOME, NO!
- KAGOME'S IN TROUBLE!
- IF YOU WISH HIM TO STOP,
USE TETSUSAIGA TO REVERSE
THE TRANSFORMATION.
[GASPS]
OTHERWISE,
HE WILL CONTINUE TO FIGHT
WHEN HE AWAKENS.
- I THOUGHT HE WANTED
TO KILL INUYASHA.
- YOU COULD HAVE
FINISHED HIM OFF EARLIER
IF YOU WANTED TO.
INSTEAD YOU MERELY HELD HIM OFF
WITH YOUR SWORD.
WHY DID YOU STOP AT THAT?
WE ALL KNOW
YOU DESPISE INUYASHA.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'VE DEVELOPED FEELINGS
FOR YOUR BROTHER.
- I WILL SLAY HIM EVENTUALLY.
WHY KILL HIM NOW
WHEN HE DOESN'T KNOW HIMSELF?
THERE WOULD BE NO POINT.
- IT'S ALMOST AS IF
HE CAME TO STOP
INUYASHA'S VIOLENT BEHAVIOR.
[MOANING]
- INUYASHA.
- HE'S COME TO.
- OH, LORD SESSHOMARU,
YOU'RE FINALLY BACK.
- RIN, I HOPE
YOU HAVE FARED WELL.
- MM-HMM.
AH AND UN AND I WERE ON
OUR VERY BEST BEHAVIOR.
JAKEN HAS BECOME
MOST MELANCHOLY, THOUGH.
- LORD SESSHOMARU!
WHAT GIVES, MILORD?
WHY DID YOU GO ALONE
AFTER INUYASHA?
MASTER,
THAT WAS MOST UNCALLED FOR.
I HOPE YOU CAN FORGIVE ME.
- HMM?
- LORD SESSHOMARU?
- INUYASHA,
YOU SHOULDN'T BE MOVING YET.
- DID I DO ALL THIS?
[GASPS]
- DOESN'T HE REMEMBER?
- HUH, LOOK AT ME.
MY CLAWS ABSOLUTELY
REEK OF THE SCENT
OF THE BANDITS' BLOOD.
- THE POOR GUY.
INUYASHA, YOU DID IT
TO SAVE THE INNOCENT.
THAT'S WHY
YOU ATTACKED THESE BANDITS.
- NO. HE'S A DEMON.
- IF YOU GET CLOSE,
HE'LL RIP YOU TO PIECES.
- YOU'RE WRONG.
- I DON'T CARE
IF HE IS A DEMON!
HE DID EVERYTHING IN HIS POWER
TO SAVE MY GRANDPA!
HE HELPED GET RID
OF ALL THE BAD MEN!
- NO.
I HUNTED THOSE MEN DOWN.
THE DEMON
THAT I WANTED TO BECOME,
THE POWER THAT I DESIRED,
IT WASN'T LIKE THIS.
- EACH TIME INUYASHA
TRANSFORMS INTO A DEMON,
HE LOSES A PIECE OF HIMSELF.
TODAY HE DIDN'T EVEN HEAR
KAGOME'S VOICE.
- MIROKU, I WANT TO STAY
WITH INUYASHA,
EVEN IF HE FULLY TRANSFORMS
INTO A DEMON.
- SANGO.
- I CAUSED SO MUCH TROUBLE
OVER KOHAKU,
BUT YOU'VE ALL STOOD BY ME
LIKE IT WAS
THE NATURAL THING TO DO.
THAT'S WHY I MUST STAND
BEHIND HIM.
- YES.
- I CAN'T GET THE SMELL OF BLOOD
OFF MY HANDS!
IT'S SICKENING!
- HERE.
- KEEP IT.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO FORCE YOURSELF
TO STAY BY ME.
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
YOU KNOW,
I WISH YOU'D ALL STOP
PUSSYFOOTING AROUND ME,
BECAUSE I DON'T HAVE A PROBLEM
WITH WHAT HAPPENED.
I DON'T GIVE A DAMN
WHAT I DID!
- DON'T KID YOURSELF.
IT MUST BE SO HARD ON HIM.
- HUH?
- OH, INUYASHA,
I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL.
- KAGOME,
I DON'T REMEMBER A THING
FROM WHEN I WAS TRANSFORMED.
IT WASN'T LIKE THAT BEFORE.
THE NEXT TIME I TRANSFORM,
I MAY EVEN COME AFTER YOU
WITH THESE CLAWS, KAGOME.
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- INUYASHA CAN'T SUPPRESS
HIS VIOLENT DEMON BLOOD,
BUT HE DOESN'T WANT TO BECOME
A MURDEROUS DEMON.
THERE MUST BE A SOLUTION.
IF HE DEFEATS RYUKOTSUSEI,
TETSUSAIGA
WILL BECOME LIGHTER
AND EASIER
FOR INUYASHA TO WIELD.
RELUCTANTLY,
HE OBEYS TOTOSAI'S ADVICE.
MEANWHILE,
NARAKU IS UP TO NO GOOD AGAIN.
NEXT TIME...
SEE YOU SOON.