- TREES.
"S," UM, UH, SQUIRREL.
"L," UH, LILY.
"Y," YELLOW!
YOUR LATE FATHER'S FRIEND
CERTAINLY LIVES
DEEP IN THE FOREST.
UH, Y-YEAH.
- WELCOME.
I HAVE AWAITED YOUR ARRIVAL.
- A VOICE FROM THE SKY!
- UH...I DON'T SEE ANYONE.
- I HAVE BEEN EXPECTING YOU,
SESSHOMARU.
- SO, YOU SAY THAT
YOU KNEW I WAS COMING,
DID YOU, OLD BOKSANO?
- YOU'VE COME TO SPEAK WITH ME
ABOUT THE SWORDS, I PRESUME.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
- INUYASHA TOLD ME
WHAT HAPPENED WHEN I WENT
OFF TO SEARCH FOR KOHAKU.
- UH...NO, MIROKU!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU'LL GET THE POISON INSECTS!
- WIND TUNNEL!
[DEMONS ROARING]
- MIROKU!
HE'S SUCKING IN
THE POISON INSECTS.
- [GRUNTING]
INUYASHA, GO AND RESCUE
SANGO AND KAGOME!
- YOU BRAVELY FOUGHT OFF
THE DEMONS WHILE I WENT
AFTER KOHAKU.
UHH!
KOHAKU!
I'M GOING TO KILL YOU,
THEN MYSELF.
IT'S MY ONLY CHOICE.
THIS IS THE ONLY WAY TO FREE YOU
FROM NARAKU.
FORGIVE ME, KOHAKU.
- STOP, SANGO!
- YAAH!
- UNH!
- [MIROKU GROANS]
- HUH?
I'M SORRY, MIROKU.
IT WAS MY FAULT YOU HAD TO DRAW
IN THOSE POISON INSECTS.
- MMM.
SAN...GO.
- WHAT IS IT?
- DON'T WORRY.
TRY NOT TO LOOK SO SAD.
THERE'S STILL HOPE FOR KOHAKU.
- MIROKU!
- TRUST ME, AND KEEP SMILING.
- [WHIMPERS]
YES, I WILL.
THANK YOU.
- MMM...
- MIROKU!
NO. SAY SOMETHING TO ME.
PLEASE HANG ON, MIROKU!
HUH?
ARRGH!
- AAH!
- SANGO, WE BROUGHT SOME WATER!
HOW IS MIROKU FEELING?
- I THINK HE'S FEELING
MUCH BETTER.
- UH, UH, UH...
- DO YOU SEEK INFORMATION
REGARDING THE TETSUSAIGA,
YOUR FATHER'S
HEIRLOOM SWORD?
OR PERHAPS...
- [GASPS]
A TREE DEMON!
- OH, LORD SESSHOMARU,
WHAT'S THAT?
- A 2,000-YEAR-OLD
MAGNOLIA TREE.
- I SEE.
- IT IS TRUE.
THE SHEATHS OF THE SWORDS,
THE TETSUSAIGA AND THE TENSEIGA,
PASSED DOWN
FROM SESSHOMARU'S FATHER,
WERE CARVED FROM
MY VERY OWN BOUGHS.
- THEY WERE?
SO THE SHEATHS FOR THEIR SWORDS
CAME FROM THIS TREE.
THEY HOLD SUCH STRANGE POWERS.
OH, I CAN SEE WHY, AFTER SEEING
THIS CREATURE.
- BOKSANO, PERHAPS YOU CAN
EXPLAIN THE LINK TO ME
BETWEEN INUYASHA
AND THE TETSUSAIGA.
- INUYASHA--YOUR YOUNGER
BROTHER?
- INUYASHA'S BLOOD HAS CHANGED.
THE FIRST TIME WAS WHEN A DEMON
BIT AND BROKE THE TETSUSAIGA.
THE SECOND TIME, HE HAD LET GO
OF TETSUSAIGA WHILE FIGHTING ME.
DIE!
THAT SCENT AGAIN.
HIS SCENT WASN'T
THAT OF A HALF-DEMON'S.
IT WAS THE SMELL
OF A PURE DEMON'S BLOOD,
LIKE MINE AND MY FATHER'S.
- HIS HAD THE SAME SCENT?
HA HA HA!
I HAVE MY DOUBTS.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
- INUYASHA IS A HALF-DEMON, BORN
BETWEEN A DEMON AND A HUMAN.
HE COULD NEVER BECOME
A FULL-FLEDGED DEMON.
SESSHOMARU, THERE IS SOMETHING
THAT YOU, A PURE-BLOODED DEMON,
ARE CAPABLE OF ACCOMPLISHING,
BUT WHICH INUYASHA
COULD NEVER DO.
- GO ON.
- IT IS SIMPLE.
I SPEAK OF PROTECTING ONESELF.
- PROTECTING ONESELF?
- YES.
IN BATTLE, FOR INSTANCE.
IF YOU FIND YOURSELF
IN A HOPELESS SITUATION,
YOU ARE ABLE TO REMAIN CALM.
YOU NEVER LOSE CONTROL OF
YOURSELF.
- HUH.
IT WOULDN'T BE POSSIBLE
FOR ME TO FALL INTO
SUCH A DESPERATE SITUATION.
- HA HA!
NO, I DON'T SUPPOSE YOU WOULD.
INUYASHA IS ANOTHER MATTER,
HOWEVER.
IF BACKED INTO A CORNER
TO THE POINT WHERE
HIS LIFE IS IN DANGER,
HIS DEMON BLOOD TAKES
CONTROL OF THE BODY,
AND IT TRANSFORMS
IN ORDER TO PRESERVE HIS LIFE.
- THAT WOULD EXPLAIN
HIS TRANSFORMATION.
- UNFORTUNATELY FOR INUYASHA,
THE PURE DEMON BLOOD OF
HIS FATHER IS TOO STRONG
FOR A HALF-DEMON
SUCH AS HIMSELF.
- WHAT WILL THE OUTCOME BE?
- WELL, IN ESSENCE,
THE DEMON BLOOD WILL
DEVOUR HIS HUMAN SOUL.
- ARRGH!
- HE WILL NOT BE ABLE TO
RECOGNIZE HIMSELF.
HE WILL NOT BE ABLE
TO DIFFERENTIATE
BETWEEN FRIEND OR FOE.
HE WILL SIMPLY KILL.
AND WITH REPEATED
TRANSFORMATIONS,
INUYASHA WILL EVENTUALLY
LOSE HIS SOUL.
HE WILL BECOME A DEMON WHO ONLY
KNOWS HOW TO FIGHT AND KILL,
AND HE WILL CONTINUE TO FIGHT
UNTIL HE IS DESTROYED.
- [SNARLING]
- I SINCERELY DOUBT THAT
YOUR FATHER WOULD HAVE WISHED
SUCH A TERRIBLE FATE
UPON HIS OWN SON.
THAT IS WHY HE BEQUEATHED
INUYASHA THE SWORD TETSUSAIGA
TO PROTECT HIS SOUL.
- THE TETSUSAIGA PROTECTS HIM?
SO...IF HE RELEASES THE SWORD,
HE IS DOOMED.
- INUYASHA, YOU'VE SURE DONE
A LOT OF GROWING UP.
- HUH? WHAT'S THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
- IT'S A COMPLIMENT.
I MEAN, YOU SAVED KOHAKU'S LIFE
INSTEAD OF KILLING HIM.
- HUH!
YEAH, WELL, I ONLY DID IT TO GET
UNDER NARAKU'S SKIN.
IF WE CAN MANAGE TO GET
KOHAKU BACK ALIVE,
THAT OUGHT TO
REALLY TICK HIM OFF.
- PUTTING ON AN ACT AGAIN.
- AND BESIDES, YOU'RE ALIVE.
KOHAKU SPARED YOU.
- HUH?
YOU WERE WORRIED?
- DO YOU NEED TO ASK?
- YOU KNOW, I WAS KIND OF
WORRIED MYSELF.
IT TOOK YOU SO LONG
TO COME BACK FOR ME.
- HMM.
IS YOUR ARM HURTING YOU?
LET ME TAKE A LOOK AT IT.
- NEVER MIND.
I CAN TAKE CARE OF MYSELF.
- HEY, IT WILL GET A LOT WORSE
UNLESS YOU TAKE CARE OF IT
EARLY ON.
- IT'S OK.
- IT ISN'T OK!
- I SAID I'M ALL RIGHT!
- ARE NOT!
- AM, TOO!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
- SORRY. I JUST WANTED
TO THANK YOU BOTH.
- HUH?
- THANK US FOR WHAT?
- FOR THE OBVIOUS,
KAGOME AND INUYASHA--
FOR STAYING WITH ME.
- CARRY ON, YOU GUYS.
- STAYING WITH HER?
WHY WOULDN'T WE?
HMM?
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
- WAAH!
- WHAT WAS THAT?
- SOUNDS LIKE IT CAME
FROM OVER THERE.
[BOY CRYING]
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- IT'S MY GRANDPA!
PLEASE, YOU'VE GOT TO HELP HIM!
- IS IT A DEMON?
- HUH?
- WHERE'S THE OLD MAN?
WHERE DID THE DEMON GET TO?
UNH!
HUH? DOESN'T SMELL LIKE THERE
ARE ANY DEMONS AROUND HERE.
- HELP!
- HUH?
- I'M UP HERE!
I'VE FALLEN, AND I CAN'T GET UP!
- HMM. YOU FELL?
- THANK YOU, LAD.
THAT'S A GREAT HELP.
- I THOUGHT A DEMON
HAD ATTACKED, BUT NO.
YOU GOT ME ALL WORKED UP
OVER NOTHING.
- GOOD THING THEY CAME ALONG.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH, LAD.
I TWISTED MY ANKLE
WHEN I FELL OVER.
AND NOW YOU'RE EVEN CARTING ME
BACK TO MY VILLAGE.
- NO NEED TO WORRY
ABOUT IT, OLD MAN,
BECAUSE IT'S MORE
OR LESS ON OUR WAY.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, INUYASHA?
- HMM.
- WELL, I CERTAINLY AM INDEBTED.
- LOOK--THE VILLAGE!
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
THERE IT IS.
TAKE CARE, YOU TWO.
- AYE.
- THANK YOU, LADY.
YOU, TOO, MR. DOG MAN.
- DOG MAN?
- INUYASHA...
- AS THANKS, I'M GOING TO
GIVE YOU MY TREASURE.
- HMM.
- HA HA HA!
- HUH?
- BYE!
THANKS AGAIN!
- WHAT DID THE BOY GIVE YOU?
- A MOLTED SNAKESKIN.
- COOL.
JUST WHAT YOU ALWAYS WANTED.
- WOW, INUYASHA!
CAN I HAVE IT
IF YOU DON'T WANT IT?
PLEASE?
WOW!
NEAT!
- GLAD YOU LIKE IT.
WE DON'T HAVE TIME
TO BE SAVING PEOPLE.
- LOOK, IT'S NOT LIKE WE WENT
OUT OF OUR WAY OR ANYTHING.
- WHENEVER YOU DO A GOOD DEED,
YOU BECOME ILL-TEMPERED
AFTERWARD.
- HUH!
HUH?
- IS ANYTHING WRONG?
- IS SOMETHING THE MATTER,
INUYASHA?
- I SMELL HUMAN BLOOD.
- WHAT?!
- SMELLS LIKE A LOT OF PEOPLE.
- HUH? HUH?
- THERE'S SMOKE COMING
FROM OVER THERE.
- ISN'T THAT THE VILLAGE
WHERE WE JUST LEFT THE KID
AND HIS GRANDFATHER?
THEY MUST HAVE BEEN ATTACKED.
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
HUH?
- THAT'S THE BOY!
- YEAH.
- PLEASE HELP GRAMPS.
OHH...
- YOU'RE SAFE NOW.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- PLEASE HELP HIM.
- KAGOME, YOU TAKE CARE
OF THE KID.
- YEAH, SURE.
- SANGO, YOU STAY BEHIND
AND PROTECT KAGOME FOR US, OK?
- YES, OF COURSE.
- LET'S GO, MIROKU!
- COMING!
- UNH!
[SCREAMING]
- AAH!
[HORSES NEIGHING]
[CHICKENS CLUCKING]
- THIS VILLAGE SUITS US WELL.
- WE'LL CAMP OUT HERE
UNTIL THE FOOD RUNS OUT.
- WOMEN, ASSEMBLE IN ONE PLACE!
DON'T EVEN TRY TO ESCAPE!
- LOOK--BANDITS!
- YOU'LL PAY!
UNH!
YAAAH!
[BANDITS SHOUTING]
I'LL TAKE CARE OF YOU
SMALL FRY LATER.
WHERE'S YOUR LEADER?
- INUYASHA, AMONG THE BANDITS!
- YEAH, I SMELL IT.
THERE'S A DEMON HIDING
AMONG THEM.
- [LAUGHING]
- LITTLE MAN, THAT SWORD YOU
BRANDISH IS MOST INTERESTING.
- HUH.
SO...YOU MUST BE THE DEMON.
CONTROLLING A BUNCH OF BANDITS,
ARE YOU?
- WHAT? YOU MEAN
OUR LEADER IS A DEMON?
- THAT'S THE DUMBEST THING
I HEARD.
- LITTLE MAN, HAND OVER
THAT SWORD OF YOURS.
- HUH?
WHAT THE HECK ARE
YOU BABBLING ABOUT?
- BETTER WATCH YOURSELF,
INUYASHA.
- HUH! AS IF I'D LOSE
TO THIS CRETIN.
- HMM.
- HRRRM.
- [LAUGHING]
IF YOU WON'T HAND IT OVER,
THEN I'LL HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO TAKE IT FROM YOU.
- HUH! I'D LIKE
TO SEE YOU TRY.
TAKE IT IF YOU CAN.
- INUYASHA STILL HAS DIFFICULTY
WIELDING HIS HEAVY SWORD.
WILL HE BE ABLE TO
HANDLE HIMSELF?
- I'LL CUT THE HIDE OFF YOUR
BACK, YOU FILTHY LITTLE DEMON!
- HMM. UNH!
- HMM.
- UNH!
- LOOK! THE CHIEF!
- HE SPLIT THE GIANT HATCHET!
- HUH.
SERVES YOU RIGHT, BANDIT.
- [LAUGHING]
THAT'S A MIGHTY SHARP SWORD.
- UNH. START MAKING
FUNERAL PLANS, GENIUS!
- I NEED A SHIELD.
HAAH!
[WOMEN WHIMPERING]
- AAH!
- OH, NO!
AAAH!
- UNH!
- HAAAA...
- HA HA. YOU'VE BEEN SHOWERED
WITH MY POISON.
UNH!
- AAH!
THAT WON'T STOP ME!
AAH!
- THAT SWORD IS AMAZING.
I LIKE IT MORE ALL THE TIME.
HAAAA...
- AAH!
- OH, NO!
[GRUNTING]
YAAAAH!
- AAH!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
- HA HA HA HA. THAT WILL KEEP
THEM OUT OF MY WAY.
- I DON'T BELIEVE IT!
- WHAT'S HE DONE?
- [LAUGHING]
IS SOMETHING THE MATTER?
ARE YOU AFRAID NOW THAT YOU KNOW
I'M A DEMON?
- UH, NO CHANCE, CHIEF.
- UH, WHO WOULDN'T WANT
A STRONG DEMON FOR A LEADER?
- WE'LL CONTINUE TO FOLLOW
YOUR LEAD, CHIEF.
- HA HA!
- SERVES THOSE FOOLS RIGHT!
AAAH!
PAIN! THE PAIN!
- IT'S A POISON COCOON.
ONE TOUCH, AND YOU'LL MELT AWAY.
THE 2 INSIDE WILL HAVE TOTALLY
DISINTEGRATED BY NOW.
[LAUGHING]
- AAAAH!
- [CHUCKLES]
IT'S A POISON COCOON.
WITH CONTINUED EXPOSURE,
YOU WOULD MELT AWAY...
LIKE THOSE FOOLS INSIDE.
HMM.
THEY HAVEN'T DISINTEGRATED?
OH. SO, THEY'VE CREATED
A BARRIER ON THE INSIDE.
- INUYASHA, CAN YOU MOVE AT ALL?
- OF COURSE I CAN MOVE.
I'LL RIP
THIS STUPID COCOON APART.
UNH, AAH!
- INUYASHA!
- YOU ARE WASTING YOUR TIME.
YOU ARE MORE OR LESS PARALYZED.
THE POISON POWDER HAS ENTERED
YOUR BLOODSTREAM ALREADY
THROUGH THE WOUND IN YOUR TORSO.
IT WILL FESTER SLOWLY.
- UNH, UNH...
- FETCH THE SWORD FOR ME.
- YES, SIR.
MMH!
- HE'S GOT YOUR SWORD!
- HERE YOU ARE, CHIEF.
- AAH!
- TETSUSAIGA HAS REJECTED HIM.
- CHIEF?
- LITTLE MAN, WHAT IS
THE MEANING OF THIS?
WHY DOES THIS SWORD REJECT ME?
- HUH!
I'LL TELL YOU ABOUT
MY TETSUSAIGA.
IT'S CHOOSY ABOUT ITS USER,
AND IT WOULD NEVER LET
A LOW-CLASS DEMON LIKE YOU
COME ANYWHERE NEAR IT.
- OH?
THEN EXPLAIN WHY THIS
LOW-CLASS BANDIT WAS CAPABLE
OF WIELDING THE SWORD.
- LOW-CLASS BANDIT?
COME ON, CHIEF!
- [GRUNTING]
- I SEE.
VERY INTERESTING,
LITTLE MAN.
YOU'RE A HALF-DEMON.
- UNH!
- HA HA HA HA.
HOW UTTERLY AMUSING.
A HALF-DEMON LIKE
YOU HAD THE GALL TO PICK
A FIGHT WITH ME,
THE DEMON GATENMARU!
[KILALA ROARS]
- THEY'RE TAKING TOO LONG.
SOMETHING MUST HAVE HAPPENED
IN THE VILLAGE.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- I'M WORRIED ABOUT MY GRANDPA.
- INUYASHA...
- INUYASHA'S WOUND
IS GETTING WORSE.
- DAMN!
THE BLEEDING WON'T STOP.
IS IT BECAUSE OF THE POISON?
- OH, WE'RE IN REAL TROUBLE.
IT'S ALL I CAN DO
TO KEEP UP THIS BARRIER.
I CAN'T MAKE A MOVE
ON THE ENEMY,
AND THIS WON'T HOLD OUT FOREVER.
- UM, CHIEF, WHAT SHALL WE DO
WITH HIS SWORD?
- DO AS YOU PLEASE.
I'M NOT INTERESTED IN A SWORD
I CAN'T USE.
- THANK YOU!
I AM MOST GRATEFUL.
- THAT SWORD OF HIS--
I MUST GET IT.
I MUST GET IT TO HIM.
- NICE BLADE.
- [LAUGHING]
- GREAT-LOOKING SWORD!
- IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE THE BARRIER WEARS OFF,
AND THE POISON COCOON
MELTS THEM AWAY.
SO I'LL JUST SIT HERE
AND ENJOY THE VIEW.
- [GRUNTING]
- [LAUGHS]
BRING THE WOMEN OVER TO ME.
[WOMEN WHIMPERING AND SCREAMING]
- AAH!
- DAMN HIM TO HELL.
- UNH...
- ARRGH...
[WOMAN SINGING BALLAD
IN JAPANESE]
- INUYASHA IS BADLY HURT
BY THE POISON MOTH DEMON
GATENMARU,
BUT HIS DEMON BLOOD KICKS IN,
AND HE SLAUGHTERS EVEN
THE BANDITS THAT BEG FOR MERCY.
HOW CAN WE REVERSE INUYASHA'S
TRANSFORMATION?
MIROKU!
SANGO!
WE HAVE TO THINK OF SOMETHING!
OH, NO!
SESSHOMARU IS THE LAST PERSON
WE NEED AT A TIME LIKE THIS!
NEXT TIME:
"THE DEMON'S TRUE NATURE."
SEE YA SOON!