>> I AM HAKUDOUSHI.
AS YOU GUESSED, I AM NARAKU'S
INCARNATION.
>> HAKUDOUSHI?
>> SO YOU ARE ONE OF NARAKU'S
CREATIONS?
>> I WILL SEARCH FOR
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
WOULD YOU CARE TO JOIN ME?
>> YOU'RE LOOKING FOR
THE JEWEL SHARD?
HUH.
I DON'T GIVE A DAMN ABOUT THE
NEXT WORLD OR WHATEVER, BUT IF
THERE'S A SHARD TO BE FOUND
THERE, THEN GO FIND IT YOURSELF!
YAH!
>> CURSE YOU.
>> WHAT IS THIS BRAT PLANNING
ANYWAY?
>> LET'S GO.
>> HEY, LOOK, I WONDER
WHAT'S GOING ON.
>> YEAH.
>> I WILL VOLUNTEER TO GO SPEAK
TO THEM.
MISS, I WANT YOU TO CONSIDER
BEARING MY CHILD.
IT'S THE CHANCE OF A LIFETIME.
>> WHAT WAS THAT, MONK?
GRR...
>> YAH...
>> WHAT AN IDIOT.
>> IT WAS A GREETING.
>> EXCUSE ME, DID SOMETHING
HAPPEN HERE?
>> IT CERTAINLY DID.
OUR VILLAGE WAS ATTACKED BY
A HEADLESS DEMON.
>> IT TORE UP
THE ENTIRE VILLAGE.
I WAS SCARED RIGHT OUT
OF MY WITS.
>> AND THE DEMON, ARE YOU SURE
IT WAS HEADLESS RIGHT FROM
THE START?
>> YES.
IT USED TO BE A MAN-EATING DEMON
WHO LIVED OUT IN THE MOUNTAINS.
WE DON'T KNOW WHO RIPPED ITS
HEAD OFF, BUT IT'S ALREADY
INJURED MOST OF THE VILLAGERS,
AND IT HASN'T STOPPED YET.
>> LEAVE IT TO US!
WE SHALL SLAY THIS DEMON FOR
YOU, GENTLEMEN!
HA HA!
>> DO YOU THINK IT'S WISE
TO LET THIS MONK HANDLE
THE PROBLEM FOR US?
>> NOT MOMENTS AGO, HE WAS
FLIRTING WITH ONE OF OUR WOMEN.
>> I DON'T TRUST HIM.
>> SO, SHALL WE CONTINUE
ON OUR WAY?
>> INUYASHA, TRACK THE DEMON'S
SCENT SO WE CAN FOLLOW IT.
>> I DON'T REALLY NEED TO.
IT'S PRETTY OBVIOUS WHICH WAY HE
WENT, DON'T YOU THINK?
>> TRUE ENOUGH.
>> SPEAK OF THE DEVIL.
>> AAH!
>> HUH?
>> THAT GIRL IS IN DANGER!
I GOTTA KEEP IT TOGETHER!
>> COME BACK!
HE'LL KILL YOU!
DAMN!
GET OUT OF HERE!
>> STOP IT!
>> UH, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> PLEASE, YOU'VE GOT TO MAKE
HIM STOP.
>> STOP?
BUT WHY?
>> AAH!
>> A BABY RACCOON DOG.
>> THAT'S MY FATHER.
I'M BEGGING YOU,
PLEASE DON'T HURT HIM.
>> RACCOON DOG?
>> I'M AN OTTER.
>> WHATEVER?
YOU SURE DON'T LOOK LIKE YOU'RE
RELATED TO THAT THING.
>> HUH?
WAIT, THAT'S NOT
MY FATHER.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU CAN MAKE
A MISTAKE LIKE THAT.
MAYBE EXPLAIN IT AFTER I TAKE
CARE OF UGLY HERE.
IRON REAPER SOUL STEALER!
>> MY NAME IS KANTA.
AS YOU CAN SEE, I'M A--
>> RACCOON DOG.
>> I'M AN OTTER!
>> HOW COME YOU DISGUISE
YOURSELF AS A HUMAN GIRL?
>> PA TOLD ME TO.
HE SAID IF I PRETENDED TO BE A
HUMAN GIRL, WHENEVER I LEFT THE
MOUNTAIN, SOME IDIOT WOULD
ALWAYS COME TO MY RESCUE.
>> YOUR FATHER SOUNDS VERY
PERCEPTIVE.
EARLIER, YOU CALLED THAT DEMON
YOUR FATHER, DIDN'T YOU?
>> YEAH.
I'M LOOKING FOR MY PA.
YOU SEE, I'VE GOT HIS HEAD
INSIDE THIS BUNDLE.
>> WHAT?
>> IT ALL STARTED 3 DAYS AGO.
PA AND I WERE FISHING
IN THE RIVER.
>> AH!
>> HA!
THAT WAS INCREDIBLE, PA!
>> IT'S EASY ONCE YOU GET
THE HANG OF IT.
WANT TO TRY?
>> YEAH!
HA HA HA!
>> OOH!
YOU'RE OK, SON.
YOU'VE GOT TO KEEP AN EYE ON THE
RIVER'S DEPTH.
CAN'T HAVE AN OTTER DROWNING
IN THE RIVER.
>> MM-HMM.
OK.
>> [ROAR]
>> JUST THEN, A BOY IN WHITE
CAME ALONG RIDING A DEMON HORSE.
>> KANTA, YOU MUST HIDE QUICKLY.
>> HUH?
>> JUST GO, HURRY.
>> UH, OK.
>> WHO ARE YOU, YOUNG BOY?
YOU'RE NOT FROM AROUND HERE.
>> AH.
>> UH...
>> SO YOU DODGED MY FIRST BLOW.
>> YOU DON'T KNOW WHO YOU'RE
DEALING WITH, KID.
>> HUH.
THIS WILL BE MORE FUN
THAN I EXPECTED.
>> UH!
ARGH!
YAH!
>> AH, PAPA!
>> KANTA, RUN AWAY!
[GASPING]
>> WITH THAT MUCH RIPENESS,
YOU'LL LAST A WHILE.
>> AAH!
>> PA'S HEAD WAS CARRIED AWAY BY
THE CURRENT AND SWEPT OVER
A WATERFALL.
>> OH, WELL.
>> THE BOY LEFT AFTER THAT.
BUT BY THE TIME I FOUND PAPA'S
HEAD AND RETURNED TO THE RIVER,
I COULDN'T FIND HIS BODY
ANYWHERE.
IT DISAPPEARED.
>> USE THIS.
>> THANK YOU.
[BLTHP]
>> FROM WHAT HE SAID, THE PERSON
HUNTING DOWN THE DEMONS--
>> HAS TO BE HAKUDOUSHI.
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
>> YEAH, BUT WHAT'S HIS PURPOSE?
>> WELL, IN HIS INFANT STAGE,
HAKUDOUSHI WENT AROUND KILLING A
NUMBER OF MONKS AND
SHRINEKEEPERS, ALL SO HE COULD
GET A GLIMPSE OF THE BORDER
BETWEEN THIS WORLD AND THE NEXT.
WHO KNOWS?
MAYBE THAT'S WHAT HE'S AFTER,
STILL.
>> AND HE'S USING THE DEMONS
TO DO IT.
THAT'S RIGHT, HE LOOKED INTO
THE HUMAN HEART.
>> SOUNDS POSSIBLE,
IF YOU ASK ME.
DEMONS AREN'T LIKE HUMANS.
THEY DON'T DIE NEARLY AS EASY.
SO YOU FIGURE IF YOU FIND YOUR
DAD'S BODY AND STICK HIS HEAD
BACK ON...
>> THERE MIGHT BE TIME
TO SAVE HIM.
>> REALLY?
>> YOU MEAN HE'LL COME BACK
TO LIFE?
>> YOUR FATHER MUST BE
INCREDIBLY TOUGH.
>> [SOBBING]
>> EASY.
>> IT'S ALREADY BEEN 3 DAYS
SINCE THEN, AND IF HIS BODY'S
BEEN SLAIN, THERE WON'T BE ANY
HOPE TO SAVE HIM.
>> DON'T GIVE UP!
INUYASHA IS HERE TO HELP YOU!
>> HUH?
>> HE HELPED ME AVENGE MY PA
BEFORE, TOO, SO I BET HE CAN
HELP YOURS!
>> TENSEIGA!
>> AH!
>> TRUST ME, INUYASHA'S STRONG.
>> HUH?
>> UM, SHIPPO?
>> IS HE REALLY THAT GOOD?
>> YEP.
HE'S SO STRONG IT MAKES UP FOR
THE FACT THAT HE'S STUPID,
CHILDISH, AND JUST PLAIN WEIRD.
>> SO YOU LOST YOUR PA, TOO,
HUH?
>> LET'S BE FRIENDS,
RACCOON DOG.
>> I'M A FOX.
>> NO, YOU'RE A RACCOON DOG.
>> I'M A FOX!
>> I'M SURE IT'S OVER THIS WAY.
>> I SENSE A TERRIBLE DEMONIC
AURA APPROACHING.
>> [SQUAWKING]
>> KEEP IT DOWN.
YOU'LL LET THEM KNOW WHERE WE
ARE WITH ALL THAT RACKET.
YOU SAY YOU WANT TO KNOW
WHAT I'M DOING?
VERY WELL, I SUPPOSE
I SHOULD TELL YOU.
ACTUALLY, RUMORS HAVE BEEN GOING
AROUND ABOUT A STRANGE BEING
STALKING AND THEN DECAPITATING
THE STRONGEST OF DEMONS.
>> AAH!
>> PUNY DEMONS LIKE YOU TWO HAVE
NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
IF IT'S STRONG DEMONS THEY'RE
AFTER, THEN YOU CAN BET THAT I,
THE GREAT CHOCHUKAI, WILL BE
TARGETED NEXT BY THE
MYSTERIOUS SLAYER.
HA HA!
>> [SIGHING]
>> THERE HE IS.
>> HMM.
>> VERMIN!
I WILL TEAR YOU LIMB FROM LIMB!
RARH!
>> BE QUIET.
>> HMM?
HUH?
WELL, I'M NOT AFRAID OF HIM.
I MIGHT BE HEARTLESS, BUT EVEN I
WOULDN'T PICK A FIGHT
WITH A KID LIKE THAT.
IT'S JUST INSANITY.
HUH.
>> [GRR]
>> AAH!
UH!
HOW DARE A MERE HORSE ATTACK ME.
AAH!
>> YAH!
>> ENTE IS SURE MAKING A FUSS.
>> PROBABLY JUST SOME MONKEYS
OR BOARS.
>> HMM.
BY THE WAY, HAVE YOU SEEN
ANYTHING?
>> THEY'RE ALL BASICALLY
THE SAME.
I CAN SEE A WORLD OF WHITE MIST
AND THOSE OBJECTS SCATTERED
BENEATH IT.
>> AH!
>> HMM...
>> MASTER JAKEN?
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> WHERE DID LORD SESSHOMARU GO?
>> I HAVE NO IDEA.
HE'S NEVER BEEN VERY TALKATIVE
TO BEGIN WITH, BUT EVER SINCE HE
FAILED TO DEFEAT NARAKU AT MT.
HAKUME, HE'S BEEN EVEN
MORE SILENT.
STILL, HE COULD AT LEAST TELL ME
WHERE HE'S GOING.
AHH...
>> CAREFUL, MASTER JAKEN,
YOU'RE GONNA SIGH ALL YOUR
HAPPINESS AWAY.
HERE.
>> HUH?
>> AAH!
>> TENSEIGA.
WHAT DISTURBS YOU?
>> AAH!
>> THE DEMON!
THE HEADLESS DEMON!
>> THERE IT IS!
>> AFTER HIM!
>> HE'S GETTING AWAY!
>> HMM?
>> DID YOU PICK UP THE SCENT OF
KANTA'S FATHER?
>> YEAH.
>> REALLY?
>> I SMELL BLOOD, TOO, THOUGH.
I WONDER IF SOMEONE INJURED HIM.
ARE WE TOO LATE?
>> [STRUGGLING]
>> WOMEN AND CHILDREN,
GO INSIDE!
THE HEADLESS DEMON MIGHT COME
BACK TO SLAY US!
>> IS THE HEADLESS DEMON
AROUND HERE?
>> I WONDER IF IT'S KANTA'S PA.
>> THIS IS TERRIBLE.
>> IF HIS BODY IS DESTROYED,
HE'LL NEVER BE BROUGHT BACK
TO LIFE.
>> HURRY, INUYASHA.
>> YEAH, THE SCENT ISN'T FAR.
I DON'T LIKE THE OTHER SCENT I'M
PICKING UP NEAR KANTA'S OLD MAN,
THOUGH.
>> [GASP]
>> IT'S HIM!
>> HE'S A SHOMARU?
>> BUT WHY?
>> PA!
HANG ON, PA!
>> KANTA, BRING OUT THE HEAD!
>> OK.
[STRUGGLING]
>> WE WERE TOO LATE AFTER ALL.
>> [WHIMPERING]
PA!
>> KANTA...
>> HEY, SESSHOMARU, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING AROUND HERE?
THIS IS NO COINCIDENCE,
CROSSING PATHS WITH YOU.
>> I DON'T OWE YOU
AN EXPLANATION.
>> WAIT, SESSHOMARU, THE SWORD
THAT YOU CARRY, THE TENSEIGA, IT
CAN SAVE A HUNDRED LIVES WITH A
SINGLE STROKE.
PLEASE HELP US.
USE YOUR SWORD TO BRING THE
BOY'S FATHER BACK.
>> WHY SHOULD I?
THIS HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH ME.
>> PA!
[SOBBING]
>> SESSHOMARU, PLEASE FIND IT IN
YOUR HEART TO HELP MY FRIEND.
>> POOR SHIPPO.
>> UH, IF HIS PA PASSES ON,
KANTA WILL BE ALL ALONE.
>> HUH.
>> STEP ASIDE.
>> PLEASE HELP MY FRIEND.
I'M BEGGING YOU!
>> OH, SHIPPO...
>> HE HAS TO.
>> YOU'RE WASTING YOUR TIME
ASKING HIM FOR HELP, SHIPPO.
SESSHOMARU ISN'T REALLY THE TYPE
TO HELP PEOPLE WHEN THEY'RE
IN TROUBLE.
AND BESIDES THAT,
THERE'S THE SWORD ITSELF.
THE TENSEIGA ISN'T SOMETHING A
GUY LIKE HIM KNOWS HOW TO USE.
>> TRUE ENOUGH.
I FORGOT THAT.
ONLY SOMEONE WITH A CARING HEART
CAN WIELD THE SWORD.
>> PRECISELY.
TENSEIGA IS STIRRING.
IS IT TELLING ME TO SAVE
THAT DEMON?
WHY?
>> HUH?
SESSHOMARU...
>> BACK AWAY.
>> HUH?
>> I CAN SEE THE EMISSARIES OF
THE AFTERLIFE.
[WIND BLOWS]
>> HE CUT SOMETHING.
>> HUH.
PA...
HUH?
PAPA!
[SOBBING]
>> LUCKY YOU, KANTA.
I'M HAPPY FOR YOU.
UH.
>> UH!
UH!
I SURE DIDN'T EXPECT TO COME
BACK TO LIFE.
>> COULD YOU DESCRIBE WHERE YOU
WERE AFTER YOU WERE BEHEADED?
>> IT WAS A VERY STRANGE PLACE,
I'LL TELL YOU THAT.
A WORLD SHROUDED IN WHITE MIST.
I WAS FLOATING THROUGH THE
PLACE, BUT ONLY WITH MY HEAD.
AND I NOTICED MANY OTHER
DEMON HEADS...
ALL WITH TERRIBLE EXPRESSIONS ON
THEIR FACES.
>> THEY MUST HAVE BEEN DEMONS
WHO WERE BEHEADED BY
HAKUDOUSHI.
>> AND WHEN I DOVE UNDER
THE MIST, I SAW SOMETHING
EXTRAORDINARY--GIANT BONES.
>> YOU SAW GIANT BONES?
>> YES.
BY THAT I MEAN THERE WAS AN
ENORMOUS SKELETON STILL CLAD IN
MAGNIFICENT ARMOR.
AND THERE WERE LOTS OF OTHER
SKELETONS, TOO.
I SUPPOSE I MUST HAVE BEEN IN
THE WORLD OF THE AFTERLIFE.
>> PA!
>> HMM?
HUH?
RIGHT.
THANK YOU FOR SAVING ME.
>> OH, SESSHOMARU, THANKS SO
MUCH FOR...
AH!
HMM.
HE LEFT WITHOUT A WORD.
>> WHAT WAS TENSEIGA
TRYING TO TELL ME?
WAS IT A SIGN TO ADVISE ME THAT
THE PLACE THE DEMON DESCRIBED IS
SOMEHOW INVOLVED?
>> YOU TAKE CARE, SHIPPO.
>> I'M GLAD IT ALL WORKED OUT.
>> I CAN'T THANK YOU ENOUGH FOR
ALL YOUR HELP.
I'LL NEVER FORGET YOU
OR YOUR FRIENDS.
>> UH, I WON'T FORGET YOU,
EITHER.
BE HAPPY WITH YOUR PA, KANTA.
HUH?
>> THANKS FOR EVERYTHING YOU DID
FOR ME AND MY SON.
>> SURE THING.
YOU TAKE CARE, PAPA!
>> SHIPPO, HE'S REMEMBERING
HIS FATHER.
>> THAT PLACE THAT KANTA'S
FATHER SAW...
I WONDER IF HAKUDOUSHI ALREADY
KNOWS ABOUT IT.
>> YEAH.
>> WHERE COULD IT BE, THOUGH,
THIS PLACE THAT'S COVERED
IN WHITE MIST AND STREWN
WITH GIANT BONES?
>> I THINK I MIGHT HAVE BEEN TO
THAT PLACE ONCE BEFORE ACTUALLY.
>> WHAT?
>> ARE YOU SAYING YOU KNOW
SOMETHING ABOUT IT?
>> YEAH.
>> HMM.
INUYASHA'S THINKING THE SAME
THING THAT I AM.
WHITE MIST AND GIANT BONES.
THE BORDER BETWEEN THIS WORLD
AND THE NEXT.
THE GRAVE OF INUYASHA'S FATHER.
>> [SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> THE LAST SACRED JEWEL SHARD
IS LOCATED AT THE GRAVESIDE OF
INUYASHA'S FATHER AT THE BORDER
BETWEEN THIS LIFE AND THE NEXT.
>> HUH.
TIME TO VISIT THE OLD MAN'S
GRAVE, HUH?
>> UNFORTUNATELY THE BLACK PEARL
WE USED TO ENTER THE GRAVESITE
CAN'T BE USED AGAIN.
>> ARGH!
ISN'T THERE SOME OTHER WAY IN?
WHAT?
A GUY NAMED HOSENKI KNOWS THE
WAY AND CAN HELP US OUT?
>> NEXT TIME, HOSENKI
AND THE LAST SHARD.
>> I'LL TAKE IT BY FORCE
IF I HAVE TO!