- ARGH!
WHAT'S ALL THIS?
- BY THE TIME WE'D MADE IT
TO NARAKU'S CASTLE,
THE MEMBERS OF THE WOLF DEMON
TRIBE HAD ALREADY BEEN SLAIN.
- WHAT?
- [GRUNTING]
- HMM? AH!
AAH!
- [GASP]
IT'S HIM!
- KOGA'S HERE.
NARAKU HAD LAIN A TRAP.
KOGA WENT AFTER INUYASHA,
BELIEVING BY MISTAKE
THAT HE WAS RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE MURDER OF HIS COMRADES.
KOGA'S RIGHT ARM GLOWED,
BUT NOT FROM THE SACRED
JEWEL SHARD EMBEDDED WITHIN.
IT BLAZED FROM THE FEROCITY
WITH WHICH HE ATTACKED INUYASHA.
- THIS SHOULD KEEP YOU OCCUPIED
FOR SOME TIME.
- HMM.
- NARAKU CERTAINLY HAS A LOVE
FOR THESE ELABORATE SETUPS.
- HE HAS THE SHORT-TEMPERED ONES
FIGHT OUTSIDE,
AND THEN HE HAS BOTH OF US
DEALING WITH THIS DEMON PUPPET?
WHAT DOES HE TAKE US FOR?
- WE MUSTN'T LET OUR GUARD DOWN.
WE'RE IN NARAKU'S CASTLE.
WHO KNOWS
WHAT TRAPS MIGHT BE SET?
- IT'S BEEN ONE TRAP
AFTER ANOTHER.
I'M GROWING TIRED OF
ALL THESE DECEPTIONS!
[GRUNTING]
- SHALL WE TEACH THEM A LESSON?
UNH! OH!
- THIS IS
BUT A MEASLY DEMON PUPPET.
WE'LL SHOW THEM HOW USELESS
IT IS AGAINST OUR STRENGTH.
- HUNH!
- [GRUNTING]
- DAMN IT.
WHERE THE HECK IS HE GETTING
ALL THIS POWER FROM?
- UNH!
- DID YOU SEE THAT?
THE ROOF WAS BLOWN OFF!
HIS RIGHT ARM POSSESSES
SOME KIND OF SUPER STRENGTH.
- WE HAVE TO THINK OF SOMETHING
QUICKLY TO STOP HIM.
IF ONLY HE KNEW IT WAS NARAKU
WHO KILLED HIS MEN,
NOT INUYASHA.
- THAT FILTHY MUTT.
YOU WON'T LIVE TO REGRET THIS!
- [GRUNTING]
- KIRARA!
- UNH!
- NICE WORK, KIRARA.
- THANKS FOR SAVING US.
- [GROWLING]
- KAGOME.
STAY AWAY FROM HER!
- YOU'RE AT FAULT
FOR TRYING TO ESCAPE.
IF KAGOME IS HARMED,
THEN IT SHOULD BE
ON YOUR HEAD.
- HE INTENDS TO FIGHT ME
TO THE DEATH.
NARAKU LAID THE TRAP,
BUT KOGA'S FORGED HIS OWN FATE.
YOU'VE PUSHED ME FAR ENOUGH!
I'LL TAKE YOU ON!
- PREPARE TO DIE.
IN THE NAME OF MY COMRADES!
- HE'S SO FAST.
[GRUNTING]
- IRON REAPER!
- I'M AFRAID I SCRATCHED YOU
IN PASSING.
- THIS IS SERIOUS.
HE SHATTERED THE BONE
IN MY ARM.
- [BOTH GRUNTING]
- THIS WILL FINISH YOU.
VENGEANCE IS MINE!
- [GROANING]
[SCREAMING]
- INUYASHA.
- AT LAST.
THAT MURDERER'S FINALLY DEAD.
[THUNDER]
NAME YOURSELF.
- WELL DONE, WOLF BOY.
WITH THE SCORE SETTLED,
YOU'RE ABLE TO DIE
WITHOUT ANY REGRETS.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT FROM ME?
- MY NAME IS KAGURA.
I WILL SEE THAT YOU HAVE
ONE FINAL DANCE.
- [GROANING]
- WHAT'S THE MEANING?
MY MEN WERE ALL DEAD.
WHY DO THEY RISE AGAIN?
- TO ATTEND YOUR FINAL DANCE.
IT WOULD KILL THEM TO MISS IT.
- YOU SORCERESS!
WAS IT YOU, THEN,
WHO SLAUGHTERED MY FRIENDS?
- I WONDER.
IT SLIPPED MY MIND.
- [GRUNTING]
- I'LL KILL YOU, SORCERESS!
ARGH!
I CAN'T MOVE.
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO ME?
- HA HA HA!
THE JEWEL SHARD IN YOUR ARM HAS
FINALLY RELEASED ITS POISON.
NOW IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO DIE.
- [GROANING]
- YOU ARE UNABLE TO MOVE.
THAT SACRED JEWEL
IN YOUR ARM IS
AN IMITATION MADE
FROM A CRYSTALLIZED POISON
AND A PARALYZING MIASMA.
THAT LEAPING AROUND MADE
YOUR BLOOD PUMP FASTER
AND SPED UP THE SPREAD
OF THE POISON.
- WENCH!
- NOW THAT YOU'RE PARALYZED,
I SHALL HELP MYSELF TO
YOUR TRUE JEWEL SHARDS.
SO, THAT MUST BE
THE SACRED ARROW.
- LOOK OUT!
- KAGOME, ARE YOU HURT?
- NO, I THINK I'M OK.
UGH.
- NOT VERY IMPRESSIVE.
UNFORTUNATELY, I CANNOT ALLOW
YOU TO CONTINUE INTERFERING.
HUH?
- UNH...
I WON'T LET YOU HURT KAGOME.
I'M THE ONE YOU SHOULD BE
COMING AFTER, NOT HER.
- STILL ALIVE, ARE WE NOW?
WOLF BOY, IT APPEARS
YOU DIDN'T COMPLETE THE JOB.
- INUYASHA.
- HUMPH!
YOU'RE KIDDING YOURSELF
IF YOU THINK THAT PUNY WOLF CUB
COULD DO ME IN
WITH THIS MEAGER ATTACK.
- OH, PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
THEN YOU ARE
UP TO A DUEL WITH ME?
- I'LL TAKE YOU ON,
BUT I WARN YOU,
YOU'RE NOT GONNA DIE QUICKLY.
TAINTING ME WITH THE BLOOD
OF THE WOLF DEMONS
AND SETTING THAT FOOL ON ME
WAS UNFORGIVABLE.
BUT EVEN MORE INFURIATING
IS THE REEK OF NARAKU
THAT CLOAKS YOU.
- NARAKU?
- [GRUNTING]
JUST THE THOUGHT
OF THAT BEAST IS ENOUGH
TO GIVE ME THE STRENGTH TO MOVE
MY WOUNDED BODY.
ARGH!
-[GRUNTING]
- THAT SMALL LEVEL OF WIND POWER
WAS ENOUGH
TO PUSH BACK
THE TETSUSAIGA.
WITH JUST ONE ABLE ARM,
I CAN ONLY DRAW HALF
THE SWORD'S POWER.
- I AM THE WIND SORCERESS.
THE WIND IN THIS CASTLE IS
ENTIRELY UNDER MY CONTROL.
[WIND BLOWING]
DANCE OF THE DRAGON!
- [GROANING]
HER WIND ATTACKS ARE CREATED
FROM HER DEMONIC POWER.
THE POINT WHERE THE WINDS
COLLIDE IS THE WIND SCAR,
AND THAT'S WHERE TETSUSAIGA
CAN ATTAIN ITS GREATEST POWER.
I CAN DESTROY HER
IF ONLY I CAN SLICE
THROUGH THE WIND SCAR.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT'S WRONG?
I CAN'T SEE THE WIND SCAR
AROUND KAGURA.
HUH?
- I AM THE WIND SORCERESS.
THE WIND IN THIS CASTLE IS
ENTIRELY UNDER MY CONTROL.
- IF WHAT SHE CLAIMS IS TRUE,
THEN MY WIND IS
UNDER HER CONTROL!
- SOMETHING IS WRONG
WITH INUYASHA.
HIS RIGHT ARM ISN'T MOVING!
- STAND BACK.
I'LL SNAG HER.
- UNFORTUNATELY,
HER AIM IS PATHETIC.
- THAT'S KAGOME'S SACRED ARROW.
KAGURA'S DEMON WIND
IS BEING DRIVEN OFF.
EXCELLENT!
THERE IS A WAY TO CREATE
THE WIND SCAR, THEN.
KAGOME!
SHOOT ME WITH YOUR ARROW!
- HUH?
- ASK QUESTIONS LATER.
JUST HURRY AND SHOOT!
- WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
INUYASHA, YOU MIGHT THINK
YOU'RE INVINCIBLE,
BUT IF MY ARROW HITS YOU,
YOU COULD DIE!
I'LL JUST HAVE TO TRUST
IN HIS JUDGMENT.
MMMPH!
- UNH!
[GROANING]
- [GASP]
IMPOSSIBLE!
KAGOME'S SACRED ARROW IS
PURIFYING MY WIND POWERS.
- JUST AS I THOUGHT.
THE WIND HAS DISAPPEARED.
- SUCH A FOOL.
I ONLY NEED TO CREATE MORE.
- WHEN THE TWO WINDS APPEAR
ONCE AGAIN AND MEET,
THEN I WILL SEE THE WIND SCAR.
GRR....AAH!
DIE!
- [GASP]
THE WIND SCAR.
[GASP]
UNH!
- THAT SCAR...
THAT CAN'T BE.
[SMACK]
- UNH!
- THE CASTLE IS DISAPPEARING!
- IT WAS JUST AN ILLUSION, TOO.
- INUYASHA,
ARE YOU HURT?
- WHERE'S THE SORCERESS GONE?
- I LET HER GET AWAY.
MY RIGHT ARM WAS
PRACTICALLY USELESS,
AND THAT'S WHY I WASN'T ABLE
TO FINISH HER OFF.
- KOGA!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- [GROANING]
- [PANTING]
- HIS SKIN IS CHANGING COLOR!
THE POISON
FROM THE COUNTERFEIT SHARD
IS SPREADING!
- WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
WE'VE GOTTA ACT FAST,
OR HE'LL DIE.
- YOU CAN'T TOUCH HIM.
THE BARRIER AROUND HIS ARM IS
SO STRONG
THAT IT DEFLECTED YOUR HAND.
- WE HAVE TO DO SOMETHING FAST.
- LET ME BE, KAGOME.
I TRIED TO MURDER INUYASHA.
- IT WASN'T YOUR FAULT.
NARAKU TRICKED YOU, KOGA.
INUYASHA HAD NO DESIRE
TO SETTLE THINGS THIS WAY.
INUYASHA.
- IT SEEMS WE WERE BOTH DECEIVED
BY NARAKU'S SCHEME.
IF YOU CAN HANG ON TO LIFE,
THERE IS A WAY TO SAVE YOU.
HOLD OUT YOUR ARM.
I WILL CUT IT
AND THE COUNTERFEIT JEWEL OFF.
- NO!
THERE HAS TO BE ANOTHER WAY!
DON'T JUST HACK
THE GUY'S ARM OFF, INUYASHA.
- WAIT A MINUTE.
WE CAN'T TOUCH
THE POISON'S BARRIER,
BUT, KAGOME,
ISN'T THE SACRED ARROW
ABLE TO BREAK THE BARRIER?
- [GROANING]
- KAGURA MURDERED MY COMRADES.
I SWEAR I SHALL TAKE HER LIFE
WITH MY OWN HANDS...
AND THAT OF NARAKU.
- UNH...
- [WHINING]
- HEY, DO YOU THINK
THAT KOGA IS GONNA BE ALL RIGHT?
- YOU NEEDN'T WORRY.
HE HAS A VERY STRONG WILL.
HE'D PROBABLY PREFER IT
IF WE LET HIM BE.
- UNLIKE ANY OF US,
I DON'T THINK
KOGA HAS EVER BEEN DECEIVED
BY NARAKU BEFORE.
- TRUE ENOUGH.
NOW, LET'S SEE EXACTLY
HOW STRONG THE OTHER'S WILL IS.
IT SEEMS HE HAS FALLEN ASLEEP.
- EVEN ONE AS STRONG AS INUYASHA
WOULD BE FATIGUED
AFTER SUCH A BATTLE.
- LET'S LET HIM REST
AND REGAIN HIS STRENGTH.
- THE SORCERESS HAD
A SPIDER MARK ON HER BACK,
AS DOES NARAKU.
WHAT STRANGE CONNECTION COULD
THE TWO OF THEM HAVE?
- IT SEEMS SHE SHARES
A SECRET WITH NARAKU.
MYSTERIOUS.
[WIND BLOWING]
- UNH!
NARAKU, WHERE ARE YOU?
UNH!
- 50 YEARS AGO,
IN ORDER TO STEAL
THE SACRED JEWEL,
NARAKU TRICKED INUYASHA
AND KIKYO
INTO BETRAYING ONE ANOTHER.
- HUH?
UNH!
- DIE, INUYASHA!
- NOW HE GATHERS
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS,
AND AS HE DOES SO,
HIS EVIL POWER GROWS.
MIROKU SUFFERS UNDER NARAKU'S
CURSED WIND TUNNEL
IN HIS RIGHT HAND.
ONE DAY, THE TUNNEL THREATENS
TO DEVOUR MIROKU'S VERY BEING.
HE MUST DESTROY NARAKU
BEFORE THAT HAPPENS.
SANGO'S FATHER AND FELLOW
DEMON SLAYERS WERE KILLED
BEFORE HER VERY EYES.
NARAKU HAD PLAYED A FOUL TRICK,
POSSESSING
SANGO'S BROTHER KOHAKU
AND SETTING HIM AGAINST HER.
IT WAS ALSO NARAKU
WHO GAVE
THE DEADLY POISON INSECTS
TO SESSHOMARU,
CONTROLLED ROYAKAN,
AND TRICKED SANGO
INTO FIGHTING INUYASHA.
- [GROWLING]
- [GRUNTING]
NARAKU, THE DESPICABLE COWARD
WHO NEVER SULLIES HIS OWN HANDS.
SOMEDAY WE WILL GET HIM.
- HMM?
- NARAKU!
- KAGURA.
SO, YOU SURVIVED THE BATTLE,
DID YOU?
- HOW DARE YOU?
YOU DECEIVED ME!
YOU NEVER TOLD ME
ABOUT THE POWER
OF INUYASHA'S SWORD.
- AH, THE SWORD THAT SLICES
THROUGH THE WIND SCAR.
I WONDERED HOW POWERFUL
IT WAS.
SEEING AS YOU CAME BACK ALIVE,
IT COULDN'T BE
ALL THAT FORMIDABLE.
- YOU ADMIT DECEIVING ME, THEN?
YOU AUDACIOUS FOOL!
THAT'S...
[GASP]
[MOANING]
- DO NOT FORGET,
KAGURA,
I HOLD YOUR HEART RIGHT HERE
IN MY VERY HANDS.
- NARAKU, DAMN YOU.
- IT WOULD BE SIMPLE TO TURN YOU
BACK INTO YOUR ORIGINAL FORM.
NEVER FORGET THIS, KAGURA.
YOU WERE CREATED
FROM A PART OF ME.
YOU'RE NOTHING MORE
THAN MY ESSENCE.
[HEART BEATING]
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
- WE MEET UP WITH A GIRL
NAMED KOHARU WHO KNOWS MIROKU.
WHAT? YOU ASKED HER TO BEAR
YOUR CHILD WHEN SHE WAS ONLY 11?
YOU PERVERT, MIROKU!
WE HAVE TO GET AWAY
FROM THIS VILLAGE
AND FAST, FOR KOHARU'S SAKE.
WAIT. SOMETHING'S WRONG.
THE VILLAGERS ARE ATTACKING US.
I'LL BET THAT FEMALE DEMON
HAS SOMETHING TO DO WITH IT.
NEXT TIME, "KAGURA'S DANCE
AND KANNA'S MIRROR."
SEE YOU SOON!