>> HERE WE COME.
IT'S THE START OF "INUYASHA."
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL THE
SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY NARAKU WITH
MY TETSAIGA.
>> NARAKU'S ENORMOUS DEMONIC
AURA DISAPPEARED INTO THE
NORTHEAST.
JUST BEYOND, A MYSTERIOUS
SPECTER APPEARS THAT IS NEITHER
HUMAN NOR DEMON.
A NEW BATTLE IS ABOUT TO BEGIN.
>> IT'S UP TO ALL OF US.
>> TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FEUDAL FAIRY TALE, "INUYASHA."
[WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> OXTIGER.
THAT'S THIS WAY, IF I'M NOT
MISTAKEN.
>> THE ENORMOUS EVIL DEMONIC
AURA FLEW OFF IN THE DIRECTION
OF THE OXTIGER, THE NORTHEAST.
EVERYONE SEEMS PRETTY SURE IT
BELONGS TO NARAKU.
>> DAMN THAT NARAKU AND HIS
LITTLE TRICKS.
WHERE COULD HE HAVE DISAPPEARED
TO?
>> I'M GUESSING HE PROBABLY WENT
INTO HIDING BECAUSE YOU MANAGED
TO BREAK THROUGH HIS BARRIER.
>> I KIND OF DOUBT IT.
KNOWING NARAKU, THAT CAN'T BE
THE ONLY REASON.
>> HANG ON A MINUTE.
>> WHAT IS IT, INUYASHA?
>> WHAT IF NARAKU IS TRYING TO
LURE US TOWARD HIS DEMONIC AURA
AND INTO ANOTHER ONE OF HIS
LITTLE TRAPS?
WE COULD BE PLAYING RIGHT INTO
HIS HANDS.
>> YES, IT'S POSSIBLE.
>> IT WOULDN'T BE THE FIRST TIME
HE'S TRICKED US, THAT'S FOR
SURE.
>> DO YOU THINK HE'LL TRY AND
PULL SOMETHING IF WE KEEP ON
HIS TRAIL AND MANAGE TO GET
CLOSE TO HIM?
>> HMM.
>> WHAT AWAITS US?
THAT'S WHAT WORRIES ME.
[PANTING]
THE DEMONS ARE RUNNING AWAY.
>> THIS SCENT--I KNOW IT.
>> ELDER, OUR DENS IN THE VALLEY
HAVE ALL BEEN DESTROYED.
>> OUR BURROWS HAVE BEEN BURNED
OUT AS WELL.
>> THE BEAST SEEMS TO BE
DEVOURING EVERYTHING IN ITS
PATH.
HALF OF THE DEMONS ON THE
MOUNTAIN HAVE ALREADY BECOME
ITS PREY.
>> OUR FANGS AND CLAWS ARE
USELESS AGAINST IT.
>> WE DON'T STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST THAT SPECTER
UNLESS WE HAVE THE
POWER OF A SACRED JEWEL SHARD.
>> GRANDPA, THE BEAST IS COMING.
>> SO THEY ATE EVERYTHING
IN SIGHT ON THE OTHER SIDE OF
THE MOUNTAINS, COME DOWN TO THE
BORDERS.
>> OUR COMRADES HAVE BEEN
DEVOURED.
>> KOGA'S THE ONLY ONE WHO CAN
POSSIBLY STAND UP TO IT.
>> DAMN IT ALL!
IF ONLY AYAME HAD GRABBED HIM BY
THE SCRUFF OF HIS NECK AND
DRAGGED HIM HOME TO US.
>> [GASP]
>> THE DEMON'S COME!
>> RUN FOR IT!
>> IT'LL EAT US ALIVE!
>> [GROWLING]
>> GRANDPA, LET'S SPLIT UP, OK?
>> AAH!
>> WHY ARE THE DEMONS ATTACKING
US?
>> THEY'RE HUNGRY.
THE BEAST HAS DEVOURED THEIR
PREY.
>> WE FLEE THE SPECTER ONLY TO
BE EATEN BY DEMONS!
>> NO, YOU DON'T!
OK, EVERYONE, HURRY AND GET
ACROSS THE RIVER.
HOW COULD THE BEASTS HAVE
DESCENDED THE MOUNTAIN SO
QUICKLY?
UH!
>> A GIANT DEMONIC AURA PASSED
OVERHEAD?
>> YEAH, AND THE WHOLE AREA IS
TALKING ABOUT IT.
>> NO ONE HAS SEEN IT SINCE,
THOUGH.
>> IT DISAPPEARED.
>> YEAH.
>> WHERE TO?
>> NO ONE KNOWS.
>> THE RIVER UPSTREAM FLOWS TO
THE MOUNTAINS IN THE NORTH.
WE'VE COME CLOSE TO AYAME AND
THE ELDER.
AYAME SAID THE DEMON HAD COME,
AND EVERYONE WAS NERVOUS.
THAT'S WHY SHE CAME TO TAKE ME
BACK.
BUT I CHASED HER AWAY.
I HAVE A BAD FEELING ABOUT THIS.
BLOOD.
>> [GASPS]
>> ELDER!
>> GRANDPA!
>> FORGIVE ME, DEAR.
I WAS JUST A BIT TIRED.
I WAS CARELESS.
>> GRANDPA, DON'T PUSH YOURSELF.
STAY STILL.
>> [GROWLING]
>> THEY'RE CLOSING IN ON US!
WE HAVE TO MOVE!
>> I'LL BE A DECOY AND ATTRACT
THE DEMONS TO COME AFTER ME.
MAKE YOUR ESCAPE WHILE YOU STILL
CAN.
>> WE CAN'T DO THAT.
YOU'LL NEVER MAKE IT OUT ALIVE.
>> PROTECT THE ELDER AND TRACK
DOWN KOGA.
AND DEFEAT THAT BEAST.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
I WON'T GET KILLED BY ANY
PIPSQUEAK DEMONS LIKE THEM.
>> NO, WAIT!
DON'T GO!
PLEASE COME BACK!
COME BACK HERE!
HE'S IN TROUBLE, AND HE'S
WOUNDED AS WELL.
>> LET'S GO, AYAME.
>> HUH?
>> WE DON'T HAVE ANY TIME TO
DELAY.
YOU MUST HONOR THE ELDER'S
WISHES AND GO.
>> [PANTING]
>> [GROWLING]
>> AAH!
AAH!
>> GET OFF HIM!
>> KOGA!
>> THANK YOU.
SO YOU'RE FROM ONE OF THE TRIBES
TO THE SOUTH?
>> ELDER, YOU HAVE THE GIFT OF
SPEECH.
>> YOU WENT TO THE TROUBLE OF
SAVING ME, BUT I FEAR MY END IS
AT HAND.
>> LISTEN, AREN'T YOU AN ELDER
OF THE NORTHERN MOUNTAINS?
>> AYAME CAME FROM THE NORTH TO
GET KOGA NOT LONG AGO.
>> KOGA?
IS KOGA HERE WITH US?
>> I AM KOGA.
>> I AM GLAD I HAD A CHANCE TO
MEET YOU, KOGA.
WE ABANDONED OUR TERRITORIES AND
DESCENDED FROM THE NORTHERN
MOUNTAINS, AS DID THE DEMONS
THAT ATTACKED US.
>> YOU FLED FROM YOUR LAND?
>> FLED FROM WHAT?
>> FROM A SPECTER.
>> SPECTER?
>> IT CAME FROM FAR BEYOND OUR
NORTHERN BORDER.
IT IS NEITHER A DEMON NOR A
HUMAN, YET ITS BODY REEKED OF
DEAD MEN AND GRAVEYARD SOIL.
AND IT STARTED TO EAT THE DEMONS
CLOSE BY.
>> WHAT DO WE DO NOW, KOGA?
>> I'M GOING.
>> WHERE?
>> TO FIND THE SPECTER THAT HE
SPOKE OF?
>> WE'RE ALREADY PRETTY BUSY
SEARCHING FOR NARAKU.
>> THIS SPECTER HAS NOTHING TO
DO WITH US.
>> WE CAN'T IGNORE THAT OUR
BRETHREN WERE SLAUGHTERED.
THE LEAST WE CAN DO IS SEE WHAT
THIS IS ABOUT.
BESIDES, THE MUTT'S HEADED THIS
WAY, SO THERE MUST BE SOMETHING
TO IT.
>> INUYASHA?
>> I'D KNOW THE STENCH OF THAT
MANGY MUTT ANYWHERE.
I AIN'T GONNA STAND AROUND AND
BE UPSTAGED BY HIM.
LET'S GO.
>> WAIT UP, KOGA!
>> IT SMELLS OF WOLVES HERE.
>> IT DOES?
>> THERE'S ONLY ONE WOLF AROUND
WITH THIS DISTINCT SMELL.
IT HAS TO BE KOGA.
>> IF YOUR SENSES ARE CORRECT
AND IT IS INDEED HIM, THEN HE
MUST BE HEADED FOR THE NORTHEAST
JUST AS WE ARE.
>> I WONDER IF HE'S COME ACROSS
SOME KIND OF CLUE.
>> DID SOMEONE MENTION KOGA?
>> THAT VOICE IS FAMILIAR.
>> UH!
WHOA!
>> YOU AGAIN.
>> AYAME, IT'S YOU!
>> AYAME?
>> INDEED.
>> SHE'S THE WOLF DEMON GIRL
FROM KOGA'S TRIBE WHO WAS
JEALOUS OF YOU, KAGOME.
>> UH, HERE.
>> THANK YOU.
I THOUGHT YOU WENT BACK TO THE
NORTHERN MOUNTAINS.
>> I DID, BUT--
>> BUT WHAT?
>> WE FLED WHEN THE BEAST CAME
AFTER US.
>> BEAST?
>> A BEAST WHO DEVOURS DEMONS.
>> I DON'T LIKE THE SOUND OF
THAT.
>> MASTER, PLEASE LISTEN TO ME.
WE MUST REACH THE MOUNTAINS, OR
WE'LL BE FORCED TO SLEEP OUT IN
THE OPEN.
SHOULDN'T WE TURN BACK TOWARD
THE VILLAGE AND FIND AN INN?
>> OH, DON'T BE SUCH A COWARD.
COME.
>> I HEARD A GIANT DEMON HAS
BEEN APPEARING IN THIS AREA IN
THE PAST FEW DAYS, MASTER.
>> SO WHAT IF THERE IS?
I SHALL SUPPRESS ANY DEMON WITH
MY SPIRITUAL POWERS.
HA HA HA!
>> AAH!
UH!
>> [GROWLING]
>> OH, NO, LOOK!
A DEMON-EATING DEMON!
MASTER, USE YOUR POWERS TO
DEFEAT HIM!
>> [CHANTING]
I CAN'T!
>> WAIT FOR ME, MASTER!
>> A SPECTER?
>> THAT'S RIGHT, AND IT DOESN'T
APPEAR TO BE EITHER DEMON OR
HUMAN.
>> IT CAME FROM--FROM THE
NORTHEAST.
>> FROM THE NORTHEAST?
THE DIRECTION OF THE OXTIGER.
>> IN NO TIME AT ALL, THE
SPECTER DEVOURED ALL THE DEMONS
AND SPIRITS THAT LIVED IN THE
MOUNTAINS.
THEN IT DESCENDED TO THE BORDERS
OF OUR OWN TERRITORY.
>> SO MANY OF OUR FRIENDS WERE
DEVOURED.
>> THE WOLF DEMON TRIBE ISN'T A
WEAK TRIBE, THOUGH.
>> THE SPECTER IS THE SIZE OF
SMALL MOUNTAIN.
>> HOW COULD THERE BE SUCH A
CREATURE?
>> IT'S BEEN SAID SINCE ANCIENT
TIMES THAT MEN WHO DIED WITH
UNFINISHED BUSINESS TURN INTO
SUCH CREATURES.
THEY NEVER LET GO OF THEIR
HATRED.
>> THERE AREN'T MANY WHO COULD
DO THIS--RESURRECT A TERRIFYING
CREATURE THAT WOULD DEVOUR
DEMONS WITHOUT ANY HESITATION?
>> IT HAS GOT TO BE HIM.
>> NARAKU.
>> I MUST LEAVE NOW AND TRY TO
TAKE THE ELDER AND THE
REMAINING WOLF DEMON CLAN TO
SAFETY, BUT--
>> SAY NO MORE.
IF WE EVER SEE KOGA, WE'LL TELL
HIM THAT YOU AND THE REST OF
YOUR CLAN WERE ABLE TO ESCAPE.
DON'T YOU WORRY.
>> KAGOME, THANKS FOR ALL YOUR
HELP.
>> BE CAREFUL, AYAME!
>> BYE! TAKE CARE!
ONE MORE THING.
THE SPECTER SMELLS OF CORPSES
AND GRAVEYARD SOIL.
>> [GROWLING AND CHOMPING]
>> MASTER KYOKOTSU.
THE SACRED JEWEL SHARDS ARE
CLOSE.
THE ONES WHO POSSESS IT ARE
APPROACHING.
>> I SEE.
IT WAS WORTH HEADING OVER THERE
BEFORE MY BROTHERS DO THE SAME.
KOHAKU, WAS IT NOT?
YOU ARE FREE TO LEAVE.
THAT IS ALL.
BUT I WILL HAVE THAT SHARD ON
YOUR BACK!
UH!
>> I'D ADVISE AGAINST SUCH
DECEIT.
>> [BUZZING]
>> HMM.
SO YOU'RE UNDER HIS PROTECTION.
VERY WELL, THEN.
I'LL LEAVE YOU ALONE.
I VALUE MY LIFE, ESPECIALLY
SINCE I'VE BEEN RESURRECTED
FROM THE GRAVE.
HA HA HA HA!
>> [WHINES]
>> KEEP YOUR HANDS OFF MY
WOLVES!
>> HA HA HA!
IS IT YOU?
ARE YOU THE ONE WHO HAS THE
SACRED JEWEL SHARDS, HMM?
>> HE'S HUGE.
>> I WILL HAVE THE JEWEL SHARDS
AND YOUR LIFE.
>> W-WHAT DID HE SAY?
>> LOOK AT THE SIZE OF THAT
THING.
>> SO YOU'RE THE SPECTER I'VE
HEARD ABOUT, JUST AS THE WOLF
DEMON TRIBE ELDER SAID.
YOU REEK.
YOU STINK OF CORPSES AND
GRAVEYARD SOIL.
YOU'RE NEITHER HUMAN NOR DEMON!
>> [GROWLS]
I STILL SMELL?
IT'S BEEN SOME TIME SINCE I
EMERGED FROM MY GRAVE.
>> HE DIDN'T BLINK AN EYE.
>> IS HE REALLY A SPECTER?
>> I'LL HAVE TO EAT MORE AND PUT
ON MUSCLES.
YOU, OVER THERE.
YOU WILL BECOME ONE WITH THE
GREAT KYOKOTSU!
>> NO CHANCE!
DAMN YOU TO HELL!
>> UH!
>> HOW DARE YOU LUST AFTER MY
BLOOD AND THAT OF MY COMRADES.
>> I SEE IN YOUR LEGS--YOU HAVE
SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL IN
YOUR LEGS?
>> KYOKOTSU, YOU SAY?
TELL ME, JUST WHAT KIND OF BEAST
ARE YOU?
I DON'T SMELL NARAKU ON THIS
ONE, SO I'M CERTAIN THAT HE
WASN'T BORN OUT OF NARAKU'S
FLESH.
>> [GROWLS]
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, WHAT AM I?
I AM HUMAN.
ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
>> NO WAY.
>> IMPOSSIBLE.
>> SO YOU'RE AN AVERAGE MAN WHO
HAPPENED TO EMERGE ALIVE FROM
THE GRAVE.
>> THANKS TO THIS SACRED JEWEL
SHARD, I FEEL MUCH BETTER THAN
THE FIRST TIME I WAS ALIVE.
>> THE SACRED JEWEL SHARD--A
REAL ONE.
DAMN IT!
HOW DID YOU GET AHOLD OF THAT?
>> AND WHAT IF I TOLD YOU?
YOU'RE STILL GOING TO END UP IN
MY BELLY.
>> YOU'RE IN SERIOUS TROUBLE IF
YOU THINK YOU CAN CAPTURE ME
WITH SUCH CLUMSY MOVES.
>> THIS IS HOW I DEAL WITH QUICK
ONES LIKE YOU.
>> NICE TRY. BAD AIM.
AND AIM STRAIGHT IF YOU'RE GONNA
HIT ME.
MISSED AGAIN.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> KOGA.
>> DEAD MAN OR NOT,
YOUR TOUGH-GUY ACT
ISN'T FOOLING ANYONE.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> AS IF THOSE TACTICS WOULD
WORK ON ME AGAIN.
>> [GRUNTING]
>> I'LL SEND YOU BACK TO YOUR
GRAVE, DEAD MAN!
>> LOOK, KAGOME.
THAT LIGHT.
>> THE GLOW OF SACRED JEWEL.
>> YES, BUT WHY IS THE LIGHT SO
BRIGHT?
>> COULD NARAKU AND KOGA BE
FIGHTING?
>> NO.
I'M NOT PICKING UP NARAKU'S
SCENT.
>> OVER THERE.
>> THE GLOW OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> THE JEWEL?
COULD IT BE?
KOGA!
>> KOGA!
>> TOO BAD ABOUT YOUR LOUSY AIM,
YOU CLUMSY CORPSE!
>> UH!
>> LOOK! HE DID IT!
>> KOGA.
>> HMM.
THAT'S A PAIN IN THE NECK.
UH!
>> SO YOU THOUGHT YOU'D BEAT ME?
>> HE'S STILL ALIVE.
>> KOGA!
KOGA, LOOK OUT!
>> SO MUCH FOR YOUR ASSUMPTIONS.
NOW I'LL DEVOUR YOU, JEWEL SHARD
AND ALL.
>> OH, YOU THINK SO?
DEVOUR THIS!
>> HA HA HA!
DOESN'T HURT ONE LITTLE BIT.
>> IT'S ALL OVER.
>> MY SACRED JEWEL SHARD!
UH!
[BUZZING]
>> KOGA!
>> KOGA, WHERE ARE YOU?
>> ARE YOU ALIVE?
>> HUH?
THOSE ARE NARAKU'S POISONOUS
INSECTS.
SO HE WAS THE ONE MANIPULATING
KYOKOTSU.
>> MERE BONES.
>> I GUESS THE SACRED JEWEL
SHARD BROUGHT HIM BACK TO LIFE.
>> THANK YOU, KOGA.
YOU AVENGED MY COMRADES AND
FRIENDS.
THOSE WHO DIED CAN NOW REST IN
PEACE.
>> SO NARAKU'S DEMONIC AURA
DISAPPEARED TOWARD THE
NORTHEAST.
>> YES.
THAT'S WHAT KAGOME SAID.
>> I SEE.
>> GOOD-BYE.
>> BE CAREFUL, AYAME.
>> THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT KAGOME
SAID.
>> SAME AS KAGOME, HUH?
>> SO KYOKOTSU IS DEAD, IS HE?
>> YES, MASTER JAKOTSU.
>> SERVES HIM RIGHT, STUPID
FOOL.
WELL, I SUPPOSE KYOKOTSU WAS THE
WEAKEST ONE OF US ALL.
SO WHAT'S HE LIKE?
>> HUH?
>> YOU KNOW, MY OPPONENT, THIS
INUYASHA.
TELL ME, IS HE REALLY HANDSOME?
>> I THINK PERHAPS YOU'D BE THE
BEST JUDGE OF THAT.
>> OH, I CAN'T WAIT.
INUYASHA.
[WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> MERCENARIES WHO HAVE BEEN
EXECUTED FOR THEIR INHUMANE
ACTS.
>> WE ENCOUNTER A GROUP OF
WARRIORS CALLING THEMSELVES
THE BAND OF SEVEN, ONE OF WHOM
CAN MANIPULATE A SWORD THAT
BENDS.
>> HOW DO YOU LIKE THE SWORD OF
JAKOTSU?
>> EVEN WHEN REPELLED, IT
STRIKES BACK JUST LIKE A SNAKE.
>> DAMN!
I CAN'T TELL WHERE THE FANGS
WILL APPEAR.
>> NEXT TIME, "THE BAND OF SEVEN
RESURRECTED."
>> INUYASHA, I WANT TO CUT OFF
THOSE CUTE DOG EARS OF YOURS.