>> HERE WE COME.
IT'S THE START OF "INUYASHA."
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL THE
SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY NARAKU WITH
MY TETSUSAIGA.
>> THE BAND OF 7 HAVE
DISAPPEARED BEYOND THE
SACRED BARRIER.
KOGA AND SESSHOMARU ARRIVE AT
THE BASE OF MOUNT HAKUREI TO
DESTROY NARAKU AND HIS
FOLLOWERS.
>> IT'S UP TO ALL OF US.
>> TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FEUDAL FAIRY TALE.
>> "INUYASHA."
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> YOU'RE MINE NOW!
AAH!
HUH?
ST. HOKUSHIN'S ORNAMENT!
>> AAH!
>> DON'T YOU DARE!
A BARRIER?
HEY, MIROKU, ARE YOU ABSOLUTELY
SURE THAT NARAKU IS HIDING IN
MOUNT HAKUREI?
>> WE'VE DECIDED THAT SANGO AND
I WILL GO SURVEY MOUNT HAKUREI.
>> INUYASHA AND KAGOME, YOU STAY
HERE.
>> JUST CHECK AROUND, BUT DON'T
TAKE ANY UNNECESSARY RISKS, OK?
>> REST ASSURED, THAT'S WHAT WE
INTEND TO DO.
>> I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THIS.
THINK THEY'LL BE ALL RIGHT?
>> WE DON'T REALLY HAVE MUCH
CHOICE EXCEPT TO HAVE FAITH
IN THEM.
[PANTING]
>> HOW ABOUT HERE?
UNH!
DAMN IT, NO LUCK HERE EITHER!
[PANTING]
>> WHAT'S KOGA'S PROBLEM?
HE NEVER LISTENS TO ANYONE.
>> NO?
ONCE HE MAKES UP HIS MIND,
THAT'S IT.
>> THERE HE IS NOW!
KOGA!
WAIT UP, WOULD YOU?
>> YOU'RE SLOW, AS USUAL.
WHAT TOOK YOU TWO SO LONG?
>> YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING.
>> IT'S NOT THAT WE'RE TOO
SLOW, IT'S THAT YOU'RE TOO FAST.
>> WHAT TO DO YOU SAY WE CALL IT
QUITS, KOGA?
>> WE'VE BEEN SEARCHING AROUND
THE MOUNTAIN FOR DAYS NOW, BUT
THERE'S NO WAY TO GET PAST THE
BARRIER.
>> BESIDES, THIS PLACE IS GIVING
ME THE CREEPS.
>> IT CAN'T BE EASY ON YOU
HITTING THAT BARRIER OVER AND
OVER AGAIN.
>> COME ON, KOGA, WHAT DO
YOU SAY?
>> LET'S JUST GIVE UP.
>> SHUT YOUR TRAP!
THE BAND OF 7 IS DEFINITELY
HERE.
I'M GOING TO BUST THROUGH THIS
BARRIER, OUT OF PRIDE.
>> HEH HEH HEH.
>> WELL, WELL, GINKOTSU, IT
SEEMS THEY CAN'T SEE US BEHIND
HERE AFTER ALL.
>> YES.
>> THIS BARRIER IS TURNING OUT
TO BE VERY CONVENIENT.
IT'S QUITE SICKENING, BUT WHY
NOT TAKE ADVANTAGE OF IT?
ALL RIGHT, GINKOTSU, FIRST GO
FOR THE LEGS.
I WANT YOU TO BLOW BOTH OF HIS
LEGS OFF.
>> YES.
>> COME ON, KOGA, AT LEAST THINK
ABOUT IT.
>> I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF YOU TWO
QUITTERS.
THE BAND OF 7 ARE HIDING IN
THERE.
SO HOW ABOUT THIS?
I'M GOING TO FIND THEM AND KILL
THEM ALL MYSELF!
>> OOH, WE'RE SCARED.
>> UNH!
>> UHH!
>> OH!
>> I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU TO BLOW
HIS LEGS OFF.
>> YES.
>> WELL, YOU DIDN'T!
[GROWLING SOFTLY]
>> INUYASHA.
>> WHAT?
>> GETTING ALL IRRITATED ISN'T
GOING TO HELP US ANY.
JUST RELAX, WOULD YOU?
>> WHAT MAKES YOU THINK I'M
IRRITATED?
>> THEN HOW ABOUT GIVING THAT
LEG-BOUNCING THING A REST?
IT'S ANNOYING.
>> HUH?
OH.
>> I WONDER IF THEY'RE OK.
>> HUH?
>> I JUST MEANT, I WONDER IF
SANGO AND MIROKU ARE GOING TO
BE OK ON THEIR OWN.
>> HAH!
ONE THING'S FOR SURE, THEY'RE
A LOT MORE DEPENDABLE THAN
YOU ARE.
>> IDIOT!
I WASN'T SUGGESTING THAT WE
COULDN'T TRUST THEM.
>> OK, THEN WHAT IS IT YOU'RE
ALL WORRIED ABOUT?
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, THIS AND
THAT, AND THIS.
>> HUH?
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN EXACTLY,
THIS AND THAT?
>> I WONDER HOW FAR THIS GOES?
THERE'S NO DEMONIC AURA, NOTHING
OUT OF THE ORDINARY HERE.
HMM.
>> WE WOULDN'T HAVE EVEN THOUGHT
TO CHECK THIS PLACE OUT IF IT
WASN'T FOR WHAT HAPPENED ON
HIJIRI ISLAND.
>> WE HAVE TO BE CAREFUL, TO
KEEP ON OUR GUARD, SANGO.
>> I AGREE.
>> MM-MM.
REMEMBER, KEEP ON YOUR GUARD.
OH, I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS!
JUST ONE LECHEROUS THOUGHT, AND
I'M FEELING SICK TO MY STOMACH.
OH, THE BARRIER OF MOUNT HAKUREI
IS STRONG INDEED TO HAVE SUCH AN
EFFECT ON ME.
>> WHAT DID YOU STOP FOR?
>> NEVER MIND ME, JUST STUMBLED
A BIT.
>> YEAH, WELL, WATCH YOUR STEP.
>> OH!
>> WHERE DID THEY COME FROM?
>> YEAH.
>> SO YOU WERE HIDING BEHIND
THE BARRIER.
>> YES, INDEED, WE CERTAINLY
WERE.
WE'VE BEEN RIGHT BEHIND YOU THIS
WHOLE TIME.
>> YES.
>> LOOKS LIKE OUR SEARCH AROUND
THE MOUNTAIN WASN'T IN VAIN
AFTER ALL.
I'M SURPRISED YOU SHOWED
YOURSELVES, THOUGH.
[CHUCKLES]
>> I SUPPOSE YOU WOULD BE.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO KNOW WHY WE
DID SO?
BECAUSE OF YOUR SHIKON JEWEL
SHARDS!
>> UNH!
THIS IS TROUBLE.
HE GOT MY LEGS ON THE VERY
FIRST SHOT.
I'VE GOT TO PUT AN END TO THIS
FAST!
>> KOGA, YOU OK?
>> STAY BACK, YOU TWO!
>> SURE, OK.
>> THINK HE EVEN STANDS A CHANCE
AGAINST THAT METAL MONSTER?
THAT THING'S DEADLY!
>> THOSE TWO ARE JUST LIKE
KYOKOTSU, RESURRECTED THROUGH
THE POWER OF THE SHIKON SHARDS.
NOW IF I CAN JUST TAKE THE
JEWELS AWAY...
>> ARRH!
>> YOU'RE THROUGH!
UNH!
I'LL GET YOU.
YOU'RE GOING BACK TO THE GRAVE!
>> GO BACK NOW, GINKOTSU.
>> YES.
>> HUH?
WHAT, YOU'RE TAKING OFF?
>> IT'S NOT WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE.
>> WHAT?
>> WE'RE STILL GOING TO DESTROY
YOU, BUT FROM A SAFE DISTANCE.
>> LOOK, THEY VANISHED.
>> HE'S DONE FOR!
HOW CAN HE DEFEAT AN ENEMY HE
CAN'T EVEN SEE?!
OW!
>> KOGA, LET'S GET OUT OF HERE!
WE'RE SITTING DUCKS!
>> I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE!
I KNEW WHAT I WAS GETTING INTO,
BUT NOW WHAT?
THEY'RE DEADLY.
HUH?
I HAVE TO FIND A WAY TO LURE
THEM OUT OF THE BARRIER.
[HEAVY BREATHING]
>> I'M A BIGGER MAN THAN THIS.
NO BARRIER'S GOING TO STOP ME!
UNH!
>> WHAT EXACTLY ARE YOU DOING
BACK THERE?
>> WHO, ME?
WHY, NOT A THING.
>> HMM.
[SIGHS]
>> DAMN IT ALL TO HELL!
I'M NOT GETTING ANYWHERE
WITH THEM!
THOSE THREADS ARE STEEL.
>> THIS IS GETTING WORSE!
>> IF HE GETS CAUGHT IN THOSE
THREADS, KOGA WILL BE DRAGGED
THROUGH THE BARRIER, AND HE'LL
BE DESTROYED!
>> DODGE THIS.
YOU CAN'T LAST FOREVER.
>> UHH!
THAT'S IT.
>> LET'S GET THIS OVER WITH.
TIME TO PUT HIM OUT OF HIS
MISERY.
>> YES.
>> HUH?
UNH!
AAH!
>> HUH?
UNH!
>> AAH!
>> SO, IS HE DEAD?
PERHAPS NOT.
EITHER WAY, I STILL NEED TO GET
THOSE JEWEL SHARDS FROM HIM.
ALL RIGHT, THEN, GINKOTSU,
PROCEED.
>> YES.
>> HE MUST HAVE BEEN BLOWN
TO BITS.
>> NOT SO LUCKY!
YAH!
>> YOU'RE ALIVE!
>> YOU SURE FELL FOR MY PLAN.
YOU'RE NOT GOING BACK BEHIND THE
BARRIER NOW.
>> IT'S A LITTLE EARLY TO BE
CONGRATULATING YOURSELF.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> WELL, YOU SEE, WE HAVE NO
NEED TO ESCAPE FROM YOU,
LITTLE MAN.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO CAN'T GET
AWAY.
>> HEY, HE'S RIGHT!
>> AND BESIDES, HOW MUCH HARM
COULD A WOUNDED WOLF DO TO US?
>> HUH?
HE KNOWS ABOUT MY LEGS.
>> FINISH HIM OFF, GINKOTSU.
>> YES.
>> RIGHT.
I DON'T THINK SO!
WE'LL SEE WHO THE REAL FOOL IS.
THEY HAVE TO BE SOMEWHERE IN HIS
BODY, BUT WHERE?
AAH!
>> DAMN HIM!
HE'S AFTER THE SHARD IN MY NECK.
UHH!
>> RENKOTSU.
>> WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?
>> THAT THING CAN TALK?!
>> HOW DARE YOU!
DAMN YOU TO HELL!
>> GINKOTSU, WHAT ARE YOU..?
>> I STUFFED THE CANNON WITH THE
ARMOR I RIPPED OFF.
>> YES.
>> NO WAY!
YOU SHOULDN'T STILL BE ALIVE.
>> DAMN YOU, FOOL.
>> YES.
>> WHAT?
ARE YOU REALLY GOING TO USE
THOSE, GINKOTSU?
>> YES.
>> HUH?
NOW WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> YES.
YES.
>> NICE GUNS, LOUSY AIM.
I'M RIGHT OVER HERE!
>> YES.
YES.
>> WHAT?!
WHY, YOU--
I'VE HAD JUST ABOUT ENOUGH
OF YOU!
>> YES!
>> AAH!
>> GINKOTSU!
>> LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE THE
LAST ONE.
[GROANING]
>> HUH?
>> I WILL NOT ALLOW RENKOTSU
TO BE KILLED.
>> WHAT?!
>> AAH!
>> HMM?
WHAT IS IT?
SOMETHING THE MATTER?
>> COME ON.
>> WHY?
WHAT'S UP?
>> NEVER MIND, JUST COME.
>> WHERE ARE WE GOING TO, INU--
OW!
>> WAIT!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> THIS IS IT!
I'VE GOT YOU NOW!
YOU'RE PRACTICALLY IN MY HANDS!
UNH!
UHH!
I KNOW I CAN DO THIS!
GET OUT!
GET HER!
NO.
THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING.
>> OK, I'M READY FOR AN
EXPLANATION.
>> HUH?
[NERVOUS LAUGHTER]
[BIRDS SINGING]
>> I REALLY MEAN IT, SUIKOTSU.
DON'T GO TURNING INTO A GOOD
PERSON ON ME IN THE MIDDLE OF
A BATTLE, OK?
>> QUIT YOUR NAGGING.
ISN'T THAT WHY WE'RE MOVING AWAY
FROM THE BARRIER?
TO AVOID ITS INFLUENCE?
DAMN THAT DO-GOOD DOCTOR,
SHOWING UP WHENEVER HE HAS
THE CHANCE.
AFTER ALL I'VE DONE TO SUPPRESS
HIM, TOO.
>> GLAD YOU FEEL THAT WAY.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET THIS PLAN
UNDERWAY, THEN.
>> SAY NO MORE.
>> THEY'RE COMING.
>> AH!
WAIT, LORD SESSHOMARU!
>> WHAT IS THAT?
>> ARE YOU NARAKU'S FOLLOWER?
>> HOW PERCEPTIVE OF YOU.
[HEAVY BREATHING]
>> GINKOTSU.
THAT'S...A SHARD!
I REFUSE TO DIE HERE.
NOT IN A PLACE LIKE THIS.
NEVER!
[GROANS]
>> HEY, WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
WAITING AROUND FOR MIROKU AND
SANGO!
>> WAITING FOR MIROKU AND
SANGO'S NOT GOING TO GET US
ANYWHERE.
THIS PLACE REEKS OF AN
EXPLOSION.
NOT ONLY THAT, BUT BLOOD.
THE BLOOD OF A WOLF DEMON.
[SOBBING]
>> INUYASHA, IT'S YOU.
AND KAGOME.
>> KOGA, HE WAS STRUCK.
>> WHAT?
KOGA!
>> HIS LEGS WERE INJURED IN
THE ATTACK.
>> HE WASN'T ABLE TO GET AWAY.
>> HE MUST HAVE BEEN CAUGHT IN
THE BLAST FIGHTING GINKOTSU.
>> HE ISN'T DEAD, IS HE?
>> DON'T BE SO STUPID.
>> INUYASHA.
>> LISTEN, KOGA IS A WOLF DEMON.
HE WOULDN'T DIE IN A PLACE LIKE
THIS!
COME ON, KOGA, QUIT LYING
AROUND!
GET UP!
>> OH, KOGA!
>> SAY SOMETHING!
>> KOGA!
>> DAMN IT, ONE GOT AWAY ON ME.
>> I'M GLAD YOU'RE OK.
>> KOGA!!
>> SO HE DID SURVIVE.
>> EVERYTHING'S GOING TO BE
ALL RIGHT.
>> SORRY, KAGOME.
I KNOW YOU MUST HAVE BEEN
WORRIED ABOUT ME.
>> HMM?
>> YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
WHAT A RELIEF!
>> KOGA!
>> ALL RIGHT, THAT'S ENOUGH,
SCRAWNY WOLF!
DROP HER HAND RIGHT NOW UNLESS
YOU--
>> INUYASHA.
>> BAND OF 7.
MORE IMPORTANTLY, NARAKU.
BE AFRAID, BECAUSE I'M COMING
FOR YOU.
>> NARAKU SENDS SUIKOTSU AND
JAKOTSU TO KILL SESSHOMARU.
>> CAREFUL, OR YOU'LL HAVE YOUR
HEAD LOPPED OFF!
>> YOU TALK A LOT FOR A DEAD
PERSON.
>> YOU WON'T GET AWAY.
>> AND KIKYO MEETS RENKOTSU.
>> THE FATE OF A DEAD MORTAL.
HAS THIS MAN'S HEART BEEN
COMPLETELY TAKEN OVER BY
DARKNESS?
>> NEXT ON "INUYASHA:"
"LURED BY THE BLACK LIGHT."
DOES SADNESS LIE BEYOND THE
BLACKENED LIGHT?