>> HERE WE COME.
IT'S THE START OF "INUYASHA."
>> WE'RE GOING TO GATHER ALL THE
SHARDS OF THE SACRED JEWEL.
>> AND I'LL DESTROY NARAKU WITH
MY TETSUSAIGA.
>> WE CONTINUE OUR JOURNEY IN
SEARCH OF OUR ENEMY NARAKU.
WE'VE MADE IT THROUGH A LOT OF
HARD TIMES TOGETHER, AND NOW A
DARK SHADOW OF DOUBT AND FEAR IS
ABOUT TO BE CAST OVER OUR
HEARTS.
>> IT'S UP TO ALL OF US.
>> TRAVEL BACK IN TIME FOR A
FEUDAL FAIRY TALE!
>> "INUYASHA!"
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
[SNIFFING]
HMM?
>> WELL, INUYASHA,
HAVE YOU FOUND THE WAY OUT OF
THIS FOREST YET?
>> SHUT UP.
I'M TRYING TO CONCENTRATE.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
BUT YOU'VE BEEN AT IT SINCE
MORNING, AND IT'S GETTING KIND
OF DARK.
>> MMM!
HUH?
HEY, HOW COME YOU'RE SHAKING
LIKE THAT?
>> AAGH!
>> MIROKU, I KNEW I DIDN'T LIKE
THIS FOREST.
>> YES, I'M SURE OF IT NOW.
WE'RE IN A DEMON'S TERRITORY.
[LOUD POP]
[WHIMPERING]
>> OOPS.
BLEW A TIRE AGAIN.
>> I WITH YOU'D GET RID OF THAT
CONTRAPTION ONCE AND FOR ALL.
>> NO WAY!
MY MOM BOUGHT IT FOR ME,
AND I'M KEEPING IT.
[WIND HOWLS]
FEEL THAT?
SOMETHING EVIL'S COMING THIS
WAY.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE WE'RE ABOUT TO
FINALLY MEET THE DEMON THAT
REIGNS OVER THIS FOREST.
>> HOPEFULLY IT'S NOTHING
WE CAN'T HANDLE.
[ALL GASPING]
>> HA!
THIS DEMON SHOULD BE EASY ENOUGH
TO GET RID OF.
QUICK STALLING AND SHOW
YOURSELF!
I'M READY FOR YOU!
[GRUNTING]
>> HA HA HA HA.
>> HUH?
>> WELCOME TO MY FOREST OF
SORROW.
>> THE TRUTH BEHIND
THE NIGHTMARE: BATTLE
IN THE FOREST OF SORROW.
>> I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
>> KAGOME, DON'T WE KNOW HIM?
>> YES.
IT'S GATENMARU.
>> OH.
SO, YOU KNOW GATENMARU?
HE'S THE BANE OF MY TRIBE OF
MOTH DEMONS.
I HEAR HE BANDED TOGETHER WITH
SOME LOWLY HUMANS, THEN GOT
HIMSELF KILLED BY A HALF-DEMON.
>> THAT'S A MIGHTY SHARP SWORD.
>> HA.
A HALF-DEMON DID KILL HIM...
THE ONE STANDING
IN FRONT OF YOU.
IT WAS A STUPID ENDING
TO THE FIGHT THOUGH.
>> WHY DOES HE CARRY THE SCENT
OF PURE DEMON BLOOD?
[ROARS]
>> FILTHY VERMIN!
>> AARGH!
>> I'LL TELL YOU THIS:
IF YOU'RE LOOKING TO AVENGE
GATENMARU'S DEATH, THEN I'LL
GLADLY TAKE YOU ON.
>> AVENGE, HA!
SURELY YOU JEST.
HE DESERVED TO DIE.
I COULD CARE LESS ABOUT HIM.
>> YEAH, WHATEVER, BUDDY.
UNFORTUNATELY, YOU'RE STILL
GONNA HAVE TO DIE, 'CAUSE,
YOU SEE, I GOT A THING ABOUT
INSECTS.
>> INUYASHA!
[HISSES]
[GRUNTING]
>> HUH?
[ALL GRUNTING]
>> WHAT IS THIS THING?
>> IT'S MOVING.
>> IT WON'T COME OFF!
IT'S STARTING TO GO
INSIDE MY BODY!
>> MY POWER...
[GRUNTS]
IT'S SAPPING MY STRENGTH!
>> HUH!
KAGOME!
[GRUNTING]
THE TETSUSAIGA CAN'T
CUT THROUGH IT!
>> HA HA HA HA HA HA!
>> HUH?
>> IT'S SO UNCOUTH TO SUCK HUMAN
BLOOD.
THESE DAYS MY TRIBE PREFERS TO
DEVOUR THE HARDENED SOUL
ENGULFED IN FEAR AND DESPAIR.
[GRUNTING]
>> DAMN!
HUH?
MIROKU!
NO!
DON'T BE SO WEAK!
MIROKU, WAKE UP!
HUH?
SANGO!
YOU'VE GOTTA FIGHT.
>> SHOUT ALL YOU LIKE,
THEY CANNOT HEAR ANYMORE.
>> SHIPPO, COME ON!
ANSWER ME!
SHIPPO!
>> BY MORNING, A PART OF ME
SHALL TAKE HOLD OF
THEIR HEARTS AND SOULS.
[GROANS]
>> I'LL USE THE WIND SCAR.
IT'S MY ONLY OPTION.
[SCREAMING]
IT'S USELESS.
THE ONLY CHANCE I HAVE OF
BREAKING THE CURSE
IS TO DEFEAT HIM.
HMMPH!
>> NOW, THEN,
I SHALL CREATE NIGHTMARES FOR
YOU, AND YOU SHALL EXPERIENCE
ULTIMATE FEAR AND DESPAIR.
HA HA HA HA HA!
[LAUGHING]
>> WAIT, KIRIRA.
COME HERE!
OH!
HUH?
OOF!
[GIGGLING]
>> ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, KOHAKU?
>> IF KIRIRA CAN BRING HIM DOWN
SO EASILY, MAYBE IT'S TOO EARLY
FOR HIM TO FACE BATTLE.
>> NO SUCH THING, FATHER.
KOHAKU IS VERY SKILLED WITH HIS
CHAINED SCYTHE.
>> KIRIRA, THIS ISN'T
FUNNY ANYMORE!
>> WELL, I'LL TRUST YOUR
JUDGMENT.
>> HE'LL BE JUST FINE.
AND IF ANYTHING SHOULD HAPPEN,
I'LL BE WITH HIM.
[GRUNTING]
HUH?
AAGH!
KOHAKU!
>> HELP ME, SANGO.
I'M SO AFRAID.
>> DO NOW WORRY.
I'M RIGHT HERE WITH--
AAGH!
[GROANS]
KOHAKU.
>> ♪ LA LA LA LA LA
LA LA LA LA LA ♪
[LAUGH]
♪ LA LA LA LA LA LA ♪
>> TREMENDOUS FUN!
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
TAKES AWAY THE CARES OF THE DAY,
WOULDN'T YOU SAY?
[GRUNTS]
>> MASTER MUSHIN, I WANT TO KNOW
WHY MY FATHER ISN'T HERE WITH
US.
>> HMM.
>> MASTER MUSHIN?
>> YOUR FATHER CONFIDED IN ME
THAT HE COULDN'T BEAR HIS FATE
UNDER THE CURSE ANY LONGER.
>> AND WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
>> IT'S ALL IRRELEVANT NOW.
>> HUH?!
FATHER!
NO!
[GASPING]
NO.
FATHER.
[GIGGLING]
>> HEY, FATHER!
[PANTING]
YOU WON'T BELIEVE IT!
LOOK HOW MANY ACORNS I FOUND!
HUH?!
[LAUGHING]
[WHIMPERING]
>> OH, FATHER!
FATHER.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER, SOTA?
>> BUYO'S INSIDE HERE SOMEWHERE.
>> HMM?
>> I'D SEARCH FOR HER, BUT IT'S
SO DARK AND CREEPY IN HERE.
>> COME ON.
YOU'VE BEEN IN HERE A MILLION
TIMES.
>> ARE YOU GOING IN?
>> HUH?
WHAT'S THIS MIASMA?
[LAUGHTER]
NO, THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
SOTA, WE'VE GOTTA GET OUT OF
HERE!
COME ON!
GET UP!
[GROANING]
>> WHAT'S GOING ON, KAGOME?!
>> WHAT'S ALL THE FUSS ABOUT?!
>> GO BACK!
STAY AWAY FROM HERE!
[BOOM]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
>> SUFFER.
BEYOND THAT SUFFERING, YOU'LL
FIND ONLY ENDLESS DESPAIR
WAITING FOR YOU.
I'LL SEE TO IT THAT YOU GET AN
AMPLE HELPING OF FEAR AND
HOPELESSNESS.
HA HA HA HA HA.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING TO TORMENT
MY FRIENDS INSIDE THAT COCOON?
>> HA HA!
I'M DOING NOTHING MORE THAN
LETTING THEM DREAM.
>> DREAM?
>> HUMANS AND DEMONS ARE ALIKE.
ALL HAVE FEARS THAT THEY
SUPPRESS DEEP IN THEIR HEARTS,
FEARS WHICH CAN ONLY BE RELEASED
IN NIGHTMARES.
AND THAT IS WHAT WE MOTH DEMONS
FEED ON.
>> HOW 'BOUT FEEDING ON THIS?!
[GRUNTS]
RELEASE KAGOME AND MY FRIENDS AT
ONCE!
>> HA HA!
AMUSING HALF-DEMON!
YOUR OWN FEAR IS WRITTEN ALL
OVER YOUR FACE.
>> I AIN'T AFRAID!
>> WITHOUT YOUR FRIENDS AROUND,
YOU'RE SO LONELY, YOU CAN HARDLY
BEAR IT.
>> THAT'S A LIE!
I CAN FIGHT FINE ON MY OWN!
IT'S JUST--
IT'S JUST THAT I'M NOT GONNA LET
YOU USE MY FRIENDS AS
INGREDIENTS FOR YOUR NEXT MEAL!
>> YOU'RE JUST ANOTHER BIG
TALKER.
HA HA HA HA HA HA!
I WILL GLADLY DEVOUR YOUR
UNBEARABLE FEAR OF BEING ALONE!
>> OH, NO, YOU WON'T.
WATCH THIS!
[GRUNTS]
WIND SCAR!
[GROANS]
HA.
NOW, WHO'S THE BIG TALKER?
[LAUGHTER]
>> THINK YOU'VE DEFEATED ME,
DO YOU?
>> WHAT?
>> EVEN IF YOU DO DESTROY MY
BODY, I SHALL DEVOUR THE SOULS
OF YOUR FRIENDS.
WITH THEIR BODIES, I SHALL GROW
A NEW BODY FOR MYSELF.
AND WHEN I DO, THAT WILL SPELL
THE END FOR YOU.
IN ESSENCE, YOU SHALL BE
DEVOURED BY YOUR FORMER FRIENDS.
THAT IS THE FATE THAT AWAITS
YOU.
THE VERY MOMENT YOU ARE
DEVOURED, YOU WILL BE TRULY
RELEASED FROM THE FEAR OF
LONELINESS.
[LAUGHS]
>> HMM!
THE COCOONS DIDN'T DISAPPEAR.
WHAT CAN I DO?
HOW DO I GET THEM OUT?!
[GRUNTING]
DAMN!
BREAK OPEN, DAMN YOU!
ARGH!
KAGOME!
SHIPPO, MIROKU, SANGO!
>> KOHAKU?
>> SIS, YOU WON'T BELIEVE THIS!
I FINALLY DID IT!
>> HUH?
>> I SLEW A DEMON ALL BY MYSELF.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHAT DEMON?
>> HA HA HA.
>> WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?!
>> FATHER'S GONNA BE PROUD OF ME
WHEN HE HEARS ABOUT THIS.
[SOBBING]
[LAUGHING]
HUH?!
WHY, SANGO?
[WHIMPERING]
>> KOHAKU!
[SOBBING]
[THWACK]
>> IT'S YOUR FAULT, SANGO.
YOU NEVER PRAISED ME OR
ENCOURAGED ME.
>> MASTER MUSHIN, LET GO!
LET GO OF ME!
>> MIROKU, YOUR WIND TUNNEL HAS
REACHED ITS LIMIT!
YOU MUSTN'T GO ANYWHERE!
>> I'LL FIND NARAKU!
HE CAN'T HIDE FROM ME FOREVER.
HUH?
[SIGHS]
HMM?
I'M SO CLOSE.
>> MIROKU, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
>> NO, STAY BACK!
>> MIROKU, WHAT IS IT?
>> MIROKU?
>> STOP--STAY AWAY!
[GRUNTS]
AAGH!
>> AAGH!
>> NO!
THAT CAN'T BE.
MY HAND WAS COVERED.
[LAUGHS]
>> MONK, WERE YOU THAT DESPERATE
TO BE SAVED?
DESPERATE ENOUGH TO EVEN WANT IT
AT THE EXPENSE OF YOUR FRIEND'S
LIVES?
>> YOU HAVE NO RIGHT TO ACCUSE
ME OF ANYTHING.
YOU CURSED MY GRANDFATHER WITH
THE WIND TUNNEL.
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
[WHIMPERING]
[LAUGHING]
>> HUH?
OH!
AAGH!
HELP ME!
OH!
>> HUH?
WHAT?
DON'T TELL ME IT WAS ALL A
NIGHTMARE.
[YAWNS]
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER, KAGOME?
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU TO JUST DOZE
OFF IN CLASS LIKE THAT.
[GIGGLING]
>> YOU WERE SLEEPING
LIKE A BABY.
>> HUH?
>> DON'T YOU THINK YOU'VE BEEN
CRAMMING A BIT TOO HARD?
>> NO, I DON'T THINK THAT'S THE
PROBLEM.
[GASPS]
NO!
>> LOOK THOSE BLACK CLOUDS!
>> WOW!
LOOK AT THAT!
>> WHERE IS THAT COMING FROM?!
>> EVERYONE RUN FOR IT!
GET AWAY FROM THE SCHOOL
IMMEDIATELY!
[GASPS]
>> DAMN IT ALL!
BLADES OF BLOOD!
[PANTING]
KAGOME!
KAGOME, DON'T GIVE IN.
YOU'VE GOT THE STRENGTH TO BEAT
THIS THING.
[GRUNTS]
YOU GONNA LET SOME NIGHTMARE SAP
ALL YOUR POWER?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE STRONGER THAN
THAT.
[GRUNTS]
I MISJUDGED YOU.
I DIDN'T THINK YOU WERE THE TYPE
TO GIVE UP SO EASILY.
IF THAT'S HOW IT'S GONNA BE,
THEN I'LL DEFEAT NARAKU ON MY
OWN.
DON'T COME CRYING TO ME WITH
YOUR REGRETS LATER ON.
[GRUNTING]
WAKE UP, KAGOME!
WAKE UP UNLESS YOU WANT THIS
MOTH DEMON TO DEVOUR YOUR SOUL.
[GRUNTING]
KAGOME, YOU'RE NOT WEAK.
I KNOW YOU CAN GET THROUGH THIS.
SAY IT.
I DARE YOU TO SAY IT.
I DARE YOU TO TELL ME TO SIT!
>> I'M GOING TO KILL YOU...
THEN MYSELF.
IT'S MY ONLY CHOICE.
THIS IS THE ONLY WAY TO FREE YOU
FROM NARAKU.
>> SANGO...
WHY DO YOU HAVE TO KILL ME?
>> I'LL KILL YOU,
THEN I'LL KILL MYSELF.
THIS IS THE ONLY WAY TO GET YOU
BACK FROM NARAKU.
UGH.
FORGIVE ME, KOHAKU.
>> SANGO, DON'T KILL KOHAKU.
WE HAVE TO GET HIM BACK ALIVE.
>> I SHOULDN'T STAY WITH YOU.
IT CAUSES EVERYONE TROUBLE.
>> WOULD YOU QUIT BABBLING AND
LET ME TALK.
IT'S WAY BETTER TO STICK
TOGETHER.
AND, BESIDES, I'M PRETTY GOOD
AT FIGHTING.
>> INUYASHA.
[GRUNTING]
>> WHAT IS IT THAT YOU'RE SO
AFRAID OF?!
>> INUYASHA!
>> IF YOU TRY TO USE THAT WIND
TUNNEL AGAIN, I'LL TEAR YOUR
STUPID ARM OFF!
DON'T YOU WANT TO DEFEAT NARAKU
AND BREAK THE CURSE OF THE WIND
TUNNEL?
'CAUSE IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT,
THEN STOP WASTING TIME AND GET
GOING!
>> YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT,
INUYASHA.
[SCREAMING]
>> COME ON, SHIPPO.
YOU CAN GET OUT OF THIS!
>> HUH?
FOX FIRE!
[GRUNTING]
YES!
>> HA.
>> HUH?
>> HI.
NICE WORK YOU DID AGAINST THIS
LIZARD DEMON, SHIPPO.
>> HMM.
YEAH!
[LAUGHTER]
[PANTING]
>> AAH!
>> KAGOME!
>> INUYASHA.
>> HI, KAGOME.
YOU SMELL NICE.
>> WHAT A THING TO SAY AT A TIME
LIKE THIS.
AAH!
RUN, INUYASHA!
YOU DON'T HAVE A CHANCE AGAINST
HIM IN YOUR HUMAN FORM!
>> YOU FOOL.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE
WITHOUT YOU.
I'M STAYING!
AND I'M GONNA PROTECT YOU.
[GRUNTS]
>> THAT'S RIGHT!
I HAVE INUYASHA WITH ME.
AS LONG AS I'M WITH INUYASHA,
WITH HIM AND MY OTHER FRIENDS,
I CAN OVERCOME ANY ADVERSITY.
[GRUNTING]
>> HA!
>> AH!
YOU DID IT!
YEAH!
THAT'S WHAT MY FRIENDS ARE MADE
OF.
>> INUYASHA!
>> COME ON!
LET'S NOT WASTE TIME GETTING OUT
OF THIS FORREST.
THAT'S OUR WAY OUT.
OK, FOLLOW ME!
WIND SCAR!
>> THE FOREST DISAPPEARED.
>> SO IT DID.
IT MUST HAVE BEEN AN ILLUSION
CREATED BY GARAMARU.
>> WHAT A SHAME.
WE WASTED SO MUCH TIME BECAUSE
OF HIM.
>> YEAH, I WON'T ARGUE WITH YOU
THERE.
>> MM-HMM.
>> WHILE YOU'RE ON THE SUBJECT,
WHY DON'T I REMIND YOU HOW MUCH
TROUBLE YOU'D BE IN IF YOU
DIDN'T HAVE ME AROUND TO SAVE
YOU ALL THE TIME.
HUH?
[LAUGHING]
WHAT ARE YOU STARING AT?
YOU GOT A COMPLIANT OR
SOMETHING?
>> NO, NO.
WE COULDN'T AGREE WITH YOU MORE.
>> SO, JUST THIS ONCE,
WE'RE GONNA LET YOU BRAG.
>> I WASN'T BRAGGING, I WAS
TELLING THE TRUTH!
>> NEVER MIND, INUYASHA!
WE ALL KNOW WHAT YOU DID
TO SAVE US, AND WE'RE GRATEFUL.
>> NO, I STILL DON'T LIKE HIS
TONE!
IF YOU PEOPLE ARE AS GRATEFUL AS
YOU MAKE OUT TO BE, THEN WOULD
IT KILL YOU GUYS TO COME OUT
WITH A LITTLE "THANK YOU"?
>> SO, WHAT DO YOU SAY?
AS OUR REPRESENTATIVE,
WOULD YOU KINDLY DO THE HONORS,
KAGOME?
>> I'D LOVE TO.
>> HUH?
NO, WAIT!
SAY IT.
I DARE YOU TO TELL ME TO SIT!
OH.
>> INUYASHA?
[GRUNTS]
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR SAVING US.
>> HUH?
WELL, THAT SURE DIDN'T TURN OUT
THE WAY I THOUGHT IT WOULD.
>> NOW THEN, SHALL WE BE ON OUR
WAY?
>> GOOD IDEA.
>> I'M PECKISH.
>> WAIT, KAGOME!
WHAT DID YOU REALLY WANT TO SAY?
SAY IT AGAIN!
>> NOPE, THAT WAS IT.
>> COME ON!
JUST SAY IT!
>> WOULD YOU GET OFF MY BACK?!
>> WHAT?!
OFF YOUR BACK?
GRR!
COME ON, KAGOME, SAY IT!
I AM--
>> ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT!
SIT!
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
>> BACK WHEN I FIRST STARTED
MY JOURNEY--SHORTLY
AFTER MY FATHER'S DEATH--
THE SNOW FELL RELENTLESSLY,
AND SOON I WAS BURIED DEEP.
THEN SOMEONE CAME ALONG AND
SAVED ME FROM A SNOWY DEATH.
>> THAT WAS WHEN YOU FIRST MET
KOYOKI?
7 YEARS AGO?
>> THAT WOMAN RESEMBLES MY
MEMORIES OF KOYOKI.
DID YOUR TEARS FREEZE INTO SNOW?
>> NEXT TIME, "THE SNOW
FROM 7 YEARS PAST."
WAIT, SHE'S NOT HUMAN!