I get what you're saying, but before you came
along, I thought I'd always be alone in life.
And here I am with my very own family.
You made that possible.
So thank you.
She said "thank you."
but I can't remember what for.
Uh‐oh, someone’s hungry.
OK, OK.
I remember now!
I saved Kayo's life.
After that, I made sure Misato and Aya were never alone,
to keep them safe from the kidnapper.
And then...
Yashiro...
I remember everything, you son of a bitch!
No way. Kazu's a carpenter?
He and Osamu look like they're doing great.
Mm‐hmm.
By the way, Misato said she
was going to come by and see you.
What? Really?
I thought she hated my guts after what happened in class.
Yeah, I remember that.
The lunch money thing she pulled was so messed up.
It was, but don't forget who started raising
funds to help pay Satoru's medical bills.
She did that, too.
I had no idea.
Tell us about the day you tailed her.
You know, when you saw the killer.
Knew it. You do remember everything.
But then why didn't you tell us?
I didn't want to get you involved.
It's been 15 years.
Whatever evidence there was is gone by now.
And besides, who'd believe me?
Like you said, it's been 15 years.
Now that you're back, I couldn't be happier,
because it's a miracle you woke up at all.
That's why I didn't bring it up before,
to spare you from the shock.
The last thing you need is someone digging
up the past when you're trying to recover.
But you remember everything.
So, if you want to catch the killer,
you don't have to do it alone.
Let us help you.
Hiromi's been coming here to visit you all these years,
and now he wants to be a doctor.
I became a lawyer,
and now I'm working with Mr. Sawada to catch the killer.
Hiromi and I are who we are because of you, Satoru.
You were a hero to us back then.
and we want to help you again, just like old times.
Just like we helped with Kayo.
You trusted me enough back
then, believed in me, you remember?
That's why I believed in you.
If someone believes in you, you're not alone.
And if I was in your situation,
I'd want someone to believe me.
Airi.
I'm not alone.
I have friends I can count on.
The killer is...
Yashiro.
I knew you remembered.
On the way up here, I tapped my
finger on your wheelchair a couple times.
I could tell you tried hard not to react.
Fifteen years ago,
you figured out what I was doing and ruined my plans.
But how?
A child isn't capable of such tings.
It's as if you were psychic or something.
Yashiro! I know your future!
Let's have it. How did you know what I was thinking?
What did you mean, you know my future?
What difference does it make?
Soon as I tell you, you'll kill me.
Oh, I know what you're up to.
You’ve got a phone in your pocket. Are you recording us?
Or is someone listening in?
Kenya, perhaps?
You have heard of the statute of limitations?
Even if I confessed, I can't be
tried for things I did 15 years ago.
And I haven't done anything wrong since then.
So you see, no matter what you
do, you can never get me, Satoru.
Oh, look, Kumi just sent you an email.
At 4:30, she'll get her daily IV.
I put a muscle relaxant in her dose and made
sure your fingerprints were all over the bag.
That poor little girl who was afraid of her
operation will die peacefully now thanks to you.
And feeling guilty, I throw myself
off the roof, isn't that right?
There you go reading my mind again.
While that might be an amazing
skill, it won't save your life.
But you might save Kumi's if
you tell me what I want to know.
If I do, then what? How do I
know you won't kill her anyway?
I can't guarantee I won't, naturally.
But there is a possibility.
If you don't talk, there won't even be that.
I hate to say it. We're out of time now.
There was a 50‐50 chance you'd tell
me how you knew about me back then.
Oh, well, I guess it doesn't matter anymore.
I'm sure it was just a coincidence
when you screamed you knew my future.
That was just a bluff.
As for your mother...
we should send her an email,
let her know how sorry you are.
Hey, kiddo, I have to work the morning shift
tomorrow, so I'll see you in the afternoon?
I'll let him sleep.
Mom?
I lied to you.
I got my...
Your memory back?
I know. It happened when Kayo came by.
Yep, she's a witch.
You're right, but how come you didn't
tell her not to bring up the past?
After Kenya and Hiromi stopped by,
I felt I made a mistake telling
them not to bring any of it up.
They couldn't say what they wanted, and that wasn't fair.
When Kayo showed up with her baby,
I didn't have the heart to ask her to do the same.
After waiting all this time for
you to wake up, who am I to stop her?
I got to see your face and talk to
you every day for the last 15 years.
Then when I heard you speak, your voice all crackly,
it finally hit me, you weren't a kid anymore.
I was happy...
My boy grew up.
Mom, I'm gonna take life head‐on.
What in the heck are you talking about?
Even when you were a little kid,
you always took it head‐on, remember?
Mm‐hmm.
Life is about filling up the void in yourself.
Indeed.
Whenever I taught sixth grade,
I always told the class that.
I remember what your face looked like.
The day they took Kayo from her mom.
The expression you had stuck
with me even after all these years.
A little while after I was born, my dad took off.
So I have no idea what he looks like.
But that day at Kayo's, you were the
dad I never had and I always wanted.
At that moment, you filled the void in me.
For the last 15 years, I've
been waiting for you to wake up.
When you slipped into your coma,
I lost the impulse that defined me,
the thing that gave my life meaning.
I've waited a long time. But now...
You're not alone anymore?
So, how are we gonna settle this?
Are you gonna turn yourself in or kill me?
Which is it?
It's already settled, actually.
You're right, I beat you.
I saved all of them from you.
Kayo, Aya, Hiromi, Yuuki.
Even my mom, who you haven't killed yet.
Your mom? Why would I kill...
Hold on, are you saying you can I'm
just telling you what you wanted to know.
I could screw up all your
plans because I knew your future.
That's it.
That's how I saved them all.
That's why you weren't able to kill
anyone I was even remotely connected to.
Why you couldn't kill me.
Wrong.
I could have killed you anytime I wanted.
Now, for instance.
But for 15 years, you let me live.
Why did you do that?
Oh, I know, you needed me, didn't you?
I was your reason for living.
I was your hope.
I was the one who filled the void in you.
I beat you back then, Mr. Yashiro...
No! No! No!
Even now, I beat you!
You see what I mean? You can't kill me.
Fifteen years is a long time.
I was asleep, so for me it all went by in a flash,
but for you, it must have felt like forever.
You're still alive 'cause I'm around.
I make you feel alive.
I had to relive a part of my life over and over again,
the part where you killed some of my friends.
Funny, I should hate you, but I don't.
'Cause right now, I'm the only one who knows you.
The real you.
You're right.
Satoru.
I can't live...
You're right.
I can't go on living without you.
The police are charging him with attempted murder.
Is Kumi OK?
Yeah, but I didn't tell her about him,
what with her surgery coming up and all.
Good.
"I believe in you." What a strange thing to say.
Huh?
Well, think about it.
If you really believe in someone,
chances are, they already know you do.
Saying it's kind of redundant, don't you think?
Not if you mean it, and you want someone to know you do.
Yeah.
I guess we say it 'cause we want to give someone hope.
Hope to keep fighting.
To let them know they're not alone in the world, right?
Now my life has a blank spot
between the ages of 11 and 25.
But in a weird way, I sort of treasure the time I lost.
In a town without me, my friends lived for themselves
and for me.
Where is he?
Heroes always show up at the last minute.
Right?
Here's Satoru.
About time.
Where you been?
What's up, dude?
You're an idiot.
Are you ever on time?
A town without me.
Time without me.
It's not my loss, it's my treasure.
Whoa!
This is great!
Whenever you dig deep,
you always come up with the most amazing angles.
Thanks. I guess I'll keep working on it, then.
That‐a‐boy. And sorry you had to schlep out here.
So, you heading out today?
Yep. Going back to Hokkaido for a break.
There's some old friends I wanna see.
Well, have yourself a great time, then.
Safe travels and have a good weekend.
Oh, almost forgot.
Congrats on your anime getting the green light.
I write and draw manga for a living now.
As for Revival, I haven't had another.
The 2010 Olympics in Vancouver
are just two short weeks away.
The athletes representing Japan are already...
I'm gonna go out for a walk.
We'll hold the fort down.
Later, boss.
Oh, I heard we'll be getting some
more snow later on, so take a jacket...
"My Hero," by Satoru Fujinuma.
"I'm not brave enough to make the first move...
That's why I don't have any real friends.
I play with other kids, but there's a difference
between playing with them and real friends.
Yesterday, I saw the last episode of 'Fight, Wonder Guy!',
my favorite anime.
In the first part of it,
Wonder Guy had to fight the bad guys by himself.
They'd knock him down again and again,
but he had the courage to get back up.
He'd say, "If I don't try, nothing will change,"
and he'd jump right back into the fight.
Other people saw how courageous he was and slowly
but surely, they joined him and became his friends.
When it looked like the bad guy was gonna
finish him off for good, he didn't worry.
He never stopped believing that
his friends would come to the rescue.
But someone like me doesn't have
Wonder Guy's courage or real friends.
To be honest, I feel kind of jealous.
I want friends like his someday.
Real friends, the kind that have my back no matter what."
Can you believe this snow?
The Weather Channel said it's the most
snow Kanto's gotten in ten years! Ten!
Mind if I hang out here with you till it stops?
I never stopped believing either.