I have a name for what happens to me:
Revival.
When it happens, I go back in time
anywhere from one to five minutes.
Then it always happens before something bad goes down.
I've managed to stop a lot of tragedies, so far.
Hey there, Satoru.
Hey, Mom.
Are you Satoru Fujinuma?
You're gonna have to come down to the station.
See Mask Man? Next week's the last episode!
Ah, I totally forgot to watch Black!
1988.
February 15th?
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning.
Well, Satoru, you gonna take your seat?
Huh? Oh, yes, sir.
Where was my seat again?
You still asleep or something?
That's Kayo's desk, you doofus.
Oh, yeah.
No Kayo.
I'll have to mark her tardy again.
Satoru, are you, like, in love with Kayo?
Huh?
You'd make a cute couple. You're both weird.
Here we go, folks.
Is this for real?
Why did I get dropped back to this time?
Here! Here! Here!
What's going on?
This is 18 years ago.
How far did you get on Dragon Quest 3?
Level 15. That's it?
Nah, just testing.
I'm on 25.
You liar!
Hey, what's wrong?
Um, my head hurts so I'm gonna see the nurse.
Then why are you taking your bag?
Don't worry about it.
I'll let the teacher know where you went.
What the hell's going on?
Is this Revival?
I don't get it.
Why'd I go back this far?
Mom!
H‐Hello.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
It's one of the neighbors.
That's right, she'd be at work now.
Mom...
Hey there, kiddo.
Mom!
What's wrong?
Nothing, just happy to see you.
You little weirdo. So what do you want for dinner?
Hamburger or meatballs?
Uh...
Hamburger?
You getting hungry or what?
Mm‐hmm.
You're in a good mood, not like this
morning when you pitched your little fit.
Guess you found your recorder, huh?
Yeah, I did.
I'm sorry.
It's nothing to cry about, kiddo.
I remember moments like this.
I guess back then I didn't
realize how important they'd be.
I let times like this slip by
without even thinking about them.
This is Revival.
It's another chance.
And there's no way I'll let this one slip by.
Mom...
Hmm?
It's really good. Thank you.
Are you sure you're OK?
Thanks for dinner.
You're welcome.
Am I supposed to do the next 18 years over again?
Good morning, Satoru!
Hey, Osamu. Morning.
If this is Revival, then I'm here for one reason:
to stop something bad from happening.
And maybe to save my mom, I have to start here.
But why so far back?
Nothing seems off here. Huh?
That's Kayo Hinazuki.
She lived alone with her mom too.
And bam.
Wow!
How'd she get that?
You know what I think sucks about this
group? There's no one to talk Dragon Quest with.
Huh? Uh...
I mean, Hiro's a Final Fantasy
fan and Kazu only plays shooters.
That's Hiro and Kazu.
I remember them.
Heck, Satoru doesn't even have a Famicom.
No, I didn't.
Jeez, Osamu, if we all played Dragon
Quest, then that's all we'd ever talk about.
The cool thing about our group is,
we all like different things so it's never boring.
That's Kenya.
Out of all of us, he was the brainiest.
Can I ask you something, Satoru?
It's kind of personal.
Sure. Go ahead.
Do you have a crush on Kayo?
I saw you staring at her.
No way. Really?
He totally was.
This morning he just stood there staring.
He couldn't take his eyes off her.
Dang it, Satoru.
If you're in love with her, you
should have come to me for advice.
Romance is right up my alley.
No "buts" about it. I'll fix it
so's you can hook up with Kayo.
Could you keep your voice down?
Why?
Well, it's like... I don't love her.
Just curious about her.
That's the same thing.
You're brave to admit it.
Don't you worry about a thing. By the end of
today, you'll be talking with your dream girl.
You're an idiot.
Damn, she's cold.
That's how you say hello?
I said that out loud.
Ah, crap.
I bet Kazu straight up told her I have a crush on her.
Um... Kayo?
I was thinking, since we walk home the same way,
maybe we could be friends?
Friends?
What is it you like about me?
Oh, she's a pain in the ass.
You don't have to answer that if you don't want to.
I think I know.
You're just like I am. You're fake, too.
Wait... does she know about me?
I saw you running home yesterday.
You looked happy. Do you love your mom that much?
Yeah.
That's good.
Wait, Kayo, hold up!
So how about it? You wanna be friends?
Are you serious?
So, like, does that mean you'd kill to protect me?
No, you don't get it, I could have saved her!
Something bad was happening to
Kayo in the days before she died.
Maybe if I can stop it, I can save her.
I think I know.
You're just like I am. You're fake, too.
I doubt she could tell I wasn't really a kid.
I guess maybe I might have been acting a little weird,
but that's pretty much how I was back in those days.
I wanted friends,
so I tried acting like the person I wanted to be.
If you have courage, you can do anything.
It was the only way I knew how to
fit in in my middle school world.
We were gonna send a search party in...
I bet she saw through that, but she said I was like her,
so maybe she's hiding her true self too.
So, how'd you make out?
Yeah, man, you gonna tell us how it went or what?
Did you guys walk home together, did you hold hands?
Jeez, no. We just talked for a little bit, that's all.
Just you two, alone?
Mm‐hmm.
Sweet! That means she totally likes you.
Dude, seriously, she never talks to anyone alone.
You want me to give her another message? Do ya?
Could they be more annoying?
Take it easy, guys.
Pressuring him like this isn't gonna help him.
You're right.
He's talking about something else, but, yeah.
Satoru, in sixth grade, we'll all be in
the same class again, so there's no rush.
Right.
Attention, students...
When did Kayo disappear, again?
I'm running out of time! ‐ Hey, Satoru, come on.
Yeah, coming.
Brrr!
It's cold. By the way,
where are those kick‐ass McGregor gloves you got?
Oh yeah. I remember I had a pair of those.
I guess maybe I left them somewhere.
Oh. Well, they're probably at the hideout then.
Hey, guys, can we go to the hideout today?
What are you talking about?
Remember? We said we wouldn't go there if it snows,
'cause everyone would see our tracks.
Oh, w‐we did?
Oh, right, yeah.
See you tomorrow.
Later, dudes.
See ya.
Kenya! Thanks for speaking up.
It's like, they were making such a
big deal out of it, I was freaking out.
Yeah, I bet you were. You don't have to thank me, though.
By the way, about Kayo...
I think it's great you want to get closer to her and all,
but I get the feeling there's something else going on.
I don't mean to be nosy or anything, but...
I'm here if you need to talk to someone.
And not just me. The other guys are, too.
Thanks. And yeah...
I know everyone's just trying to help.
Kazu did get Kayo to talk to me after all.
So, wanna talk about it?
About what?
About Kayo.
Oh, right.
Did you talk to her?
Yeah. Only for a bit.
She even opened up a little by the end.
That's good.
I know you've got a lot on
your mind, but I was wondering...
You read the essays yet?
Huh?
No, I haven't.
There are a couple of interesting ones.
You should check them out.
I better go. See you tomorrow.
See ya.
I think Kenya was hinting at Kayo's
essay being the interesting one in this.
"A Town Without Me," by Kayo Hinazuki.
"When I get bigger, big enough to go somewhere by myself,
I want to go someplace far away from here.
I want to go to an island, an island without any people,
an island that doesn't have
any pain or sadness on it either.
There are no grown‐ups, kids, classmates or teachers.
Even my mom's not there.
When I feel like I wanna climb a tree,
I can climb it.
I'll go for a swim if I want to.
And sleep when I want to.
On the island,
I'll think about what's going on in the town without me.
Kids go to school like nothing's changed,
grown‐ups go to work like nothing's changed.
Mom eats her dinner like nothing's changed.
And when I think about the town without me,
I feel relief more than anything.
All I want is to go far away."
Her essay's a cry for help.
No doubt about it.
I'm home.
Thanks for dinner.
Hmm?
Kenya probably thought I was
interested in her 'cause of the essay.
After reading it, now I'm even more worried about her.
Hey, Mom?
Yeah, what's up?
For my birthday, can I invite some friends over?
Mm‐hmm, sure, but our place is kind of small.
How many friends are we talkin'?
Not too many, just five.
You know, this is the first
time you asked to have a party.
Should I get a big cake?
Yeah! Thanks, Mom.
I know what I have to do now.
I have to get to know Kayo even better.
I'm gonna do what I didn't the first time.
If I can make her do something different now,
maybe it will be enough to change her fate.
Maybe it'll change everything.
Hey, you still awake?
You said five. Did you get yourself a girlfriend?
All right, good night, kiddo.
Witch.
I just remembered something.
I didn't show my mom my essay back then
because I knew she'd read it and see right into my soul.
What did I write about again?
I'm going home and play Dragon Quest.
Me too!
Man, it's snowing again. No hideout today.
Satoru! Kayo's leaving. Don't you want to talk to her?
Osamu...
It's OK, Kenya. It's no big deal.
And thanks, Osamu. See ya!
See you.
Later, dude.
Whoa!
Can you believe how brave he's gotten?
I didn't have to run.
I already knew where I'd find Kayo.
I was pretty sure her mom was hitting her,
and if that was true, she
wouldn't be going home right away.
She'd go hang out at the park until it got darker out.
Before I just thought she was weird.
Not anymore.
Kayo!
Satoru. What do you think you're doing out here?
I was gonna say the same thing.
I meant what I said, I wanna be friends.
I won't kill anyone, that's too much.
No duh. That was a joke.
I hate dealing with her type.
I know what you're doing, Satoru.
You're just pretending.
Pretending to smile and being nice
and worrying about people.
But I don't think it's bad or anything.
I can't tell what you're really like.
That sounds funny coming from me.
Everything you said's true. I am pretending.
I want people to like me. I wanna have friends.
So I asked myself, what can a
loser like me do to have that?
And you know what?
I tried liking everyone and it worked.
It was hard at first, but after a while, it got easier.
Yeah.
And, like, the more you do it,
the better the chance it comes true.
The more I talk about it, the
better the chance it will come true.
It's like déjà vu all over again.
To get what you want, you have to make an effort.
You have to try new things and keep inspiring yourself.
That's how you change.
Is that what Kayo's doing, too?
I can tell she's suffering now.
But unlike me, she acts like she doesn't care.
Pretending like she can't feel anything at all.
But she's only 10.
She's not strong enough to change her situation at home.
Hey, Kayo, I brought something for you.
What?
I'm having a birthday party and I want you to come.
Uh... are you sure it's OK?
I mean, won't there be tons of people?
Oh, I don't know yet.
But I wanted to give you the first invitation.
It's on March the 2nd.
You're gonna come, right?
Uh‐huh.
Hey, aren't your hands cold?
Huh? Oh, yeah. They kind of are.
I had some new gloves, but I think I lost them.
Take it easy, dude. You're 29.
Why are you getting all flustered?
Satoru, are you OK?
Uh... uh‐huh. I mean, my
hand's way bigger than yours, huh?
You're an idiot.
Even so...
you seem like you're OK. It's easy talking to you.
Well...
It's 'cause I decided to be honest with you.
I said that out loud.
Wait, Kayo!
So, um, see ya tomorrow?
She didn't have gloves either, did she?
Eighteen years ago, I saw Kayo here, alone.
And then she disappeared.
If I remember right, they found
her body after the snow melted.
This time,
I won't leave her standing here all alone.
This time...
I'm going to save her.