I'd like to tell you a little story.
It happened a long time ago,
when I was in the sixth grade.
One day at school, a girl
brought a box of hamsters to class.
And she was very upset.
She said she started with two,
and before she knew it, they'd bred.
Now she had more than she could take care of.
I happily took them for her.
When I got home that day,
I filled a big wine jug with water.
Then I dropped the hamsters in one by one.
When I checked on them three hours later,
I couldn’t believe my eyes.
One hamster was still alive,
standing atop the drowned corpse of one of its siblings.
And I was thrilled.
I named it Spice and decided to keep it for my pet.
Why? Because when I saw it in the jug, it
reminded me of a story called "The Spider's Thread."
Do you know it?
It's about a sinner in Hell named Kandata
who, while alive, once spared a spider's life.
Moved by this act of compassion,
the Buddha lowered a spider's
thread from paradise down to him.
Kandata started climbing it, and half way up,
he saw his fellow sinners climbing after him.
He tried to knock them off, and then...
the thread snapped,
sending Kandata back down to Hell.
Now, what I'm about to tell you
next might sound hard to believe,
but if anyone could understand, it would be you.
Ever since I met Spice,
I could see the spider's thread on people.
Whomever it touched, I was compelled to kill.
But then a boy came along who disrupted my duties.
And wouldn't you know it, I saw
the spider's thread attached to him.
Yashiro!
I know your future!
I tried to kill the boy, but he didn't die.
So I nicknamed him Spice,
and I kept a close eye on him.
That boy was you, Satoru!
That'll be 987 yen, please.
Thanks for shopping with us.
Satoru mentioned something to me once about the train.
Remember, you don't have to change trains to go to Ueno.
He was right.
But why did he point that out to me?
Good morning, kiddo. Sleep well?
Huh. He's in great shape for someone
who's been in a coma for 15 years.
Fifteen years.
Wow! Talking already.
It won't be long before you can start physical therapy.
I heard that for the past 15 years,
mom spent four hours a day giving
every joint in my body a workout.
About three years ago, she got one of those EMS monitor
thingies to let her know when I was conscious again.
She got another thing to stimulate my muscles.
When I was in fifth grade, I stood about 4½ feet tall.
I'm 5'5" now.
Dr. Kitamura said, if it wasn't for my mom,
I wouldn't be in as good a shape as I am.
This might be difficult but I think you're ready for it.
Try to answer my next question.
What's the last thing you can remember,
before you lost consciousness, that is?
OK. I remember I was...
Oh...
Wait.
Damn it.
It's like these memories, whatever they are,
are locked behind a door.
That's you.
Well, aren't you surprised?
Hmm?
Your face has changed a lot.
The last time you saw it, you were 11.
Well, I guess since your memories are scrambled,
it'll take a while before this all
sinks in. It's just a matter of time.
That day, I thought maybe the doc was right.
I should have felt weird waking up in this time.
But I didn't.
But the thing is, I should have.
Patience, heart rate monitor, sense of loss, arbitration.
I knew those words.
But when did I learn them?
What the heck happened to me?
Good morning, Satoru.
Good morning, Mom.
Guess what? You've got some visitors.
Look who decided to wake up.
You look great. How are you feeling?
I remember Kenya and Hiromi.
They were two of my very best friends.
Kenya's a lawyer now and Hiromi's a doctor.
We talked for hours about this and that.
Now and then I got the feeling Kenya
wanted to ask me something, but he didn't.
Maybe Mom told him not to.
We just talked about trivial things.
See ya later.
Take it easy.
There was lots of stuff I wanted to ask the guys.
But Mom being Mom, I bet she wanted to
avoid that to spare me from the shock.
For 15 years, she dedicated herself to keeping me alive,
hoping I'd wake up one day.
She doesn't want me to remember what happened.
It's probably a good thing I don't.
I got ya.
We'll try it again tomorrow, OK?
Satoru?
Congratulations, Kayo.
Yeah, I'm married. My last name is Sugita.
No way. So Hiromi's a dad now?
Mm‐hmm.
I got the feeling he wanted to tell
me something important: now I know what.
He looks just like him. He's
even got the same long eyelashes.
Yep. He's just like his daddy.
We named him Mirai.
That's a cool name. It means "the future."
You know, we felt weird about getting together.
It didn't seem right for us to be happy.
We're alive because of what you did
and because of us, you ended up in a coma.
It felt like...
like we were leaving you behind, I guess.
Kayo, whatever happened to me happened.
So don't go blaming yourself about it.
I don't have any regrets, 'cause in the end,
I'm here 'cause it's where I'm supposed to be.
After being gone for 15 years,
you're still a smooth talker.
Oh, I am?
I get what you're saying, Satoru,
but before you came along, I
thought I'd always be alone in life.
And here I am with my very own family.
You made that possible, so thank you.
She said... "thank you."
But I can't remember what for.
Uh‐oh, someone's hungry.
OK, OK.
Satoru, are you OK?
Yeah.
I shouldn’t have sprung all this on you.
It's a lot to process.
Well, we'll see you later.
Yeah, see you later.
Hey, kiddo, you have a good workout today?
Uh‐huh. Kayo came by a little while ago.
Mm. I bumped into her outside.
She's got the cutest baby.
Listen, Mom?
What's up?
Not those assholes again.
What?
Paparazzi from the gossip rags looking for a story.
Waking up after 15 years made you a celebrity.
Oh.
Screw 'em.
Anyway, you wanted to tell me something?
No. It wasn't important.
Come in.
How are we doing?
So far, so good, doc.
I was wondering...
when do you think I'll be able to walk again?
I don't know. It depends on you.
If it's OK, I'd like to do twice as much rehab.
Why?
I wanna walk outside again.
Uh, sure, I'll see what I can do.
Sorry, I have to take this.
Yes, Director. Yes, sir.
He's doing great, actually.
He should get all his memoires back any time now.
I'm sorry, no.
Like I told you the other day,
I'm not comfortable with that.
With all due respect, he's my patient, not a guinea pig...
I have to go.
You're doing great, Satoru.
Your arms and legs have gotten a lot stronger.
Congratulations.
Way to go!
You walked the whole way without our help.
Awesome job!
Hey, Satoru, Kenya stopped by for a little visit.
Hi, Kenya.
I hope it's OK I stopped by.
Are you kidding? Of course it is.
Hello, Satoru.
Have we met before?
Matter of fact, we have.
Your mom and I used to work together
back before you started elementary school.
Oh.
Come on, you honestly think he'd remember you?
That was like 20 years ago now.
All right, take care, buddy.
See you later.
We've waited 15 years. No reason to get impatient.
We should go easy on him.
Yeah.
Hi, Kumi.
Ah, so the surgery's in two weeks, huh?
They're gonna put some of my
big sister's bone marrow in me.
They said it will cure me.
But even so, I'm scared.
You were asleep for 15 years?!
I know you've been at this hospital for a while.
What's it been, like three months now?
Mm‐hmm.
It's gonna be hard to stay motivated
in physical therapy once you leave.
You’re the reason I was working so hard.
Courage...
Whenever I need courage, here's what I do.
I picture someone I really care about smiling.
It only works if I smile back, though.
"The time‐traveling pedo.
He wakes up an adult, but he's still a kid at heart.
Still hot for little girls.
Soon he'll be released. Hide your children."
What do you think?
Good angle.
Taking photos of a civilian without their permission.
Slander, trespassing.
If I see you again, I'll call the police.
Get out of here. Now.
They were some of the prettiest flowers I'd ever seen.
Oh, hello, Mr. Nishizono.
Hello, Kumi.
Satoru Fujinuma.
Uh... yes?
It's me. Don't you remember?
It's OK. I've changed a lot
since the last time you saw me.
I was your homeroom teacher once,
when you were in fifth grade.
I'm Gaku Yashiro.
I go by Manabu Nishizono now.
I changed my name a while back.
Why did you change it, if you don't mind me asking?
Not at all. I got married five years ago
and took on my wife's family's name.
Oh.
My father‐in‐law was a city
council member for a long time.
But he passed away three years ago.
I joined the council and took over his constituency.
I kept the kanji for my given name,
but I use the more common reading now.
Wow. A real‐life politician.
Just a lowly council member.
Yeah, well, still, I get the feeling you'd
be super awesome at politics, Mr. Yashiro.
Anyway, I met Kumi and her parents at
a charity event for kids with leukemia.
I know the director of this hospital,
so I pulled some strings and got her in.
That's nice of you.
When I heard you came to, I wanted to come visit.
I'm sorry it took me so long, but with work and all.
Well, thanks for taking the time.
To be honest, I've been looking
forward to this day for the past 15 years.
Yeah, well, me too.
You don't remember how close we were, do you?
I don't. Sorry.
No, it's all right.
They said it would take a while
before you got your memories back.
You'll remember me, in time.
Hello.
Mr. Yashiro.
Were you on your way to see Kumi?
Yeah. Her surgery's coming up.
The nurses said today is the
last day she can have visitors.
True. I just left her room.
She was asleep, so unfortunately I couldn't talk to her.
Well, that sucks. I guess I'll try seeing her later, then.
Uh... since you're here, can I talk to you?
Sure, but let's go someplace we can have some privacy,
away from these reporters.
Don't worry, I know the perfect spot.
OK, here we are. I'll bet you
didn't know about this elevator.
Feels like we're going on an adventure, huh?
Would you push the button for the roof?
Hmm. Too bad.
The sunset would have been amazing if it weren't raining.
At least we won't be bothered by any paparazzi up here.
But the roof's off‐limits so don't tell on me, OK?
It's funny, being up here reminds
me of how you, Kenya and Hiromi
always talked about going to your hideout after school.
Yashiro...
I remember everything,
you son of a bitch.